(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Nah-nah-nah-nah-nah Ready for the show?
OK! 立ち位置は独壇場 Listen listen!
OK! This center stage is my domain. Listen, listen!
Nah-nah-nah-nah-nah Ready for the show?
Come on! OK!
唱
Show
ハッ! ヤーヤーヤーヤーヤー Showtime!
Ha! Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya Showtime!
ほら おいで
Come on, come over here
夜はコン・デ・トオラ・ヘーイェイェイェ
Night is... [phonetic nonsense]
だんだんノリノリで中々パパパパウ
Gradually getting in the groove...
縁も終わんない 手を叩きな パンパン
The fate won't end, clap your hands, clap-clap
さあ 鮮烈に 豪華 煽り倒せ 豪華
Now, vividly and gorgeously, fan the flames gorgeously
一生 懸命 一生 懸命 声 高らかと どどど
With all your might, with your voice loud and clear
無我爛道は どどこどだ
Where is the path of selflessness?
愛流乱万 謳い上げました
Overflowing with love, I sang it out
オートマティックに溢れちゃう 本能
Instincts overflowing automatically
脱法 乱闘 時代 ウェイで はしゃげば ええ
Just have fun in this lawless brawling era
ラタタタ ウォーニ
Ra-ta-ta-ta waani
ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ラ・リ・ゴ・マ・ショー
Na-na-na-na-na ready go my show
万歳 遊ぼうぜ 鼓動 響かせ シャウト シャウト
Hooray, let's play, make your heartbeat echo, shout, shout
ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ラ・リ・ゴ・マ・ショー
Na-na-na-na-na ready go my show
お成り 感情通りに 八走飛べ シャウト シャウト
Arriving, fly just as your feelings dictate, shout, shout
ふわっと あっちゅう間 寄り寄り 寄り 寄り 真っ新な 心臓
Softly in a blink, closer and closer, a brand new heart
喰らっちゃえよ 絶頂
Take a bite of the peak
へれべれまに 豪快 限界 ガッコン 食らえ 申して その気持ち 解放
Grandly, at the limit, take a hit, express it and release those feelings
一回 死んで ちょー
Die once, please
蛇腹 ラビ ガッタ 乱れ舞いばや 準備 セット そういや ジャスタ
Jabara rabbi gatta... [phonetic lyrics]
ガッタ ガッタ なっちゃいや 全部 丸め だるまみたい 揺蕩うわ
Getting shaky, rolling it all up, swaying like a Daruma doll
蛇腹 ラビ ガッタ 乱れ舞いばや 準備 セット そういや ジャスタ
Jabara rabbi gatta... [phonetic lyrics]
ガッタ ガッタ なっちゃいや 恋の バタフライ
Getting shaky, the butterfly of love
No escape
情緒 順てぐり 相生 順てぐり
Emotion, turn by turn, affection, turn by turn
殺されても 止まらない
Won't stop even if I'm killed
衝動に 早信 描いた インブレイク
Quickly believing the impulse, an in-break drawn
廃観 全焼 キル
View of ruins, total burnout, kill
ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ラ・リ・ゴ・マ・ショー
Na-na-na-na-na ready go my show
ええい 鳴らせ 期限だ 綺麗な 餓鬼 10万
Hey, let it ring, the time is up, a beautiful brat, 100,000
ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ラ・リ・ゴ・マ・ショー
Na-na-na-na-na ready go my show
満ちた バズィカ ハー！
A filled bazooka, ha!
ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ラ・リ・ゴ・マ・ショー
Na-na-na-na-na ready go my show
万歳 遊ぼうぜ 鼓動 響かせ シャウト シャウト
Hooray, let's play, make your heartbeat echo, shout, shout
ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ラ・リ・ゴ・マ・ショー
Na-na-na-na-na ready go my show
喝采 巻き起こす ために セイ
Say, to stir up applause
一切合切 忘れて シャウト シャウト
Forget every single thing and shout, shout
鳴け 右も左も待ったったったったったー
Cry out, waiting on both left and right
嗚呼 健全に
Ah, healthily
断罪は 智は 欲を背負い シャウト シャウト
Judgment and wisdom, carrying desires, shout, shout
Your action and your words would never match
You're just a piece of trash, and that's a fact
Who's toxic? It's you!
Okay everyone, this is "Who's Toxic? It's You!"
You made me feel that I'm not good enough
I gave you my best, but you're not impressed
It's falls apart, you broke my heart
You're spreading more lies and lies and lies
I had enough, cut it out, I am begging no more
Sing with me!
It's you the one who spread the words that I am fake
It's you the one who stabbed me right in the back
And now you say that I'm misread
But I don't even really care anyway
It's you who did some things but then I took the blame
It's you who mess around and do a hits and runs
You made my days a living hell
Now I don't care, who's toxic? It's you!
Welcome to the Eclipse Breaker!
Even though you're watching me on the screen,
but I still want to hear you scream!
Can't hear you!
It's bullshit!
It's falls apart, you broke my heart
You're spreading more lies and lies and lies
I had enough, cut it out, I am begging no more
It's you the one who tried to make me go insane
It's you who should stop and feel a shame
I see your lies, it's all in vain
I better just ignore it anyway
It's you the one who turned my world upside down
It's you who break the rules and pull me under the bus
Just go away, that you can't stay
Just go to hell
Now tell me why...
You make me question my reality
Now I have the lesson learned
This is all I need to know
It's you...
the one who makes me feel that I am weak...
Your words hit so hard make me black and blue
I know the truth but you deny
Who cares about it anyway?
It's you the one who spreads the lies with any flag
It's you the one who does the sins and never regret
I have to warn you, you know this karma
I need no drama
So who's toxic, it's you!
Screw this!
I don't care
Who's toxic, it's you!
Hoo! Guys!
You are on fire guys!
Akhirnya! Akhirnya kita melakukan 3D lagi guys...
Finally! Finally we're doing a 3D live again guys...
...setelah menunggu beberapa tahun lamanya ya guys.
...after waiting for quite a few years.
Buat kalian yang ingin ikut menghype stream ini,
For those of you who want to hype up this stream,
kalian bisa pakai hashtag #EclipseBreaker3DLive.
you can use the hashtag #EclipseBreaker3DLive.
3D LIVE!
Sebelum itu, Moona mau ngenalin nih guys.
Before that, Moona wants to introduce something.
Kalau misalnya kalian lihat nih di belakangnya Moona ya...
If you look behind Moona...
Wow! Kece banget banget banget ya guys.
Wow! It's really, really cool, guys.
Apalagi nih Moona paling suka monitornya guys.
Especially, Moona loves the monitor the most.
Soalnya monitornya itu guys, uh, bulan banget.
Because the monitor is, uh, very moon-like.
Everything in here is Moona Hoshinova coordination.
Belum lagi nih guys, belum lagi nih.
Not only that, guys. Not only that.
Kalau misalnya kalian lihat ya guys di belakangnya Moona ya guys...
If you look behind Moona, guys...
We have the Monavitas!
They are kind of... kind of shy right now so they didn't move anything.
They just like want to be a pose of a robot-y. So...
Gimana? Kalian suka nggak sama nyanyi-nyanyiannya Moona?
How is it? Do you like Moona's singing?
Semoga kalian suka ya, karena ya
I hope you like it, because actually
sebenarnya cukup capek ya Moona loncat-loncat dari tadi.
Moona's quite tired from jumping around since earlier.
Tapi, kita masih ada lagu-lagu nih buat kalian.
But, we still have more songs for you.
Sebelum kita pindah ke lagu selanjutnya, Moona ganti baju dulu ya.
Before we move on to the next song, Moona will change her clothes first.
Tunggu sebentar ya!
Wait a moment!
Gimana nih? Wow! Wow! Wow!
How about this? Wow! Wow! Wow!
Gimana? Bajunya bagus banget ya guys. Eclipse Breaker.
How is it? The shirt is really good, guys. Eclipse Breaker.
Di lagu kali ini Moona akan nyanyi lagu-lagu yang agak-agak nge-band dikit guys.
In this next song, Moona will sing songs that are a bit more band-like.
Soalnya kita konsepnya itu ala-ala band gitu biar live-nya berasa banget.
Because our concept is like a band, so the live feel is really strong.
Jadi kita akan mulai dengan...
So we will start with...
Na na na na na... I got Deja Vu.
We're gonna start with DEJAVU!
I hope you guys are ready.
Na na na na na... I got Deja Vu...
It's been many years I'm thinking
how effortlessly we should be together
The beginning it was sweet but it's a shame
how quickly it turned sour
You let the good things slip away
I waited for hours
you would lead me astray
While you lied on her bed
Oh no...
Now I'm done...
we were never meant to be but oh...
I got Deja Vu me and you
never got to finish what we started
How you always want to somebody new
had me broken hearted
But I realized you were no good
now I'm gonna look back to laugh about it
I'm so glad that we are through
I got Deja Vu, you're so crazy...
Did you think of me?
Did I have your full attention?
But I wasn't the only one.
Guess you just forgot to mention.
I'm so over it.
Thank god I dodged a bullet.
Made so many mistakes,
but they made me who I am.
I'm alright.
That's a lot of better, better oh...
I got deja vu, me and you.
Never got the finish what we started.
How you always run to somebody new.
Had me brokenhearted.
But I realized you were no good.
Now I'm gonna fight to laugh about it.
I'm so glad that we are through.
And I get deja vu.
Nothing stayed the same.
And I yet played your game.
I have no complaints because you made me who I am.
Looking back and smile.
Can't believe how far I've come.
What was I thinking?
It got me singing.
I got deja vu, me and you.
Never got the finish what we started.
How you always run to somebody new.
Had me brokenhearted.
But I realized you were no good.
Now I'm gonna fight to laugh about it.
I'm so glad that we are through.
And I get deja vu.
I got deja vu.
High Tide
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: ZSunder
When you look up at the night sky, what do you see?
The glowing beauty in the twilight's a mystery.
No words are said as it lights it all up.
When the time has come I'll be rising high.
Drowning for me like a lifeline. Whenever you see my show.
Head's follow just high.
It's pulling you in like gravity.
You will be bowing on your knees, yeah.
Pulling you in close to me.
Watch my glory and my...
Following me like a high tide. My reign will never stop.
The tide begins to rise to the top.
Let my power ignite. Following me like a high tide.
I can be a bright enigma. It's no surprise.
That you'll give in to the brilliance. Like a moth to a light.
Playing hard to get but I'm patient.
Yes, you'll come to my radiant, yeah.
When you look up at the night sky, what do you see? My show.
Head's follow just high.
It's pulling you in like gravity.
You will be bowing on your knees, yeah.
Pulling you in close to me.
Watch my glory and my...
Following me like a high tide. My reign will never stop.
The tide begins to rise to the top.
Let my power ignite. Following me like a high tide.
Following me like a high tide.
I'll shine the brightest in the night.
The way the waves come night.
Okay guys, that's High Tide.
And after this we continue to Perisai Jitu.
If you guys know this song, please sing it with me.
Thank you!
Perisai Jitu
Lyrics: Donne Maula / Music, Arrangement: Ari Renaldi
Wajah cerah yang terlihat
A bright face that's seen
Diriku mahir sembunyi rasa
I'm skilled at hiding feelings
Sebenarnya hitam pekat
Actually it's pitch black
Kutup rapat jadi rahasia
I keep it tight, it becomes a secret
Satu dua kali
Once or twice
Kun tak apa-apa
I'm okay
Kamu pikir hidupku baik-baik saja
You think my life is just fine
Siapa yang peduli
Who cares
Kupunya air mata
I have tears
Kamu hanya minta diri berikan tawa
You only ask me to give a laugh
Ha ha ha...
Wajah yang ku perisai jitu
The face I use as a perfect shield
Ha ha ha...
Tapi sampai kapan ku begitu
But how long will I be like that?
Malam hari berwahana
Roaming at night
Pikiran liar ku juaranya
My wild thoughts are the champions
Bukan ku tak berusaha
It's not that I'm not trying
Ingin ku lepas sekuat tenaga
I want to let go with all my might
Satu dua kali
Once or twice
Kun tak apa-apa
I'm okay
Kamu pikir hidupku baik-baik saja
You think my life is just fine
Siapa yang peduli
Who cares
Kupunya air mata
I have tears
Kamu hanya minta diri berikan tawa
You only ask me to give a laugh
Ha ha ha...
Wajah yang ku perisai jitu
The face I use as a perfect shield
Ha ha ha...
Tapi sampai kapan ku begitu
But how long will I be like that?
All right, you guys ready for the next?
Yes.
Taut Hati, let's go!
Tak perlu selalu bicara
No need to always talk
Tapi kau pasti yang ku percaya
But you're definitely the one I trust
Tempat berbagi cerita
A place to share stories
Tangis pilu tawa gembira
Grieving tears and joyful laughs
Tak jumpa bagaimana kita
No matter how we meet
Saling mengerti tanpa ada kata-kata
Understanding each other without words
Kita bisa selalu saling menjaga
We can always look out for each other
Tak paksa sayap ku jauh
Don't force my wings to fly far
Tanpa takut ku kan terjatuh
Without fear that I will fall
Jika lelah aku tahu
If I'm tired, I know
Dirimu tempat ku berteduh
You're the place where I take shelter
Senangmu bahagiaku
Your joy is my happiness
Kesalmu pasti lah sedihku
Your annoyance is surely my sadness
Walau kita jarang temu
Even if we rarely meet
Kita selalu bisa saling bertumpu
We can always rely on each other
Ru ru ru...
Bisa saling bertumpu
Can rely on each other
My body and soul...
この手で make you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine
Wow wow wow...
(Yeah) Wow wow wow...
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと...
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever...
君を見るたび 上書きされてゆく欲望に
Every time I see you, desire rewrites
重なる eyes, eyes, eyes 胸を突く smile, smile, smile
Overlapping eyes, eyes, eyes... your smile, smile, smile strikes my heart
ねえ その姿かたち 全てが拍車かけてく
Hey, that figure, that shape... everything's driving me wild
恋から愛、愛、愛 毎秒可笑しくなってく
From a crush into love, love, love... every second, I'm losing my mind
手を伸ばせばもう 届く距離
If I reach out, it's close enough
危険な A to Z 試したい
A dangerous A to Z, let's try it out
穏やかに恋したい どんなシーンも私に見せて
I wanna love you gently... show me any scene, let me see it all
このまま stay by my side
Stay by my side, just like this
どこにも行かないで
Don't go anywhere
100% 純粋な愛だから
100% pure love, that's for sure
ねえ いいでしょ?
Come on, isn't it okay?
止められない感情
These feelings, I can't hold back
その腕で抱きしめてよ
Wrap me up tight in your arms
もう 遠ざけななや
No more distance, no way
ずっと もっと近くで
I need you closer, every day
認め合いたい
Let's be real, no more lies
暴れ狂う衝動 持て余す駆け引きさ
Wild emotions running free... If I can't control it, it's too much for me
Hey, me! What's wrong with me?
Say!
何も問題ない 普段通り
Nothing's wrong, just me being me
My name!
君の全部知りたい
I wanna know all about you
I do need you, 今すぐ
I do need you, right now
最初は声を聞く それだけで良かった
At first, just hearing your voice was enough
ふと気づいた なぜ わがままになったんだ
But then, slowly, "Why?" I became selfish
誰かに微笑みかけ
When you smile at someone else
その誰かに苛立ち 隠せない
It frustrates me, I can't hide it
自分に気づいた
I realized it was me.
独り占めしたい
I wanna keep you all to myself
いっそ鎖に繋いで
Maybe I should chain you up
二人きりの部屋 至近距離
in a room just for us, so close
言動 発言 監視したい
I wanna watch everything you do and say
頬寄せて眠りたい
I wanna sleep with my cheek next to yours
そっと吐息感じさせて
Let me feel your breath on me
永遠に Stay by your side
Stay by your side, forevermore
どこにも行かせない
I won't let you go anywhere
100% 私だけに依存して
100% depend on me, that's all
ねぇいいでしょ
Come on, isn't it okay?
縺れ詰まる愛憎
Love and hate turning black
丸ごと受け止めてよ
Take it all in, don't hold back
(Boy, I wanna touch your love)
私おかしいかな
Is something wrong with me?
だとしても引き返せない
Even if it is, there's no turning back
昂ぶる衝動
Wild emotions running free
歯止め効かない絶対
No stopping me, no way
Hey, me! What's wrong with me?
何も問題ない フツーだし
Nothing's wrong, just me being me
(my name)
君の全部知りたい
I wanna know all about you
I do need you, 今すぐ
I do need you, right now
目を閉じたなら 止められない愛が
When I close my eyes, it's endless
触れたいんだ
I want to experience love, my way
Boy, you
私の... 私だけ...
Mine... all mine...
このまま Stay by my side
Stay by my side, just like this
二度と離れないで
"Don't ever leave me"
100% 純粋な愛だから
100% pure love, that's for sure
ねぇいいでしょ
Come on, isn't it okay?
この感情 抑えられない
These feelings, I can't hold back
腕の中で抱きしめてよ
Wrap me up tight in your arms
(Boy, I wanna touch your love)
もう遠ざけない
No more distance, no way
ずっともっと近くで 求め合いたい
I need you closer, every day
昂ぶる衝動
Wild emotions running free
持て余すくらいさ
If I can't control it, it's too much for me
Hey, me! What's wrong with me?
何も問題ない フツーだし
Nothing's wrong, just me being me
(my name)
君の全部知りたい
I wanna know all about you
I do need you, 今すぐ
I do need you, right now
Wow wow wow
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever...
Whoa! Nerissa!
Finally our duet together song came true!
Finally our duet together came true!
I know!
Thank you so much!
I can't believe that I get to sing with you, the Moona Hoshinova!
It's such a dream come true!
Oh my God, me too!
So, this song...
is actually about two girls who falling in love with one person and wanted to become their lover.
Um, this song's actually not talking about a good romance, everyone.
So it's more like some... another toxic relationship who want to be loved...
100%, right Nerissa?
Right!
Uh, you know, we all probably have some experiences with toxic love.
But, Moona, I have to tell you,
when I was recording this, I was actually thinking about you.
Hehe.
Oh! You love me 100%?
Mm-hmm, I do, 100%!
Nice.
Anyway, thank you so much Nerissa for accepting my offer to do it with me.
Oh my God, I love your voice so much!
Thank you!
Ah, that means so much to me because I love your voice so much!
Thank you for inviting me, and also, Happy Birthday!
I hope this next year of your life is even better than the last!
Aw, thank you!
And also, thank you everyone!
All right, after this, there will be another member to join to sing with me.
So, are you guys ready?
Now let's move to the next song!
Yeah!
Yay!
Maze Town
Lyrics: 米澤海人, 藤原彩豊
Music: 米澤海人, 藤原彩豊, サイトウリョウスケ, PASSION KING
Maze Town
Lyrics: Kaito Yonezawa, Ayato Fujiwara
Music: Kaito Yonezawa, Ayato Fujiwara, Ryosuke Saito, PASSION KING
月明かり 闇を睨む今宵も
The moonlight glares at the darkness again tonight
Cos' I'm waiting 溶け
Cos' I'm waiting melting
日の光降る朝
The morning when the sunlight falls
期待みたいね
It's like anticipation, isn't it?
重い扉の奥で
Behind the heavy doors
さあ その時を待ってる
Come, I'm waiting for that moment
いつまでも繋がる
Connected forever
永遠なんてない 誰が決めた？
Who decided there's no such thing as eternity?
時も命も 飛び越え
Leaping over both time and life
信じよう
Let's believe
Maze Town Maze Town 逃れられないわ
Maze Town, Maze Town, you can't escape
迷い続ける 幾多の魂
Many souls continue to wander
何千もの雨風 乗り越えて
Overcoming thousands of rain and wind
守ってきた
I have protected it
Maze Town どんなに暗い場所だろうと
Maze Town, no matter how dark the place may be
進み続ける まだ見ぬ未来も
I will keep moving forward, even into an unseen future
大切なもの 壊さぬように
So as not to break the things important to me
足音に耳 澄ます
I listen closely to the footsteps
そこにいるのは 誰？ 誰？ 誰？
Who is there? Who? Who?
鏡越し 不気味な音で Let you know
Through the mirror, with an eerie sound, let you know
この場所へ 私たちの棲み処
To this place, our dwelling
ないはずの 黒い影うごめけ
Black shadows that shouldn't exist, wriggle
不気味なシルエット
An eerie silhouette
確かにあるもの
Something that certainly exists
離さない 未来まで
I won't let go, until the future
信じてきた この想い ここに
The feelings I've believed in are here
Maze Town Maze Town 離れられないわ
Maze Town, Maze Town, I can't leave
回り続ける 記憶とこの場所
Memories and this place keep spinning
僅かな時間と 思い出も
Even the small amount of time and memories
守っていくから
I will go on protecting them
Maze Town 明けない夜を飛び越えて
Maze Town, leaping over the night that never ends
今蘇る 彷徨う魂
Wandering souls now come back to life
境界線 曖昧に溶け出してく
The boundaries are starting to blur and melt
心に耳を当てて
Place your ear to your heart
そばにいるのは 誰？
Who is by your side?
さあ 動き出した
Come, it has started moving
永遠に 踊り続けましょう
Let's keep dancing forever
巡る 巡る 時を乗り越えて
Overcoming the spinning, revolving time
進み続ける 私は変わらず
I continue to move forward, unchanged
どんな日でも 守りたいものを 守ってきた 今
No matter the day, I've protected what I wanted to protect, and now...
動き出した
...it has started moving
Maze Town Maze Town 逃れられないわ
Maze Town, Maze Town, you can't escape
迷い続ける 幾多の魂
Many souls continue to wander
何千もの雨風 乗り越えて
Overcoming thousands of rain and wind
守ってきた
I have protected it
Maze Town どんなに暗い場所だろうと
Maze Town, no matter how dark the place may be
進み続ける まだ見ぬ未来も
I will keep moving forward, even into an unseen future
大切なもの 壊さぬように
So as not to break the things important to me
足音に耳 澄ます
I listen closely to the footsteps
そこにいるのは 誰？ 誰？ 誰？
Who is there? Who? Who?
あなたの逃げ場は私 魅惑が手引きする
I am your refuge; fascination will guide you
ある夜に あなたの居場所はない 奈落はない
On a certain night, you have no place, there is no abyss
朽ちるまで 光りましょう ましょう
Let us shine until we rot, shall we?
魔性少女
Bewitching Girl
Lyrics, Music: なきそ
Lyrics, Music: Nakiso
はじめましてのキスをしましょう
Let's share a first-time kiss
味気ないだけの ドラマと違う 私は毒気
Different from a boring drama, I am poisonous
まるで運命の糸を 結びつける
It's as if I'm tying the thread of fate
お遊び 大胆に抱きしめてあげる ほら虜
Just for play, I'll hold you boldly, look, you're captivated
奪っちゃった 心ごと 恨み言を どうぞさあ どうぞ どうぞ
I've stolen your heart, go ahead with your grudges, please, come on
魔法のような超常現象 誰もが夢中 愛してる
A supernatural phenomenon like magic, everyone is obsessed, I love you
ねぇあなたの逃げ場は私 魅惑が引き寄せる
Hey, I am your refuge, my charm draws you in.
あの世にあなたの居場所はない ならばしょうがない
In the next world, you have no place, so it can't be helped.
朽ちるまで光りましょう
Let's shine until we decay,
ましょう
shall we?
はじめましてのキスをしましょう
Let's have a first-time kiss.
何も考えないで 毒々舞う 私の路地
Don't think about anything, poisonously dancing in my alley.
まるで運命の糸を結びつける
It's as if I'm tying the thread of fate.
お遊び 簡単に騙されて お利口 ほら虜
Just playing around, easily deceived, such a good boy, see, you're a captive.
ねぇあなたの逃げ場は私 魅惑が引き寄せる
Hey, I am your refuge, my charm draws you in.
あの世にあなたの居場所はない ならばしょうがない
In the next world, you have no place, so it can't be helped.
朽ちるまで光りましょう
Let's shine until we decay,
ましょう
shall we?
あなたの居場所は私
I am your place to be.
あの子にあなたへの愛はない ならばしょうがない
That girl has no love for you, so it can't be helped.
私たち契りましょう 明かしましょう
Let's make a vow, let's reveal it.
ねぇあなたの逃げ場は私 魅惑が引き寄せる
Hey, I am your refuge, my charm draws you in.
あの世にあなたの居場所はない ならばしょうがない
In the next world, you have no place, so it can't be helped.
朽ちるまで光りましょう
Let's shine until we decay,
ましょう
shall we?
エチュードは1曲だけ
Etude wa 1 Kyoku Dake
カーテン揺らす風が 窓の外からそっと
The wind shaking the curtains softly from outside the window...
教えてくれたのね 出会いの時を
...told me about the time of our meeting.
あなたが弾くピアノは アジサイに軽く歌い
The piano you play sings lightly to the hydrangeas...
立ち止まる私にも ポロポロ 降り注ぐ
...and sprinkles down on me as I stop in my tracks.
戻れるの
I can go back,
今なら大丈夫さ
it's okay now.
嘘は言わないで 噂の人
Don't tell lies, you rumored person.
ノンノン 響いてるわ
Non-non, it's resonating,
ギュンギュン ぴゅあなハートに
gyun-gyun, in my pure heart.
ダメダメ まだ
No, no, not yet,
ダメ 流し目だけは
no, at least not that sidelong glance.
ヤンヤン あなたの指が
Yan-yan, your fingers,
ダンダン 弾く動き
dandan, their plucking movements.
ドキドキ ドキドキ ドキドキ ドキドキ いたずらなエチュード
Thump-thump, thump-thump... a mischievous etude.
大切に過ごしたい 春と夏の真ん中
I want to spend time carefully, in the middle of spring and summer.
あの子と同じように 奪われちゃった
Just like that girl, I've been stolen away.
無邪気にハシャぐ声で つま先が彷徨うのよ
With an innocent, cheerful voice, my toes are wandering.
ねぇアジサイ 私だけハラハラ 慰めて
Hey hydrangea, just for me, harahara, comfort me.
帰れるの
I can go home,
気にしなくていいさ
you don't have to worry.
曖昧な優しさ 憎たらしい
Vague kindness is so detestable.
ノンノン 聴きたくないの
Non-non, I don't want to hear it,
ギュンギュン 甘いメロディ
gyun-gyun, that sweet melody.
ダメダメ やっぱ
No, no, as expected, no,
ダメ 今度はどの子
which girl is it this time?
ヤンヤン 待ちぼうけでも
Yan-yan, even if I'm kept waiting,
ダンゼン 許してしまう
I definitely end up forgiving you.
テテテテ ドキドキ 2人だけエチュード
Te-te-te-te, thump-thump, an etude for just the two of us.
ずっと もっと 独り占め エチュード
Always more, an étude just for me.
えー えー えー あー
Eh eh eh ah...
本当に戻れるの？
Can we really go back?
今なら 1曲だけなら大丈夫さ
Right now, if it's just one song, it'll be fine.
嘘は言わないで 噂の人
Don't tell lies, person of rumors.
何だ 響いてるんだよ ギュンギュン ピュアハートに
What's this ringing in my throbbing pure heart?
ダメ ダメ ダメ まだダメ
No, no, no, not yet.
独り占めだけは
Just keeping it to myself is...
やーやー あなたの指が だんだん激しく動き
Yeah, yeah, your fingers move more and more intensely.
ドキドキ ドキドキ 二人だけ エチュード
Thump-thump, thump-thump, an étude for just the two of us.
いや いや もういや いたずらな エチュード
No, no, I've had enough of this mischievous étude.
Yeah, semuanya!
Yeah, everyone!
Itu adalah lagu-lagu kita hari ini.
Those were our songs for today.
Gila! Wow! Banyak banget ya lagunya hari ini.
Crazy! Wow! There were so many songs today.
Kita semua beneran bernyanyi.
We all really sang our hearts out.
Ngomong-ngomong ya, tentang lagu-lagu yang udah kita nyanyiin sama temen-temen,
By the way, about the songs we sang with friends,
member-member Hololive. Terima kasih semuanya!
Hololive members. Thank you everyone!
Semoga kalian semua suka, dan semoga semuanya menyenangkan.
I hope you all liked it, and I hope everything was fun.
Duh, capek banget guys. Semuanya ya...
Man, I'm so tired guys. Everything...
selama persiapan untuk 3D ini tuh, wow, wow, panjang banget.
during the preparation for this 3D, wow, wow, it was a very long journey.
Soalnya ini kan untuk birthday ya kita,
Since this is for our birthday,
kita sudah bersama kurang lebih hampir 5 tahun.
we've been together for almost 5 years now.
5 tahun guys, gila gila gila!
5 years guys, crazy crazy crazy!
Jadi, Moona mau bilang terima kasih semuanya telah mendukung Moona.
So, Moona wants to say thank you to everyone who supported Moona.
Dan juga semoga kalian tertarik untuk membeli merch-nya...
And also I hope you guys are interested in buying the merch...
Moona Hoshinova! Woo! Jadi ini dia merch-nya!
of Moona Hoshinova! Woo! So here is the merch!
Yay! Ini dia semuanya.
Yay! This is it, everyone.
Kita panggil dulu kali ya announcer, Moona Hoshinova.
Let's call the announcer persona, Moona Hoshinova.
Selamat datang semuanya yang telah datang dan menonton Moona Hoshinova.
Welcome everyone who has come to watch Moona Hoshinova.
Ini merupakan Birthday Commemorative Full Set yang diisikan oleh...
This is the Birthday Commemorative Full Set, which includes...
MoonRadiance Wide Rubber Mat yang diilustrasikan oleh Nyori-mama.
The MoonRadiance Wide Rubber Mat illustrated by Nyori-mama.
Ya guys, jadi ini kita ada MoonRadiance Wide Rubber Mat,
Yeah guys, so here we have the MoonRadiance Wide Rubber Mat,
ada ilustrasi dari Nyori-sensei, Nyori-mama. Terima kasih, I love you so much!
with illustration by Nyori-sensei, Nyori-mama. Thank you, I love you so much!
MoonRockMelody Plushie Keychain.
The MoonRockMelody Plushie Keychain.
Kapan lagi nih punya plushie Moona Hoshinova yang versi rock guys?
When else can you get a rock version plushie of Moona Hoshinova, guys?
Keren, keren!
It's cool, cool!
MoonAMP Shoulder Bag.
The MoonAMP Shoulder Bag.
Ini tuh dia tuh apa ya, kayak tas selempangan gitu guys.
This one is like a sling bag, guys.
Jadi tuh kalian bisa taruh HP kalian, taruh dompet kalian...
So you can put your phone, put your wallet...
pas kalian lagi ng-event. Wih keren banget guys, keren asli.
when you're at an event. Wow, it's really cool guys, seriously cool.
Terus, buat kalian nih, kalo misalnya kalian menonton,
Then, for you guys, if you're watching,
kalian teriak, kalian 'oi oi oi oi'!
you're shouting, doing the 'oi oi oi oi'!
Pasti kalian haus!
You must be thirsty!
Jika begitu, maka kalian harus minum!
If so, then you must drink!
Jika kalian minum, maka kalian harus menggunakan MoonStar Brew Tumbler!
If you drink, then you must use the MoonStar Brew Tumbler!
Ada gambar Moona guys di... dengan radiasi bintang.
There's a picture of Moona on it... with star radiation.
Radiasi! Hahaha!
Radiation! Hahaha!
Bintang Aquarius!
Aquarius Star!
Yeay! Dan selanjutnya...
Yeay! And next...
...buat kalian nih.
...for you guys.
Buat kalian yang suka sama voice-nya Moona...
For those of you who like Moona's voice...
...suka sama suaranya Moona...
...like Moona's voice...
Moona ada...
Moona has...
...tiga Situation Voice Pack...
...three Situation Voice Packs...
...yang berisi tiga bahasa!
...in three languages!
Walau jika kalian membeli full set-nya...
Though if you buy the full set...
...akan ada bonus postcard...
...there will be a bonus postcard...
...dengan ilustrasi dari Nyori-sensei...
...with an illustration by Nyori-sensei...
...dan ditandatangani oleh Moona!
...and signed by Moona!
Jumlahnya terbatas lho!
The quantity is limited!
Jadi jangan sampai kehabisan.
So don't run out.
Wow, kemudian nih...
Wow, then...
...ini waduh...
...this, wow...
...nggak habis-habis guys!
...it never ends guys!
Sebagai bonus dari pembelian full set premium merch...
As a bonus for purchasing the full set premium merch...
...akan ada tambahan bonus satu kartu...
...there will be an additional bonus card...
...yang bisa digunakan di hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME...
...that can be used in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME...
...yang dijual tahun lalu.
...sold last year.
Nah, kartu ini hanya tersedia untuk pembelian...
Now, this card is only available for purchase...
...di official shop hololive production.
at the hololive production official shop.
Bonus yang bisa didapat adalah...
The bonus you can get is...
...kartu Oshi Holomem Card.
...the Oshi Holomem Card.
Tapi kartunya hanya tersedia dalam bahasa Jepang...
But the card is only available in Japanese...
...jadi mohon pengertiannya ya.
...so please understand.
Untuk detail kartu dan cara bermain...
For card details and how to play...
...silakan cek homepage-nya.
...please check the homepage.
Ya!
Yes!
Itulah...
That's...
...pengumuman untuk merch di birthday kali ini.
...the announcement for the merch for this birthday.
Abis ini kita akan ada lagu lagi teman-teman...
After this we will have more songs, friends...
...yaitu Multiverse...
...namely Multiverse...
...dan Nightmare!
...and Nightmare!
Jadi Moona mau ganti baju dulu ya.
So Moona is going to change clothes first.
Bye-bye! See you later!
Oh yeah
Cried about a thousand tears 真夜中に
Cried about a thousand tears in the middle of the night
彷徨うことは何度もあった
I've wandered many times
I found myself in that place of the real me
全てには意味があったの
Everything had a meaning
I've got a side to me that I haven't shown
My every scar shows a different kind of glow
飛び立つのよ So I'm moving to a higher plane
Flying off, so I'm moving to a higher plane
あの日々は like a faraway icon
Those days are like a faraway icon
何度でも
Again and again
傷ついてきたから
Because I've been hurt
Never want to lose myself in the unknown
偽りない旅へと
To a journey with no lies
I'll throw my soul out to burn
広がる multiverse
The expanding multiverse
増えていく my universe, my universe now
Increasing my universe, my universe now
美しく彩っていく my multiverse
Beautifully coloring my multiverse
I crawl from the dirt
Here and now my destiny is calling
光射す元へ saying softly
To where the light shines, saying softly
Even when I fall gotta dust it off
Even when I'm lost gotta keep it up
Step on it, step on it, bet everything like... oh!
全てを込めて出掛けるの yeah
Pouring everything in and leaving, yeah
It's just my game
重力を追い越しこのまま yeah
Surpassing gravity like this, yeah
I'm on my way
It's a lonely journey
No one's here to save me no I've got to go on
振り返らずに
Without looking back
I'll throw my soul out to burn
広がる multiverse
The expanding multiverse
増えていく my universe, my universe now
Increasing my universe, my universe now
暗闇の先には輝く world
At the end of the darkness is a shining world
捧げる all to the heart
Dedicate all to the heart
続いていく my universe, oh yes, 踊って
My universe continues, oh yes, dance
美しく彩っていく my multiverse
Beautifully coloring my multiverse
I crawl from the heart
I crawl from the dirt
I crawl from the pains of the days
Burn!
I crawl from the heart
I crawl from the dirt
I crawl from the pains of the days
When troubles come my way, that's when the stars are made
Watch as I queen and rise higher, higher
In every darkest day, it's how to see the stray
I'll throw my soul out to burn
Woo!
広がる multiverse
The expanding multiverse
増えていく...
Increasing...
My universe, my universe, my universe now
暗闇の先　君は輝くを
Beyond the darkness, you shine
捧げる　Offer the heart
I offer, offer the heart
続いていく　my universe　my always 全て
Continuing, my universe, my always, everything
この軌道に乗り nothing's gonna stop me
Riding this orbit, nothing's gonna stop me
美しく彩って my multiverse
Beautifully coloring my multiverse
Grab from the heart
満ちるなら 固く 閉め切って
If it fills up, shut it tight
聞こえるの歌 感情はない
I hear the song, there's no emotion
Dark knight, I won't cry
Yeah Nightmare
Nightmare
Crazy
歪む嘘さえ 目に沁みる Blackness
Even distorted lies soak into my eyes, blackness
意味のない Sympathy, oh no
Meaningless sympathy, oh no
どうして堕ちる Falling hole
Why am I falling into a hole?
目眩のする衝動 場面は透けた Evil
Dizzying impulse, the scene became transparent evil
指差してあざ笑う 空想
Pointing and laughing, a fantasy
ここまでは果たせない 何て脆い
I can't reach this far, how fragile
浮かび上がらせた 重たい足で
Bringing it to the surface, with heavy feet
今日も歩き出す
I start walking again today
In the night 犠牲的な制御
In the night, sacrificial control
うぬぼれるなよ 聞こえてくる Nightmare
Don't get conceited, I can hear the nightmare
きっと眠れない 砕けそうな干渉
Surely I can't sleep, interference that seems about to break
渦巻く感情 手放せたら 響き渡る Shadow
Whirling emotions, if I could let go, the shadow would resound
Yeah Nightmare
Nightmare
Crazy ぶつかるメモリ
Crazy, colliding memories
本当に私は必要ない
Am I really not needed?
常識とは Telling lies
Common sense is telling lies
閉ざした答えの 闇 消せない間違い
The darkness of the closed answer, an unerasable mistake
誤魔化すほどに 零れ落ちる 期待
The more I try to hide it, the more expectations spill out
In the night 犠牲的な招待
In the night, sacrificial invitation
欲のなき希望 失う前 Nightmare
Hopeless wish, before losing, nightmare
ああ もっと 手を伸ばす 続いていく残像
Ah, reach out further, continuing afterimage
振り解けば 笑えるのかな
If I shake it off, will I be able to laugh?
紅い手 許される
Forgiven with red hands
望み 満たされたい
Desire, I want to be fulfilled
信じる事が出来たなら
If I could believe
In the night 犠牲的な制御
In the night, sacrificial control
うぬぼれるなよ 聞こえてくる Nightmare
Don't get conceited, I can hear the nightmare
きっと眠れない 砕けそうな干渉
Surely I can't sleep, interference that seems about to break
渦巻く感情 手放せたら 目覚め
Whirling emotions, if I could let go, awaken
Yeah Nightmare
Nightmare
Crazy
Thank you!
MOONA HOSHINOVA
THE FIRST ALBUM
PANDORA
[TRACKLIST]
Limited Bonus Edition
Regular Edition
Pre-orders open today at 22:00 JST / 20:00 WIB!
MOONA HOSHINOVA "PANDORA"
This will be the first album from hololive Indonesia.
The album includes four brand new songs,
including the collaboration track 100% with Nerissa, which I just performed today.
It also features previously released songs
like Nightmare from last year, making a total of 10 tracks.
The CD comes in two editions:
Limited Bonus Edition and Regular Edition.
Limited Bonus Edition includes a CD jacket with my handwritten autograph.
This is a one-of-a-kind autograph just for you.
Comes with an online meet & greet lottery application ticket,
plus a special letter from Moona and two clear bookmarks.
It's a super deluxe package!
Regular Edition comes with one random trading card.
There are four different types plus one secret type.
Can't wait to see which one you get!
Pre-orders open right after this
on the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP. Make sure to grab your copy!
By the way, the digital album is set to release on April 12th,
the day after my first ever livestream anniversary.
Thank you for all your incredible support.
I wouldn't be able to make music without you.
Moona Hoshinova, PANDORA.
Hope you're as excited as I am!
Thank you for coming to my 3D Birthday ✨
your love and support make everything shine even brighter!
It's been an incredible-almost 5 years together and
I can't wait to make even more amazing memories with all of you! ♡
Let's keep shining together !!!
-Love Moona ☽