(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
青い水平線を今駆け抜けてゆく
Now, running across the blue horizon.
RIDE ON TIME
Lyrics, Music: 山下達郎
Lyrics, Music: Tatsuro Yamashita
研ぎ澄まされた時の流れ感じて
Feeling the sharpened flow of time.
ときめきへと動き出す世界は
The world that's beginning to move towards excitement.
忘れかけてた遠い夢の訪れ
The arrival of a distant dream I'd nearly forgotten.
Ride on time 彷徨う想いなら
Ride on time, if these are wandering thoughts.
優しく受け止めてそっと包んで
Catch them gently and wrap them up softly.
Oh Ride on time 心に火をつけて
Oh, Ride on time, set your heart on fire.
溢れる喜びに広がる Ride on time
Spreading through overflowing joy, Ride on time.
僕の輝く未来まわり始めて
My shining future has begun to turn.
虚ろな日々も全て愛に溶け込む
Even the hollow days all melt into love.
何という朝今すぐ君の元
What a morning, right now to your side.
届けに行こう燃える心迷わず
I'll go to deliver it, my burning heart without hesitation.
Ride on time 時を走り出せ
Ride on time, start running through time.
鮮やかな光出せ目もくらむほど
Radiate a vivid light, enough to dazzle the eyes.
Oh Ride on time 心に火をつけて
Oh, Ride on time, set your heart on fire.
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride on time
I'll send it to your soul as it takes flight, Ride on time.
届けに行こう燃える心今こそ
I'll go to deliver it, my burning heart, right now.
Oh Ride on time 時を走り出せ
Oh, Ride on time, start running through time.
鮮やかな光出せ目もくらむほど
Radiate a vivid light, enough to dazzle the eyes.
Oh, ride on time...
心に火をつけて
Setting my heart on fire
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride on Time
Sending it to the soaring soul, Ride on Time
Oh, oh, oh, ride on time...
彷徨う想いなら
If they are wandering thoughts
優しく受け止めて
Gently receive them
そっと包んで
Softly envelop them
Oh, ride on time...
心に火をつけて
Setting my heart on fire
あふれる喜びに
Into the overflowing joy
広がる Ride on Time
Spreading, Ride on Time
Oh, ride on time...
時を走り出せ
Start running through time
愛は光りだせ
Let love start shining
目もくらむほど
So much it's dazzling
Oh, ride on time...
心に火をつけて
Setting my heart on fire
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride on Time
Sending it to the soaring soul, Ride on Time
Special Medley
水面に映る自分がいた
There I was, reflected on the water's surface
嗚呼、私は悪いサメです
Ah, I am a bad shark
ずっと恐れていた
I had always been afraid
赤く光るその目
Of those eyes that glow red
海の底、暗闇に消えていく
Disappearing into the darkness at the bottom of the sea
ごめんね、今さら
I'm sorry, it's too late now
気づかなかったことがあるんだけど
But there's something I didn't realize
こうしてあなたが
Because you were here
いてくれたから今の私がいる
Like this, the current me exists
過去はいらない そんなことはない
I don't need the past—no, that's not it
未来は見えない おかしくないじゃない
I can't see the future, but that's not strange
さよなら ありがとう
Goodbye, thank you
すべて受け入れて生きていくから
Because I will live on, accepting everything
海の底はつまらないけど
The bottom of the sea is boring, but...
あなたのことは忘れないから
Because I won't forget about you
いつでも どこでも
Anytime, anywhere
私らしく生きていこう
I'll live as myself
ト・ト・ト・東京わびさびララバイ
To-to-to-Tokyo Wabi-Sabi Lullaby
眠れない夜には褒めたい
On sleepless nights, I want to praise you
Oh nananananana
ねえ、元気してる？話したいよ
Hey, how are you doing? I want to talk
寂しさこらえて
Enduring the loneliness
「またね」って君は笑ってた
You were smiling, saying "See you again"
Oh nananananana
ねえ、今年の夏 また会えるのかな
Hey, I wonder if we can meet again this summer
桜の花びらが咲き始める頃会いに
Coming to see you when the cherry blossoms begin to bloom
やあ 久しぶりだね
Hey, it's been a while
そんな幻想を小銭に維持
Maintaining such illusions with pocket change
東京わびさびララバイ
Tokyo Wabi-Sabi Lullaby
眠れない夜には褒めたい
On sleepless nights, I want to praise you
Oh nananananana
ねえ、元気してる？話したいよ
Hey, how are you doing? I want to talk
会いに来てくれたら君は笑ってくれるかな
If I come to see you, will you smile for me?
ああ とても綺麗だ
Ah, it's so beautiful
一人で見上げた夜空に花火
Fireworks in the night sky I looked up at alone
Never low, straight my heart...
何もかも蜃気楼
Everything is a mirage
夏の女神の
The summer goddess's...
きまぐれね
Whimsical nature
Stay my heart
何食わぬ顔をして
Putting on an innocent face
キスを奪って
Stealing a kiss
Don't go away
いつかまたなんて
Saying "some other time"
I'll never say
唇に裏腹
The opposite on my lips
残したまま
Leaving it behind
まわれ
Spin around
turn around
Myth or Treat, your oshi's waiting in the closet tonight
No wait, stop, she's dead set on giving you a fright
Trick or treat but now we're all out of candy
Feeling just a little sick, this chainsaw oughta come in handy
Chat is blushing, the gators' red cheeks
I'll fix that up, drain all your
blood, that's what
you seek
Myth or treat, oh what a crucified stream
There's no bones about it, you'll scream
Only show ya on Halloween, our spookier, terrifying,
scarier sights
Oh what a gotcha-ya night
Mythic witches with endless spite
Can't escape our idol-ized might
No candy in sight, so your souls will suffice
パレード パレード パレード
Parade, parade, parade
輝くんだよ
It's shining
悔しさも愛しさも
Both your regrets and your love
連れておいで
Bring them along
風 夢 羽
Wind, dreams, wings
飛び立てるさ
You can fly away
ささやかな祈りが 終わりなき兆し
A small prayer is an endless sign
君と
With you
飛び込んでゆく
Diving in
素敵にスタートさ
It's a wonderful start
ここから Colorful World
From here, a Colorful World
パレード パレード パレード
Parade, parade, parade
Face to face with time again
We walk once more to the end
Burn it down
Waves can't put out my flame
Death will never write my name
Burn it down
They say the memory of me is fading
I've heard it all before
Don't tell me everyone around is waiting
And they all say
Tear it down
Burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down
Burn it down
When the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend
If this is the end, I'll do it again
Voices rise in my head
The hands that pull at my thread
Let them drown
Burn it down
Wait for wash in the tide
In the abyss is where I will hide
...will hide
Let them drown Burn it down
They say the memory of me is fading
I've heard it all before
Don't tell me everyone around is waiting
And they all say
Tear it down Burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down burn it down
When the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend
If this is the end
I'll do it again
We swim against the current's aim
In dark we change as smoke returns to rain
Navigating sunken depths and all of its debris
And no more hands upon my words
They only speak for me
For all the ones who try to silence thunder
I'm the wave that pulls you down and under
Everyday I'll stand with me
And I'll fight the drought of shallow sea
As ships sail winds of jealousy I'll listen
carefully
Let it all burn down
As they all say
Tear it down Burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down Burn it down
When the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend
If this is the end
I'll do it again
Hi, hello, hello hello thank you hello
Hi, um, from the very bottom of my shark heart,
thank you.
Um, if I could borrow your ear
for just a... just a bit more time,
I want to thank you, um, again.
Thank you for letting me be your shark idol
for the last half a decade.
Five years, wow. Just about five years or so.
Um, in this time, I... I...
I have loved performing for you...
...here or on stage or in my bedroom,
any... anywhere really.
Um, I... yeah, wow.
Speaking... speaking of half a decade,
when I first joined Hololive,
I had barely any experience in streaming
or dancing or singing in front of people.
I couldn't even sing in front of my own mother.
Um, but... but now, now look at me, right?
Um, I won't lie, it was really hard to get my footing.
Um, sometimes it was terrifying.
No, a lot of the time it was terrifying.
But spending time with you and all of the
incredibly talented members Hololive has
been an absolute pleasure...
...and I can truly say, a highlight in my life.
I will never forget my time here at Hololive.
I... I feel like I've been able to grow a lot
in these past years.
Not in height or brain activity, but...
In my heart,
like my confidence...
my confidence in myself,
I believe in myself a whole lot more now than I did five years ago and...
oh, it's thanks to you.
So thank you everyone
for your compassion, your creativity,
and your dedication
to me,
your Goomba.
Thank you to my Myth ladies.
We've been through so, so much together.
And I am honored to have been able to go on this journey with you girls.
Thank you to Nacho-mama
for always working so hard and making me so darn cute.
And thank you to my chumbuds
for always being there for me,
for pushing me to try new games,
new songs, new experiences.
Thank you for everything.
Ah! I-I-I've got a Gulf Stream current to catch.
Time to Otsu-same one last time.
Ready?
OTSU-SAME!
The biggest!
Take care
and be kind to yourselves.
Okay?
Okay.
Good night
and goodbye.
Goodbye, goodbye!
Bye-bye!
Goodbye!
Gawr Gura
～がうる・ぐら 卒業ミニライブ～
Graduation Mini Live
Gawr Gura
- Gawr Gura Graduation Mini Live -
Graduation Mini Live
Thank you guys so much for coming tonight!
みんな、本当にありがとう！
Everyone, thank you so much!
I love you all! Bye-bye!
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING