(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Cecilia Immergreen 3D SHOWCASE #Cece3D
8/8 - 5:00PM [PDT] / 8/9 - 12:00AM [UTC] / 8/9 - 9:00AM [JST]
Well, you might be wondering how I got here.
It all started on my debut one year ago.
Hmm hmm hmm...
Whoops! Ah!
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Are you going to play your entire debut VOD?
No, but I have a three-hour video essay prepared.
But no, you don't have time or budget for that.
What?
Let me fix this.
Kronii, no!
Ah, oh man, I wish I had 3D.
Whoa, whoa.
Huh?
get flashbanged haha
Spin to win!
Ah, my ankles.
Ah, ah, my ankle.
Hello everyone! It's me, Cecilia Immegreen from Hololive English -Justice-.
Spin to win!
Yay, I'm 3D!
Oh my god, I'm so nervous, I'm so excited.
Hi everyone. Hello todos. Hello everyone in chat. Hello, hello.
It's me, and I was just born out of this egg. Non-canon by the way.
Today we'll be going on a beautiful adventure and maybe having some guests.
And actually, our very first guest is right here on my shoulder. Who could it be?
It's Ottotori! Yay!
Oh, so cute.
Yeah, this is our very first guest today. I wonder who else is going to come today. Hmm...
Maybe, maybe some people.
Oh, Otomo! What do you... what do you want?
Wait, you're so cute! *laughs* What do you want, Otomo, huh? What is it?
Mhm.
Uh, can I say no?
Okay, so... Otomo has just said... I don't know if you can understand him, he has a very weird dialect.
But he just said that since it's been a year since I crashed that car, we're supposed to learn how to drive.
Do you guys want to go learn how to drive? Huh? Huh? Should we do it?
I guess we should do it, Otomo. Okay, I think...
I wonder what we should be doing next.
Okay, let's see guys. Here are options. Please vote in chat.
What should we do now?
a) find a driving teacher
b) ask otomo what to do next
First, find a driving teacher.
Or ask Otomo what to do next. Maybe he has a better idea.
Hmm, I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
But yeah, while we're waiting for the poll to end, maybe I can show off a little bit.
This is what I look like. Finally, you can see me from the back.
Ah, this is my bow, my pretty bow. Yay!
A, B... no, you don't have to type it into chat, you're going to have to like put it into the poll.
Okay, is the... is the poll... is the poll good? Shall we see? Oh, not yet.
Okay. Mhm, yeah, the bow. And then if you look closely, you can see that...
...everything reflects, everything that's made out of metal. And Ottotori is here too, of course, not forgotten.
Never... never forgotten. And Otomo's very cute.
Oh, the poll is over! It's done. Okay, which one won?
A, find a driving teacher.
Okay, I think I know exactly where to go.
Wait, but I forgot. If we're going to drive, I'm going to have to take off the skirt...
...because it's very stiff and I can't sit in it. Let's do that real quick.
Excuse you! Back off, Otomo, back off!
Ta-da! This is what I look like without the skirt on.
Wait! Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Okay, let's go this way.
Let's find a driving teacher!
Hmm...
Huh.
According to the Otomo, this is where
I'm supposed to go.
But no one's here.
Huh?
Be careful!
Cece! Cece!
Oh my god!
Hi everyone!
What are you guys doing here?
Oh, actually a little Otomo told us...
...you were really bad at driving.
No...
No!
No, that's a lie!
That's fake!
But anyway...
Very big galaxy brain Ririka...
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
...and Biboo...
古石ビジュー
Koseki Bijou
...and Sora-senpai...
ときのそら
Tokino Sora
...are gonna tell you...
...how to drive!
Can you guys drive?
Sure! We're the best!
I totally have a license!
No I don't. But it is fine.
Okay, I think if you guys are teaching me,
I have nothing to worry about.
So, let's do it!
Okay! Well, if you're ready...
...please get on the vehicle.
Your noble steed.
So what do I do?
Um, you do the...
...you turn the...
...you go...
Wait, wait!
Cece! Are you okay?
Are you alright?
Time for destruction!
Wait, wait! No, no!
I'm okay, I'm okay!
Guys, don't worry.
Oh, well she...
No, it's okay.
Oh, but that could've gone better,
I think.
So let me show you how it's done!
Okay!
We'll call this the practical test.
Get hit and you'll go boom!
Holokart Time Attack!
Holokart Time Attack
Our racing course is ready!
The rules are simple.
The four of us will compete to see...
Rule: Race through the course 3 times while avoiding all the obstacles! It's a 4-player showdown for the fastest lap time!
...who has the fastest time...
...completing the course...
...while avoiding all the obstacles!
The course starts with two cones.
Uh, feel free to dodge it...
...or just knock it down if it's in your way
if you want.
Then you'll enter the barrel zone!
Dod-dodge them like a pro!
And then finally you aim for the
perfect park...
...at the finish line...
...to clear the course!
Simple enough, right?
Easy, easy, easy!
No problem!
But, but, if you mess up or hit anything
other than the pillar...
Rule: Careful! Touch anything other than cones, and a big explosion awaits!
...total explosion!
And it won't just explode. Heads up!
Each explosion adds a penalty of
three seconds to your time.
So, try not to...
Risk it, or risk it, or risk it to do it fast.
It is totally up to you.
I don't want to die! No!
Okay, I'll go first and show Cece how it's done!
So nervous.
Okay, okay, okay!
Always pre-race interviews.
Sora-senpai, is there anything you would
like to say?
I'll do my best and have fun!
Okay! Sora-senpai, are you ready to...
Okay!
The Holokart Time Attack starts...
Now!
Go!
Whoa! Look at Sora-chan! Acceleration!
Okay, she goes to the first corner! Whoa!
Look at her go! Look at her go!
She's so fast! Whoa!
Okay, second corner! Whoa!
She's going fast! Okay, second lap is a start!
Keep going, Sora-chan! Go, go, go!
Whoa! Oh, she hit the stuff! Whoa!
She's really good! Professional!
Here we go, first corner! Go, go, go, Sora!
Look at her! Sora is coming!
She's got this! She's so safe!
And she's on the straight! But the last part is so difficult!
To the finish line! To the finish line!
Go! Get it! Whoa!
Yeah! I did it!
Yeah! Good job! Good job Sora-chan!
That was explosive!
Yeah!
Okay, now we're checking the final time.
So, in the meantime, how was it? How do you think?
Ah, I think I did great!
Okay, let's look at the time.
Oh, one minute and three seconds!
FINAL TIME 01:03
That's actually really good.
And you got one explosion, so three seconds is added.
Ah, but very fast! So fast!
Okay, okay, okay. Who's next?
Who will be our next challenger?
Hey, I'll go! Yeah!
Okay, Raora-chan, step up to the starting line right here.
All right, Raora-chan, is there anything you would like to say to the audience or Senpai or anything?
I will show you my Holomunky seat! Nice driving!
All right, Raora-chan, are you ready?
Sure! I can do it!
Okay! She sounds very, very sure about herself.
Let's see if she can put her skills to the test.
All right, the Holokart Time Attack starts...
Now!
Okay, okay, okay, you got this!
頑張って！
Do your best!
Go!
Woohoo! Oh! Stay away!
Go away from me! No!
I don't want to die! No!
Whoa! No! Stop!
Ah! No!
Stop it!
Oh! You got this! Go!
Go! Finish line! Finish line!
Ah! I did it!
Yeah! Raora-chan! Finish line!
That was really good.
We're checking the time now, but let's hear it. Are you okay from the challenger?
Yeah, I'm fine. How was it?
I will never drive. I met Kisama.
That might be for the best, you know.
Yes, I have to be your sensei and senpai.
All right, Raora-chan, your time...
...is one minute and nine seconds!
FINAL TIME 01:09
Yeah!
You received five explosions, so five penalties, a total of fifteen second penalty.
So that means I was faster than Sora-chan Senpai?
You were, but you hit the stuff, so yeah.
Our next...
...next...
...Biboo!
It's Biboo's turn now!
Hehe... It's Biboo's turn.
Anything you'd like to say?
I will win!
She's gonna lose.
No, Biboo's so good.
Don't have confidence?
Yeah, she's good at gaming,
so maybe driving is also very good.
We'll see.
Okay...
...start...
...now!
Uwah!
Go, go, go!
Uwah! Sugoi!
Uwah! Awesome!
Uwah!
I'm coming!
I'm the best!
Uwah! Final lap!
Final lap! Here's the finish! Uwah!
Yeah, that was really good!
Good job!
You okay?
I win!
I win! I win! I win!
Just taking the time of Holokart.
Let's see, let's see...
That was...
...maybe I shouldn't drive either.
Guys, you are my teachers.
Only Sora-chan so far has driven safely.
Oh wait, time is coming.
Oh, so finally...
...you were 1 minute and 11 seconds!
FINAL TIME 01:11
So that means you were the slowest.
You got four times explosions.
So that means 20 seconds added.
Dang it, oh well, whatever.
Anyway, I still had the time of my life though.
It was a blast!
No battle please.
For our last challenger...
...we have prepared for you a special course...
...because you are our student, right?
Because you've already seen this...
...so you have an advantage going last.
So we're not going to give you that advantage, okay?
Here it is!
Wow!
It's Justice!
Yeah, Justice 3D was not in our budget, so...
...we have cutouts.
Thanks, guys!
Also, just so you know,
this is your driver's practical,
so you're going to have to beat our average time.
And our average time...
...was 1 minute and 8 seconds!
Driving test cleared if the trio's average time is faster than 1 minute and 8 seconds!
So that's the time that you've got to beat.
I got this.
Okay, watch me.
It's okay, guys, don't worry.
Easy, easy, easy.
This is what I've been training for...
...for the last 10 minutes.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, I'm ready.
Alright...
...anything you'd like to say before the race?
Spin to win!
Wulululululu!
Yeah, you should spin as much as possible.
I'll do it for you.
Thank you, thank you. Okay, let's go.
Any advice for Cecile-senpai?
At first...
First...
...never slow down.
Second...
...go faster than Okone-chan!
Wow! Go faster!
You can do it!
The Holokart Time Attack...
...starts...
...now!
Get hit and you'll go Boom! Holokart Time Attack
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Don't hit me! Oh!
I'm so good! Whoa!
Okay, second lap, let's go!
Watch out! No!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay...
Okay...
Okay! Now for the finish!
You have to park!
Park!
Yay!
That was... wow. That was really... are you sure you should be teaching us?
Maybe I should be teaching you guys.
What do you think your time was?
Faster than AZKi's or not?
20 seconds.
20 seconds?! No way!
But how do you feel after the race?
Invigorated. I feel like I learned so much today.
Were we good teachers?
You especially, IRyS.
Oh, time's coming.
What? Your time is... 56 seconds! Oh my god!
FINAL TIME 00:56
Yay!
You only got one penalty! Oh my god!
Wow, Cece. You... passed!
Oh, your driving was spot on! So, off you go!
Bye-bye! Thank you for teaching me!
Bye-bye! Have fun in the car!
Wait, I want to go too! Wait, wait, let's go!
Wait, can I get in a car? Wait, wait! Whoa!
Wait, what are we doing?
Going on a drive.
Wait, we need a third.
Ah, right.
Biboo!
Carbonated Love
Lyrics: momii Music, Arrangements: 筑佐泰洋 (SUPA LOVE)
Lyrics: momii Music, Arrangements: Yasuhiro Tsukasa (SUPA LOVE)
One, two, three, let's go!
Lost hope in love, I thought I'd never understand
Couldn't help it when you took my hand
Roads ignored before, you left me wanting more
Destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead
Neon lights fly by, is it fake or reality?
Not sure of much but know I'm ready
Soaring these streets make me complete
Full throttle, come give me your all
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last till the sun's up
One, two, three, let's go!
Nother' shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end but we'll... let's go!
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up
and don't look back again
Carbonated love
One, two, three, let's go!
Took a bet on love, it's better than I could've dreamed
Look at what we've done, we're too extreme
Pour me your favorite drink, so much until we sink
Down to the bottom, don't wanna miss a thing
The track we're on might crash, oh what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring old avenues
Race through the night, my guiding light
Sparkling, I'm right here with you
Engine's not keeping up with the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
Till the sun's up
One, two, let's go!
Another shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach a line, mark the end but we'll
Let's go!
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Let's go!
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love's the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, fire it up again
Time is up, not enough, fill it up
and don't look back again
Carbonated love
Come overflow my cup, I'm empty without you
Make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm the fool
Another night of bliss, speed up, let's make it new
Love me despite the way I'm crazy just for you
Another shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach a line, mark the end but we'll
Let's go!
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, fire it up again
Our time is up, not enough, fill it up
and begin
Carbonated love
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
It's your fault!
(Chuckles) Losers.
Oh! Otomo, you took people's place!
Wow! Amazing!
Can you even see the road?
Wait, wait, I saw the road. I saw the road.
No, no, don't worry guys. It's fine, there's no cars here.
There's barely any cars, so... really, it's completely fine.
But yeah, do you see? Do you see how much I've learned in such a little time?
Do you feel safe next... guys, do you feel safe next to me in this car?
What are you saying, Otomo? Do you... I... Is it safe here? Huh?
Yeah, I think so. Whoa!
What's that? Otomo, look!
Can you... Otomos are popping up and look!
Oh! I had turned this off for today because I didn't want it to disrupt, you know, my special day, but...
I guess since we're in the car, it makes sense that... that Otomos would fall from the sky!
Yeah, every membership or gift membership gives a little plop!
It's like a birth. Wow, the circle of Otomo life! That is so beautiful.
Wow, that's incredi... whoa!
I wish I could see you Otomo, but you're so small.
I wish you could see the road and be impressed with how good I am at driving, you know?
Wow! (Laughs) You are so cute. Wait, can I pet you?
Pet pet pet pet pet pet pet.
Okay, okay. Well, anyways, I hope you are impressed by my driving today. Yeah, I really do hope so.
But I think that's too... I think that's too many. I think that's enough Otomos, because otherwise I'll struggle with seeing the road.
Okay, that's enough! Okay, okay, you can stop now! No! No! Ah! Hey!
Stop, stop! Stop it! Stop! No, no, no, no, stop! Stop, it's enough!
Stop! Stop! That's too many! Stop, stop!
Ah! I can't see! Get rid of those!
Ah! I can't see! I can't! I can't see! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ahhhhh!
What? What?
Where?
What is this?
Where am I?
Whoa!
It's so pretty in here!
Wait, I think I want to match this aesthetic a little bit better.
Let me get my skirt back.
Ta-da! Wow!
Otomo! Otomo! Otomo!
Oh...
There you are! You little—
—this is your fault!
How dare you fall on top of my car and make us crash!
You stupid little—you—
—why did you do that to me...
...with all your little Otomo friends, huh?
What did I ever do to deserve that, huh?
You know what? This is your fault as well!
How dare you make me crash!
You little—
You stupid—
I worked so hard for this!
I worked so hard today and you—
No. Okay. No.
No, it's okay. Come back up. Come back up.
Come back up, you baby. It's okay.
And guys, not the right answer.
This—no...
Oh, Otomo is shaking, I guess.
I guess he must be really afraid.
Okay, I'll take a step back.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Anger's not the right answer right now.
We are trapped in this beautiful world and maybe...
...hmm, we're gonna have to find out what we have—what we're supposed to do here.
Otomo, do you have any ideas?
Huh? Of course!
How did I not think about that?
This is the inner clockwork world of our minds!
Both you and me, Otomo, or just me, I'm not sure.
What do you think?
Hmm... He doesn't know either.
Okay, so what we have to do here, apparently, is...
...Otomo wants to learn how to feel emotions.
Human emotions.
Otomo wants to be human.
So, even though I'm an automaton...
...I do understand a lot of emotions...
...with all my time on Earth.
And I think my favorite emotion of all time is...
...Joy!
So, let's teach Otomo some joy, shall we?
And what's the most joyous thing in the entire world, guys?
Of course... music!
Playing music with others.
So, let's play some music, shall we?
Yay!
Ah! Flashbang.
What? Why do I have—
—why do I have my violin?
Huh. That's weird.
Cece! Cece! Cece!
Whoa! Oh my god!
All of you here!
And with instruments!
Yeah!
Does that mean that my dream...
...of having a school band is finally coming true?
Yeah! Let's join her!
Okay, okay! Shall we play a song together?
Yeah!
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's do it! Woo!
Shiny Smily Story
Lyrics: 金光佳史 Music, Arrangement: 中野領太
Lyrics: Yoshifumi Kanamitsu Music, Arrangement: Ryota Nakano
Whoo! Yeah!
Yay! Thank you so much, guys!
Oh, look!
Otomo?
So cute!
Is that a gear of emotions?
Oh my gosh! Is he gonna learn?
Whoa!
Ah! She learned joy!
She learned joy! Yay! Happy, happy!
Thanks to you guys! Thank you so much!
Thank you! Thank you guys!
Bye-bye!
I gotta go!
Come on!
Okay, you can go now. Okay.
Okay, bye!
Yay!
Okay, wait, let me put this away for now.
I'll get it back in a second. Wait.
That was so much fun! What did you think, guys?
Oh, Otomo, did you learn how to be happy? Are you happy now?
Yeah?
So cute! That was so much fun!
Yay! It was like... okay, that's enough.
That was like a dream come true for me to play with everyone together,
so I'm really happy about that.
Wow, dreams really do come true in this Clockwork World, huh?
But don't you worry, we have more emotions that we need to learn.
Um, next one is representative for me, guys.
What do you think? What do you think is me?
What is weatherly me right now, always? Hmm...
Hmm... what could it be?
No, not that one. No, not that one.
No, not that one. No, it's not hate.
No! It is... laziness!
So, Otomo, don't you worry, I'll, I'll, I'll teach you how to be really, really lazy.
And, um, we, let's try, let's see. What do you think?
What should we do, Otomo? If you want to be lazy, which one, which option of these two would you do?
What should we do now?
a) Let's go on a hike!
b) I'm hungry let's get some food.
A) Let's go on a hike!
Or B) I'm hungry, let's get some food.
On a hike? Seriously?
Oh, no, no, these options are terrible. Terrible options,
terrible, awful, awful, terrible options. Eugh!
That's not how you're lazy, Otomo! No, this is...
...this is how you're lazy!
So please, guys, you have to vote again.
What should we do now?
a) Let's just not do anything...
b) You decide...
A) Let's just not do anything...
Or B) You decide...
And with 'you' I mean me. Not you. No, you. No, no, me.
I decide. I should have written Cecilia Immergreen decides.
You want food? Well...
What should we do now?
a) Let's just not do anything...
b) You decide...
But yeah, ultimate laziness is when you don't do anything.
Oh, you have deadlines? Meh.
Oh, you have really important things to do? Procrastinate.
Oh, things are coming up in your calendar? Meh, forget about it.
Everything's messy and it's the worst it's ever been in your room?
Meh, forget about it too. Just stay in bed and do absolutely nothing.
Yeah, I think that's really important.
And it's very, very important that you learn how to do that...
...because that's one of the many emotions of being a human.
Okay, let's see, what's the poll result?
What's the poll result? Hmm... Hmm...
Let's just not do anything.
Wow, Otomos are so smart.
Okay, don't do anything.
And we... (laughs)
That's exactly it. I'm so proud of you Otomo.
That's how you learn, that's how you learn laziness and how to be lazy.
Oh, there it is! There's the gear of emotion.
Okay... He's taking it in. Oh...
Cute! Oh, that's so...
Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Anyways, so, what is the next emotion that we need to learn?
Obviously, what is human if not...
...okay, so we have joy, lazy...
...and the next one is obviously...
Hate.
So, no, come back Otomo, it's okay. I'll tell you a little bit about the things that I hate.
So, I hate... hmm... Okay, okay, okay, listen.
I hate coffee. I hate raisins.
I hate green peas. I hate olives on pizza.
I hate when something stops working and suddenly starts working again when you turn it off and on again.
I hate long queues. I hate waiting.
I hate when I can't sleep at night.
I hate when the pillow is too warm and the blanket's too warm.
But then you take off the blanket but then it's too cold and then you have to put the blanket back on.
And I hate when they make updates for programs and websites that are absolute downgrades.
Okay. Okay.
And you know what I also hate Otomo?
The fact that I prepared a lot of stuff for today, but you...
...and you, made it so that I crashed and I came into this world...
...and now I can't prepare it, I mean, show it to you.
But maybe I should show you anyways.
Okay, I'll show you. I'll show you anyways.
It's fine. I mean, this is a circular stage.
Okay, Otomos, please listen.
薔薇の誓い
Music: 光宗信吉
Oath of the Rose
Music: Shinkichi Mitsumune
Yay!
That was Bara no Chikai from Revolutionary Girl Utena OST.
I love it, I love that OST, it's one of my favorite OSTs.
Oh, what? What? Huh?
Oh, sorry, I just got a message.
Oh, apparently I read the poll wrong earlier and it was actually "You decide".
My bad guys.
I decide what to do next.
You know what I decide?
I decided that we're going to look
at this beautiful stage!
It's so warm!
Oh my god!
Well, this looks so cool though!
Where did all the fire come from?
I guess from our rage.
So Otomo, did you learn how to be...
I mean, hate, hatred?
Did you learn how to be hateful?
He's learned...
Oh!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa, Otomo, whoa! Don't say that!
No, don't listen to him! Don't listen to him!
No! No, don't! No, we're gonna get demonetized!
No, no, no, no, no!
Okay, okay, okay, just ignore him.
Okay, I'm gonna talk a little bit louder
so you can't hear him cursing.
Okay, well, this is a really cool stage
and everything, but it's way too warm!
So, I think we're...
Shut up!
Okay, this is way too warm,
so I think we're going to have to turn it back.
How about that?
And since this is the inner clockwork
of our, clockwork world of our minds...
I can turn it back with just a spin!
Turn it back!
Ah, that's way nicer.
Wow, look! So pretty!
No, that's so nice. I'm so excited.
And it's green! Everything's green!
Just like Cecilia Immergreen
from Hololive English -Justice-!
Yay!
Okay, well, what do we have next?
Oh, another emotion shall we, Otomo?
Because obviously, it's four emotions
because there's four people in Justice...
...so the best number in the entire world is four.
Two peace, two, four, four, four, four Justice!
So Otomo, I'm going to...
I have one song prepared for you.
And for you! I worked really hard on this one.
It's a bit scuffed, but that's okay,
you know, that's okay.
Please listen and watch
as I perform my next song.
薔薇獄乙女
Lyrics: 宝野アリカ Music: 片倉三起也
Baragoku Otome
Lyrics: Arika Takano Music: Mikiya Katakura
夜の世に美しく私",
In the world of night, I am beautiful
着飾るは闇の毛皮",
Dressed in the fur of darkness
谷間の百合 踏みつけても",
Even if I trample the lilies of the valley
あなたの場所へ向かうため",
To head towards where you are
牙を立てる 憎しみの甘さは",
Setting my fangs, the sweetness of hatred is
結実の身の 不実の夢",
The faithless dream of the bearing fruit
交わりましょう",
Let us intertwine
逃げてるのか 追ってるのか",
Am I fleeing? Or am I pursuing?
分からなくなるまで",
Until I no longer know
私を見て もっと深く",
Look at me, even deeper
溺れ乱れ 満ちて地獄",
Drown, be disheveled, filled with hell
魔女の爪 証の骨",
Witch's claws, bones of proof
軋みもっと響かせ",
Make them creak and resonate more
これが愛か 憎しみなのか",
Is this love? Or is it hatred?
答えは必要ですか",
Is an answer necessary?
あつ、暴かれた 心臓は",
The heart, hotly exposed, is
あなたの 凍りの刃",
Your blade of ice
指の中で 生き返るわ",
Reviving within my fingers
悲しみだけ 飼い慣らしても",
Even if I tame only my sadness
余所は蝶の 微笑",
Elsewhere is the smile of a butterfly
足首 結わく 綺麗な鎖",
A beautiful chain binding my ankles
奈落の扉に つながり",
Connected to the doors of the abyss
舌でなぞる 鍵穴の先は",
Tracing with my tongue, beyond the keyhole is
地の味に しける小道",
A path damp with the taste of blood
進みましょうか",
Shall we proceed?
抱いてるのか 抱かれてるのか",
Am I embracing? Or am I being embraced?
分からなくなるほど",
To the point that I no longer know
あなたを見る まなざしでは",
With the gaze that watches you...
裂いて",
Tear it
満ちてゆく茨の獄
The prison of thorns filling up...
九条の月 紅蓮の夜
The moon of the ninth article, the crimson lotus night
欠けてはまた満ちる
Waning and then waxing again
これが恋でも 恨みでも
Whether this is love or resentment...
屍は同じでしょう
...the corpse shall be the same.
ああ 手に慈しんだものから
Ah, from those things cherished in my hands...
その目に色褪せぬように
...so that they do not fade in those eyes.
何度だって 生まれ変わる
Over and over again, I shall be reborn.
逃げてるのか 追ってるのか
Am I running away, or am I chasing?
わからなくなるまで
Until I can no longer tell.
私を視て 音を捉えて
Look at me, catch my sound.
燃えて紅蓮 茨の獄
Burning crimson, the prison of thorns.
行きたいのか 落ちたいのか
Do I want to live, or do I want to fall?
もうわからないけど
I don't know anymore, but...
これが愛で 苦しみならば
...if this is love and suffering...
終焉が欲しいですね
...then I want the end.
ああ 奪い取って その心
Ah, snatch away that heart...
虜に変わるがいいわ
...and let it turn into a prisoner.
身体ごと 閉じ込める
Locking away the entire body.
Yay!
Yay! What did you think, Otomos?
Oh, claps! Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you!
My... That was me and my short ballet performance.
So, Otomos, did you learn? This emotion...
...it was "Obsessiveness". Yeah!
Because when I get introduced to things, I get like really obsessed with them and it's really a lot of fun.
Oh, what's with your facial expression?
What's— Whoa!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Whoa! Otomo? Otomo, are you okay?
Oh! AHH!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa! No, Otomo! No!
Why are you so big? Whoa! Oh no!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Stop, stop, stop! Not again!
Umm... he's going crazy.
Okay guys, don't worry, I got this. I can protect you...
...because this is what fighting— this is what we're fighting for.
This is what justice is for! So...
FOR JUSTICE!
Hah! Yah!
I'll never leave my Otomo here. Wait, wait!
No, you should come with me!
Come on, let's run, let's run!
Oh! Oh, you— you don't want to?
Are you so scared? Are you— you can't come with me?
It's okay. I might not be able to help *this* Otomo, but I can sure help *you*!
Hah! Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come on! Let's run!
Oh no, you're limping! Come on!
Now Loading...
Again? What the— where are we this time?
Ah! Oh! A stage! Hello, Otomos, hi!
Oh my god, it's an idol stage! So pretty!
Ah, I'm so excited! Oh...
My car!
No!
No, we've gone through so much together.
How could this...
Wait, a water gun!
I can save you! I can save you!
No, no, I won't let it end like this!
Oh, well that was easy.
Oh wait. Wait, I see something.
Look guys!
It's... It's my merch!
This is my 3D merch!
Cecilia Immergreen Pouch & Socks
It's an Otomo pouch and an Otomo Otomo socks.
And then you put the socks into the Otomo, into the pouch,
and then you buy seven of these so you have socks for every day of the week.
And then you get seven of these too because it's one... two-in-one!
Technically I guess three-in-one because it's two soc- Oh yeah!
So please look out for these! They're going to be releasing after the...
セシリア・イマーグリーン ポーチ＆ソックス
Cecilia Immergreen Pouch & Socks
...just collab! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
And then I also have...
I also have this!
1st Anniversary Merch Set
My anniversary merch!
It's still up to have for three more days, so please go get it! It's very cute.
Here's a very helpful Otomo and here's a completely evil, evil, evil Otomo.
So yeah, please, please get... if you're interested, please check them out.
I think maybe they're in the description, I'm not sure. Okay!
So obviously now that we're here on this beautiful stage,
we're going to have to sing a song, shall we?
But after the song, there's one more...
HUGE announcement! So please wait for after the song as well.
Yeah, I'm very excited.
Okay, my army of Otomos, are you ready?
Are you ready for the next song?
Okay! Let's go!
Thank you so much for coming to my 3D everyone!
Thank you Staff! Thank you Manager-chan!
Intergalactic Bound
Thank you Otomo!
Come on, I feel like there's something about this song.
It's like we knew how it would go all along.
So put down your worries and raise your cups.
There's nowhere to go but up!
Let's dance with the rhythm from New York to Japan,
and you'll never be alone.
At first glance we're miles away, but our hearts are connected through these soundwaves.
Nothing but up-up-up-up! (Yeah!)
Cut through the clouds, nothing but up-up-up-up!
We're never coming down! Jump! Jump!
Without a doubt, nothing but up-up-up-up!
Intergalactic Bound! Whoa, whoa!
Intergalactic Bound!
If you're oldie or fresh on the scene,
Come put your lights up, we'll make a wave of green.
Bridge the beginning to us all here and now.
Just take a deep breath and let me hear you shout! (Yeah!)
Let's groove with the static in the air.
A breakthrough that can bring us anywhere.
It's your move, so take the lead.
From the crowd to the stage, what sights can we see?
Nothing but up-up-up-up! (Yeah!)
Cut through the clouds, nothing but up-up-up-up!
We're never coming down! Jump! Jump!
Without a doubt, nothing but up-up-up-up!
Intergalactic Bound!
A thousand little voices sing.
It's a fiesta from now on.
With your faces always by our side,
to help us make this song.
Through the dark of the night, I know we will be alright.
As a universe of positivity beyond the sky.
Ten thousand of the stars, they will keep on burning bright,
with this light between you and I.
Nothing but up-up-up-up! (Yeah!)
Cut through the clouds, nothing but up-up-up-up!
We're never coming down! Jump! Jump!
Without a doubt, nothing but up-up-up-up!
Intergalactic Bound!
Whoa...
...whoa...
Hey!
Intergalactic bound!
Whoa...
...whoa...
Hey!
Intergalactic bound!
Yay!
That was... Ami-go-round's "Intergalactic Bound".
I hope you liked that.
I really like that song,
so I'm really happy.
Yippee!
Okay, okay.
And now for the... grand announcement.
Yay!
I've been working on this for a while and, um... yeah.
So today, maybe you've seen it already,
there's a waiting room up for it.
Um... I wrote, composed, and produced
my first original song
with the help of Ethra, who's also an amazing producer.
So please, um, wait a little bit longer,
so we are redirected to it,
and then you can listen to it. Yeah,
it's called "Wind Up".
So, um, yeah.
I'm very nervous.
I hope you like it.
But um, thank you very much for coming to my 3D showcase today.
It was a lot of fun.
And um, yeah, thank you very much
to staff, management, and everyone,
and all the Otomos.
Wait, I wanted to do one thing.
They love me.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Okay, wait, let me give you a hug.
Mmm.
Okay, okay, that's enough.
Back off, back off, back off.
That's... that's... that's enough.
Okay, well, thank you so much, Otomos!
Thank you everyone!
Thank you for watching my 3D!
Um, maybe we should take care of the fire, huh?
Hmm.
'Cause otherwise, if we don't take care of the fire,
there... there might be a forest fire, you know, for all we know.
Also, don't forget, tomorrow is...
...Raora's 3D!
So you better watch that one as well, okay?
Otherwise, you... you know what's gonna happen.
Don't worry, I know exactly...
...I know exactly...
Oh, my knee!
I know exactly what to do to take care of this fire. Okay.
There we go. Easy, easy.
Oh.
Easy, easy.
I'm too tired for this.
I'm too... I'm too...
Stop.
Whatever.
Goodbye.
Dearest otomos!
Thank you! Thank you for always supporting me,
for believing in me and cheering for me
throughout all this time!
It's already been a year and I couldn't have asked
for a better community than the one we've built together.
You know, I'm always bad with words but I just want
to say that I am forever grateful for how much joy
you bring me and that I can proudly stand here
today and show you the things we work on
with the hope that we can enjoy it together!
I truly wish that I can give back to you
even a fraction of the happiness that you've
given me and make you smile even if it's just
for a while (hey that rhymed)
And to make you slight-breath-out-of-your-nose-laugh!
That would be my biggest goal!
You are my biggest motivation and I hope I can
keep creating distractions on rough days or
entertainment on others and I will keep trying
my very best!
I'm so happy to be here with you!
And I hope we can keep having fun together!
Yours, Cecilia Immergreen
Otomo will return
3D SHOWCASE #Cece3D
8/8 - 5:00PM [PDT] | 8/9 - 12:00AM [UTC] | 8/9 - 9:00AM [JST]