(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
RIDE ON TIME / Lyrics, Music: 山下達郎
RIDE ON TIME / Lyrics, Music: Tatsuro Yamashita
青い水平線を今駆け抜けてく
Running through the blue horizon now
研ぎ澄まされた時の流れ感じて
Feeling the flow of sharpened time
ああ ときめきへと
Oh, towards excitement...
動き出す世界は
...the world starts moving
忘れかけてた
I'd almost forgotten...
遠い夢の訪れ
...the arrival of a distant dream
Ride on time
Oh Ride on time
溢れる喜びに
With overflowing joy
広がれ Ride on time
Spread, Ride on time
Oh Ride on time
心に火を点けて
Light a fire in your heart
溢れる喜びに
With overflowing joy
広がれ Ride on time
Spread, Ride on time
僕の輝く未来
My shining future
さまよい始めて
Has begun to wander
うつろな日々もすべて
And all those hollow days
愛に溶け込む
Dissolve into love
ああ なんという朝
Oh, what a morning
今すぐ君のもと
Right now, to your side
届けに行こう
I'll go to deliver it
燃える心 迷わず
With a burning heart, without hesitation
Ride on time
時を走り出せ
Start running through time
愛を光り出せ
Start shining with love
目も眩むほど
So bright it's blinding
Oh Ride on time
心に火を点けて
Light a fire in your heart
飛び立つ魂に
To the soul taking flight
送るよ Ride on time
I'll send it, Ride on time
届けに行こう
I'll go to deliver it
燃える心
With a burning heart
今こそ
Right now...
Oh Ride on time
Ride on time
時を走り出せ
Start running through time
愛を光り出せ
Start shining with love
目も眩むほど
So bright it's blinding
Oh, Ride on time
心に火をつけて
Light a fire in your heart
飛び立つ魂に送るよ
Send it to your soaring soul
Ride on time
Oh, Ride on time
さあ思いなら
If you have feelings,
優しく受け止めて
gently accept them
そっと包んで
and wrap them up softly
Oh, Ride on time
心に火をつけて
Light a fire in your heart
溢れる喜びに広がる
Spreading out with overflowing joy
Ride on time
Oh, Ride on time
届け明日へと
Reach for tomorrow,
刻みだした汗
with the sweat we've shed
ああ、光る汗
Oh, shining sweat
目も眩むほど
Dazzlingly bright
Oh, Ride on time
心に火をつけて
Light a fire in your heart
飛び立つ魂に送るよ
Send it to your soaring soul
Ride on time
Stay my heart
なに食わぬ顔をして
With an innocent look on your face,
キスを奪って
you steal a kiss.
Don't go away
いつかまたなんて
Things like 'some other time'...
I never say
唇にうらはら
Contrary to what my lips say,
残したままで
leaving it all behind.
Turn around
Myth or Treat
Your oshi's waiting in the closet tonight
No way to stop, she's dead set on giving you a fright
Trick or treat but now we're all outta candy
Feelin' just a little sick?
will hide
Let them drown
Burn it down
They say the memory of me is fading
I've heard it all before
Don't tell me everyone around is waiting
And they all say
Tear it down
Burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down
burn it down
when the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend
If this is the end
I'll do it again
We swim against the current's aim
In dark we change as smoke returns to rain
Navigating sunken depths
and all of its debris
And no more hands upon my words
They only speak for me
For all the ones who try to
silence thunder
I'm the wave that pulls you
down and under
Every day I'll stand with me
And I'll fight the drought of shallow sea
As ships sail winds of jealousy
I'll listen
carefully
Burn it all!
As they all say
Tear it down
Burn it down
And they'll all pay
When I tear it down
Burn it down
When the world falls through
And all is ash again
While you all pretend
If this is the end
I'll do it again
Hi! Hello! Hello, hello, thank you. Hello! Hi!
Um... from the very bottom of my shark heart,
thank you.
Um, if I could borrow your ear for just a...
just a bit more time, I want to thank you, um, again.
Thank you for letting me be your shark idol
for the last half-decade.
Five years. Wow.
Just... just about five years or so.
Um... in this time, I... I... I have loved
performing for you.
Here, or on stage, or in my bedroom,
any... anywhere. Anywhere, really. Um, I... yeah.
Wow. Speaking... speaking of half a decade,
when I first joined Hololive, I had barely any
experience in streaming, or dancing, or singing
in front of people.
I couldn't even sing in front of my own mother.
Um, but... but now, now look at me, right? Um...
I won't lie, it was really hard to get my footing.
Um, sometimes it was terrifying.
No, a lot of the time, it was terrifying.
But... spending time with you and all of the
incredibly talented members of Hololive has been
an absolute pleasure.
And I can truly say, a highlight in my life.
I will never forget my time here at Hololive.
I... I feel like I've been able to grow a lot
in these past years.
Not in height or brain activity, but...
in my heart,
like my confidence—
my confidence in myself,
I believe in myself
a whole lot more now than I did five years ago and
oh, it's thanks to you.
So thank you everyone
for your compassion,
your creativity,
and your dedication
to me,
your Goomba.
Thank you to my Myth ladies.
We've been through so, so much together,
and I am honored to have been able to go on this journey with you girls.
Thank you to Nacho Mama
for always working so hard and
making me so darn cute!
And thank you to my Chumbuds
for always being there for me,
for pushing me to try new games,
new songs, new experiences...
thank you for everything.
I've got a Gulf Stream current to catch.
Time to Otsu-same
one last time.
Ready?
おつさめ！
Otsu-same!
The biggest!
Take care and
be kind to yourselves,
okay?
Okay.
Good night and goodbye.
Goodbye, goodbye...
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye...
Bye bye!
Goodbye!
がうる・ぐら 卒業ミニライブ
Gawr Gura Graduation Mini Live