(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D Showcase
September 17 20:00 PDT
September 18 05:00 CEST 12:00 JST
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
With an invincible smile, she messes with the media
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
I want to know her secret, she's so mysterious
抜けてるところさえ彼女のエリア
Even her clumsy moments are within her charm's reach
完璧で嘘つきな君は天才的なアイドル様
You, perfect and full of lies, are a genius idol
今日何食べた？好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
If you go out for fun, where do you go?
何も食べてない、それは内緒
I haven't eaten anything, that's a secret
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
Dodging any questions asked
そう淡々とだけど燦々と
So nonchalantly, yet so brilliantly
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
Secrets almost visible but not, taste like honey
あれもないないない
That's not there, not there
これもないないない
This isn't there, not there
好きなタイプは？相手は？さあ答えて
What's your type? Who's the person? Come on, answer
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ」
"I don't really know what it's like to fall in love with someone"
嘘か本当か知り得ない
Impossible to know if it's a lie or the truth
そんな言葉にまた一人落ちる
One more person falls for those words
また好きにさせる
Enthralling them once again
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone's eyes are being stolen
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You're the perfect and ultimate idol
金輪際現れない一番星の生まれ変わり
A star that'll never appear again, a reincarnation of the first star
その笑顔で愛してるで誰も彼も虜にしていく
Captivating everyone with that smile and those "I love you"s
その瞳がその言葉が
Those eyes, those words
嘘でもそれは完全なアイ
Even if they're lies, it's a perfect love
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yeah, yeah, that girl is special
我々は端からおまけです
We are just extras from the start
お星様の引き立て役Bです
Just character B making the star look good
全てがあの子のおかげなわけない
There's no way everything is thanks to her
洒落臭い妬み嫉みなんてないわけがない
There's no way there's no petty envy and jealousy
これはネタじゃないからこそ許せない
Since it's not a joke, it's unforgivable
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない
I won't forgive you if you're not perfect
自分を許せない
I can't forgive myself
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't accept anyone but the strongest you
誰もが信じ崇めてる
Everyone believes in and worships you
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Truly the strongest, invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない一番星を宿している
Showing no weaknesses, you house the brightest star
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
Don't ever show any weak spots
知りたくないとこは見せずに
Hiding the parts we don't want to know
唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ
You have to be one and only, or else
それこそ本物のアイ
That is what true love is
特意の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Working the media with a signature smile
隠しきるこの秘密だけは
Keeping this one secret hidden
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア
Building a career on the lie of "I love you"
これこそ私なりの愛
This is my version of love
アイドル
Idol
#3Dronii
これこそは私なりの愛だ
This is my own kind of love
流れる汗もきれいなアクア
Even the flowing sweat is beautiful aqua
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
These eyelids that hide rubies
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
Singing and dancing, I am Mary
そう、嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, lies are an extraordinary kind of love
誰かに愛されたことも
Having been loved by someone
誰かのこと愛したこともない
Or having loved someone—I've never done either
そんな私の嘘がいつか本当になること信じてる
I believe that such lies of mine will one day come true
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
One day, I'll surely have it all
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
That's because I'm a greedy idol
等身大でみんなのことちゃんと愛したいから
Because I want to love everyone properly as my true self
今日も嘘をつくの この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
I lie today as well, wishing for the day these words will come true
それでもまだ君と君にだけは言えずにいたけど
Even so, I still haven't been able to say it only to you
あ、やっと言えた これは絶対嘘じゃない
Ah, I finally said it. This is definitely not a lie
愛してる
I love you
Hey! Kronichiwa!
Oh! Whew!
We did it. I hope that was good.
And, well, I hope I looked like
an idol on stage.
And if you liked the performance so far,
be sure to use the hashtag #3Dronii.
And, well, speaking of the stage, take a look at this!
Ah, it's so beautiful.
And it's like the stage was, like, made for me,
and only me.
Look at just how grand it is.
And, well, whew!
Yeah, it's looking a little too bright right now,
so shall we turn it down a bit?
Whew! Okay, that is much better.
Ooh! Oh yeah,
I guess I forgot to tell you...
...this, um, can change from daytime to nighttime.
I can control the time of day according to my will.
Oh wait! Hey!
Wait, wait, wait. Look at you. Wait, you got invited? What?
How many supers did you have to pay to get that VIP seat?
Wait, and you? Wait!
Get out of here! I didn't invite you.
Ah, whatever. But, oh yeah,
how'd you think about the song?
Um, I know it's pretty overdone,
but I thought it was pretty fitting
for this show today, don't you think?
But, yeah. It's a pretty good start for today.
But it doesn't stop there.
Because stay tuned, the first ever
Cronie Awards is happening right now.
Today, tonight, with all of you and all of me.
What does that mean?
Well, you've gotta stick around for that.
All right, let's get this show on the road.
Take a look at this!
Ladies and gentlemen...
...welcome to the Cronie Awards!
Today, we'll be joined by not one, not two...
...not even three, but four different Kroniis.
That's right! And each Kronii will display
their amazing talents...
...and the best one will receive the award
in this ceremony.
Crony.
Yeah.
Uh, let me show you what this...
...sick award is going to look like. Give me a second.
All right, here it is.
That's right, it's the...
...Golden Crony trophy.
I know, it's looking pretty amazing.
I want it in my room.
I want it plastered everywhere.
Man, whoever gets this will be a lucky Crony.
Gold, man.
But, you know, that's whatever.
None of my concern because I'm not participating,
unfortunately.
With that, let me introduce today's participants!
First off, we have...
...you guessed it, Miss Ouro Kronii!
Let's all give a warm welcome to...
...Kronii with the actress role!
Woohoo! Onwards!
Bow down to your Queen.
It's Your Majesty.
BEST ACT Kronii
Qronii
And well...
...I believe I should win because...
...I mean, just look at me.
If I don't, I believe it's heresy.
And everyone who didn't vote for me...
...should be sentenced for life,
because that's what they deserve.
And well, anyway...
I don't know if you can already tell, but...
...I'll be reenacting the Snow White today.
And, you know, you can obviously tell...
...with the crown and the apple.
But I'll be the Queen.
That's going to be exciting.
I know I fit the role so well, so we'll see.
And with that, shall we begin?
Feast your eyes!
Hmm, okay.
Let's see.
I don't know if this mirror is actually going to work.
So...
I think I might give it a little bit of a test run.
Yes, what an amazing idea, Kronii.
Thank you.
Okay, well...
Mirror, mirror on the wall...
...who is the cutest of them all?
Boros!
I mean...
...Boros is pretty cute, I guess.
Yeah, it's a cute little snake boy.
Okay.
Yeah, it works, it works.
Okay, you can go now.
Okay, thank you.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, now for the real deal then.
Okay.
Mirror, mirror on the wall...
...who is the fairest of them all?
Huh?
What?
Are you serious?
It's just broken.
No.
No, don't give me that happy face.
But...
...get out of here!
Go, shoo! What?
Disgusting!
My God!
Okay, ugh.
Whatever.
I gotta get that image out of the way.
Um...
Maybe they don't understand what 'fairest' means.
Okay.
Mirror, mirror on the wall...
...who is the most beautiful of them all?
Motoaki Tanigo
Okay.
That was...
...weird.
Um...
Okay.
I don't...
Hmm...
Okay.
Mirror, mirror on the wall...
...and you best be right this time...
...or else I'm going to hand you over to a second-hand shop.
It's your last chance.
Who is the fairest of them all?
Ay!
Oh my god, what took you so long?
Oh, you know, I was just doing my hair.
Oh, please.
You look better with or without.
You're always so on point, girl.
Oh you, you're always so humble.
Oh, stop it.
So like, what's up?
Uh, excuse me?
Didn't you hear?
I was like calling you multiple times.
Oh well, I didn't call you...
...but you know, when people say who's the prettiest girl in town...
...I mean, you know.
I mean, prettiest girl in town, look around.
It has to be you.
Well, yeah, but...
Ay!
Hmm, I guess... I guess you don't look half bad yourself.
I think you could probably take second place even.
Or even first place.
Ay!
So...
...what are you doing after this?
Uh, you know...
...just hanging out, relaxing, alone.
Completely free.
Nothing going on.
Um...
...up for some 1v1 or some local multiplayer?
Oh! Was that an invitation?
Hmm...
...take it as you will.
Yeah.
You know what? I think I will.
Oh...
Ay!
We're going to save that for later.
Yeah...
...keep it on the lowdown.
You get out of here.
No, YOU get out of here.
No, stop it.
I'm going to chuck this apple at you if you don't go.
Yeah? You know what?
I'm going to get out of your hair.
I'm just going to... just...
Uh, you know?
No, no, no. I'm going to get out first.
No, no, it's fine.
I'll go first. It's fine, it's fine.
No, no, no. Stop it.
I'll be the bigger person here.
What?
I'm the bigger person here.
Yeah, well, watch me leave.
Oh my god, no, stop!
My gosh.
Can't believe she did that.
Oh my gosh.
Silly girl.
Goodness.
Oh, yeah, yeah. We were on screen, right?
Well, thank you so much.
I hope you liked our little performance.
It was pretty great.
I mean, my performance, but our, our could also work.
And well...
An apple a day keeps the doctor away.
Yeah.
Why did I say that?
I don't really know.
But that is the moral of this story.
Yes.
Apples, apples are very good for you.
Okay.
Well anyway, I got things to take care of...
...so toodeloo. Bye-bye.
Thank you so much for that wonderful act, Miss Kronii.
Your performance was truly moving.
And I could sense the chemistry...
...between Mirror Kronii and Kronii.
And truly I would love to see...
...that show again if I could.
And you know what?
I think I like it so much that I'll watch the VOD again later.
I mean what?
Anyway, next up,
let's call the next Kronii up to the stage.
Let's all give her a warm round of applause.
Let's go! She needs it.
She doesn't really. She's got the confidence,
but let's just give her an applause. Woo!
Um, hi.
Singronii
Um, yeah.
Um, it would be nice if I can win because I,
you know, worked hard.
Yeah.
Oh, um, by the way, I'm Singronii.
I'm the one that sings, if you can't tell
from the idol outfit and everything.
I'm kind of camera-shy.
I don't really know what to do
in this kind of situation.
But yeah, I'm gonna try my best,
so it'd be nice if you guys like it too.
Um, but if you don't, it's okay.
That's okay too.
Ah, okay. Please listen to this song,
Charles.
さよならはあなたから言われた
Goodbye was said by you
それなのに頬を濡らしてしまうの
Yet, I find my cheeks becoming wet
そうやって昨日のことも消してしまうなら
If you're going to erase yesterday's events like that,
もういいよ
then forget it
笑って
Smile
シャルル Lyrics・Composition: バルーン
Charles Lyrics・Composition: Balloon
花束を抱えて歩いた
Carrying a bouquet of flowers, I walked
意味もなくただ街を見下ろした
Aimlessly, just looking down at the town
こうやって理想の縁に心を掠めるもいいか
Is it okay to tickle my heart on the edge of my ideals like this?
空欄でいよう
Let it be empty
それでいいの?
Is that okay?
伝い青で満たしたのならどうだろう
If I filled it with the blue that overflowed, I wonder how it'd be
こんな風に悩めるのかな
Could I worry like this?
愛を謳って謳って雲の上
Singing of love, singing above the clouds
濁りきっては見えないや
It's so muddy I can't see
イヤイヤイヤ
No, no, no
遠く描いていた日々を
The days I pictured far away
語って語って夜の群れ
Telling of them, telling to the crowd of the night
いがみ合ってきりがないな
Bickering with each other, it's endless
否否否
Not here, not here, not here
笑い合ってさよなら
Smiling at each other, goodbye
朝焼けとあなたの溜息
The sunrise and your sigh
この街は僕らの夢を見てる
This town is watching our dreams
今日だって未題のことを忘れていくんだね
Today too, you're forgetting about your tasks, right?
そうでしょう
Isn't that right?
黙ってよ
Be quiet
それでいいの?
Is that okay?
苛まれたとしても別にいいよ
Even if I'm tormented, it's fine
こんな日も意味があるなら
If a day like this has meaning too
愛を謳って謳って空の上
Singing of love, singing above the sky
汚れきった言葉を今今今
The words are all dirty now, now, now
ここには誰もいないえそれは
There's no one here, and that's...
謳って謳って二人の果て
Singing, singing for the two of us
毟り合って何もないな
Fawning over each other, there's nothing
否否否
Not here, not here, not here
痛みだって教えて
Tell me even of the pain
シャルル
Charles
愛を謳って 謳って 雲の上
Singing of love, of love, above the clouds
濁って 濁って 夜の群れ
Muddy, muddy, the crowd of night
さよなら さよなら
Goodbye, goodbye
Hah... okay.
Um, I hope you guys liked that.
Uh, that was... that was pretty tiring, but...
Yeah, uh, I'd like to think that I did my best,
so hopefully I can, uh...
maybe be considered to- to win? I don't know.
Oh, um, do you guys want to see some- some poses, I- I guess?
Okay.
Odd request, but I'll- I'll try. Okay.
Glowing, so... um, let's see.
Uh, what kind of pose do you want?
Um, like- like this? Like maybe maybe a little bit like that?
I don't really know.
Like, maybe like this?
I'm not really sure what you guys want.
Like that? Happy?
Maybe? Is this- is this good?
Uh, one- one last one?
Um, I already- I already- I already did one.
Yeah, that's- that's it. That's- that's all from me.
I'm gonna- I'm gonna go now. Okay.
Get this camera out of my face. Okay, bye.
Thank you very much, Miss Kronii, for that amazing song.
Your singing definitely has captured our hearts.
My heart, in fact, which is the most important one.
And next up, we are going to call the next Kronii up on stage.
And let's all give her a warm round of applause.
Oh, but before we get on with the show,
we're going to have a bit of a commercial break.
That's right, we are sponsored by... guess who it is?
Yep, you got it. Miss Ouro Kronii.
Oh my goodness, what a giving gal.
Thank you, thank you so much, Kronii.
Oh, you're welcome.
What? Anyway,
let's get on with the show, with the commercial break! Woohoo!
NOWLOADING...
What are you looking at?
That's right.
Oh!
Hey, what is up? I'm here to win!
And you know why? It's because I'm so on point.
BEST Comedian Nronii / Funnyronii
Get it? 'Cause, you know, swords?
I'm so sharp and witty today.
Hah! I did it again.
Oh man, I'm so silly like that.
It's- it's mind-blowing.
How could I get any better than this?
Well, today, I'm gonna be chopping up some fruit
and make some fruit salad.
Whoa!
This is gonna be great, it's gonna be a fun time.
Oh! Oh, thank you, Kronie.
What's that? Pineapple?
That's so cute. Thank you.
Yeah, I'm gonna be chopping these up for today, so that's gonna be exciting.
Thank you so much for showing it off.
And with that, Kronies, stand by!
All right, good, good, good. Back in position.
It's time to show you all what I got. Music, start! Let's go!
Fruits! Come on, let's go!
Hah!
Sick, sick, sick.
Damn, look at that. I'm doing so good.
Look at the accuracy. Insane.
Bam!
Whoop, bam!
Ugh, look at that.
One shot, one kill.
Look at... amazing.
Oh, oh! Time stop! Ho! Okay. Phew!
Bam!
Um, it's okay. This one's pretty durable.
Hah! Look at that. Okay, nice, nice.
You guys didn't see anything. Perfect.
Just one cut, one clean cut.
Oh, man! That was great and all, but you know...
...I'm kind of not feeling it. I wish I could spice things up, but I don't know how.
Eh... eh...
What... what can I do? What can I do?
Oh? What? What?
Guys! You want to join, too?
No, I'm making fruit salad, not clock salad. What the heck?
Sigh... okay. Well, you asked for it.
The things I do. All right, come on up!
Hah! Yeah!
You guys are so durable, what the heck? You're so thick.
Lose some weight, bro.
Phew, man, what a... what a hassle.
I'm, like, surrounded by Kronies with some...
woop, weird, weird things that I can't really say on the show.
But anyway, I gotta patch you guys up now.
Hah! Hah!
Okay. See? Good as... good as new. Yay!
You're welcome, guys. Always have to make things weird for me, but you know what?
I'll live with it.
Anyway, I got the stage just a little bit dirty with all the fruit juice...
...oil, maybe? I don't even know. But I hope you all enjoyed it!
And with that, I'm gonna go. Kronie, out! Woo!
Yay! Come on!
Thank you for that stunning display, Ms. Kronii.
Um, the stage is a bit soiled with all the fruit juice,
but let's not mind that.
Because the next Kronii will help with the mess. Oh, what could that mean?
Oh my goodness, who could the next Kronii be?
But let's not keep the suspense any longer.
Next up, the next Kronii is coming up on stage.
Let's all give her a warm round of applause!
Hey-o, what's up? It's me, Cleaneronii.
Cleaneronii
You know, it's... good to be here.
I think the reason why I should win is because I'm so chill.
Everyone's angry or just so hyper,
and I'm just, like, down with the chillness, you know?
And also, I'm here to make this world a cleaner place
with my awesome power washer here. So, yeah, let's...
Wash-up, my dunes.
Haha, get it? It's like a pun on what's up,
but I'm washing things, so it's wash-up.
Hahaha! I'm funny too. Damn.
Funny-ronii, watch out.
Okay, anyway, let's get this job done and over with.
Let's do this! Woohoo!
Alright, I'm here to wash. Let's do this! Woohoo!
Oh man, this statue is looking so gnarly, bro. Woo!
Alright, okay, well, let's begin.
Damn, this is like, so dirty, dude.
Is it from the fruit juice? Like, what happened in this place?
Like, man, that's insane.
Man, this statue's so big and I'm just so small.
This world is just so big and I'm like a speck of dust.
What am I? Makes me think about life, really.
Oh, okay, looks done.
Damn, time passes so fast when I'm just cleaning.
Damn. But yeah, that looks great.
Oh, what? There's another one?
Okay, well, actually I'm not complaining.
More cleaning for me! Woohoo!
Let's go! Yay!
Phew! Okay, well...
...let's go. One last ride.
Dude, this is so therapeutic.
Like, I can do this all day, man. Ah.
You know, Kronii's legs are so long.
Like, what does she do?
Just so beautiful.
And her being in gold just makes it so much better,
you know? That's like the best part.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, Gold Kronii in all her glory.
It's done. It's done, it's my masterpiece. Phew!
Well, it seems like my work here is done
with all these beautiful statues restored to its former glory.
Man, if you need any help, you can call me anytime.
I'm just gonna wash everything like pshow pshow pshow.
It's gonna be dun-zo because I'm just so amazing like that.
Rock on, bro.
And you know, I hope that as quick as it was
because of my pro skills,
I hope everybody enjoyed this therapy session
'cause it always is therapeutic for me.
So yeah, with that, I'm gonna bid you adieu, my dunes.
See you around. Or not.
Alright, bye-bye. Pshow pshow pshow. Yay!
Ooh! Look at her! Wow!
The stage is now squeaky clean. Look at that.
I can almost see the reflection of myself.
Oh my goodness, your eyes are beautiful.
Ah, okay, anyway, thank you so much to Powerwash Kronii!
And that is all the performances we have for today.
I know, I know, already? Oh well.
But thank you to our fellow participants for showing off
your beautiful, stunning abilities.
No wonder there were four Kroniis because
if we were to show off one Kronii, then this would have taken forever.
How could we just, you know, narrow it down to just one hour?
It's gonna be like six hours, or 48 hours,
or God knows how long. But yeah...
It's lucky for you guys or...
...unlucky? I don't know.
But anyway, let's move on to the award ceremony!
Woohoo! Let's go!
And there we have it!
Those were all the performances we had for tonight.
What a... amazing turnout.
As expected from me, obviously.
Now now, if our fabulous guests are lucky...
...they might have the chance of grabbing...
...this absolutely glorious Kronii statue...
...endorsed by, again, me, Kronii.
And oh, it's so shiny.
Gosh, I wish I could get one.
But I'm not participating, so... oh well.
But with that, let's hear from the nominees, their thoughts...
...on their stunning performances tonight.
To start us off, let's hear from Qronii.
BEST ACT Qronii
Qronii
I felt a little bit of heat towards the end...
...but I really do feel like I conveyed the feelings of Kronii...
...very much so.
At the end of it all, I truly believe all Kroniis...
...are beautiful in their own respective ways.
These amazing qualities of mine...
...understanding, humble, and most of all, attractive.
Oh, what defines me as a supreme overlord.
Everyone loves me because who wouldn't?
They should all bow before my raw awesomeness.
And because of that, and only for that reason...
...I deserve the award.
Ah, slaaaay!
Thank you, Qronii. How humble of you.
Wow. Um, I think... but I love the apple, by the way.
Can I... can I touch it?
Ooh. Oh my God, that's... that is amazing.
That is fresh. Damn.
Ooh. Okay, I'm too mesmerized.
Anyway, up next is Singronii. Let's hear it!
BEST SING Singronii
Singronii
I feel like I tried to do my best.
Um, I hope it shows and... um...
...you know, I guess for that effort...
...it would be an honor to receive the award.
But, uh, if not, that's... that's okay.
Um, I guess I'll just try harder next time.
Um, I mean, I've been practicing...
...uh, so you know, maybe next time I'll do much better...
...and... win.
I guess I just gotta do better. Just just do better, right?
Heh. Yeah. Yeah.
Um, anyway, I should just pass it over to the next person. Yeah.
Singronii, we wish you luck on your idol journey.
And I see what you did there with the idol outfit.
Clever, very clever. Cute, too. Ooh.
Okay, she looks like she's about to cry...
...so let's just move on right here, okay?
Funnyronii, let's hear what kind of words you have to say...
...about today's performance.
BEST Comedian Funnyronii
Funnyronii
If you don't think that I deserve it...
...then I think you need to have better taste in humor...
...because you lack common sense and any reason...
...an average human is supposed to have.
And besides, did you see the Kroniis?
They seemed to have liked it.
Like, I mean, they were literally jumping at the opportunity...
...to be part of the performance.
And sure, they ended up in the hospital and they're suffering...
...um, and all that fun stuff, but that's entertainment for ya...
...you know? No pain, no gain.
And there was a lot of gain to be had.
What exactly is it?
I'm not going to tell you that.
You gotta find the answer yourself, buddy!
Since you're the funny one here,
I'll go ahead and assume you're joking there.
No?
Okay... just gonna pretend I didn't hear that.
But if you don't win this time,
you're definitely in the running for...
...most humble next to Kronii over there.
Last but not least,
let's hear it from Cleaneronii!
Cleaneronii
BEST wash Kronii
Ugh... like...
it was such a radical experience, dude.
I felt like...
my soul was being cleansed...
along with the dirt.
Like... totally tubular, man.
I was like...
going off on those statues like...
Kachow!
You know... like...
dude...
it was like a swell time.
I was like...
frothing at the mouth almost because...
like...
dude...
that was like...
the mother pearl...
the mother pearl kind of experience, you know?
Yeah... Yeah, you get me. Yeah.
And there we have it!
Um, thank you for all your rather
interesting speeches.
I'm sure someone out there,
far, far out there,
will find them heartwarming.
Maybe.
You know what?
Since I'm here, I think I'll make a little speech too.
You know, why not?
After all, I did my hair extra special
for today and everything.
So, I deserve it
because I was the main organizer, first of all.
And also, I'm the only Kronii here with a clock.
Yes, I made it extra large for today.
And I came prepared,
and I honestly look the best out of everyone here.
No offense.
I'm not saying that I'm part of the candidates,
but if I was, I would be the MVP here.
You know, that's all from me though.
Oh, you guys! Oh, stop it.
You don't have to give me those charming looks.
I know.
I know I'm pretty amazing,
cool, talented,
absolutely just out of this world and...
Oh! Oh.
It looks like we're finally ready
to announce the winner.
The votes are in, the polls are shut,
and without further ado,
the Kroniis have decided.
The winner of this time's glorious
Kronii Awards Award Show...
See, who could it be?
Who... who could it be?
It's me!
Ah, yes.
My baby is finally here.
Back home in my arms.
Thank you so much for this award,
and I'd like to thank everybody who made this possible.
And not you guys...
...me, myself, and I!
What?!
No way!
How is that even possible?
This is rigged!
I mean, you were the host!
And besides, we don't know...
...what you're talking about.
This is just...
I think I'm going to be sick!
Shut up!
Of course I have to win!
Who's the one that planned all this, huh?
Look around! Say "wha"!
Yeah.
So...
Sorry, I can't hear
because it seems like your mics
have suddenly stopped working.
Oh, what a shame.
And oh, oh look at that. The show's ending.
Oh, oh no, oh no.
Thank you to everyone who tuned in
and stay safe out there.
And remember, maybe next time,
you too could be right here,
standing where I'm standing.
One day, maybe.
Nah, who am I kidding? Bye!
So, how was it? Aren't I just amazing?
Thank you so much for watching up to this point.
And now, a few announcements here.
What do you think it's going to be? Let's see.
Bam!
Warden's Capely Embrace Blanket
It's a blanket! And not just any blanket.
It's inspired by my cape.
That's right. Look at this.
But, you'll have to wait a little bit longer.
I know you want this cape ASAP,
but you can get it after the 3D group collab.
So keep an eye out for that, okay? Yay!
And now, you can join my club, Cape Gang. Woohoo!
So, what are you waiting for? Go get it right now.
Don't you want this cape?
It's going to be available
as soon as this showcase ends,
so keep an eye out for that, okay?
Um, but before we end things,
I have a short message for everyone.
Yeah, I know. Ooh, sudden unplanned stuff. Oh my.
Okay, well, you guys want to see a magic trick?
I don't have anything in my hands right now, but...
Now I do! Whoa, magic!
All right, let's see. Um...
Yeah, okay. Time to read this letter.
So, I never would have expected
to ever be here
years before all this.
And because of you guys,
I'm able to have this chance
to experience so many new things
and meet so many people in just one lifetime.
So, thank you for helping me
break out of my shell,
and I hope we can continue
accomplishing great things together.
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
Well, time to get that
sappy stuff out of the way. Um...
Okay, but before we end things off,
let's finish it off with a song. Let's go!
And the final song is going to be
from one of my favorite animes
and it's going to be called Eternal Snow.
So please give it a listen. Thank you.
いつの間に...
Before I knew it...
君のことを好きになって
I've fallen in love with you.
どれくらいたつのかな
I wonder how much time has passed.
気持ち膨らんでゆくばかりで
My feelings just keep growing,
君はこの想い気付いているのかな
and I wonder if you've noticed these feelings.
ETERNAL SNOW
一度も言葉にはしてないけど
I've never put it into words before,
雪のように静かに
Silently like the snow,
降り積もり続けてゆく
It just keeps falling and piling up.
Hold me tight こんな思いなら
Hold me tight, if it was going to be like this,
誰かを好きになる気持ち 知りたくなかったよ
I didn't want to know the feeling of falling in love.
I love you 涙止まらない
I love you, the tears won't stop,
こんなんじゃ 君のこと知らずにいれば良かったよ
If it's like this, I wish I'd never known you.
君をいつまで想っているのかな
How long will I keep thinking of you?
ため息が窓ガラスを曇らせた
My sighs have clouded up the window glass.
揺れる心 灯すキャンドルで
With the candle lighting my trembling heart,