(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
waiting...
GOT START THE SHOW!!!
あの交差点で
At that intersection
みんながもしスキップをして
If everyone were to skip
もしあの街の真ん中で
If in the middle of that town
手を繋いで空を見上げたら
We held hands and looked up at the sky
もしあの街のどこかで
If somewhere in that town
チャンスがつかみたいのなら
If you want to seize a chance
まだ泣くのには早いわよね
It's still too early to cry, right?
暗いマイナスは睡眠下かな
Are those dark negatives below the surface?
いやいや
No, no
PONPON出してしまえばいいの
You should just let it all out, PONPON
全然しないのつまらないでしょ
It's boring if you don't do it at all, isn't it?
ヘッドフォンつけて　リズムに乗せて
Put on your headphones, get into the rhythm
Way Way　あけて　あたしの道を
Way way, make way for my path
PONPON進む　いろいろなこと
PONPON, moving forward with various things
どんどん来てる　あなたの気持ち
Your feelings are coming more and more
ポイポイ捨てる　悪い子はなれ
Throw them away, poi poi, become a bad kid
そうそういい子　Ah Ah You make me happy
That's right, a good kid, ah ah you make me happy
Everyday Pon Everyday Time is Pon
メリーゴーランドみたいなの
It's like a merry-go-round
Everyday Pon Everyday Time is Pon
たぶんそんなんじゃだめでしょう
That probably won't do
PONPON出してしまえばいいの
You should just let it all out, PONPON
全然しないのつまらないでしょ
It's boring if you don't do it at all, isn't it?
ヘッドフォンつけて　リズムに乗せて
Put on your headphones, get into the rhythm
Way Way　あけて　あたしの道を
Way way, make way for my path
PONPON進む　いろいろなこと
PONPON, moving forward with various things
Way Way Way Way PON PON
Hic
ア・イ・ヤ・イ・ヤ・イ・サマー・デイ、ナ・ハ・イ・ヤ・イ・ヤ・イ。
A-i-ya-i-ya-i summer day, na ha i-ya-i-ya-i.
パンパンと進む、色々なこと。
Moving forward step by step, various things.
どんどん来てる、あなたの気持ち。
Your feelings are coming steadily.
ポイポイ捨てる、悪い子だーれ？
Throwing them away... who's the bad kid?
そうそういい子、あぁ、you make me happy.
That's right, good kid. Ah, you make me happy.
Every day fun, every time is fun.
ナニイコなーみたいな。
Something like...?
Every day fun, every time is fun.
たぶんそうなんじゃん、ダメでしょ？
It's probably like that, isn't it? That's no good.
パンパン、ウェイウェイウェイ... パンパンパン...
Pan pan, way way way... Pan pan pan...
ウェイウェイパンパン... ウェイウェイパンパン...
Way way pan pan... Way way pan pan...
（歌唱）
(Vocalizing)
Hey everyone! It's me, Small Ame!
Small Ame's birthday, right? Right?
Small Ame! Small Ame!
So, what do you guys think?
Hmm? Do you like my new idol outfit?
Well, I guess since I'm wearing this...
I gotta dance and perform too!
Look at everyone so cute!
Okay Bubba, I think I'm ready.
Hit the track, Bubba!
Catch You Catch Me
Megumi Hinata
会いたいな 会いたいな
I want to see you, I want to see you.
切ないな この気持ち
It's painful, this feeling.
会えないの? 痛いの
Can't we meet? It hurts.
チャンス逃してばかり
I keep missing my chances.
だって だって
But, but...
翼広げふたりで
Spreading our wings, the two of us...
空をマラソン 夢をユニゾンしたい
Running through the sky, I want to unison our dreams.
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me 待ってて
Look, catch you, catch you, catch me, wait for me.
こっちを向いて 「好き」だと言って
Turn this way and say you love me.
So Nice To Meet You Good To See You きっと
So nice to meet you, good to see you, surely.
あたしの想い あなたに 飛んで 飛んで 飛んでゆけ
My feelings, fly, fly, fly to you!
迷わないで
Don't hesitate.
たまにね、なくなっちゃう
Sometimes, you know, I end up crying.
からだのバッテリー
My body's battery.
あなたの笑顔で
With your smile...
いつも充電満タン パワー爆発しちゃえ
I'm always fully charged, let the power explode.
お願い お願い
Please, please.
まずはお友達から
Let's start as friends.
笑ってみつめて 楽しい毎日にしたい
I want to laugh and look at you, making every day fun.
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me 絶対
Look, catch you, catch you, catch me, definitely.
運命だって お似合いだって
Even if it's fate, even if we're a match.
So Nice To Meet You Good To See You きっと
So nice to meet you, good to see you, surely.
誰にも負けない あなたに世界で 一番 一番 一番 一番
I won't lose to anyone, you're the number one in the world...
恋してる
I'm in love with you.
回らぬ頭にほたる
Fireflies in a head that won't turn
飛んで飛んで飛んでゆけ
fly, fly, fly away
迷わずに...
Without hesitating...
Catch me Catch me Catch me Catch me 絶対
Catch me, catch me, catch me, catch me, definitely
埋め立てて折り合って
Filling it up, compromising
それで Nice to meet you 靴によけた
And so, "Nice to meet you," avoided the shoes
誰にも負けないあなたに世界で一番
To you, who I won't lose to, the best in the world
一番一番一番一番
the best, the best, the best, the best
恋してる
I'm in love
Woo!
「愛のしるし」
PUFFY
"Ai no Shirushi"
やわなハートがしびれる
A soft heart tingles
心地よい針の刺激
The pleasant sting of a needle
わけもないのに輝く
It shines for no reason
それだけで愛のしるし
That alone is a sign of love
いつかあなたには
Someday, I'll reveal...
すべて打ち明けよう
...everything to you
I'll reveal everything to you
少し強くなるために
In order to become a little stronger
河原のほとりでひとり
Alone by the riverside
恋してゆく
I continue falling in love
夢の中でも会える
I can meet you even in my dreams
めくるめく夜の不思議
The wonder of a dazzling night
たったの思い出と
With just memories
風がささやいたも
Even if the wind whispered
うれし泣きの宝物
A treasure of happy tears
何でもありそうな国で
In a country where anything seems possible
たったひとつ
Just one
やわなハートがしびれる
A soft heart tingles
心地よい針の刺激
The pleasant sting of a needle
わけもないのに輝く
It shines for no reason
それだけで愛のしるし
That alone is a sign of love
「Shiny Smily Story (Ska ver.)」
hololive
"Shiny Smily Story (Ska ver.)"
同じ未来見ていたい
I want to keep seeing the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grab that dream
それぞれ違った心で
With our different hearts
走れ (GO!)
Run! (GO!)
どこ見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えた
It sprouted in a place that's dark no matter where you look
ほんの小さな希望に
In a tiny hope
この瞳奪われた
These eyes were stolen
不安で揺れる心をうまくチューニングして
Successfully tuning my heart that wavers with anxiety
ほんの小さな勇気を
Squeezing out...
振り絞っていたよ
...a tiny bit of courage
あきらめの文字消して前へ進む
Deleting the word "giving up" and moving forward
苦しい時もう私は
Even in painful times, I am no longer...
ひとりじゃないから
...alone
だからもっと夢追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dreams more
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
ソワソワ越えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that goes beyond restlessness
それぞれ違った...
With our different...
We took our hands towards our brightest state
This is me and my shiny page
Tears of joy and happy old days
Just a star that we had just made
Hold my hand to see our moonlight
Please dear dreams come true for my life
Let the legend start
Step by step, a miracle
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
Giving all we are, now a team
I'll blow your mind, now take my hand
We'll show this world our dreamland
We'd make our choice, with different voice
Oh yes we will create our way
"Ookami Blues" Inia Kino
ウルウル寂しいウルフです
Feeling teary, a lonely wolf
ムリムリでも群れたくて飛びついて
Even if it's impossible, I want to pack up and pounce
泣いたり振ったりタレ調子
Crying and shaking, in a drooping mood
オオカミブルース
Wolf Blues
遠吠えなんか窓に届くかな
I wonder if my howl will reach the window
一しきり吠えたきりカウント通り
Howled for a while, just like the count
今も一匹のオオカミ誕生
Even now, a single wolf is born
オオカミプリンセス
Wolf Princess
ご飯がポロリ
Food drops down
涙もポロリ
Tears drop down
今日の骨の味はしょっぱいな
Today's bone tastes salty
明日目覚めたらベロ門下
When I wake up tomorrow, under the tongue's tutelage
溢れててメロメロにする予定
It'll be overflowing, planning to make you fall head over heels
後で泣かれても知らないまねまった
I won't care even if you cry later, just wait
明日
Tomorrow
ガミガミ言われるオオカミは
The wolf being nagged at
何もたずサバサバで仲直り
Doing nothing, making up with a frank attitude
喧嘩の理由も忘れてトロッペスですか
Forgetting the reason for the fight, is it Troppes?
主役はずばりウルフできまり
The star is definitely the wolf, decided
ウルフできまり
Decided to be a wolf
モフモフして今日もキリッな
Fluffy and sharp today too
まわれまわれ楽しい
Spin, spin, it's fun
ハグレビリビリ一緒に
Stray and tingling together
みんな本当はやさしい
Everyone is actually kind
だからほら私がボスになってあげる
So look, I'll be your boss
このしっぽにすずつけ
A bell on this tail
ウルウル寂しいウルフです
Feeling teary, a lonely wolf
振り向けば一人きりカウント通り
If I look back, I'm all alone, just like the count
巻いたり振ったりタレ調子
Rolling and shaking, in a drooping mood
オオカミ
Wolf
"Hare Hare Yukai"
Aya Hirano, Minori Chihara and Yuko Goto
ナゾナゾみたいに地球儀を解き明かしたら
If we solve the globe like a riddle...
みんなでどこまでも行けるね
...we can go anywhere together.
ワクワクしたいと願いながら過ごしてたよ
I've spent my days wishing for excitement.
叶えてくれたのは誰なの
Who was it that made it come true?
時間の果てまで BOON UP DE!
Boon up to the end of time!
ループなこの思いは
These feelings that are looping...
何もかも巻き込んだ想像で ASOBO!
...with an imagination involving everything, let's play!
ある晴れた日のこと
On a certain sunny day...
魔法以上の愉快が
...fun beyond magic...
限りなく降り注ぐ
...pours down boundlessly.
不可能じゃないわ
It's not impossible.
明日また会う時
When we meet again tomorrow...
笑いながらハミング
...humming with a smile...
嬉しさを集めよう
...let's gather up our happiness.
簡単なんだよこんなの
Something like this is easy.
追いかけてね 捕まえてみて
Follow me, try to catch me.
大きな夢＆夢 好きでしょ?
Big dreams and more dreams, you like them, right?
イロイロ予想ができそうでできない未来
A future that seems predictable but is not...
それでもひとつだけわかるよ
...even so, I understand one thing.
キラキラ光って熱い雲の上を飾る
Shining brightly, decorating the top of hot clouds...
星たちが希望をくれると
...the stars give us hope.
時間に乗ろうよ BOON UP DE!
Let's ride on time, boon up!
クールな女子ならね
If you're a cool girl...
寂しがっちゃ恥ずかしいよ なんてね言わせて
...it's embarrassing to be lonely. Just let me say that.
手と手を繋いだら
If we hold hands...
向かう所無敵でしょ
...wherever we go, we're invincible, right?
輝いた瞳には
In those shining eyes...
不可能がないの
...nothing is impossible.
上だけ見ていると
If you just look up...
涙も乾いちゃう
...your tears will dry.
変わりたい心から
Because I want to change...
強く思うほど伝わる
...the stronger I feel, the more it gets across.
走り出すよ 後ろの人も
I'll start running. Those behind me, too...
おいでよドキドキするでしょ?
...come on! It's exciting, right?
BOON UP DE! ループなこの思いは
Boon up! These feelings that are looping...
何もかも巻き込んだ想像で ASOBO!
...with an imagination involving everything, let's play!
ある晴れた日のこと
On a certain sunny day...
魔法以上の愉快が
...fun beyond magic...
限りなく降り注ぐ
...pours down boundlessly.
不可能じゃないわ
It's not impossible.
明日また会う時
When we meet again tomorrow...
笑いながらハミング
...humming with a smile...
嬉しさを集めよう
...let's gather up our happiness.
簡単なんだよこんなの
Something like this is easy.
追いかけてね 捕まえてみて
Follow me, try to catch me.
大きな夢＆夢 好きでしょ?
Big dreams and more dreams, you like them, right?
Ah, thank you everyone for coming!
All right, you guys can go now. Later!
Bye-bye, ya get outta here.
All right, you guys know what time it is?
For merch! That's right.
Birthday merch, what could it be?
(Drumroll) Ta-da!
Amelia Watson's starter pack.
Birthday Celebration 2023
On Sale January 7 (JST)
And what's the special item you say?
Bubba, show the special item!
And, ta-da!
Your very own Amelia Watson Dakimakura!
Watson Amelia Official Pillow Cover
Art by nabi
Drawn by Nabi-mama, thank you so much Nabi-mama, so cute.
And uh, do we have something else?
All right, you must be thinking, 'Ame, well...'
"...this doesn't really improve my daily life that much."
"What else can I use?"
Ta-da!
We have the Watson's Task Manager...
Watson's Task Manager
With magnet on its back!
...along with some beautiful cute magnets!
Magnet Sticker Sheet
Art by nabi
And (Drumroll)...
...the number one item, I can't wait to show you guys...
...the Bubba Lamp!
Squishy Bubba Night Lamp
You can choose from 3 levels of brightness!
Oh my god, it's so squishy and round, I just want to... (Squeaks)
So thank you guys for coming to the 3D birthday live.
I really appreciate all of your support.
Bonus for the Complete Set
Birthday Merch Complete Set
...and to be honest, I'm actually in Japan right now
because I snuck into Small Ame's luggage
and yeah, we're going to go on over to Ame Japan!
Live to the Ame Japan!
All right, bye everyone.
Thank you guys so much, and thank you Kanade,
and thank you, thank you everybody for watching.
I love you guys. Thank you, thank you.
Bye-bye! Yeah!
Hello, hello, hello!
Ah! Oh my god, I'm here! Ah!
Hi everyone, can you guys hear me?
Test, test, hello...
All right. Thank you Small Ame for that wonderful introduction.
Thank you guys for all the birthday wishes. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
There's so much to talk about after that. Oh my god. Whoa!
So as Small Ame said, I'm actually in Japan right now. Yatta!
They let me in. The best birthday gift ever!
Um, what'd you guys think? Hmm? Was it a pretty good concert? Right?
A nice little bite-sized mini-live.
Happy birthday, oh thank you, thank you, thank you.
As you can see, we also have a new background by Melon Turtle
and a huge shout-out to Kanade, um, for, you know,
taking care of all of the mo-cap data for that concert.
Uh, but thank you guys. I'm glad you had fun.
I'm glad you had so much fun. I'm glad you guys enjoyed.
Do I sound okay? Does the mic sound okay? Test, test.
You love the live? Oh thank you, thank you.
Oh my hat's cut off a little bit. Let me fix that. There we go.
Yeah, sounds good? Okay, sweet.
Oh, I was going to add something else. So, yes, I'm in Japan right now.
I wanted to go over the merch again because Small Ame did it like super, super fast.
Um, so let's go over the merch again.
Really quick, let's see, the slideshow. Oops.
Don't mind that. Don't mind, don't mind.
All right, let me restart it. Will this restart it?
All right, let me bring up the image manually so that we can take a look.
Ah, thank you guys. The static, yeah, was it getting crunchy at all during the...
it's, uh, it's getting a little crunchy sometimes. I don't know why it does that.
Ah, but it goes away after a little bit.
All right, so the first item in the merch,
um, yeah, a dakimakura.
Excuse me. Dakimakura drawn by Nabi-mama.
Let's zoom in on this. Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Damn! Whoa!
So this is, uh, actually a cover. You do have to get the pillow separately,
but you can get the cover if any of you guys are interested in that.
Um, and then after that, I think these items should be up for sale in one minute
if you want. If you want, you don't have to of course.
But then also there's this, uh, this is actually a magnet,
and this is like something to put on your fridge
and write down the tasks that you've got to do for the day, right?
The Ame-toes, yeah, they're covered unfortunately for you sick ones out there.
Um, yeah, this one's a task manager. It's a magnet
and it comes with a Small Ame pen. Look at her.
Um, so yeah, this is pretty useful, you know, help you finish your tasks.
And there's also these, um, magnets, which look at them, so cute.
These are magnets to go along with the set.
You can see the artist here. Haru-ya, Haru-ya.
So cute.
And then the my favorite item personally is this Bubba lamp.
Look at the Bubba lamp! It lights up and it's also a little squishy.
Squishy Bubba lamp. Um, please do not dent his face, okay?
Yeah, this one's really cool. All the items are available for purchase separately.
Um, so you can get this just by itself if you don't want the dakimakura
or any of the other stuff. That's totally fine.
I'm pretty sure they're available for purchase separately.
Um, manager confirm?
Yeah, gotta take good care of the lamp. That's right. Head pats only.
Don't punch it, okay?
All right, the merch is live. Yeah, all the links are in the description.
It'll be live for one month, so if you guys need to save a little bit...
Watson Amelia Official Pillow Cover
Watson's Task Manager
Magnet Sticker Sheet
Squishy Bubba Night Lamp
a little tiny dakimakura card...
...which uh has my signature back there...
...and a special message...
...which is uh I don't want to spoil it for you guys...
...so you gotta wait until you get it in one year.
Wait what? Hopefully it won't take that long.
Yeah, sorry about the static. I don't know why it does that.
It does that every now and then.
I hope it's not that bad.
I don't think it's part of the BGM,
I think it's just the audio setup that I'm using.
So sorry, sorry, sorry!
Um so yeah, that's uh pretty much everything.
I'm gonna put this slideshow back up here.
Birthday Celebration!
And yeah, oh what'd you guys think of the...
What'd you guys think of... Here I'm gonna bring it,
I'm gonna bring it up here.
Okay let's switch to here actually.
Let's do this!
Ta-da!
I think I forgot to put chat and myself on the screen. Oops.
Very busy day.
Uh but I hope you guys enjoyed the birthday concert.
It was a lot of uh recording and stuff.
Yeah we'll talk about that now.
Uh but at the start, did you guys get to play this game?
Did you guys get to play with the uh claw machine?
This was really cool uh to work on.
It's actually interactive, so if you guys put in controls in the chat...
...like forward, grab, left, right, um up, down...
Up down? I don't know about up down.
But yeah this is uh something that I wanted to show.
I wanted to show grab, grab, what are you guys gonna grab?
GOT WATSON CONCOCTION!!!
There's actually, there might be some surprises!
Oh, is it time for that huh?
I'm just kidding, I don't have anything planned for that.
It's just I think there's some random items in there.
So yeah you guys can control this.
This is gonna be our new intro screen.
And it'll be really fun like if there's a day where you guys get to decide...
...what I wear for my hat. You know, like what I wear...
I think that'll be really cool.
I do have some more, I have another announcement...
...but I'm gonna do it in a little bit after some chatting.
And I guess there's some fanmade projects
that you guys worked together on that we're gonna take a look at.
I believe there's a VRChat world and there's also a fanbook.
So we'll probably do that.
Um so yeah, I'm gonna put down the recap here
because I think that... Uh...
Okay it's gone, it's gone.
I think the um the recap will help
'cause people will tune in and they'll be like...
"Wait where's the 3D Live?" Well you missed it.
So we're gonna put the recap here, we're gonna type there...
...so that they know that they missed it.
And then what's up next on the list?
Put the chat here. I'm gonna put this thingy here somewhere.
Why don't we put this, I'll put this down here.
What'd you guys get now?
I'm putting it right in here.
That way you guys can still play while I'm doing this recap thing, okay?
RECAP:
All right recap. 3D Live.
Maybe I should get a little checkmark symbol in here.
I do have another announcement besides all this.
I know we've already had so many new things, right?
So many new things. 3D Live check.
Recap. Merch. Merch announcement check.
- 3D LIVE
3D LIVE ✔
- MERCH ANNOUNCEMENT ✔
Announced that I'm in Japan. Japan check.
- JAPAN ✔
Yeah I wanted to, I wanted to tell you guys a little bit about how Japan is.
So we'll talk about that. Um let me put this back here.
Merch announcement Japan check.
Um what else should I put on this recap?
I guess we haven't really done so much yet.
Did you guys get my hat? You found my hat.
That must be my spare then.
Um okay so yeah I'm in Japan now
and I actually already met up with Mumei and Kiara.
And yeah it was fun and Mumei and I went to eat
at one of those conveyor belt places with sushi.
That was fun. I haven't met anyone else yet,
but I'm still, I have only been here for like a few days.
So I just been exploring and it's been really cool.
It's crazy, Japan is pretty crazy. It's really cool.
It feels like unreal that I'm here, you know?
It's like a dream. It's like a dream.
You know, getting here is with you guys...
...and all your support making it possible,
so thank you.
I never— I don't know, even though at the start...
Oh!
ちょっと待って、ちょっと待ってください。
Wait a minute, please wait a minute.
あ、今は...
Ah, right now...
今、
Now,
アメは
Ame is
日本です！
in Japan!
そして、
And,
国を...
the country...
めっちゃ、
it's very,
めっちゃ、かっこいい！
very, very cool!
あ、日本の食べるが、
Ah, Japanese food is,
おいしい。
delicious.
めっちゃおいしい。
Very delicious.
うーん、日本の建築はかっこいい！
Uhh, Japan's architecture is cool!
City planning, すごい！
City planning, amazing!
電車はすごい！
The trains are amazing!
Yeah, everything is really cool here. I love the— Oh wait, wait wait, let me say one more.
日本のコンビニの食べるはめっちゃおいしい。
The convenience store food in Japan is very delicious.
めっちゃおいしい。
Very delicious.
どかっこおいしい。
It's so, so delicious.
Yeah, it's really cool. Uhm... yeah when I first got here,
it was really nice.
I mean, it's thoroughly nice, but there's so much food everywhere.
All the food everywhere you go,
it's like it smells good, tastes good...
Oh, I actually have an announcement. I have an announcement, a very cool announcement.
The bread here,
for some reason... Okay, you guys are gonna think I'm crazy or lying,
but it doesn't make me sick!
I haven't been sick, and I— I've been eating a ton of bread.
I— I had like a little bit... I got a little itchy yesterday,
uh, but I think there's a reason for that.
But I found out that I guess in the US they spray...
they spray wheat with something,
and it can— some people could be allergic to it or it's like bad for your tummy,
but they don't do that in like other parts of the world, so...
I don't know. Maybe it's because I've been walking— Oh!
ちょっと待ってください！
Please wait a minute!
Ah!
Now my ears...
Yeah, I don't know what it is. Maybe I've been walking,
I've been eating healthier, maybe that helps.
Yeah, I'm not sure, but it's been really cool.
Let's see, my favorite thing that I had so far,
I had curry udon that was really, really, really, really tasty.
Oh, it was so good!
I'm so happy I was able to eat it. I don't know if it made me sick or not, but...
It was really fun.
So yeah, I— I'm planning to meet some other Hololive members...
soon, but uh...
I think I do have a collab stream planned coming soon,
so you guys will have to wait and see.
But now, I do have another announcement.
But first, I guess I'll take a look at some fan stuff. Alright.
はい。
Yes.
Um, yeah.
I'll be in my hotel chilling, playing Mario Kart.
We'll be gaming.
Any nice moss?
I've only seen one thing of moss,
and I touched it and it was pretty soft.
It was pretty soft.
No, this is not pre-recorded. It's not.
How could it be pre-recorded? Look, you guys are like
trying to control the claw machine right now.
See? Isn't it addictive? It's very addictive.
Did I keep any dirt?
No, apparently you're not supposed to bring
any plants or dirt back.
But maybe dirt is okay.
But every time I try to buy something, it's like
Oh, Bubba!
I encounter two types of people while I'm buying stuff
here in Japan. It's like I ask them a question.
Oh, like I had to buy a hard drive, so I was like,
「すみません。パソコンのハードドライブは、どこですか？」
“Excuse me. Where are the computer hard drives?”
And so, they might try to respond like in Japanese,
but one thing I didn't account for
is everybody speaks really fast. So I'm just like,
trying to listen, I'm like, "Hai, hai. Oh..."
trying to listen, I'm like, "Yes, yes. Oh..."
「あ、すみません、わかりません。」
“Oh, sorry, I don't understand.”
Um, but then there's another type, yeah, where
they just immediately, as soon as I speak,
they pull out their phone and they use Google Translate.
「ありがとうございます。」
“Thank you very much.”
Yeah, yeah. But it makes me so nervous
because, you know, even when I speak English,
I'll stutter when I'm speaking to new people,
and I'll mess up what I'm saying.
So, you know, in another language I'm like,
I always mess something up.
Even though I practice it in my head,
and I think it's fine. I just need to practice more.
Um, Google Translate 助かる。助かる。
Um, Google Translate helps. It helps.
All right. I have the fan book here.
Oh... I just gotta practice more, right?
So far I've only seen, um, I guess like,
you know, more urban places. Yeah.
I want to see more like trees and stuff.
Maybe I'll go to a park or something.
I'll let everybody go to the park.
All right, apparently you guys made a birthday book.
A birthday book. It's a PDF. I'm downloading it now.
Yeah, I saw Kiara and Mumei... I don't know...
I think Kiara talked about it a little bit,
but yeah, we went to the arcade.
We mostly just did claw machines there. We didn't really play...
Oh, we played Mario Kart, and Kiara won.
Okay, she won this time!
But I was... they kept using
the abilities on me because I was in front.
I was first a lot of the time.
And so, you know, if you're first,
you end up getting hit with the most items.
And she got it. She got it right at the end.
Ow, my ears.
All right, let me try to add this.
Okay, we're going to switch to the intro screen
for just a second while I add this fan book.
I'm sorry, hold on. What was it?
Ah, you got the time distortion! Ah!
And technically, here we go.
Now you guys can still play.
Okay, let me make the recap text smaller.
All right, I'm going to take a look at this fan stuff.
Thank you guys so much for all of the,
all of the Super Chats and all of the support.
And... I'm going to take a look at this.
Then, thank you for all the birthday wishes...
...and thank you for all the memberships. And thank you, thank you, thank you.
Without you guys, I wouldn't have been able to get this far celebrating our third birthday together.
Is it our third birthday together? Our third one? So...
本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so very much!
Yes, wow. Our third birthday together. It went by pretty fast, though.
It went by pretty fast!
Alright, so take a look at this fanbook. I don't know, some of you guys may have contributed.
I think there's a scroll function here.
Oh yeah! Whoa, don't look, don't look, don't look, don't look! I'm just kidding. I'll let you guys look just for today, okay?
Wow, look how pretty! Our illustration by Ardenlolo.
Ah, it's it's it's it's... Ow! Foreword: Teammates Case File No. 002.
This book was made for the one and only Amelia Watson, including content from the VRC map portion of the project.
I don't know if we'll be able to look at the VRC map today. I'm not sure if we'll have any time.
But, um, yeah, I definitely want to take a look at it on stream at some point. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that'd be really fun.
Messages within this book from teammates are for the eyes, only for the eyes of Ame.
Wait, does that mean I can't stream it? Oh well, you guys are you guys are put on the spot now!
Put on the spot now!
Front cover art, rear cover art, page design, assets. Thank you, thank you!
Only one copy of the book will be printed, which will be sent to you, Ame #1237.
That's me! Uh-oh, just in case this one has been lost in another timeline, burnt by Small Ame, stolen by Bee Ame, etc.
Yes, the digital copy. You guys are all put on the spot now!
To all Ames who have their birthday on January 6th, this project was made and compiled especially for you by teammates all over the globe.
This is our way to say thank you for all that you do for us. You mean a lot to every teammate, and this is our way to show it.
Whoa, everyone involved has worked incredibly hard to make this gift, which goes to show how special this community is that you've built...
...and all the values and inspirations you've given us. Whoa, you guys are too nice.
Here, here, let me help you guys out. Hold on. For those of you guys still playing, trying to get every item...
I think there's some pretty rare items in there that you guys haven't gotten yet in the claw machine.
Excuse me... Grab! What is it?
Whoa, my hat! You guys have got that one already. How many of those do you need? Do you each need a hat? Is that it?
Uh, okay, let's see. As mentioned before, this project also includes the 3D VRC map...
...so we hope you can check it out if you have some time. This book contains the art from that map, but we still hope you check the map out.
Whoa! We apologize for any kind of scruff you might find in the book, we hope you enjoy your gift nonetheless.
It's okay, scruff is par for the course. Par for the course.
Hold on, let me drink some water though. You guys having fun?
Par for the EN course, right? Oh, my magnifying glass!
Ah! Papaya! Uh, teammates always look forward to spending more time with you...
...and we can't wait to see more of your achievements in the future. Oh, thank you. Oh, cute! Shuzzo!
By Shuzzo! Whoa, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi!
Don't look, don't look! And a message... Ah, sorry, I think my computer's lagging a little bit. Here we go.
Thank you for always bringing joy to everyone with your stream. I can't express how much we appreciate your hard work on trying to push the boundaries of EN Vtubing...
...setting up collabs with your coworkers. Me personally, you were my first time someone used my art for a thumbnail...
...and gave me the greatest joy and motivation to continue grinding my art skill. I'm happy to see how much you've grown well since debut.
Oh, that's so sweet. Thank you! Ah, I'm happy that you let me use your art for a thumbnail. That's so sweet. Thank you, thank you.
Ame, you are awesome beyond comprehension, truly a one of a kind human, even if you are British.
Kidding aside, you have gone beyond measure in your endeavors as an idol, a detective, and a friend.
I wish you the happiness of all timelines combined and please know that no matter into what adventure you get into, your investigation will be behind...
...cheering and supporting you all the way! Oh, thank you!
RECAP: - 3D LIVE, - MERCH ANNOUNCEMENT, - JAPAN
GOT SMOL AME!!
GOT AME'S HAT!!
GOT DETECTIVE'S THINGY!!
GOT BUBBA PLUSHY!!
Ah...
Constant source of enjoyment... Oh, you guys are too sweet! You're so sweet!
You guys got Bubba!
Oh, I miss Bubba. Bubba's doing good though.
Bubba is being watched over by Brother Watson, so...
Bubba's having a good time.
Yeah, Bubba really likes him, so he's doing good.
Ah... "3D models off-collab with your JP senpais despite language barriers"...
Yes! Now we'll, hopefully at some point...
Not hopefully, there will be um, at least one off-collab that I have planned.
So, hope you guys look forward to that!
Oh... watching improve your skills from debut... always willing to help...
...not only your genmates but all members in general.
Ah, thank you, thank you!
You guys are gonna... you guys are gonna make my head way too big! Look at it! It's already too big!
Ah, cute! "Keep reaching for the stars, Ame!"
Ah, thank you! Oh, I liked this one on Twitter.
GOT SMOL AME!!
Ah, yes, a comic artist. "Sincerely, an Ame fan."
Ah... "I hope the concert..." It turned out pretty good, right?
I did a lot of mocap recording for it.
And it took me a long time to record the songs because I...
...like, to record each song will probably take me somewhere between like...
...three to six hours because I record it and I'm just like, "No, this is not it. This is not it."
And so I keep going and then I look at the time and I'm like, "Oh my god, I've been doing this for over two hours."
And then I keep going until I get something I'm satisfied with!
Um, my mic doesn't get static, it's just the BGM. Okay, that's good to know.
Oh, thank you!
I love the Gator animation where you guys slap it to grab it.
The Bee Ame! The Bee Ame!
Oh, you guys are so sweet! Thank you, thank you!
¡Feliz cumpleaños! ¡Muchas gracias!
Happy birthday! Thank you very much!
You know, actually when I was... when I like buy something here in Japan...
...I'll be saying like, "はい、はい！"
...I'll be saying like, "Yes, yes!"
And like it's happened twice already where I accidentally went like, "¡Sí! ¡Sí! Oh, はい、はい！"
And like it's happened twice already where I accidentally went like, "Yes! Yes! Oh, yes, yes!"
¡Perdón! すみません！
Sorry! Excuse me!
"Saturday of March last year when I fell hard down the rabbit hole... I spent the whole day watching everything Hololive EN related."
And I got to... all the things you did for your genmates...
...and that was when you became my favorite. At that moment, my interest only increased over time.
"Woah! You built a 3D studio!" Yeah!
Yes, I used the Ame Studio for the concert.
I don't know if you guys could tell, the hands were a little... I still need to work on the hand mocap, but...
GOT BEE AME!!
...everything else I thought looked pretty good. There were like some hiccups every now and again with like an arm or two or...
But yeah, I thought it turned out really nice, especially like on my official 3D model.
I thought it turned out really nice.
Yeah, huge shoutout to... That was actually my first time watching it with you guys, and I was like laughing.
I love the Small Ame idol outfit. That was by Seafoam. I'd like to use that again at a later date...
...because it's really cute and we only got to see it for one song! Ah!
I'm glad you guys liked it!
Oh, "I love your karaokes, I love all the different Ames you come up with... I love when you speak Spanish!"
GOT GATOR PLUSHY!!
¡Sí, sí, muchas gracias para venir a mi cumpleaños! How do you say party?
Yes, yes, thank you very much for coming to my birthday! How do you say party?
¡A mi fiesta! ¡Ame fiesta! ¡Ame fiesta!
To my party! Ame party! Ame party!
¡Ame fiesta! ¡Ame fiesta!
Ame party! Ame party!
Oh, thank you! So sweet!
The Pie Maker says thank you. Oh, cute!
Oh, I like the hair like this, all curly!
¡Ame fiesta! Yay yay yay!
Ame party! Yay yay yay!
"Hello, happy birthday Ame! Started to watch your streams more religiously back in March... became a member after seeing all the fun VR stuff you've done."
Oh, thank you! Similar hobbies! やった！
Oh, thank you! Similar hobbies! Yay!
Hey, thank you for your membership!
Oh, Gator... whoop!
What was that? A gator what?
I haven't seen that one yet. Is that a new one?
Gator plushie!
Oh, so sweet!
...wishing you brightened up my day.
Thank you so much for being an amazing person.
Aw, proud to be an Investigator! So cute!
Thank you! Are you guys just spamming Grab?
No, you guys are planning this out, right?
Hehe! The few of you playing.
Thank you, thank you!
Oh, Albert!
And prosperous growth of the channel and community.
Oh, thank you! Oh, you guys got it again!
Twice in a row!
Is it a sign? Should we have...
...maybe we should get a Gator plushie.
I still have one more announcement left!
What could it be?
I'm just kidding! It's not more merch.
By the way, the merch is...
I think I'm blocking it with my head, oh!
Hold on, I'll just go a little bit like this.
The merch is on sale, yeah!
There's the links underneath the stream.
Oh, and you know what's interesting? I'm just saying...
I'm a doctor. Oh wait, let me read.
I wanted to congratulate you and thank you...
...because your streams light up my day.
You guys are so sweet! I'm glad you enjoyed the stream.
Thank you, thank you!
I hope you're all having a beautiful day too!
What happens? Can we put a timer on...
...for how often the audio... it's like on a cycle.
I was hearing this all throughout the concert.
But I'm glad you guys couldn't hear that.
Aw, cute!
Look how time flies! Ame, it's already been 3 years!
Thank you for your hardworking spirit!
Please drink more water, right? I actually have...
...hold on, let me get something.
My version of the cake, which I got from the konbini...
My version of the cake, which I got from the convenience store...
...is a fruit sando!
...is a fruit sandwich!
Which I don't think it makes me sick, I don't know.
I don't want to get too TMI with you guys, but...
...obviously since I have my PDF...
...and I'm also a doctor. You guys are also a doctor.
So maybe your opinion would be helpful.
Okay, right?
I don't know if I want to share details, but...
Okay, you know when you eat something, okay...
...and later, like between 3 to 8 hours later...
...hopefully, you go to the bathroom, right?
And something might come out, or might not.
If you're an idol, definitely nothing would come out.
The color can change depending on what you eat, right?
Okay, well, sometimes people allergic to bread...
...they eat bread, and they have to go to the bathroom...
...right away and it makes them really sick.
But for me, it's the opposite.
Okay, I don't go to the bathroom, 'cause I'm an idol.
Okay, you guys getting what I'm getting at?
But when I eat the bread at home...
...it makes my tummy hurt.
And I make such, like, all the stuff that comes out...
...is like a weird color, okay.
But then when I eat the bread here, everything's normal!
So, I think it's all 大丈夫, is what I'm trying to say.
So, I think it's all fine, is what I'm trying to say.
So I have a fruit sando here, which is my cake.
So I have a fruit sandwich here, which is my cake.
I wanted to put some cakes from Twitter on the screen...
...but I kind of ran out of time.
Is it okay with you guys? Just play...
...just play the claw machine.
It's like when a mom, or like a parent, you know...
...they're busy with something, so they just...
...they give their kid an iPad. Okay.
Can you guys... you guys look at the iPad.
I'm gonna try this fruit sando...
I'm gonna try this fruit sandwich...
...while I search for a cake to put on the screen.
Mmm!
The fruit sandwiches here are so good!
True, right?
True.
I still haven't eaten, like...
I want to have Tempura Udon.
But I haven't eaten any yet.
But when Mumei and I went to conveyor belt sushi...
...I had, like, a tempura fried shrimp.
It was so good!
It was so tasty.
I want more.
I also had, um...
...even though I...
Even though... okay, so you know like...
...they have the ekibento...
...which is like the type of bento that you eat while you're on like the Shinkansen or something.
I think? Ekiben? Ekibento?
It's like a bento you're supposed to eat while you're on a train.
Well, I was just like exploring around and...
...I saw like a place selling them while I was like trying to get on a train.
And, uh, I ate one.
And it was so good!
Oh! It had like fried rice and...
...it had like a little tiny fried... what's it called?
Katsu... like a pork...
I forgot what it's called.
Katsu...
Katsudon?
Katsudon? Karaage?
It did have a piece of karaage too.
It was just Tonkatsu! Tonkatsu!
Yeah, even though it was like cold...
...it wasn't like crunchy or fresh, it was still so tasty!
It was so tasty.
The food here is so good! It's so good.
I don't know what kind of miracle it is that I actually can eat it.
But... I don't know, it seems like it's okay. Maybe it's because I've been walking so much.
I don't know.
It's... it's crazy.
Victory Don!
Yeah, good news, right?
I don't know, maybe it is making me sick, but I'm like powering through it or something.
I still get really sleepy.
All right, I'm gonna...
Um... I can't find any like cakes to put on there...
...but there's some really, really good cake art, thank you, thank you.
All right, let's continue with...
...the fanbook.
And then I want to chat with you guys for a little bit, just do some questions.
And then that'll probably be it for our birthday stream.
But yeah, I still want to chat.
Ah, very cute. "Happy Birthday #1 Detective".
By Jeys. Thank you.
Yeah. Excuse me.
I went to eat ramen at a place...
...and it was like a really small place...
...and I was like one of the only people in there.
And the... I think it was the owner.
The owner was there and he was like standing there with his arms crossed watching me.
And I was like really full already...
...but I was trying to eat as much as I could.
But afterwards, Kiara told me, she's like...
..."Yeah, you're supposed to, you know, slurp really loudly".
And I was like trying to be quiet because, you know...
...I just didn't want to be like rude, I don't know, because, you know...
...they see like a girl, they're like, "Oh, why are they being so messy?".
You know, that sort of thing.
But afterwards, Kiara told me that... yeah, they like want to hear you slurp really loud.
Yeah, I was trying to be polite.
But he was like staring me down as I was eating!
But it was good.
It was kind of weird. It had like some...
...it was like ground beef or something.
I don't know what it was, but I ate it.
I'm sorry, I'm going for another bite of my fruit sando.
The food here is the best!
If you guys haven't been to Japan, I hope you can go at some point because the food is so good.
I feel like if I never went to another country...
...I'd probably just be satisfied.
Just cause this is the first time I've ever gone anywhere.
This is the first time I've ever traveled anywhere.
You know, aside from being brought over from Englisland, which is...
...if you guys know, you know.
So it's my first time.
It's scary because I thought maybe they would ask...
...like while I was in the airport.
I thought that customs would maybe like question...
...whether or not, like why, why do you have a laptop?
Why do you have a microphone? And what are you really doing here in Japan, you know?
But thankfully nobody asked any questions. So that was nice.
It was really simple. Very easy.
And the laptop's allowed, no no no, it's fine, it's fine.
Yeah, it's scary going first time. I'll be here for a little while...
...for a little while and then I'm going to go back, and then who knows...
...I might come again, come back again soon. Alright let's continue.
Happy birthday Ame, I hope you'll have a wonderful birthday celebration this year too.
It was pretty cool. Watching your streams always brightens up my day.
It always brings me joy to watch and talk about your streams with other people...
...in the community because of how friendly you taught them to be.
Yeah, you guys are being nice right? Be nice to each other, huh?
And to the other fanbases too, right? Yeah, yeah.
Have I met Yagoo? Um, I met Yagoo um...
...it was also a few months ago I met Yagoo during our first Myth off-collab.
But I haven't seen her yet. This trip, not yet. Not yet.
Hopefully though. Um, let's see.
The amount of hard work you put in for your friends... I can't even count how many times...
...your streams have watched something new or different... Thank you, thank you, thank you...
...for the support all the way through. All the way through the journey.
Yagoo meet up when? Um, I might be able to meet Yagoo at some point soon, I think.
Probably. Um, alright let's see. Man I want to meet IRyS too.
Want to meet IRyS. I know the BGM gets fuzzy.
And then we'll see, maybe we'll meet some other senpais.
Hopefully, lots of people to meet, right? Here we go.
I remember following Ame... your fearlessness to be innovative...
...you guys are too sweet. Oh, thank you, anonymous teammate. Oh thank you.
Oh cute! Oh this cake, oh my god.
I've had so much, so many different types of cakes since I got here.
So many different types of cakes. I had an orange cake, I had tiramisu.
I had a strawberry... no, I don't think I've had strawberry cake yet.
But I had pistachio cheesecake. Um, yeah and I tried like pretty much all the conbini food.
And that was like the only thing I ate for the first two days I got here.
I just had conbini food. They have like cream puffs, they have really tasty onigiri...
...and these different sandwiches. Oh, like I have egg sando right now in my bag.
They're so good, right? You have to eat the conbini food.
Because the 7-Eleven in the US, they just sell the stinky hot dogs.
But here they have like a crispy chicken, a piece of crispy chicken, it's so tasty.
And they also have um... was it? Oh yeah I had the curry bread, curry bread.
So good. All the food here is so good. And a lot of it is like pretty cheap too.
It's kind of crazy. How much good food there is for not even that much.
Yes! Now the new year started after I'm done traveling. Then we'll get back to normal streams.
Happy birthday Ame! May your special day be as epic...
...and sweet as you are.
Oh, this is so cute!
I like this Smolsen.
I like this Smolsen here.
I don't know, can you guys see my cursor?
I don't think so, but maybe.
And this Japanese food, I can see why...
Oh my god, everything is so tasty!
I— every time I go to bed, I'm just like so full.
It's a good thing I've been walking a lot,
so I'm like burning it off.
Well, I decided that even if it was going to make
me sick, I would still eat bread and stuff anyways.
But it seems like it's okay.
I mean, I get really sleepy pretty early...
...and then I just take a nap on the train.
And then I just keep going.
Let me take this last bite.
Maybe it's jet lag? Hmm... yeah, maybe.
I'm honestly...
Well, I got kind of lucky with my timing cause I
have a friend group that's also visiting Japan...
...and then Hololive people as well.
So I just kind of tag along, but then I'll also
just like go by myself...
...and I'll get lost in some random street.
But I just keep walking because everything is so
interesting to look at, you know?
Even if it's not like the usual tourist stuff.
I'm just going to like some of the back streets
and like the alleys and stuff like that.
And it's so nice.
It's fun to get lost.
Yeah, the best way to visit, right?
No, not the backrooms. Yeah, back alleys.
And even like compared to the US, everything is
so clean and the buildings are so cute!
I see some like vending machines that they look
like I could pick them up, you know what I mean?
Oh my god, and I've done so much
gacha gacha, gachapon!
痛てっ！
Ouch!
I've done so much gacha.
It's great.
Gacha everywhere.
Every time I see like a few I'm just like,
'Okay hold on, let me pull out my coin purse.'
Got anything good?
I did get some good stuff, but I don't remember
right now off the top of my head, so maybe it wasn't that good.
Is it cold in Japan?
It's a little cold, but it's nice.
The wind is really cold.
Ooh, long hair Ame! Art by Zen! Thank you!
Yeah, cold is better than hot, right? Cause it's
like when you're hot, you can only take off so much clothes.
You can't take off your skin.
But when you're cold you just put on more clothes, so easy.
Hi Ame, I'm a long time viewer of yours,
and while you may not see my name in chat,
but I really do love your content and streams.
I've watched the streams you do since debut,
even though I can't sub, but I hope and got membership...
so I try to support your content by watching.
I hope someday I will be able to get a membership.
But keep doing what you're doing,
the streams are great and entertaining.
I will always try to catch your streams.
Thank you for many great ones and hope it
will keep on going. Thank you Ame! Iris-chi.
Well thank you Iris-chi! I hope I said it right.
See, this is why gifted memberships are nice
cause look, some people can't get it, but they
might get lucky in the chat and get some gifted ones.
It's so sweet, thank you so much.
Hi Ame, happy birthday! Your streams have gotten
me through many hard days throughout the past two years,
and brighten many more. You're an inspiration to
me and watching you motivates me to grow my creativity
and work ethic. Ah, my work ethic needs some
work too. Thank you for all your hard work
and you put into your projects and streams, looking
forward to seeing what you do and accomplish in the future.
Well thank you, Rinsuke.
Thank you for always working hard, your smile gives
happiness to many people, thank you so much, Zinia.
Oh, actually I have an asset that Zen made for me.
Is this like a... hold on.
I'll just leave it. What'd I do? What'd I do?
Ah, thank you for the gifts! No, I wasn't trying to
get you guys to gift... oh, I see because it's supposed to be a book!
Ah, yeah yeah yeah, this is the other side.
Ah, thank you, thank you, thank you for the gifts.
Dear Ame, Happy birthday Ame! Three birthdays already!
Time flies by so fast... oh this is cute!
...letter. Like, it's just like a scan of a letter.
Ah!
I hope the birthday girl is having a wonderful birthday.
Thank you for introducing the rest of Hololive to me, always so supportive of your friends...
...and coworkers, Holo-Birds just to Holo-Pro, for me...
...as a Teammate, to feel like part of a big Hololive family.
Supportive of anything and creativity has created countless memories...
...for other Holo members and Teammates.
Mmm!
When you debuted, I was still just a kid, living the toughest years of my life...
...seeing things I'd rather forget.
You've come into my life...
...always streaming early morning in my time zone, gave me something to look forward to...
...every time I wake up.
Watching streams to start my day always brightens me up, and being developed since this year.
Ah! A kid while watching. Mmm.
Seen attitude and values, you do things in your own way...
...doing things you know is right for you, even when people tell you otherwise.
It's truly an inspiration...
...and has helped me make some important decisions.
Aww, well I'm glad I could help! Keep working hard.
Yeah, growing up isn't an easy road.
But, I'm glad you enjoyed the streams. Thank you so much for all your support.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Oh, there's so much of this book, and I want to go through all of it...
...but I don't think we'll have time.
Aw, so cute! Gismo! Look at this cute art!
Hehe!
You're someone I met on the other side of the world, you can't imagine I say I love you, what!
Ah!
Oh, so sweet! So cute!
So cute, so cute, so cute!
Wwwwww.
This art is really good too.
Ah, so cute!
Alright, alright. We'll be scrolling all day if we stay here...
...so I'm going to look at the rest off-stream, and... um...
...I think my manager mentioned something about possibly getting an actual printed version...
...maybe at some point.
So I'm looking forward to that, actually holding it in my hands, and...
I'm going to keep it on my coffee table. Is that weird?
I'm going to keep it on my coffee table.
Haha!
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you!
Uh, alright. Now you guys plan on your iPad. Give me a second.
Hehe!
You give me one moment.
Ah, hold on, I wanted to, um... do this.
It is just so sweet. Thank you so much for all the work put into the fan book. It's really nice.
It's really nice, and I can't wait to get, uh, a hardcopy version.
I'm going to bring the crane up here, but give me a second.
We'll put it right here. There.
Okay, just give me a second while I prepare one more thing. I'm going to do my...
...final announcement. Final announcement, I believe.
Coz then it's time to get ready for Mario Kart!
Let me see.
(Humming melody)
Ah, looking for the perfect files. Excuse me.
All right, we're going to hide... uh...
...we're going to hide this for a second actually. Oh, let's... let's... so you guys get the last item.
Huh, Bubba!
Bubba plushie! Alright, we'll pause.
Actually, let me move over. We'll put it here for a second.
We'll go this way. Put this here.
Okay.
Oh.
All right, are you guys ready? We're going to play a game.
Now everything's ready.
Tada! Wait, tada! Wait, you can't see it.
Tada! Wait, can you guys see that?
Okay, there. There we go.
What is that? There's a new item on the screen.
GOT SMOL AME!!!
There is a new item.
Can you guys get that?
Are you guys able to grab that? I don't know.
It's kind of in a weird spot, huh?
Kind of in a weird spot.
I need you guys to grab it.
Uh, a little bit more to the right. Okay.
A little more to the right. You guys got the the concert start symbol really fast.
Really, really fast.
A little bit more to the right. Come on, come on.
Oh, you guys are so close.
You're so close.
Oh! Right there, it's right there, it's right there.
Don't grab yet. Don't grab yet.
The shadow, do you guys see the shadow? It's like almost on it.
You might be able to get it.
Wait, oh! Right there, right there. Okay.
Grab, grab, grab!
Eh? Okay, that should be good if you go that far.
Are you guys... you guys are over it, I think.
Grab!
Oh! Yep! What is it?
GOT ORIGINAL SONG PREVIEW
Original song preview! I misspelled it.
That's right, I have an original song... now.
But it won't be releasing until the 14th of January.
So you guys do have to wait.
But I have some more surprises in store for that.
Hold on, I have a logo that I am going to put here,
which I totally did not prepare beforehand.
But I do have a little preview that I'm going to show you guys.
I have a little preview that I'll show you.
Just give me a second while I put this on the screen.
An original song, finally!
And here it is.
It's called... wait, let me move this over.
It's called...
Ta-da! Chiku Taku. Chiku Taku,
which means tick-tock,
but it's not, you know, it's Chiku-Chiku Taku.
Not tick-tock. Chiku Taku.
Okay, I'm going to play a little preview for you guys.
There's no vocals, but it's a really nice preview,
and you guys will have to wait until January 14th PST.
It'll be January 15th JST.
You guys will have to wait to hear it then.
But for now, please listen.
Hopefully it doesn't get buzzy, but please listen.
Sorry.
Sorry. Can you hear it?
Okay, I'll let it play one more time because last time it got messed up.
Okay, from the beginning one more time.
Yay!
So yeah, that's... it's kind of a different mix...
But you guys will be able to hear the full original song,
obviously with vocals, on January 14th.
So please listen and please wait for the music video premiere
on January 14th.
I just had to delay it a little bit to finish up something for it.
But you guys will see.
And yeah, I have some more surprises in store on that day.
So we'll do another stream for sure on that day
during the premiere
and we'll do like a watch-along and yeah, some other stuff.
I really can't wait for you guys to hear it,
the official version. So yes, please look forward to it.
And I'm gonna end this stream right about now.
As the pinned message showed before, the merch top pinned...
I will be reading super chats at a later date.
I'd like to read them
even though I'm gonna have a lot, a lot piled up.
But I'd still like to do it anyways.
So thank you guys so much for all your support.
And thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Thank you.
And we still have some more exciting stuff later in the month.
So yeah, collabs, off-collabs, whatever,
original song, やった！
original song, yay!
And thank you so much to all the people that made this possible.
Um, thank you Hemma for your help.
And thank you Kanuru for the concert
and See-Pohm for help with the 3D stuff.
And this is Wanderer-P who did the...
this song that you guys will be able to hear.
And if I'm forgetting other people...
Nabi, Ruff, Proon-dot...
yeah, thank you and to everybody that helped.
And to all of you guys with the fan book, thank you so much.
Hello Calli, thank you
and Nabi's gift card, thank you.
やった！
I did it!
Those are all the announcements for today.
And Melon Turtle for this really cool new background that we have.
やった！ I'm gonna make sure I'm not missing anything.
Yay! I'm gonna make sure I'm not missing anything.
Oh, and to K-Ace...
I think it's K-Ace? For the quick mix.
Yes, thank you Calli for the connection,
the connect, the hookup.
Happy birth... oh thank you guys! Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I will be exploring Japan, so I do...
I would like to stream some more and do some off-collab streams.
So I'll keep you guys updated and I'll let you know.
And now that it's known that I'm here in Japan, I'd like to share,
you know, some... some maybe some stuff I've eaten.
Not very identifiable things.
But yeah, I'll take some pictures of food for you guys.
And I'll probably be updating the members with that more likely.
I'm too nervous to post it like on Twitter.
But yeah, thank you guys!
Thank you for watching and thank you for all your support.
And I hope you had fun. I had fun this birthday.
So thank you guys for all the love.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I can't wait for you guys to hear the original song.
I hope that this birthday stream met your guys' expectations.
I worked really hard on the mocap and the dancing,
which I definitely need to work on that more.
And the recording... and the recording for the song.
And planning a lot of things out.
And yeah, I can't wait for January 14th.
It was great! Um, glad you guys liked it.
Alright, I'm gonna go now.
I don't have an ending screen. Wait, maybe let's do this.
All right, goodbye everyone.
Thank you again for watching.
If you are interested in the merch,
it's now available for sale
on the link pinned in the chat.
And I'll see you guys very soon.
Okay, thank you again for all your support.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you!
thank you for watcing!
thank you for watching!
GOT SMOL AME!!!
GOT WATSON CONCOCTION!!!
GOT BUBBA PLUSHY!!!
GOT BYE BYE!!!