(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
supported by Pocky / ACL
Ayunda Risu
Kureiji Ollie
Vestia Zeta
Moona Hoshinova
Anya Melfissa
Kaela Kovalskia
Airani Iofifteen
Pavolia Reine
Kobo Kanaeru
TERIMA KASIH!
THANK YOU!
CHROMATIC FUTURE
hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も
Body and soul...
この手で make you mine
...with these hands, I'll make you mine.
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever.
君を見るたび 上書きされていく欲望に
Every time I look at you,
my desires are overwritten.
重なる Eyes, Eyes, Eyes
Overlapping Eyes, Eyes, Eyes
魅せろ your smile, smile, smile
Show me your smile, smile, smile
ねえ その姿形 全てが拍車かけていく
Hey, that silhouette,
everything just spurs it on.
恋から 愛、愛、愛
From affection to Love, Love, Love
毎秒可笑しくなっていく
I'm going crazy every second.
手を伸ばせば、もっと届く距離
Let's keep going until we reach the distance
Kicking the night, 試したい
Kicking the night, I want to try.
穏やかに、恋したい
I want to fall in love peacefully
どんなシーンも、私に魅せて
Whatever scene you show me
このまま Stay, stay, stay
Stay just like this, stay, stay, stay.
どこにも行かせないで
Don't let me go anywhere.
100パーセント 純粋な愛だから
Because it's 100% pure love.
止められない感情 そっと抱きしめてよ
These unstoppable feelings, hold them gently.
もっと 近くで
Closer...
ずっと もっと 近くで
Always, even closer.
混ざり合う色ほど もてあますだけなら Stay
The more the colors mix,
if it's too much to handle, then Stay.
Tell me what's wrong with me
名もなき普通だし
It's just an unnamed normalcy.
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you.
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you, right now.
最初は声を聞く それだけでよかった
At first, just hearing your voice was enough.
だけど次第に Why, わがままになった
But gradually, why, I became selfish.
誰かに笑いかけ その仕草に
苛立ち隠せない自分に気づいた
I noticed myself unable to hide the irritation
at your gestures toward someone else.
独り占めしたい 一緒 鎖に繋いで
I want you all to myself,
chained together forever.
二人きりの部屋 近距離
A room for just the two of us, close range.
強硬発言 禁止したい
I want to forbid strong statements.
解して 眠りたい
I want to unwind and sleep.
鋭い吐息 感じさせて
Let me feel your sharp breath.
このまま Stay by your side
Stay by your side just like this.
どこにも行かせない
I won't let you go anywhere.
100パーセント 私だけに依存してね
Depend 100% only on me, okay?
色付く合図 まるごと受け止めてよ
Accept every signal of coloring.
あぁ 私達なら たとえ息ができないほどに
Ah, if it's us,
even if we're breathless.
混ざり合って あともう行かせない 絶対
Mixing together, I won't ever let you go,
definitely.
Tell me what's wrong with me
名もなき普通だし
It's just an unnamed normalcy.
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you.
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you, right now.
瞳を閉じたら、止めどない id:entity 触れた意味を。
Even if I close my eyes,
there's no stopping id:entity... the meaning of touch.
あぁ 私の歌声だけ
Ah, only my singing voice.
このまま Stay by my side
Stay by my side just like this.
二度と離れないで
Don't ever leave again.
100パーセント 純粋な愛だから
Because it's 100% pure love.
声が
A voice...
命令
...commands.
止められない感情
An unstoppable emotion.
そっと抱きしめてよ
Hold me gently.
あの日からかや
Since that day, perhaps...
ずっと もっと近くで
I've wanted to be much closer always,
認め合いたい
wanting to acknowledge each other.
暴れだす衝動 持て余すだけならスラスト
If you're just stuck with a raging impulse, thrust.
Tell me what's wrong with me
何の問題もない普通だし
There's no problem, I'm just normal.
曖昧な意味全部知りたい
I want to know all the ambiguous meanings.
I need you 今すぐ
I need you right now.
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby, I need you, I need you always.
逃げるなら今だ 気圧を
If you're going to run, now's the time.
勝利を願っちゃって
The pressure is on, pray for victory.
ハメ苦茶 This is hollow
It's all a mess, this is hollow,
Labyrinth together OK!
Are you anonymous? もしてさ
Are you anonymous? If so,
ゆえなきさ 15 minutes
it's for no reason, 15 minutes.
目伏せた目 半日先にほら
Look, with eyes cast down, half a day ahead,
誰か人生スキャニング
someone is scanning life.
LOBでは Standby now
In LOB, standby now,
今さら仕掛け 飽き飽きなんだよ
I'm already bored of the setup.
さあ今回せ 残酷
Now, turn the cruelty,
私には血の味ね
for me, it tastes like blood.
乱舞に罪を添えて
Add sin to the wild dance,
目的なき大和撫子
a Yamato Nadeshiko with no purpose.
あの子みたいになるのなんかより
Rather than becoming like that girl,
正しい愛を 呪縛力
righteous love is a binding force.
Day by day 所詮あらあら
Day by day, after all, oh my,
得たこと全部ピンを指した
I've pinned down everything I've gained.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
You can laugh if you want,
皆言われるがまま ギラギラを壊すだけで
as everyone just breaks the glitter as told.
Victory to the world
手に入れた罰と感動は きっとかけがえのないものよ
the punishment and emotion gained are surely irreplaceable.
見てて見ててよ この境界を
Look, look at this boundary,
手に入れて
and seize it.
ランダムに乱舞を添えて 救いたいなら解体なんか
Randomly adding a dance, if you want to save, disassemble...
並べた言葉の不信感 期待し過ぎる愛しの上
Distrust in the lined-up words, on top of too much expectation...
ここはドコラバ
Where are we, lover?
拾い上げた万年筆
The fountain pen I picked up,
葛藤私を強くしてくわ
conflict only makes me stronger.
ポジショニング 好守から 覗かれるのは癪で
Positioning, it's annoying to be peeked at from a good defense.
Oh, 警戒 1 2 3
Oh, watch out 1 2 3,
死ぬのは嫌で Trip to trip
I hate the idea of dying, trip to trip.
気が付いたら どん底で
Before I knew it, I was at rock bottom.
アレレ 隠れていただけで
Oh my, I was only hiding.
Naila naila fighting かながな
Naila naila fighting barely,
ラララ邪魔なもの全部はキャンセル
La la la, cancel everything that's in the way.
成り果て 止めないさ
I won't stop what's become,
これが私の今日バイバイになるかもしれずにね
without knowing this might be my goodbye today.
Victory to the world
共に作り戦いたいんだ 愛おしくてたまんないわ
I want to create and fight together, it's so dear I can't stand it.
心地良いのこの境界を
This comfortable boundary,
君に染まっちゃって
dye yourself in it.
こみフロー！
Komi-flow!
ハイアニマル！
High animal!
アイ・アニ・アルダー！
A-ani-alder!
アイ・アニマル、声は？
I-animal, where's the voice?
ハジメマシテ
Nice to meet you...
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ ぶれないで
Hey, hey, hey, don't waver.
Day by day もううって丸々
Day by day, already shot through,
降り出しにカンパトって
back to the start with a toast.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
You can laugh if you want,
皆いつかチャンピオンポイントを追わすだけ
as everyone just chases champion points eventually.
Victory to the world
絶対追い抜くわあの光で 勇気色を
I'll definitely overtake with that light, with the color of courage,
忘れられないほどの
so much that it's unforgettable,
勝利を願っちゃって
pray for victory.
境界を行こうジジ
Let's go to the boundary, Gigi.
Hah...
Siapa di sini yang lelah dengan kehidupan?
Who here is tired of life?
Aku! Aku!
Me! Me!
Kalau capek enaknya gimana nih Holo-ID?
If you're tired, what's the best thing to do, Hololive ID?
Dappou saja!
Just escape!
Cakep!
Nice!
ブラフも既に日常茶飯
Bluffs are already a daily occurrence,
お釈迦様でも気づかぬ地平
a horizon that even Buddha wouldn't notice.
Saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya
When the world doesn't go as it should
Oh oh...
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya
Maybe it's finally time
Kau coba lepaskan saja
For you to just try and let go
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
No need to ask why anymore
Jika memang...
If indeed...
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi
Don't cry about it
Coba lalui teka-tekinya
Try to get through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Just let it be
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Jalani saja
Just live your life
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Jalani saja
Just live your life
Walau kadang mati rasa
Even if you're sometimes numb
Bahkan hingga tak berdaya
And even feel helpless
Dan usahamu terasa
And all your efforts feel...
Sia-sia, sia-sia, sia-sia
In vain, in vain, in vain
Jika memang...
If indeed...
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi
Don't cry about it
Coba lalui teka-tekinya
Try to get through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Just let it be
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Lepas semua kendali
Release all control
Tancap gas dan berlari
Step on it and run
Terima dan sudahi
Accept it and end it
Jika memang...
If indeed...
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi
Don't cry about it
Coba lalui teka-tekinya
Try to get through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Just let it be
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Jalani saja
Just live your life
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Jalani saja
Just live your life
Ma-i-ka!
Whatever!
Comic Frontier! こんばんは！
Comic Frontier! Good evening!
こんばんは！ こんばんは！
Good evening! Good evening!
ようこそ...
Welcome to...
『hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary
LIVE Chromatic Future』へ！
hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary
LIVE Chromatic Future!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ワギヤワギヤワギヤ！
Wow wow wow!
5周年のライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to our 5th anniversary live!
まさかもう5周年とはね！
I can't believe it's already been 5 years!
じゃあ自己紹介から始めましょうか？
まずはゼータから！
Shall we start with self-introductions?
Starting with Zeta!
はいはいはい！
Yes, yes, yes!
よし... あ、後ろか
Alright... oh, behind me
アアア！ ミッションスタート！
スケート！ スケート！ スケート！
Ahhh! Mission start!
Skat! Skat! Skat!
ホロライブインドネシア3期生の
ベスティア・ゼータです！ よろしくお願いします！
I'm Vestia Zeta from Hololive Indonesia Gen 3!
Nice to meet you!
よろしくゼータ！ よし次はカエラ！
Nice to meet you Zeta! Alright, next is Kaela!
はいはい！ カエロ！ 毎日鍛冶をやってる
ホロライブインドネシア3期生の鍛冶屋！
Yes! Kaelo! Grinding every day,
the blacksmith from Hololive Indonesia Gen 3!
カエラ・コヴァルスキアです！
よろしくお願いします！
I'm Kaela Kovalskia!
Nice to meet you all!
よろしくカエラ！ 次はこぼだ！ こぼ！
Nice to meet you Kaela! Next is Kobo! Kobo!
やっほー！ ぼこぼこぼ～こぼ・かなえる、
アットユアサービス！
Hi! Bokobokobo~ Kobo Kanaeru,
at your service!
君の日々を照らす太陽になりましょう！
えへっ！
Let me be the sun to shine your days!
Ehe!
Kobokers、声を上げて！
Kobokers, let me hear your voices!
ウォー！！
Whoaaa!!
3人で...
The three of us...
ホロライブインドネシア3期生、
holoh3roでーす！
Hololive Indonesia Gen 3,
we are holoh3ro!
やあ、ついにホロライブID 5周年ライブが
できるとはね。ついにあったんだ！
Wow, finally a Hololive ID 5th anniversary live.
It's finally happening!
1曲目からもうめっちゃカッコいいよね！
その熱き、感じてるわ！
The first song was already so cool!
I'm really feeling the heat!
Ya ampun, asik banget ya, iya nggak sih? Iya nggak sih?
Oh my god, it's so fun, right? Don't you think?
Parah sih!
It's crazy!
Adrenalinnya berasa kan ya? Pengen lari aku rasanya nih!
You can feel the adrenaline, right? I feel like running!
Woi woi woi woi woi! Mau ke mana?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! Where are you going?
Iya iya iya stop stop stop stop stop stop stop!
Okay, okay, okay, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Nanti keringetan lho! Nanti keringetan!
You'll get all sweaty! You'll get sweaty!
Ah, kalau Kaela gimana?
Ah, what about you, Kaela?
Aduh, seru banget. Aku nggak nyangka sih, sampai aku bisa ada di sini ya.
Wow, it's so much fun. I never expected that I could be standing here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong, konsernya masih panjang banget, jadi kalian tetep semangat ya sampai akhir!
But by the way, the concert is still very long, so keep your spirit up until the end!
Semangat semangat semangat semangat semangat!
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Eh tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi, emang pada tahu judul konsernya apa?
But speaking of the concert, do you guys know what the title is?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah 'Chromatic Future'!
The title of our concert this time is 'Chromatic Future'!
Ada yang tahu nggak artinya apa? Ayo absen!
Does anyone know what it means? Let's check!
Nah, ini, Kobo paling tahu.
Now, this, Kobo knows best.
Heh? Ah...
Huh? Ah...
Yang jelasin yang paling tinggi, yuk let's go!
The tallest one should explain, let's go!
Segitu ya... ya sudahlah... ya sudahlah...
Is that how it is? Well, fine... fine...
Nih ya guys ya buat kalian yang belum tahu, 'Chromatic Future' itu artinya tuh masa depan yang berwarna-warni.
So guys, for those who don't know, 'Chromatic Future' means a colorful future.
Jadi karena Hololive Indonesia kan udah 5 tahun nih...
Since Hololive Indonesia has been around for 5 years now...
Kita sama-sama dari hari satu sampai sekarang...
We've been walking together from day one until now...
Nah jadi itu untuk ke depannya kita tuh juga harapannya tuh kita bisa nyiptain waktu...
So for the future, our hope is that we can create time...
...dan memori yang berwarna-warni...
...and colorful memories...
...sama seluruh fans dari Hololive Indonesia!
...together with all the fans of Hololive Indonesia!
Ya gitu, betul Kaela Kovalskia! Catat, catat!
That's right, Kaela Kovalskia is correct! Take notes!
Iya iya iya...
Yes, yes, yes...
Nah, kalian sekarang udah pada tahu kan karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
Now you all know, since Kaela just explained it.
Kalau gitu, konsernya kan udah mulai nih...
Since the concert has already started...
Kalian mau nge-post soal konser ini di medsos...
...when you post about this concert on social media...
...jangan lupa hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture ya!
...don't forget the hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture!
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh... apa sih...
Because we really want to see your... what is it...
...pengen lihat semangat kalian!
...we want to see your passion!
Ya itu betul banget, iya nggak?
Yeah, that's absolutely right!
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
No typos, no typos!
Asik, share ke semua, oke?
Nice, share it with everyone, okay?
Jadi tapi jujur deh, kalian tuh pas dibilang kita bakal konser lho di Indonesia, kalian pada kaget nggak sih?
But honestly, when you were told we'd have a concert in Indonesia, were you guys surprised?
Halo, ada yang dengerin?
Hello, is anyone listening?
Ayo ayo...
Come on, come on...
Betul, aku setuju juga.
That's right, I agree too.
Aku merasakan empati terhadap ini adik saya Zeta.
I feel empathy for my little sister Zeta here.
Empati iya iya...
Empathy, yes, yes...
Kalau Kaela gimana, Kaela Kovalskia?
What about you, Kaela Kovalskia?
Aku juga waktu itu nggak nyangka banget kayak 'hah, beneran nih? Real nih?' gitu kan.
I also didn't expect it at all, like 'huh, for real? Is this real?'
Kayak 'lho, bisa gitu? Akhirnya... mana udah bersembilan di Indonesia pula ya kan?'
Like 'wow, it's finally happening... and all nine of us in Indonesia too, right?'
Keren banget! Keren banget!
It's so cool! It's so cool!
Ini kan konser pertama Hololive Indonesia yang bersembilan.
This is the first Hololive Indonesia concert with all nine members.
Sebenarnya tuh nggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar dan terpenting juga untuk fans Hololive Indonesia...
Actually, it's not just the biggest and most important moment for Hololive Indonesia fans...
...tapi seluruh dunia juga pasti bakal nonton nggak sih?
...but everyone around the world must be watching, right?
Iya nggak?
Right?
Iya, jawab!
Yes, answer me!
Iya iya makasih, makasih semuanya...
Yes, yes, thank you, thank you everyone...
...tapi tentu saja ini pencapaiannya nggak bakal cuma sampai di sini aja kan?
...but of course, this achievement won't just stop here, right?
Jadi next-nya mungkin kita bisa apa ya... dominating the world gitu.
So next, maybe we can... like, dominate the world.
We are ready, we ready ready!
We are ready, we're ready, ready!
Ready ready ready! Betul banget Kaela, Zeta!
Ready, ready, ready! You're absolutely right, Kaela and Zeta!
Selain dari dukungan fans in this opportunity, kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih...
In addition to the fans' support on this opportunity, we also want to say thank you...
...untuk semua sponsor yang mendukung terjadinya konser ini. Terima kasih!
...to all the sponsors who supported the realization of this concert. Thank you!
Terima kasih! Makasih makasih makasih semuanya! Thank you thank you thank you!
Thank you! Thank you, thank you, thank you everyone! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Eh tapi ngomong-ngomong di konser ini kayaknya ada yang beda nggak sih?
By the way, doesn't something feel different about this concert?
Ela, kamu nyadar nggak? Soalnya kamu paling peka nggak sih?
Ela, did you notice? You're the most observant one, right?
Wits... ya sadarlah, kalau Kobo mah nggak bakal sadar.
Wits... of course I did. Kobo wouldn't even notice.
Nih nih nih nih yang beda tuh kali ini tuh model kita...
Look, look, look, look. What's different this time is our models...
Ini model baru nih!
These are new models!
Gemes banget! Lucu lucu!
So adorable! So cute!
Wiii! Lucu lucu lucu lucu lucu!
Wheee! So cute, cute, cute, cute, cute!
Kameranya dekatin ke aku! Kameranya dekatin ke aku!
Bring the camera closer to me! Bring the camera closer to me!
Nih nih nih nih kalian mau lihat keimutan Kobo nih nih...
Look, look, look, look! You guys want to see Kobo's cuteness? Here, here...
Oshiri!
Butt!
Eh eh eh eh...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Wait wait wait wait, ini kamera diambil Kobo semua nggak sih? Ini ke aku aku juga aku juga!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, Kobo is hogging all the cameras, right? Here, to me too, me too!
Jangan Kobo doang!
Not just Kobo!
Sini sini sini sini kamera kamera kamera Kobo lagi!
Here, here, here, here, camera, camera, camera! Kobo's turn again!
Stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop! Mulai mulai mulai semua kamera diambil!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop! She's starting again, taking all the cameras!
Semua kamera diambil!
She's hogging all the cameras!
Oke oke oke...
Okay, okay, okay...
Kalau gitu... aduh aduh aduh sampai kehabisan napas... Jangan rebutan di depan konser!
Alright then... wow, I'm out of breath... Don't fight in front of the concert!
Iya...
Okay...
Iya iya iya...
Yes, yes, yes...
Zeta kalau marah serem lho.
Zeta is scary when she's angry.
はいよ ゼータが怒ると怖いからね
Okay, because Zeta's scary when she's angry.
こわいよー
Scary!
もういいや ゼータがカメラも独り占めしちゃダメっていうのは… うーん、しょうがない
Fine, if we can't hog the camera from Zeta... Hmm, I guess it can't be helped.
ファンのみんなと遊ぼう！
Let's play with the fans!
さっきみんなからも大きな声もらったわけだし 今度はこっちがみんなに大きな声を出したいっす！
Everyone gave us their loud voices earlier, so now it's our turn to give a loud voice to everyone!
はいはいはい
Yes yes yes.
そうっすよ、カエラの配信時間ほど長くはならないから安心して
That's right, it won't be as long as Kaela's stream time so don't worry.
そう！ みんなにじゃなく、みんなとね
Right! Not *at* everyone, but *with* everyone.
そうそう！ そういうことっす！
Yeah! That's what I mean!
だってこれから歌わなきゃいけないから まず声を温存しなきゃでしょ？
Because we have to sing after this, we need to save our voices first, right?
そうっすよ、そんなにカエラの配信時間ほど長くはならないから安心して
That's right, it won't be as long as Kaela's stream time so don't worry.
まあいい 大声出していいから好きにして
Well fine, you can shout as much as you want.
みんな準備はいいかな？
Everyone, are you ready?
準備出来てる？
Are you ready?
もう出来てるみたいっすね！ じゃあここから！
Seems like you're already ready! Then from here!
一緒に「BOKOBOKOBO！」って叫ぼう！ よろしくいくよ！
Let's shout "BOKOBOKOBO" together! Here we go!
いち、に、さん！
One, two, three!
BOKOBOKOBO！
BOKOBOKOBO!
いいわねいいわね！次はゼータ！
Good, good! Next is Zeta!
はいはいはいはい！
Yes yes yes yes!
「ミッションスタート」って言ったら一緒に「スタート」って言ってわね！
When I say "Mission Start", say "Start" together!
いいかな？ アアア！ ミッション…
Ready? Ahhh! Mission...
スタート！
Start!
次はカエラ！
Next is Kaela!
よしよしよしよし！ きてみんもそしてholoh3roも
Good good good good! To the audience and holoh3ro too.
「holoh3ro！」って言ったら「HU-HA！」で返してね！ 簡単でしょ？
When I say "holoh3ro!", respond with "HU-HA!"! Easy, right?
さあさあさあ！
Come on, come on, come on!
準備はいい？ holoh3ro！
Are you ready? holoh3ro!
HU-HA！
HU-HA!
いいわねいいわね！
Good, good!
いいわね ついに３期生は息ぴったり
Nice, finally Gen 3 is in perfect sync.
そうね まだまだ元気が有り余りそうね
Yeah, looks like there's still plenty of energy left.
だって、今日の一曲目だもん でももうすごく伝わってくるんだもん
After all, it's the first song of the day. But it's already coming through so much.
みんな、まさか私達の一曲目が「100%」だなんて思ってた？
Everyone, did you ever think our first song would be "100%"?
思うわけないよな 私もびっくりした
No way we'd think that. I was surprised too.
ホシノヴァ気分でライブ開始だなんて！ すごいよね？
Starting the live in Hoshinova mood! Amazing, isn't it?
やばい！
Crazy!
かっこいいっすね、しかもさっきゼータと歌った… いや違う
It's cool, and singing with Zeta earlier... No wait.
ゼータとか？
Zeta or something?
ゼータとカエラが歌った時はもう本家の「100%」みたいっす
When Zeta and Kaela sang, it was just like the original "100%".
マジかっこよすぎなんだけど なんか、うーうー！ってなってきて！
It was seriously too cool, I was like "Ugh! Ugh!".
あんなにかっこいい歌を歌ったことあるのかな？
I wonder if I've ever sung such a cool song before?
かっこつけてんの？
Are you trying to look cool?
そう、かっこつけてる
Yeah, acting cool.
本物のかっこつけ だってムーナの曲がかっこいいもん
Real cool. Because Moona's song is cool.
だってゼータがいつもスタイリッシュとかジャズっぽい曲ばっかだしね？
Because Zeta usually sings stylish or jazzy songs, right?
だからさっき「100%」を歌った時 めっちゃ雰囲気が違う
So when singing "100%" earlier, the atmosphere was totally different.
しかもカエラのラップも！
And Kaela's rap too!
なんかこう… ダダダダダダダダダダダダ！
It was like... dadadadadadadadada!
とにかくかっこよかった！ すごいわ！
Anyway, it was cool! Amazing!
でも、それだけじゃないよ！ 次の曲が「NEW[zom]BIE!!」でした！
But that's not all! The next song was "NEW[zom]BIE!!"!
これだれの曲かわかるよね？
You know whose song this is, right?
もちろんらよ うちの先輩だ
Of course, it's our senpai.
さっきもあれさ… holoroのパフォーマンスもめっちゃかっこよかったよ まるでゲームの中にいるみたいだった
Earlier that too... holoro's performance was also very cool, it was like being in a game.
そうっすわ！ しかもバックダンサーもいたし
That's right! And there were back dancers too.
かっこよかったっね！
It was cool, wasn't it!
かっこいい！
Cool!
他になんかあったかな？ レーザーも花火も！あと…
Was there anything else? Lasers and fireworks too! And...
すごいギミックがたくさんあったっすわ！
There were lots of amazing gimmicks!
あのバックダンサーたち あたしのソロライブに雇うっす
I'll hire those back dancers for my solo live.
おっと、もうソロライブの話？
Oops, talking about a solo live already?
まあ言霊も祈りってやつ
Well, words have power.
でもこのライブはまだ終わらないよ！ まだまだ！
But this live isn't over yet! Still more!
でも…さっき何の歌を歌ったか知ってる？
Bu-but... do you know what song we sang earlier?
もちろんらよ 私の新しい曲だから 「dahlah.」
Of course, because it's my new song. "dahlah."
そうっすね まあいいや
Right. Oh well.
まあいい
Oh well.
いやいや！ タイトルは「dahlah.」だよ！ 「dahlah.」！
No no! The title is "dahlah."! "dahlah."!
おぉなるほど
Oh I see.
「dahlah.」だったか… まぁわざとだったけど 「dahlah.」だったか、先に言ってよ！
So it was "dahlah."... Well, we were doing it on purpose, but so it was "dahlah.", you should've said so!
だっていつもそれ言ってるじゃん 本当にもういいやって思ってた
Because you're always saying that. I thought you were really fed up.
それ言って帰ると思ってた
I thought you'd say that and go home.
いやいや、かわいそうだから
No no, that would be sad.
じゃあ「dahlah」ってどういう意味？
So what does "dahlah" mean?
人生はしょうがないって意味
It means "it can't be helped" in life.
人生は重いからまあいいやって言えばいいだけ
Life is heavy, so just say "oh well".
その後人生を続けようって意味
It means "let's continue life after that".
そうっすね、大人になったらわ
That's right, once you become an adult.
Untung lagunya santai, easy listening,
Fortunately, the song is relaxed and easy listening,
jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan, nyapa fans, gitu ya?
so we can walk around and greet fans, right?
Asyik banget ya tadi ya?
It was really fun, wasn't it?
Aku juga suka banget tadi bagian reff-nya ya!
I also really liked the chorus part!
Dala dala dala...
Itu... itu beda lagu gak sih?
Wait... isn't that a different song?
Gak gitu deh... kayaknya...
I don't think it's like that...
Ya tapi pokoknya asyik lah ya,
But anyway, it's fun,
kalau nyanyi lagu chill santai-santai kayak gini.
singing a chill and relaxed song like this.
Iya, santai dong!
Yeah, take it easy!
Tapi ngomongin soal santai,
But speaking of relaxing,
kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu.
we actually can't relax just yet.
Hei, santai!
Hey, relax!
Lho katanya nggak boleh santai tadi?
Wait, didn't you say we can't relax?
Iya iya iya, jangan santai-santai. Jangan terlalu santai.
Yeah, yeah, don't relax too much. Don't be too casual.
Karena konsernya tuh masih panjang!
Because the concert is still long!
Jadi, sebelum itu, kalian ada nggak yang mau kalian sampaiin dulu?
So before that, do you guys have anything you want to say?
Mulai dari ini nih, nggak bisa diem.
Starting from this one, who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja.
Just three words.
I Love You.
Keren! The best!
Cool! The best!
Sangat jelas ya.
Very clear indeed.
Tetap semangat! Tetap semangat menjalani hidup ya.
Keep the spirit up! Stay motivated in life.
Dah gitu aja.
That's it.
Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang. Semangat!
Anyway, it's still a long way. Keep fighting!
Saranghaeyo! Gomawoyo!
I love you! Thank you!
Oke, kalau aku... ya, semangat selalu!
Okay, for me... yeah, always stay spirited!
Semangat santai.
Relaxed spirit.
Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius. Semangat santai ya!
Don't take life too seriously. Take it easy!
Semangat santai apa tuh?
What do you mean 'relaxed spirit'?
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjutkan!
Okay, then let's continue!
Wait wait wait tunggu dulu!
Wait wait wait, hold on!
Sebelum selesai-selesai ini nih ya,
Before we finish this,
kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu nggak sih?
shouldn't we shout together with the audience?
Iya dong! Ayo ayo ayo!
Of course! Let's go, let's go!
Oke oke.
Okay, okay.
Jadi kita teriak bareng ya, dalam hitungan ketiga
So let's shout together, on the count of three,
kita sama-sama teriak Chromatic Future. Oke ya?
let's all shout 'Chromatic Future' together. Okay?
Chromatic Future! gitu kan ya?
'Chromatic Future!' like that, right?
Iya iya kayak gitu.
Yeah, yeah, like that.
Oke langsung ya, sambil liat sini sini sini.
Okay, right away, while looking here, here, here.
Aku, aku yang penonton ini nih!
I'll take this audience here!
Aku ini nih yang tengah, yang tengah.
I'll take the ones in the middle, the middle!
Oke bareng-bareng ya.
Okay, all together.
Satu, dua, tiga!
One, two, three!
Chromatic Future!
Everything was easy, I did it all alone.
So effortlessly, I spread my wings
and let my magic unfold.
Got all problems solved without any setbacks,
there is nothing uncontrolled.
There's no way I can begin,
dream life that I need to win.
I need to feel how all these things
crumble into little pieces.
I know I gotta soar a little higher.
Hope all turns to be the things I desire.
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap,
Like a peacock spreading its wings,
kan ku taklukkan gelap dengan sihir angin.
I will conquer the darkness with wind magic.
Kan kuajak semua yang terlelap
I will invite all who slumber
tuk bangkit melawan dunia.
to rise and fight the world.
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves,
we could rise above the pain, stronger than that.
Walking step by step, trusting my own pace,
giving me what I deserve to have. Let's go!
Just believe me! Let it go,
they'll never bring me down.
they'll never bring us down.
Aiming for royalty, still in my royalty.
And when the universe works against me I would just...
Let go! If it's spicy just sip something, let it go.
Let go!
I've been living carefree,
there's no bitter words that could affect me.
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold,
not letting it show, stings
but I'm bigger than my feelings,
so that will be enough.
There is no way I can begin, dream life that I need to win.
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces.
I know I gotta be better than ever.
Hope all turns to be sweeter than ever.
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap,
Like a peacock spreading its wings,
kan ku taklukkan gelap dengan sihir angin.
I will conquer the darkness with wind magic.
Kan kuajak semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit...
I will invite all who slumber to rise...
melawan dunia
...against the world
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than them
Walking step by step
Trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Believe me,
let it go
They'll never bring me down, just believe me
Let it go,
it'll never bring us down, just believe me
Won't let their cruelty steal my royalty
And when the universe works against me, I will do
Let it go
Come on guys, ready to do this?
One, two, three!
Let it go!