(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
CCGG 劇場
[Title: CCGG Theater]
曖昧3センチ そりゃぷにってコトかい? ちょっ!
3 ambiguous centimeters, does that mean it's squishy? Wait!
らっぴんぐが制服...だぁぁ不利ってこたない ぷ。
Wrapping it in a uniform... there's no way that's a disadvantage, hah.
がんばっちゃ? やっちゃっちゃ
Shall we do our best? Let's do it!
そんときゃーっち&Release ぎョッ
At that moment, catch and release, whoa!
汗(Fuu)々(Fuu)の谷間に
In the sweaty valley...
Darlin’ darlin’ F R E E Z E!!
Darling, darling, FREEZE!
なんかダるー なんかデるー あいしテるー
Feeling kind of lazy, something's coming out, I love you!
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Huh, that one thing is different!
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒ー
Worried kid, high bar...
おいしん簿ー
Gourmet journal...
いーかげんにシナサイ
Stop fooling around!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
They say his flying, flushed body...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just that of a normal girl.
驚いたあたしだけ?
Am I the only one who's surprised?
豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだ
Another bowl of tonkotsu ramen with extra-firm noodles!
BON-BON おーえん団
Bon-bon cheer squad!
Let’s get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN かんげー会
Ran-ran welcome party!
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation!
はい！存在感テンションはMAXで！
Yes! Presence, tension is at MAX!
ぶつかって解けました方程式
We collided and solved the equation!
おーい！みんなで試練じゃん！
Hey! It's a trial for everyone!
持って行け！最後に笑っちゃうのは私のはず！
Take it away! The one laughing in the end should be me!
セーラー服だからです 結論！
Because it's a sailor uniform. Conclusion!
月曜日なのは 機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
It's Monday, what should we do about the bad mood?
夏服がいいのです 可愛い！
Summer uniform is great! Cute!
曖昧3センチ
Vague 3 centimeters...
そりゃぷにってコトかい？ ちょっ！
Does that mean squishy? Wait!
がんばって はりきって Nus！
Do your best, get pumped up!
マイダーリンダーリンプリーズ
My darling, darling, please!
もりもり もり下がり もり下がり
Rising, falling, falling down...
まだ内緒にしといて凛々
Keep it a secret for now, dignifiedly!
甘えん坊 用心棒 通信簿
Spoiled child, bodyguard, report card...
調子こいて玉砕！
Getting cocky and completely shattered!
ポンと 愛する 恋する タイプ
Suddenly, the type to love and be in love,
っていうか圧倒的じゃない？気にしない！
I mean, isn't it overwhelming? I don't care!
絶対 惨敗 一番 生意気決まり！
Absolute crushing defeat, the cheekiest!
するりとおねだり たらららら
Smoothly begging, ta-ra-ra-ra-ra!
ぽんぽん妄想で Let's go!
Pon-pon, with wild delusions, Let's go!
パルシィでやいやいストライキ
With Parsee, hey-hey, on strike!
ぶつかって テンション MAX
We collided, tension is at MAX!
アルバイト 探したら 見つかって
Looked for a part-time job and found one!
当然 人生丸ごと 決定なんです！
Of course, my whole life is decided!
やってみよう 新規に 狙うのは 私の挑戦！
Let's try, aiming anew is my challenge!
セーラー服 着替えても 私！
Even if I change out of my sailor uniform, I'm still me!
週末はどうよ？ チラ見せだって ありきたり
How about the weekend? Even a peek is ordinary.
セーラー服は簡単よ 楽ちん！
Sailor uniform is easy, comfortable!
妄想 冷めない
Delusions won't cool down,
抱きついてたいもんだ ぎゅっ！
I want to cling to you, squeeze!
胸ときめき 弾けて
Heart fluttering, bursting,
シュガーシュガースウィート
Sugar, sugar, sweet!
ねえねえ、新曲についてなんだけど... いいじゃん、それ！
Hey, about the new song... That sounds great!
えー、それはないよー え、そうなの？私は好きだけどなー
Huh? No way... Really? I like it though.
じゃあさ、これでいこうよ！ いいね！
Then, let's go with this! Sounds good!
みんなでがんばろうね！ うん！
Let's all do our best! Yeah!
これ、すごく楽しいね！ そうだね！
This is so much fun! You're right!
まだまだ行くよー！
We're still going!
ぽんぽんぽんで
Pon-pon-pon!
ワン・ツー、うっ・うっ・あー！
One, two, uh, uh, ah!
らららん、ちょっ・ちょっ・いー！
La-la-lan, cho-cho-ee!
ルック・アップ、ふっ・ふっ・はー・はい！
Look up, fuh-fuh-hah, yes!
エデュケーション、らびー
Education, lovey-dovey!
えぶりしんぐ、なんかだなんかだ 晴れて晴れて 決定なんです！
Everything is kind of, cleared up and decided!
持って行け！最後に笑っちゃうのは私のはず！
Take it away! The one laughing in the end should be me!
セーラー服だからです 結論！
Because it's a sailor uniform. Conclusion!
月曜日なのは 機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
It's Monday, what should we do about the bad mood?
夏服がいいのです 可愛い！
Summer uniform is great! Cute!
やっぱり最後に笑っちゃうのは私のはず！
In the end, the one laughing should be me!
セーラー服だからです 結論！
Because it's a sailor uniform. Conclusion!
曖昧3センチ
Vague 3 centimeters...
それぷにってコトかい？ わお！
Does that mean squishy? Wow!
らっぴんぐがセーラー服
Wrapping is a sailor uniform.
よし、ぷにってコトない！ ごー！
Okay, not squishy! Go!
がんばっちゃう、やっちゃっちゃ
Doing our best, doing it...
がっとっちゃう、わっちゃっちゃ
Getting it, wacha wacha!
マイダーリンダーリンにゅー！
My darling, darling, nyu!
Now, this is what I'm talking about!
That's what we need!
We need... we need another hit show!
We need an anime opening!
No, no, we need, no, we need a show. We need, we need something with substance.
I just thought that our show was failing because we didn't have an anime opening.
No, our show is failing because it's really bad.
It's not that bad.
It's really bad! Have you seen the reviews?
They're wrong, though.
It's an acquired opinion.
Oh, well, well, it's so complicated! I didn't sign up for this. I'm just, look...
I can be...
...eye candy.
Well, your eye candy isn't getting us any ratings.
Well, yours isn't either, because look, look at...
...this arm!
Now, stop. Stop, no one wants to see that. Stop.
We need an idea.
We can both sell ourselves out!
No, that's not going to work. That's not enough.
I have an idea.
What?
We steal other people's concepts.
You're a genius!
We just make what's already popular...
...but we make it ours.
Yeah! We put our name on it.
Yeah, we'll get all the credit.
What are they going to do? Nothing!
We'll get all the funding back...
...and then we can finally do what we're really passionate about!
Oh my god, oh my god! But we're going to have to...
We're going to have to do so much research on what's popular.
What do we do? What do we do?
We need... influencers.
We need influencers?
We need... sexy ladies.
We have that. I guess we already have that.
I cannot offer it. Wait, what else do we need?
We need to sell out.
Ah... I'm so tired from all this thinking.
I think we need to explore other genres, Cecilia Immergreen.
Like what?
Every genre.
I think that's the only way.
You're boring me... kind of.
What?
Oh, a sympathetic sleeper!
Oh...
Where... Where are we, Gigi?
What is this?
Are we... Are we in my head? Wait, are we in your head?
Are we in my head?
What?
This is just like fanfiction!
Does that mean we're going to steal people's ideas?
Oh no, they're our ideas. We're in my head.
I'm going to steal your idea.
You't can't steal my ideas.
I could!
Wait, what if... No.
What if I see every single idea that's in your head and then I take them from you?
Stop!
Cecilia, if you go too deep into my brain, you'll get to the yaoi parts!
Oh. Oh.
Maybe we should start with my brain. It's okay, it's okay.
Wait. Wait.
What's in your brain?
A thing.
Actually, there's a lot in my brain. For example...
Your brain is full of bad romance novels! We can't put that in our show!
Yes, we can!
We can't put it in our show!
Let's put it in our show! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Romance...
Romance.
I guess we need to break free out of this place.
DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL
[Title Card: DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL]
THE FOLLOWING SCENE IS AS FOLLOWS: CROY AND GIBRIELLA ARE AT A PARTY. CROY LOVES BASKETBALL AND GIBRIELLA IS NOT LIKE OTHER GIRLS...
[Title: Croy and Gibriella are at a party. Croy loves basketball and Gibriella is not like other girls...]
I don't want to sing. I'm just a normal boy.
I just want to play basketball with my friends and get my head in the game. I can't sing!
I'm just Croy!
Get it together, Gibriella! We don't have time for extracurriculars, we have to get into college!
I'm not like other girls, I just want to stay at home and read books!
ばかみたい 子供なのね
Like a fool, I'm just a child, aren't I?
夢を追って傷ついて
Chasing dreams and getting hurt
嘘が下手なくせに
Even though you're bad at lying
笑えない笑顔みせた
You showed me a smile you couldn't laugh with
I love youも ろくに言わない
You wouldn't even say 'I love you' properly
口下手でほんまに不器用
You're bad with words and truly clumsy
なのにおなのにどうして
Yet, yet, why
サヨナラは言えたの
Could you say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, it's bad, it's just no good
あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
I love you so much, I love you too much
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the alcohol is
歪まない思い出が
The memories won't get distorted...
ばかみたい
...like a fool.
ばかみたい 本当バカね
Like a fool, you're really a fool
あんた信じるばかりで
Always believing in you
強い女のふり
Pretending to be a strong woman
切なさの夜風浴びる
Bathed in the night wind of heartache
一人になって 3年が過ぎ
Three years have passed since I became alone,
街並みさえも 変わりました
Even the cityscape has changed.
なのに なのに どうして
And yet... And yet, why...
未練だけ 置き去り
...am I left with nothing but regrets?
ほんまに ロクな男やない
You really are a good-for-nothing man.
揃いの指輪 はずします
I'll take off our matching rings.
ざまあみろ せいせい するわ
Serves you right, what a relief!
いい加減 待ってても
Even if I wait forever...
馬鹿みたい
...I'm just a fool.
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
No good, no good, no good at all.
あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much.
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the alcohol,
歪まない思い出が
the memories don't distort...
馬鹿みたい
...I'm just a fool.
ほんまに ロクな男やない
You really are a good-for-nothing man.
揃いの指輪 はずします
I'll take off our matching rings.
ざまあみろ せいせい するわ
Serves you right, what a relief!
なんなのよ この涙
What are these tears?
馬鹿みたい
I'm just a fool.
Whoa, yeah, yeah. Musicals is where it's at.
I think, I think this could really be...
This is gonna get us the big dollars.
Yeah, hopefully the big mouse is not gonna shoot us in the head.
Ten billion dollars!
What big mouse?
Ten... don't worry about it.
Ten billion dollars! Yeah! / It's really good.
We might need like a different type of show too, you know? Just for variety. So they can't shoot us...
A variety show? / Yeah.
Like a variety game show? / Yeah.
The Autofister Games.
The Autofister... physicals?
Games. Physicals.
105!
But first, a word from our sponsors.
Whoa! / Whoa!
Slow down there, partner!
Hold your horses! Don't you think you're scrolling a little too fast?
Yeah, put down the phone and full screen our video instead, because...
We are about to show you the new hottest thing in town!
Introducing the...
Autofister Network!
Get it? Cuz it's Autofister Network, but this is our merch.
We wanted to take this opportunity to show you all of our cool fun merch before it goes live!
We've got Cemimis,
Gimimis,
Grems,
Otomos,
And this neat acrylic stand of the both of us!
Yay! And if you hurry up, you'll even be able to get the limited set with a postcard signed by both of us!
Woohoo!
It will be live at these exact times! So make sure to check it out then!
Coming soon to a stream near you!
And we're back from our commercial break!
Thank you everyone for waiting!
Welcome back to the official... Autofister...
Physical Autofister! 100!
100!
And with us, we have our lovely contestants...
Bae! / Okay!
I'm going to win!
Su!
Su-base, comfortable...
Towa!
Towa-sama!
As said before, we're here to find out who is the ultimate winner of...
Physical Autofister...
100!
And before our commercial break, each contestant will have to compete in our physical obstacle course of fun!
Fun!
If you're just now tuning in, here is a quick recap.
Everyone starts in a line, you run to the other side while avoiding obstacles, and do a quick little physical activity.
Grab a question from the dragon, who telepathically gives it to you in your brain, run back and answer the question. Yeah!
We'll do four rounds and the person with the most points at the end of four rounds is the winner!
Okay! Well, everyone, get into position!
Yeah! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Okay, okay.
I think there's something very big in the way. What is this?
It's huge.
So, so, as said before, of course, since a lot of these questions will be in English...
Yes.
...Bae has a handicap.
She'll have a handicap... very, very difficult questions.
What is this? Nice! Nice! Nice! Nice!
Okay, okay, okay, everyone in position?
Yes, yes.
The first run. The first run is: you run over there...
...and you do five jumping jacks.
Five jacks.
Five jumping? Okay.
走って、ファイブジャンプやって...
Run, do five jumps...
...質問取って、走って帰る。
...get the question, run back.
Okay, okay.
Three...
...two...
...one... go!
1、2、3、4、5！
One, two, three, four, five!
Okay, first question. First...
おいしょ、おいしょ。I was betrayed.
Heave-ho, heave-ho. I was betrayed.
Please read the question out loud.
おいしょ、おいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
Okay, えーと...
Okay, uh...
...I like...
...strawberry!
Name a fruit!
Name a fruit. Strawberry!
One point! One point!
Okay, you can give me your questions over here.
Well, next round.
Next round. Everyone ready?
No, no, no, we have to display...
Yeah, but is everyone ready for the next round?
すごいステップ踏んじゃってる。
I'm stepping on some amazing steps.
Yeah, yeah.
And now, the crab walk, like this!
Crab walk, like this!
Crab walk!
Oh! Crab walk!
Crab walk and five squats!
5スクワット？蟹歩きして5スクワット。
Five squats? Crab walk and do five squats.
Five!
Wait, do they have to jump?
No, we can walk.
Walk!
They have to jump. Okay.
帰ったときもこれ？
Do we have to do this going back too?
帰るときも。Okay, okay.
When going back too. Okay, okay.
Okay, everyone ready?
Three...
...two...
...one...
...go!
1、2、3、4、5！
One, two, three, four, five!
It was close! It was close!
Okay, come... Oh, I ripped... I ripped the mind telepathy paper!
You can't rip our telepathy paper.
13 times 6... 78!
Yay! She's actually really good at math. She's good at math. Wow!
バナナ？
Banana?
またバナナなんだけど。
It's banana again.
え？
What?
2回連続バナナなんだけど。
It's banana twice in a row.
This one...
Two banana question?
おい、日本語書いてるじゃねえか！
Hey, isn't Japanese written on it?!
What? I was given a handicap because the questions are in English, they're written in Japanese!
Okay, okay, we gotta keep it rolling, guys. Keep it rolling.
Do I still have to go around and around?
Yes, yes.
Those are the rules by our producers, who are not us.
On my telepathy paper, the next one is... sexy walk.
Sexy walk. Sexy walk.
Sexy walk? Sexy, sexy. Okay, okay.
Do we get disqualified? Do we have to start again if it's not sexy enough? / Yes.
Shiori, please make up your mind.
We'll see. We'll see.
And three pushups!
Three!
腕立て伏せ3回？Okay.
Three pushups? Okay.
Okay.
And sexy walk.
Sexy walk. Sexy walk、ね。
Sexy walk. Sexy walk, right.
Okay, okay.
Sexy walk, sexy jump. Sexy jump.
セクシーさが足りなかったら、万が一やり直しって言われてるから。
They said that if it's not sexy enough, we might have to redo it.
What?! セクシーが足りない？
What?! Not sexy enough?
Sexy, sexy, sexy. Okay, okay.
任せろ、任せろ。
Leave it to me, leave it to me.
Towa-sama! Sexy, sexy, sexy.
Okay!
Everyone ready?
Three, two, one, go!
Go!
Sexy, Bae! Sexy!
Woah!
You tried to do it sexy?
一！
One!
二！
Two!
三！
Three!
トワ様！
Towa-sama!
Sexy, sexy!
It's more sexy!
That's how you do it!
Oh, sexy!
All right, sexy Bae.
I'm sexy.
もう一回！
Once again!
あれ？
Huh?
セクシーじゃない？
Isn't that sexy?
セクシーじゃない、もう。
That's not sexy anymore.
You tried... that's sexy!
Hey Bae, you only have to do it on the way there.
On the way back, you can go straight.
No, no, no...
Hey, don't help the contestant.
Wait.
Name a flower!
パンジー！
Pansy!
Oh, yeah! Pansy!
知ってる？
You know that?
Oh, yeah!
Okay, okay!
One, one, one.
One, one, one!
Wait, have you been counting the points?
Yeah, one, one, one.
Oh, really? One, one, one?
One, one, one.
Oh, tiebreaker!
Tiebreaker. Okay, okay.
最後のポイントは...
The last point is...
Are you ready?
100ポイント？ 100ポイント？
100 points? 100 points?
Last round!
Can I get rid of this?
No! Last round!
Do this, you have to do this well.
Okay.
Lunge walk!
きつい！
This is hard!
やばい。
Oh my gosh.
来た、来た、来た！
Here we go, here we go, here we go!
3回！
Three times!
Okay, okay!
How many times?
3回！
Three times!
3回！ 3、3、3！
Three times! Three, three, three!
3回！
Three times!
And then three...
Wow, you're so good!
がんばろう。
Let's do our best.
わかりました？
Do you understand?
オーケー！ オーケーです！
Okay! Yes, okay!
わかりました。
I understand.
死にそうな顔。
You look like you're gonna die.
Me too, me too.
Can I skip this?
No! No, no, no!
Or parts of it will get cut.
Come on, come on.
Bae, fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
がんばる！
Let's do this!
Three, two, one, go!
ほい！ ほい！
Hoi! Hoi!
Get to the center!
こぼ、何してるの？
Kobo, what are you doing?
Hurry, hurry!
Are your knees not touching the ground?
Towa-sama is fine, she's doing her best.
一、二、
One, two,
二、
Two,
3！ こぼ、早く！
Three! Kobo, hurry up!
トワ様、強い！
Towa-sama is so strong!
Wait, let's wait for Bae to come back.
Bae, come on!
Come on, Bae!
We can answer, Bae, come on!
Come on Bae, we can't decide the winner until you get over here.
Hey, you need high five!
Hey, squat over here.
Come on, come on!
Wow! All right, here's your question.
Say a French word!
French... French...
French. French.
知ってますかね？
Do you know any?
ボンジュール！
Bonjour!
Oh! Yes!
Yes, yes!
Towa is the winner!
Our winner of today!
勝つ時にいねえじゃねえかよ！
Why weren't you here when we won?!
Well, contestants have something to complain about no matter what we do.
Yeah, we did our best.
They should try to do the last level, it was like insane!
やってみない？ やってみ？ 一周。
Do you want to try? Try it, one lap.
一周回って？ 結構しんどいよ。
Go around once? It's pretty exhausting.
No, no, no, stop, stop, stop, Bae only.
Ah, Bae only.
Security! Security!
Yeah, security!
Security got her.
Can we give our winner her crown?
Here is your crown!
Yeay!
Oh, thank you! Thank you!
This is not fair!
Please leave, we need a tiebreaker!
Tiebreaker! Tiebreaker!
This is Bae.
This is Su.
This is Towa-sama!
And you're watching the Autofist Network!
That rat sucked.
Yeah, she should go back to the gym or something.
She should go back to school and retake PE.
Yeah, but Towa-sama was really strong. Wow! She even got the cool crown! Amazing.
Yo! / Yo!
Also, the hosts were amazing.
Really charismatic, so beautiful! Every time they were on screen, I was electrified!
I think this is what's gonna get us the, the funding.
Yeah, I think we're going to get 10 million dollars for this one.
And the more budget they have, the, the more difficult the challenges can get, and then the death... you know...
Penalty!
...can be even greater.
Anyways...
...what if...
...anime, but live-action?
I don't feel so good.
(screaming)
I'm so tired, Gigi.
Me too! I'm so tired! I've been working so hard!
We've been working so hard making so many shows. I'm so sleepy!
And we are always recording, and we're in the studio every single day!
And there's never tea parties! Nobody ever invites me to their tea parties!
You know what? Actually, I have been preparing something.
Is it this background? This really, really cool background...
...you probably stole from the internet?
Who said I stole it? I stole it.
You stole it from the internet?
Yeah! And this is my tea party, so welcome in!
But yeah, I have one more surprise, Gigi Murin.
You have a surprise for the tea party?
Yeah. Where are our models?
Where's me? Where's me?
You know what? We got some graphics updates!
A graphic update?
You want to see?
You want to see? I want to see! I want to see me!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! It's me, Cecilia Immergreen, from Hololive English Justice!
Spin to win!
You look great!
Oh, thanks!
You look freaking amazing!
I guess I'll go sit down real quick.
Oh my god, I look so good. Look at my shoes!
Wow!
Hey Gigi, come on, come on in, it's okay.
Oh! I get one, too?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Gigi Murin, everyone! It's Gigi Murin from Hololive English Justice!
Just dance!
I'm so happy to be here!
Wow, you look good!
I guess it's time for me to sit down also.
Look at my shoes, too.
Wow! Wow! Wow, those look good.
Those look kind of hard to walk in actually. That's crazy.
No, I'm a natural! Let me sit down.
Sit down already.
And together, we are... Autofist! Autofist Network! Yay!
Finally, we get some time to relax. Wow, you look really good.
Ah, thank you! You look really good, too.
Oh, we're hugging again.
Oh, I just can't, I just really like hugging you.
I can't help that I keep hugging you.
You really like hugging.
Oh, my hood came off. That's fine.
I'm so excited!
So excited!
I'm really excited. Oh, are you hungry?
I'm really hungry, will you feed me?
Okay, I'll feed you, I'll feed you.
Say "ah"...
Ah... oh, it's a cupcake! Oh, it's good.
Oh! Wait, oh, I'm really hungry, too, I guess.
Oh my god, you're getting this all over me. It's getting really messy.
Oh, why are you getting it on your face, too? Ew!
It tastes really good.
Let me feed you again. Oh, do you mind? I got my spit on it. You don't mind, do you?
Wait, wait, wait, let me wipe that off. You got something on the side of your mouth. Let me just get that for you.
Let me get it off of you, too. Oh, you have something on your mouth.
Oh, okay, okay, that's enough, that's enough.
Thirsty? / I'm thirsty, I'm really thirsty.
Okay, I'll pour you some tea.
Mmm, glug glug glug glug. I'm really excited.
Here's your tea. / It's really hot!
Oh, be careful, be careful. / Oh my god, it's really, oh my god, it's really hot! Oh, it's all over my body.
Oh no, you spilled some, oh my god. / Oh, it's on, oh my god, it burns! Atsui, atsui!
Oh my god! I... oh no!
I feel like I got a third-degree burn just now.
Why did you do that to me?
I'm sorry! Let me wipe it off.
Let me wipe it off of you.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that. I just got really overzealous.
Oh, but it's really good now, it's cooled down.
You like it? What type of tea is it?
It has a little floral note on it. Here, try some.
Try from my finger, try from my finger.
(Sucks finger / giggles)
How's the taste?
Yummy.
Mmm, mmm, mmm. That's really good.
Okay, that's, that's enough. / I finished my cup. It was really, it was really delicious.
You know, if Elizabeth was here, she would tell us that after having a really good meal, we should work out.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, so let's get up.
Let's go stand over there by the horse.
Yeah, let's stand by the horse. That horse is really amazing.
You're making so much noise!
Sorry, my... my shoes are just really big and clunky.
You know what? I think it'd be really cool if we were to do 50 push-ups right now.
I... I want to do... You know what, I want to do 50 push-ups!
Me? I really want to... - No, no, no...
I really... I really want to do 50 push-ups.
Okay, okay, wait, I changed my mind. - Oh, you changed your mind? - I want...
I want, um... 50 lunges!
50 lunges? - Oh, oh, your knee hurts?
Oh... yeah, I got into an accident about 200 years ago.
Did you get hit by a car? - I got hit by a car 200 years ago.
Okay, I guess that's just how it is.
You know what, Chichimori? - Don't touch me!
Stop touching me. - Stop touching me!
What? Why are you always fighting with me? You're just always fighting!
Why are you always fighting? I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you so much! I hate your hair!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey... - Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I got... sorry, I was being mean. I was acting out. Do you forgive me?
I guess so.
I'm sorry for yelling. - I'm sorry for yelling at you.
I didn't mean to. Can you kiss my knee, please?
I feel really good now.
Do you feel better? - I feel better.
And I feel really sleepy all of a sudden.
Me too, actually. I'm so sleepy.
I'm so sleepy.
But there's only one bed! What should we do? Should we get in together?
I guess so. I guess we'll get into... Let me just take off my shoes.
Oh yeah, I think it would be really, really weird to get into bed with shoes on. - Yeah, that would be strange.
But let me help you. Let me fluff this pillow for you. Oh, you look so...
Here you go, princess.
Okay, let me... Let me just lay down.
Oh, let me get into bed too. I have to take my shoes off too. - I'm already getting so comfortable.
Please, please, don't go to bed without me!
I'm so tired. If someone doesn't get into bed quick, I'm just going to fall asleep without you.
Oh, no, don't, don't! It's just my... my achy-achy bones. I'm trying to get into bed, please!
I guess your knee really hurts still. - It does. Oh, I feel so comfortable.
Thanks for coming to my tea party, Cece.
Thanks for inviting me, Chichimori. - Good night.
Oh, oh, we're holding hands. - It's because I get scared in the dark.
Oh, of course. Yeah, yeah. - So I'm glad that we have each other. Good night, Cece.
Good night, Chichimori. - Good night.
I'm Cece! - And I'm Chichimori!
And you're watching... - The Autofist Network!
I don't know if that's going to make us any money.
Well, on to the next idea!
みんなが大好 きっ!!
Everyone's favorite...!!
延々続行 ルララ miracle sing time
It's our never-ending lu-la-la miracle sing time
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
I'll sing, I'll sing, it's the absolute best way to express my love!
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even if the composition is clumsy or the lyrics are iffy
届けたい 精一杯のsoulを
I want to convey my soul with all I have!
どうしよう オートマティックに決められてる
What can we do, with this timetable...
時間割じゃ追っつかないの
...that's been automatically decided for us.
夢 無限 したいこと 怒涛
Billowing waves of us infinite dreamers...
廊下もダッシュで集まるよ
...dash out and assemble in the hallway!
お行儀悪かったら sorry! でも
Sorry if my manners are bad! But...
なりふりも構わずに
...don't mind how I look.
どっぷりハマっちゃう play
I'm totally addicted to playing...
キラリって もしやこれが青春
...a sparkle, maybe this is what youth is!
ever ever... forever shine
ほんとに 大好 きっ!!
I really love you!!
テンション上昇 ルララ powerful gig time
It's a tension-rising lu-la-la powerful gig time
ハートって ハートって ワクワク探す天才
My heart is, my heart is, an excitement-seeking genius
アレッ!?って言われても ミス連発でも
Even if I say "Huh!?" or start racking up misses
放ちたい 湧いてくる braveを
I want to set free my boiling bravery
し かける トレモロ 応える フラム
On with the tremolo, followed by flam
いいじゃん いいじゃん ノリノリで いんじゃない
Ain't it awesome, ain't it awesome, ain't it awesome to feel so good
ハッピーは いつだってね “今”感じるもの
I'm always so happy, it's the way "now" feels
...つかないの
...I can't keep up!
どうしても ホームワーク よりも 重要 課題
No matter what, it's a more important task than homework.
放課後 の お茶 おしゃべり 練習
After-school tea, chatting, practice.
ユーモア ナチュラル めくるめく 笑い
Humor, natural, dizzying laughter,
ウケ過ぎでお腹痛い
my stomach hurts from laughing too much.
呼吸ぴったし excellent!
Breathing perfectly, excellent!
でも苦手なリフまだあったの
But there was still a riff I was bad at.
特訓つきあってくれる?
Will you accompany me for special training?
も少し門限までだって帰りたくない
A little more until the curfew, because I don't want to go home.
never never…can't say good-bye
Never never... can't say good-bye
めちゃめちゃ大好きっ!!
I really, really love you!!
超絶ぞっこん ルララ wonderful show time
Transcendent, deeply in love, lalala, wonderful show time!
音楽って 音楽って もう私たちまんま
Music, music, it's just like us!
スタンディングオベーション賞 オーディエンスなしでも
Standing ovation award, even without an audience,
奏でたい 瞬間 の real を
I want to play the real of the moment.
昨日の後悔って明日の心配って
Yesterday's regrets, tomorrow's worries,
ぶっちゃけぶっちゃけ誰得? 何得?
to be honest, to be honest, who benefits? What's the gain?
ラッキーはいつだってね “今”つかむもの
Lucky is always something you grasp "now".
欲張れ乙女 与えられん、さらば
Be greedy, maiden, it won't be given to you, farewell!
どんな本も書いてない 授業じゃちょっと教わんない
Not written in any book, you won't be taught in class,
けど一生忘れない
but I'll never forget it for the rest of my life.
この世にないと思ってた奇跡
The miracle I thought didn't exist in this world,
一緒にね歌えば
if we sing together...
信じられるんだ 強くなれるんだ
I can believe, I can become stronger!
みんなが大好きっ!!
We love everyone!!
延々続行 ルララ miracle sing time
Endless continuation, lalala, miracle sing time!
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
Sing, sing, the strongest way to convey love!
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even with a clumsy song, even with subtle lyrics,
届けたい 精一杯のsoul 等身大のlifeを
I want to deliver my soul, with all my might, my life-sized life.
今日は昨日みたい? 明日は今日みたい?
Is today like yesterday? Is tomorrow like today?
大丈夫 大丈夫 楽しかっ たら大正解
It's okay, it's okay, if it's fun, it's the right answer!
ロッカーはいつだってね “今”やんちゃ盛り
Lockers are always, "now", in their naughty prime.
進め乙女 抱きしめて、希望を
Advance, maiden, hold onto hope!
大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you,
大好きをありがとう
thank you for the love!
歌うよ 歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing,
心こめて 今日も歌うよ
putting my heart into it, I'll sing today too!
大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you,
大好きをありがとう
thank you for the love!
歌うよ 歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing,
愛をこめて ずっと歌うよ
putting my love into it, I'll sing forever!
Please hold.
We will soon be changing the channel.
We are about to switch the channel.
Please wait.
The channels will be changed soon.
Please stay seated.
As the channels are about to switch.
Don't change the channel,
because we'll do it for you.
Do not touch the remote...
...'cause we will be doing it.