(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
T.A.N. The Autofister Network 3D LIVE
[Title: T.A.N. The Autofister Network 3D LIVE]
CCGG 劇場
[Title: CCGG Theater]
曖昧３センチ そりゃぷにってコトかい？ ちょっ！
Around 3 centimeters, and that's squishy? Wait!
らっぴんぐが制服…だぁぁ不利ってこたない ぷ。
My wrapping is a uniform... there's no disadvantage to it, pbbth.
がんばっちゃ▼やっちゃっちゃ
I'll give it my best, I'll do it.
そんときゃーっち＆Release ぎョッ
In times like that, it's catch & release, gyo!
汗（Fuu）々（Fuu）の谷間に Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
In the gap between drops of sweat, darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
もってけ！セーラーふく
Lyrics: 畑 亜貴 Music: 神前 暁
[Song: Motteke! Sailor Fuku]
[Lyrics: Aki Hata / Music: Satoru Kosaki]
なんかダるー なんかデるー
I feel kinda sluggish, I feel kinda out of it.
あいしテるー あれ一個が違ってるんるー
I love you; what's that? One piece is different?
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒ー
Worry-wart, high bar.
おいしん簿ー いーかげんにシナサイ
Gourmet, cut it out.
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
About the flushed body of that girl who jumped,
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
she's just a so-called "normal" girl.
驚いたあたしだけ？
Am I the only one who was surprised?
豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだ
Another helping of pig bone wires.
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON, we're cheerleaders.
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie.
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN, a welcome party.
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation.
はい! 存在感‥小惑星
Yeah! The feeling of existence... asteroids.
持っていきなよ
Go ahead and take it
最後には笑っちゃうのは私のはず
In the end, I'll be the one laughing
セーラー服だからですけど
But it's because I'm in a sailor uniform...
スケ番!
Delinquent!
月曜日なのに機嫌悪いのどうするよ
It's Monday, and I'm in a bad mood, what should I do?
マツプクぐらいがいいのです
Something like 'Matsupuku' would be nice
可愛い!
Cute!
Wait, I guess we already have that.
I cannot afford friends.
Wait, what else do we need?
We need to sell out.
Ah... I'm so tired from all this thinking.
I think we need to explore other genres, Cecilia Immergreen.
Like what?
Every genre.
I think that's the only way.
You're already kind of...
What?
Huh?
Where... Where are we?
Gigi? Where...
What is this?
Are we in my head?
Wait, are we in your head?
What... this is just like fiction.
This is just like fiction!
Does that mean we're gonna steal people's ideas?
Oh no, they're my ideas.
We're in my head.
Wait, but this is my head!
I'm gonna steal your idea!
You can't steal my ideas.
I could!
Wait, what if... No!
What if I see every single idea that's in your head...
...and then I take them from you and then I kill you?
Stop! You're taking my idea!
If you go too deep into my brain, you'll get to the yaoi part.
Oh... oh...
Maybe we should start with my brain. It's okay.
Wait, what's in your brain?
Nothing.
Um, actually, there's a lot in my brain. For example...
Your brain is full of bad romance novels.
We can't put that in our show!
No! Yes we can!
Yes we can put it in our show!
Yes, let's put it in our show! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Romance, hmm, romance.
Romance.
I guess we need a break free out of this place.
DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL
[Title: DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL]
THE FOLLOWING SCENE IS AS FOLLOWS:
CROY AND GIBRIELLA ARE AT A PARTY.
CROY LOVES BASKETBALL
AND GIBRIELLA IS NOT LIKE OTHER GIRLS...
A FICTIONAL TALE OF SONG AND BASKETBALL.
[Scenario: Croy and Gibriella are at a party.
Croy loves basketball and Gibriella is not like other girls...
A fictional tale of song and basketball.]
I don't want to sing.
I'm just a normal boy.
I just want to play basketball with my friends and get my head in the game.
I can't sing. I'm just Troy.
Get it together, Gibriella.
We don't have time for extracurriculars, we have to get into college.
I'm not like other girls, I just want to stay at home and read books.
馬鹿みたい 子供なのね
So foolish. You are a child.
夢を追って傷ついて
Chased dreams and got hurt.
嘘が下手なくせに
Even though you’re a bad at lies,
笑えない笑顔みせた
you showed me a humourless smile.
I love youも ろくに言わない
You can’t even say “I love you”.
口下手でほんまに不器用
You’re really clumsy and bad with words.
なのになのにどうして
Even so, even so, why
サヨナラは言えたの
could you say “goodbye”?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
This is no good. No good. No good at all.
あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much.
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink,
歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
the memories are never muddied; what a fool.
馬鹿みたい 本当バカね
So foolish. Truly stupid.
あんた信じるばかりで
All I did was believe in you;
強い女のふり
pretending to be a strong woman,
切なさの夜風浴びる
showered in a sorrowful night wind.
ばかみたい
[Song: Baka Mitai]
一人になって 三年が過ぎ
It's been three years since I was alone,
街並みさえも 変わりました
even the streets have changed.
なのになのにどうして
Yet, yet why...
未練だけ置き去り
...is only my longing left behind?
ほんまに ロクな男やない
You're really no good, not a decent guy,
揃いの指輪 はずします
I'm taking off that matching ring.
ざまあみろ せいせいするわ
Screw you, I feel so free now,
いい加減 待ってても 馬鹿みたい
it's just foolish to keep waiting like this.
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, it's no good, it's just not right,
あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
I love you so damn much.
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink is,
歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
these memories that won't fade are just foolish.
ほんまに ロクな男やない
You're really no good, not a decent guy,
揃いの指輪 はずします
I'm taking off that matching ring.
ざまあみろ せいせいするわ
Screw you, I feel so free now.
なんなのよ この涙 馬鹿みたい
What the hell are these tears? It's just foolish.
Wow, yeah, yeah, musicals is where it's at.
I think, I think this could really be something.
This is gonna get us the big dollars.
Yeah, hopefully the Big Mouse... is not gonna shoot us in the head.
Ten billion dollars! With Big Mouse!
Ten... don't worry about it. Ten billion dollars.
Yeah, it's really good.
We might need like a different type of show too,
just for variety so they can't shut us down.
A variety show?
Yeah.
Like a variety game show?
The Autofister Games.
The Autofister... Oh! Physicals!
Physicals!
One hundred and five!
But first, a word from our sponsors.
Whoa! Slow down there, partner! Hold your horses!
Don't you think you're scrolling a little too fast?
Yeah, put down the phone and full-screen our video instead...
...because we are about to show you the new hottest thing in town!
Introducing the Autofister Network!
Get it? Because it's Autofister Network, but this is our merch.
We wanted to take this opportunity to show you all of our cool fun merch before it goes live.
We've got Cemimi plushie keychain...
...Gimimi's!
Grems!
Otomos!
And this neat acrylic stand of the both of us!
Yay!
And if you hurry up, you'll even be able to get
the limited set with a card signed by both of us!
Woo-hoo!
It'll be live at this exact time, so make sure to check it out then!
Coming soon to a stream near you!
And we're back from our commercial break!
Thanks to everyone for waiting!
Welcome back to the official...
Physical Autofister 100!
And with us we have our lovely contestant, Bae!
A-Bae! I'm gonna win! A-Bae!
So-chan!
Su-be! Come for-bas!
Towa-sama!
As I said before, we're here to find out...
...who's the ultimate winner of Physical Autofister 100!
Before our commercial break, each contestant...
...will have to compete in our physical obstacle course of FUN!
If you're just now tuning in, here is a quick recap!
[Rules]
1. Start in a line
2. Run to the other side while avoiding obstacles
3. Do pre-decided physical activity
4. Grab a question from dragon
5. Run back and answer the question in ENGLISH
We'll do four rounds...
...and the person with the most points at the end of four rounds is the winner!
Okay! Well, everyone get into positions!
Is everyone excited?!
Yes!
Let's go! Let's do this!
I see something very big in the... what is this?
Excuse me?
As I said before, of course, since a lot of these questions will be in English...
...Bae has the handicap.
What is this?!
The first run, the first round is...
...you run over there and you do five jumping jacks.
Five jacks! Okay!
走って、5回ジャンプやって、
Run there, do five jumps,
質問とって、走って帰る。
take a question, and run back.
OKですか？
Are you okay?
Three, two, one, GO!
1! 2! 3! 4! 5!
I was betrayed!
Please read the question out loud!
Okay... eh...
I like... strawberry!
[Question: NAME A FRUIT!]
[Answer: Strawberry]
Okay, she had to name a fruit!
Name a fruit! Strawberry!
One point for Kobo!
You can give me your questions over here.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Mama! Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Well, next round!
Next round! Everyone ready?
Wait, we have to play. Is everyone ready for the next round?
I'm the crab walk like this!
Crab walk like this!
Oh! Come on!
Crab walk and five squats!
5回スクワット？スクワット、クラブウォークと5回スクワット？
Five squats? Squats, crab walk and five squats?
Wait, do they have to jump?
No, they can walk.
Jump! They have to jump!
帰った時もこれ？
Even when returning?
Yes.
Three, two, one, GO!
えっと、なんてんだっけ？えっと... 1! 2! 3!
Wait, what was it? Uh... 1! 2! 3!
それスクワットじゃねえし！
That's not even a squat!
4! 5!
Come on! Oh, I ripped the mind telepathy paper!
You can't rip our telepathy paper!
[Question: 13 x 6 = ?]
[Answer: 78]
13 times 6!
78!
Oh, she's kind of really good at math!
She's good at math! Wow!
またバナナなんだけど！
It's banana again!
え？2回連続バナナなんだけど！
Eh? Twice in a row it's banana!
[Towa's 1st Question: WHAT COLOR IS A BANANA?]
[Towa's 2nd Question: WHEN'S THE LAST TIME YOU ATE A BANANA?]
おい！日本語書いてんじゃねえか！
Hey! Why is it written in Japanese?!
What! I was given a handicap because the questions are in English...
...but they're written in Japanese!
Okay, okay, we've gotta keep it rolling, guys!
Do I still have to go around and around?!
Yes!
The next one is... Sexy walk!
Sexy walk! Sexy walk!
Do we get disqualified, do we have to start again if it's not sexy enough?
Yes! Hot, please make up your mind!
And three push-ups!
腕立て伏せ3回！
Three push-ups!
And sexy walk!
Yes, sexy walk! Sexy jump! Sexy jump!
で、セクシーさが足りなかったら万が一やり直しって言われてるから。
If the sexiness isn't enough, we might have to redo it!
ええー？！セクシーが足りない？！
Ehh?! Not enough sexiness?!
任せろ任せろ！
Leave it to me, leave it to me!
Sexy Su-chan!
Okay, everyone ready?
Okay, three, two, one...
Go!
Whoa!
Sexy Bae!
You try! It's sexy!
1, 2, 3!
Towa-sama!
Sexy, sexy, sexy!
It's more fancy.
Steps have to take!
Oh, Sexy Su-chan!
あれ、sexy Bae?
Wait, sexy Bae?
Sexy Bae!
あれ？あれ？
Wait, what?
え、セクシーじゃない！セクシーじゃない！もう一回！
What, that's not sexy! Not sexy! One more time!
You try running it, it's sexy.
Hey, you only have to do it on the way there. On the way back you can go straight.
No, no, no. Hey, hey! Don't help the contestant!
Wait.
第1問：花の名前を答えて！
[Question: NAME A FLOWER!]
パンジー！
[Answer: Pansy]
Oh yeah, Pansy!
知ってる？
You know it?
Oh yeah! よかったすいちゃん！
Oh yeah! Way to go Su-chan!
Nice, sexy!
Wait, GG, GG. Have you been counting the points?
Yeah, 1-1-1.
Oh really? 1-1-1.
Oh, tiebreaker! Last round, tiebreaker! Okay, okay.
最後のポイントは… Are you ready?
The final point is... Are you ready?
100ポイント！
100 points!
Can I get rid of this? No!
Last round!
Do this, you have to do this well. Lunge walk!
え… きつい！やばい！
Ugh... this is tough! No way!
きた、きた、きた！
Here we go, here we go!
三回！
Three times!
How many times? 三回！
How many times? Three times!
三、三、三回！三回！
Three, three, three times! Three times!
え？ Wow you're so fast!
Wait? Wow, you're so fast!
Wow!
Okay, okay, がんばろう！
Okay, okay, let's do our best!
わかりました！Okayです！
Understood! It's okay!
わかりました！
Understood!
しんどそうだな…
That looks exhausting...
Me too!
Can I sue this? No!
Oh but it will get cut! Come on, come on!
They're fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Everyone... がんばれ！
Everyone... Do your best!
Two, one, go!
Hey!
Get to the ground, Bae!
どこでするの？
Where are you doing it?
Hey, you're almost touching the dragon!
Towa-sama is fast! Doing her best!
一、二、二、三！
One, two, two, three!
Whoa, he's disqualified!
Survivor!
よいしょ！よいしょ！
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
トワ様、すいちゃん！がんばれ！
Towa-sama, Su-chan! Good luck!
Wait, let's wait for Bae to come back.
Oh, Bae, come on!
Come on, Bae!
We can't decide the winner until you get over here!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, you need a high five!
Hey, squat over here!
Come on, come on!
Wow! All right, here's your question!
第2問：フランス語を一言答えて！
[Question: SAY A FRENCH WORD!]
え！ちょっと待って！
Eh! Wait a minute!
知ってますかね？
Do I know one?
Bonjour!
Okay! やった！
Okay! We did it!
The winner! The winner!
The winner of today...
やった！勝ったわけじゃないかよ！
We did it! Didn't we just win?!
は？！
What?!
Well, I guess the contestants have something to complain about no matter what we do.
Yeah, we did our best.
They should try to do the last round, that was like insane.
やってみなよ！一周！
Try it yourself! One lap!
一周回って？ 結構広いよ。
A full lap? It's pretty big.
No, no, no! Stop, stop, stop! Bae only!
Bae onlyか？
Bae only?
Security! Security!
Yeah, security! Towa, I got her!
Can we give our winner her crown?
Your crown!
Yay!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Oh, thank you!
You're gonna have to leave!
This is unfair! Please leave!
Heartbreak! Heartbreak!
NO SIGNAL PLEASE STAND BY / しばらくお待ちください
[Title: NO SIGNAL PLEASE STAND BY / Please wait a moment]
This is Bae!
This is Su!
This is Towa-sama!
And you're watching the Autofist Network!
The Rat sucked.
Yeah.
She should go back to the gym or something.
She should go back to school and retake PE.
Yeah.
But Towa-sama was really strong!
Wow, she even got the cool crown! Amazing!
And Su-chan was so cute!
So cute! / So cute!
Yeah, also the host was amazing.
Really charismatic.
So beautiful. Every time they were on the screen...
...I was electrified.
I think this is what's gonna get us the funding.
Yeah, I think we're going to get 10 million dollars for this one.
And the more budget they have, the more difficult the challenges can get...
...and then the death, you know...
Penalty... can be even greater.
Anyways, what if...
[Text: Anime but live-action]
I don't feel so good.
I'm so tired, Gigi.
Me too, I am so tired because we've been working so hard.
We've been working so hard, we've been making so many shows.
I'm so sleepy.
I've been out in the recording in the studio every single day.
I deserve a tea party.
If only someone were to invite me to their tea party.
You know what, actually, I have been preparing something.
Is it this background?
Yes, this realistic background that you probably stole from the internet.
I stole it. I stole it.
Stole it from the internet.
Yeah, and this is my tea party, so welcome in!
It's... but I have one more surprise, Gigi Murin.
You have a surprise for the tea party? Yeah.
Where are the models? Where's me? Where's me?
You know what, we got some graphics update.
A graphic update?
You want to see? You want to see?
I want to see me! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
It's me, Cecilia Immergreen from Holo EN Justice!
Just spin and whee!
You look great!
Oh thanks, thanks!
You look freaking amazing!
I guess I'll go sit down real quick.
Oh my god, I look so good. Look at my shoes!
You look so good!
Hey Gigi, come on, come on in, it's okay.
I get one too?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Gigi Murin, everyone!
It's Gigi Murin from Hololive English Justice!
I'm so happy to be here!
Wow, you look great too!
I look great! I guess it's time for me to sit down also.
Look at my shoes too!
Wow, wow, wow! They look good.
Those look kind of hard to walk in, actually. That's crazy.
No, I'm a natural. Let me sit down.
Sit down already.
And together we are...
Autofist!
Finally, we get some time to relax.
Wow, you look really good.
Aww, you look really good too. Are we hugging again?
I just can't, I really like hugging you.
I can't help that I keep hugging you.
You really like hugging, I guess.
I'm so excited! So excited!
I'm really happy to be here. / Are you hungry?
I'm really hungry. Will you feed me?
Okay, I'll feed you, I'll feed you. Say "ah"!
Ah!
Oh, I accidentally applied it... Oh wait...
...oh I'm really hungry too, I guess I should...
Oh my god, I'm really... Oh, you're getting this all over me.
It's getting really messy.
Oh, why is it getting on your face too?
Eww! Oh, it tastes really good.
Let me feed you again.
Do you mind if I got my spit on it? You don't mind, do you?
Wait, wait, let me wipe that off you.
You got something on the side of your mouth. Let me get that for you.
You're so... Let me get it off of you too.
Oh, you have something on your mouth.
Oh, okay, okay, that's enough. That's enough.
Thirsty?
I'm thirsty, I'm really thirsty.
I'll pour you some tea.
Here's your tea.
Eee! It's really hot!
Oh, be careful, be careful.
Oh my god, it's really... oh my god, it's really hot!
Oh, I spilled it on myself!
Oh god, oh, it's all over my body! Oh no, you spilled it!
Oh my god! Ah, it's hot! Oh my god, it burns!
熱い、熱い！ Oh my god!
It's hot, it's hot! Oh my god!
I feel like I got a third-degree burn just now.
Ah! Why did you do that to me? You're poking me!
I'm sorry! Let me blow your ouchie.
Let me wipe it off of you.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that. I just got overzealous.
Mmm, but it's really good now it's cooled down.
You like it? What type of tea is it?
It's like a note, a little floral note on it.
Here, try some. Try from my finger.
Try from my finger.
How's the taste?
Yummy!
That's really good. Okay, okay, that's enough. That's enough.
I finished my cup. It was really delicious.
You know, if Liz was here, she would tell us that...
...after having a good meal, we should work out.
Oh yeah, yeah, so we should work out.
Let's get up.
Let's go stand over there in this corner.
Yeah, let's stand by the horse. That horse is amazing.
You're making so much noise!
Sorry! My shoes are just really big and clunky.
You know what? I think it'd be really cool if we were to do 50 push-ups right now.
I... I want to do... you know what? I want to do 50 push-ups.
I want to do 50 push-ups.
Me? I really want... no no no.
I really want... I really want to do 50...
Okay okay wait, I changed my mind.
Why did you change your mind?
I want... I want 50 lunges.
50 lunges? Oh... oh your knee hurts?
Oh! Thank you. Yeah, I got into an accident about 200 years ago.
Did you get hit by a car?
I got hit by a car 200 years ago.
Okay. I guess that's just how it is.
You know what, Gigi Murin...
Don't touch me! Stop touching me!
Stop touching me!
What? Oh my god! You always do this!
Why are you always fighting with me?
Like this! Oh you want to fight?
I'm gonna hit you! I hate you!
I hate you so much! I'll take your hair!
Hey hey hey hey... Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I was getting mean. I was acting out.
Will you forgive me?
I... I guess so.
I'm sorry for yelling. I'm sorry for yelling at you.
I didn't mean to.
Can you kiss my knee please?
I guess... oh, I feel really good now.
Do you feel better?
I feel better. And I feel really sleepy all of a sudden.
Me too, actually.
Oh so sleepy. I'm so sleepy.
Oh, but there's only one bed.
What should we do? Should we get in together?
I guess so. I guess we'll get in together.
Let me just take off my shoes.
Oh yeah, I think it'd be really really weird to get into bed with shoes on.
Yeah that would be strange. Let me help you.
Let me fluff this pillow for you.
Oh you look so... here you go, princess.
Okay, let me just lay down.
Oh, let me get into bed too.
I'll take my shoes off too. I'm already getting so comfortable.
Please, please don't go to bed without me!
I'm so tired. If someone doesn't get into bed quick...
I'm just gonna fall asleep without you.
No, don't, don't! It's just my achy achy bones.
I'm trying to get into bed, please.
I guess your knee really hurts still.
It does. Oh, I feel so comfortable.
Thanks for coming to my tea party, Gigi Murin.
Thanks for inviting me, CC.
Let's... oh, we're holding hands.
It's because I get scared in the dark.
Oh, of course. Yeah, so I'm glad that we have each other.
Goodnight, CC.
Goodnight, Gigi.
I'm CC!
And I'm Gigi!
And you're watching the Autofister Network!
T.A.N. The Autofister Network
[Title: T.A.N. The Autofister Network]
I don't know if that's gonna make us any money.
Well, on to the next idea!
みんなが大好きっ!!
Everyone's favorite...!!
延々続行ルララMiracle Sing Time
It's our never-ending lu-la-la Miracle Sing Time
歌って歌って愛伝える最強手段
I'll sing, I'll sing, it's the absolute best way to express my love!
つたない曲でも微妙な歌詞でも
Even if the composition is clumsy or the lyrics are iffy
届けたい精一杯のsoulを
I want to convey my soul with all I have!
Utauyo!! MIRACLE
Lyrics: Shouko Ohmori / Music: Tom-H@ck
[Song: Utauyo!! MIRACLE]
[Lyrics: Shouko Ohmori / Music: Tom-H@ck]
どうしようオートマティックに決められてる時間割じゃ
What can we do, we can't follow this time table
追っつかないの
That's been decided for us automatically
夢無限したいこと怒涛廊下もダッシュで集まるよ
Billowing waves of us infinite dreamers dash out and assemble in the hallway
お行儀悪かったらsorry!
Sorry if my manners are bad!
でもなりふりも構わずに
But don't mind how I look
どっぷりハマっちゃうplayキラリって もしやこれが青春
I'm totally addicted to playing; a sparkle, maybe this is what youth is
ever ever... Forever Shine
ほんとに大好きっ!!
I really love you!!
テンション上昇ルララPowerful Gig Time
It's a tension-rising lu-la-la Powerful Gig Time
ハートってハートってワクワク探す天才
My heart is, my heart is, an excitement-seeking genius
アレッ!?って言われても ミス連発でも
Even if I say "Huh!?" or start racking up misses
放ちたい湧いてくるbraveを
I want to set free my boiling bravery
しかけるトレモロ応えるフラム
On with the tremolo, followed by flam
いいじゃんいいじゃんノリノリでいいんじゃない
Ain't it awesome, ain't it awesome, ain't it awesome to feel so good
ハッピーはいつだってね"今"感じるもの
I'm always so happy, it's the way "now" feels
生きろ乙女本能で、裸の
Live on, fair maidens, with your bare instincts
みんなが大好きっ!!
Everyone's favorite...!!
延々続行ルララ Miracle Sing Time
It's our never-ending lu-la-la Miracle Sing Time
どうしてもホームワークよりも重要課題
No matter what, there's subjects more important than homework
放課後のお茶 おしゃべり 練習
It's our after school tea, chatting and practice
ユーモア ナチュラル めくるめく笑い
I get so much humor, feeling natural and dazzling smiles
ウケ過ぎてお腹痛い
It makes my stomach hurt from laughing so much
呼吸ぴったし excellent!
Our breathing was excellent!
でも苦手なリフまだあったの
But there were some riffs that weren't so good
特訓つきあってくれる?
Will you give me some special training?
も少し門限までだって帰りたくない
It's just about my curfew, but I don't wanna go home
never never... Can't Say Good-bye
めちゃめちゃ大好きっ!!
I love you so much!!
超絶ぞっこんルララ Wonderful Show Time
It's a totally awesome lu-la-la Wonderful Show Time
音楽って 音楽ってもう私達まんま
Music is, music is already so us!
スタンディングオベーション賞
Standing Ovation Award
オーディエンスなしでも奏でたい瞬間の real を
Even without an audience, we wanna play this moment for real
昨日の後悔って 明日の心配って
Yesterday's regrets, tomorrow's concerns
ぶっちゃけぶっちゃけ誰得? 何得?
Frankly, frankly, what good do they do? Who do they do good for?
ラッキーはいつだってね "今" つかみもの
I'm always so lucky, it's something I've grasped "now"
欲張れ乙女 与えられん、さらば
Be desirous, fair maidens, if it's not given to you, say farewell
どんな本も書いてない 授業じゃちょっと教わんないけど
It's not written in any book or taught even a bit in class
一生忘れない
But I'll never forget it for the rest of my life
この世にないと思ってた奇跡
A miracle I thought didn't exist in this world
一緒にね歌えば 信じられるんだ 強くなれるんだ
If we sing together, we can believe in it, we can become stronger
みんなが大好きっ!!
Everyone's favorite...!!
延々続行ルララ Miracle Sing Time
It's our never-ending lu-la-la Miracle Sing Time
歌って歌って愛伝える最強手段
I'll sing, I'll sing, it's the absolute best way to express my love!
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも届けたい
Even if the composition is clumsy or the lyrics are iffy, I want to deliver...
精一杯の soul 等身大の life を
I want to convey my soul with all I have, and my true-to-life self
今日は昨日みたい? 明日は今日みたい?
Is today like yesterday? Will tomorrow be like today?
大丈夫大丈夫 楽しかったら大正解
It's okay, it's okay! If we're having fun, it's the right answer!
ロッカーはいつだってね "今" やんちゃ盛り
Rocker is always in its prime 'now'
進め乙女 抱きしめて、希望を
Go forth, girls! Embrace your hopes!
大好き 大好き 大好きをありがとう
I love you, I love you, thank you for all the love
歌うよ 歌うよ 心こめて 今日も歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, with all my heart, I'll sing today too
大好き 大好き 大好きをありがとう
I love you, I love you, thank you for all the love
歌うよ 歌うよ 愛をこめて ずっと歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, with all my love, I'll sing forever
Please hold.
We will soon be changing the channel.
We are about to switch the channel.
Please wait.
The channels will be changed soon.
Please stay seated...
...as the channels are about to switch.
Don't change the channel...
...because we'll do it for you.
Do not touch the remote...
...because we will be doing it.