(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
TAN The Autofister Network 3D LIVE
[Title: TAN The Autofister Network 3D LIVE]
CCGG 劇場
[Title: CCGG Theater]
曖昧3センチ そりゃぷにってコトかい?
Three centimeters of ambiguity.
Does that mean it's squishy?
ちょっ!
Wait!
らっぴんぐが制服…だぁぁ不利ってこたない ぷ。
Wrapping in a school uniform...
It's not necessarily a disadvantage. Poo.
がんばっちゃ▼やっちゃっちゃ
Do your best, let's do it!
そんときゃーっち＆Release ぎョッ
Then catch & release. Gyo!
汗々(Fuu Fuu)の谷間に
In the valley of sweat (Fuu Fuu)...
Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
もってけ! セーラーふく
Lyrics: 畑 亜貴 Music: 神前 暁
[Song: Motteke! Sailor Fuku
Lyrics: Aki Hata, Music: Satoru Kosaki]
なんかダるー なんかデるー
Something's heavy, something's coming out.
あいしテるー あれ一個が違ってるんるー
I love you, but one thing is different-run-run.
なやみン坊ー 高鉄棒ー
Worried child, high horizontal bar...
おいしん簿ー いーかげんにシナサイ
Gourmet report... cut it out already!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
That guy who flew off, his flushing body...
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is supposedly an ordinary girl.
驚いたあたしだけ?
Was I the only one surprised?
豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだ
Pork bone, extra-firm noodles, another serving! Da da da!
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON cheerleading squad!
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
ハイ！アップ センセーション！
Hi! Up sensation!
ハイ！存在感 テンション アップ センセーション！
Hi! Presence, tension up sensation!
ぶつかって解きました 凡戦
Clashed and solved the mediocre fight,
大いに歌って チャレンジャー
sing out loud, challenger!
持っていけ 最後には笑っちゃうのは
Take it! The one who laughs in the end
私のはず セーラー服だからです
should be me, because I'm in a sailor uniform!
結論！
Conclusion!
月曜日なのに機嫌悪いのどうするよ
It's Monday, but why are you in such a bad mood?
夏服がいいのです かわいい
Summer clothes are good, they're cute.
制服がいいのです かわいい
The uniform is good, it's cute.
斬新 三振 生まれてチュッパ
Novel, strikeout, born to be chupa!
よん！がんばって！はききって！
Four! Do your best! Give it your all!
ハイ ダーリン ダーリン プリーズ！
Hi darling, darling please!
モリソバニ モリサヨニ コイサヨニ マダナイショニ
Next to forest, next to sand, next to love... keep it a secret!
甘えん坊 用心棒 通信簿 チョウシコイテ ギョクサイ！
Spoiled brat, bodyguard, report card... getting cocky, then shattered!
プレット あいての きょうりょく だい
Plate, your partner's cooperation is great,
おおげさ ちらり くらり はい！
exaggerated, peeking, dizzy, hi!
絶対残業 いっちょ なまえし
Absolute overtime, a little naming...
スルピガ オレダリ ダダダダダ！
[Rapid fire vocalization]
ボンボン もっとぜん レッツゴー パリシンデ
Bonbon, more zen, let's go Paris-nde!
ややい そらブス ワッツアップ テンション
Yayai, look at that... what's up tension!
おい！そうしちゃうぜん アルバイト
Oi! I'll do it all, part-time job.
探したら見つかって 当然 実践 丸つけ
If you look, you'll find it, naturally! Practice, checking off...
挑戦！
Challenge!
やってみろ 真剣に 狙っちゃうのは
Give it a try! The one aiming seriously
私の挑戦 制服着替えても
is my challenge, even if I change uniforms...
私！
It's me!
週末は土曜 ちら見せなんて
Weekends on Saturday, showing just a peek is
ありきたり 全部は簡単
so common, everything is easy.
世の中 厳しい！
The world is tough!
ウソ サメ 抱きついて 我慢だ ギュッ
Lies, shark, hug it and endure, squeeze!
胸ドキ マシドキ アンシュダイ
Heart pounding, pounding more, [vocalize]...
シュガシュガ スウィート！
Sugar sugar sweet!
ボンボン ボンボン レッツゴー ウッウッアッ
Bonbon, bonbon, let's go! Ooh ooh ah!
ラララ チョーチョーキッ ルックアップ フッハッハッ
La la la, very very ki! Look up! Fuh ha ha!
ハイ！エデュケーション ダヴィ エブリシング
Hi! Education, [vocalize] everything!
ウンダカダ ウンダカダ ヤヤ ハレテ モレテ キレナイ
Undakada, undakada, yay! Clear up, leak out, can't stop!
持っていけ 最後には笑っちゃうのは
Take it! The one who laughs in the end
私のはず セーラー服だからです
should be me, because I'm in a sailor uniform!
結論！
Conclusion!
月曜日なのに機嫌悪いのどうするよ
It's Monday, but why are you in such a bad mood?
夏服がいいのです かわいい
Summer clothes are good, they're cute.
やっぱり 最後には笑っちゃうのは
After all, the one who laughs in the end
私のはず セーラー服だからです
should be me, because I'm in a sailor uniform!
結論！
Conclusion!
あいまい サンセンチ スルプニ トコトカイ
Ambiguous 3cm, [vocalize]...
ワッ ラッピング ガ セイフク ヨシクリッテコトナイ
Wow, wrapping is uniform, [vocalize]...
ゴッ がんばっちゃ やっちゃっちゃ
Go! Do your best, do it, do it!
アトキャッ ボジャステハッ
[Vocalize]...
センセ センセ デキタラ ダーリン ダーリン アミューズ！
Teacher, teacher, if you can... darling, darling amuse!
TAN The Autofister Network 3D LIVE
[Title: TAN The Autofister Network 3D LIVE]
Now this is what I'm talking about!
That's what we need!
We need... we need another hit show!
We need an anime opening!
No, no, no, we need... no, we need a show!
We need... we need something with substance.
I just thought that our show was failing because we didn't have an anime opening.
No, our show was failing because it's really bad.
It's not that bad.
It's really bad! Have you seen the reviews?
They're wrong though.
It's called an opinion.
Oh, well, that's so complicated.
I didn't sign up for this. I'm just the eye candy.
Well, your eye candy isn't getting us any ratings.
Well, yours isn't either because there's none!
No, stop, stop, no one wants to see that. Stop.
We need an idea.
We can both sell ourselves out.
No, that's not gonna work. That's not enough.
I have an idea.
What?
We steal other people's concepts.
You're a genius!
We just make what's already popular...
but we make it ours.
Yeah, we'll put our name on it.
Yeah, we'll get all the credit.
What are they gonna do? Nothing!
We'll get all the funding back!
And then we can finally do what we're really passionate about.
Oh my god! Oh my god!
But we're gonna have to do so much research on what's popular.
What do we do? What do we do?
We need influencers! We need influencers!
We need... sexy ladies!
What?
And we... I guess we already have that.
I can look for it. Bennie... what else do we need?
We need a sell out.
We need to sell out. Ah... I'm so tired from all this thinking.
I think we need to explore other genres, Cecilia Emergreen.
Like what?
Every genre. I think that's the only way.
What?
Where are we? GG?
What is this? What is this? Are we... are we in my head?
Wait, are we in your head? Are we in my head?
This is just like fan fiction.
This is just like fan fiction! Does this mean we're going to steal people's ideas?
No, they're my ideas. We're in my head.
But this is my head! I'm going to steal your idea.
You can't steal my ideas. / I could!
Wait, what if... what if I see every single idea that's in your head and then I take them from you and then... I kill you?
You're taking my ideas! If you go too deep into my brain, you'll get to the yaoi part.
Oh, oh! Maybe we should start with my brain. It's okay, it's okay.
Wait, wait! What's in your brain? / Nothing.
Um, actually, there's a lot in my brain. For example...
Your brain is full of bad romance novels. We can't put that in our show!
Yeah we can! We can put it in our show! Yeah, let's put it in our show! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Romance... romance... romance.
I guess we need a break free out of this place.
DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL
[Text: Dropped Out of School Musical]
～とあるふたりの青春譚～ ある日、パーティーに参加したクロイとジブリエラ。バスケットボールが大好きなクロイと他の子とは何かが違う、ジブリエラ。
[Text: ~The Youthful Tale of a Certain Duo~ One day, Croy and Gibriella attended a party. Croy loves basketball, and Gibriella is a bit different from other girls...]
I don't want to sing. I'm just a normal boy.
I just want to play basketball with my friends and get my head in the game. I can't sing. I'm just Troy.
Get it together Gibriella. We don't have time for extracurriculars, we have to get into college.
I'm not like other girls, I just want to stay at home and read books.
ばかみたい 子供なのね
I'm like a fool, I'm just a child
夢を追って傷ついて
Chasing dreams and getting hurt
嘘が下手なくせに 笑えない笑顔みせた
Despite being a bad liar, you showed me a smile you couldn't laugh with
I love youも ろくに言わない
You won't even say "I love you" properly
口下手でほんまに不器用
You're bad with words and really clumsy
なのになのにどうして サヨナラは言えたの
Yet, yet, why were you able to say goodbye?
ダメだね ダメよダメなのよ
It's no good, it's no good, it's just no good
あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the liquor is
歪まない思い出が バカみたい
The memories that don't warp, it's like a fool
馬鹿みたい 本当バカね
It's like a fool, truly a fool
あんた信じるばかりで
Just believing in you
強い女のふり 切なさの夜風浴びる
Pretending to be a strong woman, bathed in the night wind of sadness
ばかみたい
[Song: Baka Mitai (Like a Fool)]
一人になって...
Since I became alone...
三年が過ぎ
three years have passed.
街並みさえも
Even the streets...
変わりました
have changed.
なのになのにどうして
Yet, yet why...
未練だけ置き去り
am I left with only regrets?
ほんまに ロクな男やない
You're really not a good man.
揃いの指輪 はずします
I'm taking off the matching ring.
ざまあみろ せいせいするわ
Screw you, I feel so free now.
いい加減 待ってても
Waiting around forever...
馬鹿みたい
is just foolish.
だめだね だめよ
It's no good, it's no good.
だめなのよ
It's just not right.
あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
I love you so much, too much.
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink is,
歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
these memories that won't fade are just foolish.
ほんまに ロクな男やない
You're really not a good man.
揃いの指輪 はずします
I'm taking off the matching ring.
ざまあみろ せいせいするわ
Screw you, I feel so free now.
なんなのよ
What's with...
この涙
these tears?
馬鹿みたい
It's just foolish.
Wow, yeah, yeah,
musicals are where it's at!
I think this could really be something.
This is gonna get us the big dollars.
Yeah, hopefully the Big Mouse is
not gonna shoot us in the head.
Ten billion dollars!
The Big Mouse?
Don't worry about it—ten billion dollars!
Yeah, it's really good.
We might need like a different type of show too,
you know? Just for variety...
...so they can't shut us down.
A variety show?
Like a variety game show?
The Autofister Games!
The Autofister... Physicals!
Physicals!
One hundred and five!
But first, a word from our sponsors.
Whoa! Slow down there, partner!
Hold your horses! Don't you think
you're scrolling a little too fast?
Yeah, put down the phone and full-screen
our video instead...
...because we are about to show you
the new hottest thing in town!
Introducing the... Autofister Network!
Get it? Because it's Autofister Network,
but this is our merch.
We wanted to take this opportunity to show you...
This is a tumble weed
[Caption: This is a tumbleweed]
...all of our cool fun merch before it goes live!
Cemimi Plushie Keychain (Cecilia Immergreen)
[Merch: Cemimi Plushie Keychain (Cecilia)]
We've got Semimi's!
Gimimi Plushie Keychain (Gigi Murin)
[Merch: Gimimi Plushie Keychain (Gigi)]
Gimimi's!
grem Friends Mascot Keychain
[Merch: grem Friends Mascot Keychain]
Grem's!
Otomo Friends Mascot Keychain
[Merch: Otomo Friends Mascot Keychain]
Otomo's!
Red Carpet CCGG Acrylic Diorama Stand
[Merch: Red Carpet CCGG Acrylic Diorama Stand]
And this neat acrylic stand of the both of us!
Yeah! And if you hurry up, you'll even be able to...
Set Purchase Bonus: Limited Edition
Autographed postcard
[Set Bonus: Limited Edition / Autographed Postcard]
...get the limited set with a card signed
by both of us!
Woohoo! It'll be live at this exact time,
so make sure to check it out then!
11:10AM JST / 4:10AM CEST / 7:10PM PDT
[Release Time: 11:10AM JST / 4:10AM CEST / 7:10PM PDT]
Coming soon! To a stream near you! Woohoo!
SHOW TIME / Physical Autofister
[Title: SHOW TIME - Physical Autofister]
And we're back from our commercial break!
Thanks to everyone for waiting!
Welcome back to the official...
Physical Autofister!
100!
And with us we have our lovely contestants,
Bae!
I'm Bae, I'm gonna win, ay!
Su-chan!
Su-chan's comfortable!
Towa-sama!
トワ様だ！
It's Towa-sama!
As I said before, we're here to find out who's the ultimate winner of
Physical Autofister
100!
Right before our commercial break, each contestant will have to compete in
our Physical Obstacle Course of Fun!
Fun!
If you're just now tuning in, here is a quick recap.
Everyone starts in a line.
You have to run to the other side while avoiding all obstacles
and do a quick little physical activity.
Grab a question from our dragon, who telepathically gives it to you in your brain.
Run back and answer the question.
Yeah!
We'll do four rounds and the person with the most points at the end
of four rounds is the winner!
Okay, well, everyone get into position.
As I said before, of course,
since a lot of these questions will be in English,
Bae has the handicap. She has the handicap.
Okay, very simple question.
What is this? Nice!
Okay, okay, okay, everyone in position?
Yes, yes. The first run,
the first round is you run over there
and five jumping jacks.
Five jacks! Okay!
Five jumping! Okay!
Five jumping jacks? これ？
Five jumping jacks? This?
走って、5ジャンプやって、質問取って、走って帰る。
Run, do 5 jumping jacks, take the question, and run back.
OKですか？ OK!
Is that OK? OK!
Three, two, one, GO!
1! 2! 3! 4! 5!
I was strained!
Please read the question out loud!
よいしょ...
Heave-ho...
Okay, um... I like...
Strawberry!
Yes! She had to name a fruit!
Name a fruit!
Fruit!
Strawberry!
One point for Su-chan!
You can give me your questions over here.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Well, next round.
Next round! Everyone ready?
No, no, no, wait, we have to complain.
Yeah, but is everyone ready for the next round?
ハンディだろう。
It's a handicap, right?
Ready, ready!
And you have to crab walk like this!
Crab walk like this!
Crab walk!
Come on!
What? Crab walk and
five squats.
5スクワット？ スクワット？
5 squats? Squats?
Crab walk and five squats?
Crab walk.
Wait, do they have to jump?
No, they can jump.
Jump!
Jump! They have to jump.
Okay, okay.
帰った時もこれ。
Even when returning, do this.
Okay, everyone ready?
Three, two, one, GO!
何だっけ？
What was it again?
1, 2, 3... それスクワットじゃねえ！
1, 2, 3... That's not a squat!
Okay.
Come on, I ripped... I ripped the mind telepathy paper.
Hey, you can't rip our telepathy paper!
13 times 6!
78!
Yes! Oh, she's kind of really good at math.
She's good at math! Wow!
またバナナなんだけど。
It's banana again.
2回連続バナナなんだけど。
It's banana two times in a row.
Two... two banana questions?
おい、日本語書いてんじゃねえか！
Hey, isn't it written in Japanese?!
What? I was given a handicap because the questions are in English,
they're written in Japanese!
Hey, but the questions are really... okay, okay.
We've got to keep it rolling, guys. Keep it rolling.
Do I still have to go around and around?
Yes, yes! Those are the rules by our producers, who are not us.
On my telepathy paper,
the next one is
Sexy Walk.
Sexy walk! Sexy walk!
Can we get disqualified? Do we have to start again if it's not sexy enough?
No. Yes.
はあ？ どっちかにしてよ。
What? Please make up your mind.
We'll see, we'll see.
And three push-ups.
Three!
腕立て3回。
Three push-ups.
And Sexy Walk.
Sexy walkね。
Sexy walk, right.
Okay, okay, okay. Sexy walk and sexy jump.
でセクシーさが足りなかったら万が一やり直しって言われてるから。
And I was told we might have to do it over if the sexiness isn't enough.
えー！ セクシーが足りない...
Whaaat! Not enough sexiness...
Sexy, sexy, sexy.
任せろ、任せろ。
Leave it to me, leave it to me.
セクシーしゅば！
Sexy Shuba!
セクシーしゅばー！
Sexy Shubaaa!
Okay, we will see. Everyone ready?
Okay, we'll see. Is everyone ready?
Okay! Ready!
Three, two, one, GO!
Sexy Bae!
You try but sexy!
You try to be sexy!
1, 2, 3!
いち、に、さん！
One, two, three!
いち、に、さん、しー！
One, two, three, four!
トワ様！
Towa-sama!
Oh! Sexy! Sexy, sexy!
It's my turn, yay!
It's my turn to take!
It's my turn to take it!
Oh, Sexy-chan!
あれ？ Sexy Bae?
Huh? Sexy Bae?
Hey, Sexy Bae! Sexy, sexy!
Do it again!
あれ？あれ？
Huh? Huh?
What? セクシーじゃない！
What? That's not sexy!
セクシーじゃない！もう一回！
That's not sexy! One more time!
You try running back step sexy!
Bae, you only have to do it on the way there. On the way back you can go straight.
No, no! Hey, hey, don't help the contestant!
Wait!
NAME A FLOWER!
えー...
Uh...
パンジー！
Pansy!
Oh yeah, Pansy!
知ってる？
Do you know it?
Oh yeah! Oh, よかった、正解！
Oh yeah! Oh, thank goodness, it's correct!
Nice Biboo! Okay!
One, one, one!
Wait, did you... have you been counting the points?
Yeah, 1-1-1!
Oh, really? 1-1-1!
Oh, tiebreaker! Tiebreaker!
Last round! Okay, okay!
最後のポイントは... Are you ready?
The final point is... Are you ready?
100 pointo! 100 points!
100 points! 100 points!
Last round!
Can I get rid of this? No!
Do this! You have to do this well. Okay!
LUNGE WALK!
きつい！やばい！
This is tough! Oh no!
And then... きた、きた、きた！
And then... Here it comes, here it comes!
さんかい！ Okay, okay!
Three times! Okay, okay!
How many times? さんかい！
How many times? Three times!
さん、さん、さん！さんかい！
Three, three, three! Three times!
And then さんかい！
And then three times!
Wow, you're so good! Wow!
Okay, 頑張ろう！頑張ろう！
Okay, let's do our best! Let's do our best!
わかりましたか？ Okay!
Do you understand? Okay!
OKです！わかりました！
It's OK! I understand!
しんどそうな顔... Me too, me too...
Such an exhausted face... Me too, me too...
Can I sue this? No! No, no, no!
Oh, part of it will get cut! Come on, come on!
They fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
They're fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Everyone! 頑張る！
Everyone! Do your best!
頑張れ everyone! Two!
Do your best, everyone! Two!
One, GO!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Get to the ground! ここどうするの？
Get to the ground! What do I do here?
よいしょ！よいしょ！ Hey, you aren't touching the ground!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Hey, you aren't touching the ground!
Towa-sama's fine, she's doing her best! 1, 2! 2! 3!
うわー、 disqualification! Disqualified!
Whoa, disqualification! Disqualified!
Okay, okay! よいしょ！よいしょ！
Okay, okay! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
よいしょ！よいしょ！よいしょ！
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Towa-sama! Shuba-sama!
Wait, let's wait for Bae to come back. Oh, Bae, come on!
Come on, Bae! We can answer!
Come on Bae, we can't decide the winner until you get over here!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, you need to high five! Hey, squad over here!
Come on, come on! Whoa! Alright, here's your question!
SAY A FRENCH WORD!
Oh! えーっと待って...
Oh! Uh, wait...
French, French, French...
知っていますかね...
I wonder if I know any...
Bonjour!
Oh! OK! Yay!
The winner! The winner!
A winner! A winner today!
やったー！勝った！気持ちええじゃないかよ！はぁー！
I did it! I won! This feels great, doesn't it?! Haa!
Well, looks like the contestants have something to complain about no matter what we do. Yeah, we did our best.
Well they should try to do the last... the last was like insane. やってみなよ、やってみて、一週！
Well they should try to do the last... the last was like insane. You should try it, try one lap!
一週回って、結構広いよ！
Going around once, it's quite a wide area!
No, no, no, no! Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Bae, Bae only! Bae only! Bae only!
Just... Security! Security!
Yeah, security! Security! Towa, I got her! Security!
Can I give a winner a crown? Your crown! Yay!
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, thank you! You're gonna have to leave!
This is unfair! Please leave!
Quick, heartbreak! Heartbreak! Heartbreak!
NO SIGNAL
PLEASE STAND BY
しばらくお待ちください
NO SIGNAL
PLEASE STAND BY
[Please wait a moment]
This is Bae!
This is Sue!
This is Towa-sama!
And you're watching the Autofist Network!
The rat sucked.
Yeah, she should go back... should go back to the gym or something.
She should go back to school and retake P.E.
Yeah, but Towa-sama was really strong. Wow, she even got the cool crown! Amazing!
And Sue was so cute!
So cute! / So cute!
Also the host was amazing. / Really charismatic.
The host was so beautiful.
Every time they were on the screen I was electrified.
I think this is what's gonna get us the funding.
Yeah, I think we're going to get 10 million dollars for this one.
And the more budget they have, the more difficult the challenges can get...
...and then the death, you know, penalty...
...can be even greater.
Anyways, what if...
...anime...
...but live action?
I don't feel so good.
Ah! Ah! Ah! (screaming)
I'm so tired, Gigi.
Me too! I am so tired because I've been working so hard.
We've been working so hard, we've been making so many shows. I'm so sleepy.
As I have recorded in the studio every single day!
I deserve a tea party.
If only someone were to invite me to their tea party.
You know what? Actually, I have been preparing something.
Is it this background?
Yes! This really realistic background that you probably stole from the internet.
I stole it, I stole it.
It was right from the internet.
Yep! And this is my tea party, so welcome in!
It's... but I have one more surprise, Gigi Murin.
You have a surprise for the tea party?
Where's our models? Where's me? Where's me?
You know what? We got some graphics update.
Graphics update?
You want to see? You want to see?
I want to see me! Yeah, yeah, yeah! It's me!
Cecilia Immergreen from Hololive English Justice!
Spin!
You look great!
Oh thanks! You look freaking amazing!
I guess I'll go sit down real quick.
Oh my god! I look so good. Look at my shoes!
You look so good!
Hey Gigi, come on in. It's okay.
I get one too?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Gigi Murin, everyone!
It's Gigi Murin from Hololive English Justice!
I am so happy to be here.
Wow, you look great too!
I look great! I guess it's time for me to sit down also.
Look at my shoes too.
Wow! Wow! Wow!
Those look good.
Those look kind of hard to walk in actually, that's crazy.
No, I'm a natural. Let me sit down.
Sit down, sit down, sit down already.
And together we are...
Autofist!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Finally we get some time to relax.
Wow, you look really good.
Thanks, you look really good too.
Are we hugging again?
I just can't, I just really like hugging you. I can't help that I keep hugging you.
Really like hugging, I guess. Oh, my hood came off. It's fine.
I'm so excited! So excited!
I'm really happy to be here. Oh, are you hungry?
I'm really hungry. Will you feed me?
Okay, I'll feed you, I'll feed you.
Say ah.
Ah... oh, I accidentally dropped it!
Wait, oh, I'm really hungry too. I guess I should...
Oh my god! I'm... you're getting this all over me!
It's getting really messy.
Oh, why is it getting on your face too?
It tastes really good.
Let me feed you again.
Do you mind if I got my spit on it? You don't mind, do you?
Wait, wait, let me wipe that off.
You got something on the side of your mouth.
Let me just get that for you.
Are you so... let me get it off of you too.
Oh, you have something on your mouth.
Okay, that's enough, that's enough.
Thirsty?
I'm thirsty. I'm really thirsty.
Okay, I'll pour you some tea.
I'm really excited.
Here's your tea.
It's really hot!
Oh, be careful, be careful.
Oh my god, it's really hot!
Oh, I spilled it on myself!
Oh god, oh it's all over my body!
Oh no, you spilled it!
Oh my god! It burns!
あつい! あつい!
It's hot! It's hot!
Oh my god, oh... I feel like I got a third-degree burn just now.
Why did you do that to me? You pushed me!
I'm sorry! Let me blow on it. Let me wipe it off of you.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that. I just got really overzealous.
But it's really good now it's cooled down.
You like it? What type of tea is it?
It's like a note, a little floral note on it.
Here, try some. Try from my finger.
How does it taste?
Yummy!
That's really good.
Okay, okay, that's enough.
I finished my cup. It was really delicious.
You know, if Liz was here, she would tell us that after having a really good meal...
...we should work out.
Oh yeah, we should work out.
Let's get up.
Let's go stand over there in this corner.
Let's stand by the horse.
That horse is really amazing.
Oh, you're making so much noise!
Sorry, my... my shoes are just really big and clunky.
You know what? I think it'd be really cool if we were to do 50 push-ups right now.
I... I want to do... You know what? I want to do 50...
I want to do 50 push-ups.
Me, I really want... no no no...
I really want... I really want to do 50 push-ups.
Okay okay wait. I changed my mind.
What, you changed your mind?
I want... I want... 50 lunges.
50 lunges?
Oh oh your... Oh your knee hurts?
Oh... oh... Oh thank... yeah, I got into an accident... about 200 years ago.
Did you get hit by a car?
I got hit by a car 200 years ago.
Okay... I guess that's just how it is.
You know what? Chichi-moring...
Don't touch me!
Stop touching me!
What? Oh my god, you're always doing this!
Ah! Why are you always fighting with me?
Like this! Ah! You're such an upstart!
No, I'm not gonna... I hate you! I hate you! I hate you so much!
I'll take your hair!
Hey hey hey hey hey...
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry... I got... sorry, I was getting mean. I was acting out.
Will you forgive me?
I guess so.
I'm sorry for yelling...
I'm sorry for yelling at you. I didn't mean to.
Can you kiss my knee please?
I guess... oh, I feel really good now.
Do you feel better?
I feel better.
And I feel really sleepy all of a sudden.
Me too actually. Oh, so sleepy... I'm so sleepy.
Oh, but there's only one bed. What should we do?
Should we get in together?
I guess so... I guess we'll get into... let me just take off my shoes.
Oh yeah, I think it'd be really, really weird to get into bed with shoes on.
Yeah, that would be strange.
But let me help you. Let me fluff this pillow for you.
Oh, you look so... here you go, princess.
Oh, let me get into bed too. I'll take my shoes off too.
I'm already getting so comfortable. Please, please don't go to bed without me!
Oh, I'm so tired... If someone doesn't get into bed quick, I'm just gonna fall asleep without you.
Oh, no don't, don't, don't! It's just my... my achy-achy bones! I'm trying to get into bed, please!
I guess your knee really hurts still.
It does. Ah... I feel so comfortable.
Thanks for coming to my tea party, Chichi-moring.
Thanks for inviting me, CC. Let's hold hands... oh, we're holding hands.
It's because I get scared in the dark.
Oh of course, yeah.
So I'm glad that we have each other. Goodnight, CC.
Goodnight, Chichi.
I'm CC!
And I'm Chichi!
And you're watching... The Autofister Network!
T.A.N The Autofister Network
[Logo: T.A.N The Autofister Network]
Um... hmm...
I don't know if that's gonna make us any money.
Well... on to the next idea.
みんなが大好きっ！！
Everyone's favorite...!!
延々続行 ルララ Miracle Sing Time
It's our never-ending lu-la-la Miracle Sing Time
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
I'll sing, I'll sing, it's the absolute best way to express my love!
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even if the composition is clumsy or the lyrics are iffy
届けたい 精一杯のsoulを
I want to convey my soul with all I have!
Utauyo!! MIRACLE
[Song: Utauyo!! MIRACLE / Lyrics: Shoko Omori / Music: Tom-H@ck]
どうしようオートマティックに決められてる
What can we do, we can't follow this time table
時間割じゃ追っつかないの
That's been decided for us automatically
夢無限したいこと怒涛 廊下もダッシュで集まるよ
Billowing waves of us infinite dreamers dash out and assemble in the hallway
お行儀悪かったらsorry!でもなりふりも構わずに
Sorry if my manners are bad! But don't mind how I look
どっぷりハマっちゃうplayキラリって もしやこれが青春
I'm totally addicted to playing; a sparkle, maybe this is what youth is
ever ever・・・Forever Shine
ever ever... Forever shine
ほんとに大好きっ！！
I really love you!!
テンション上昇 ルララ Powerful Gig Time
It's a tension-rising lu-la-la Powerful Gig Time
ハートって ハートって ワクワク探す天才
My heart is, my heart is, an excitement-seeking genius
アレッ！？って言われても ミス連発でも
Even if I say "Huh!?" or start racking up misses
放ちたい 湧いてくるbraveを
I want to set free my boiling bravery
しかけるトレモロ 応えるフラム
On with the tremolo, followed by flam
いいじゃん いいじゃん ノリノリでいいんじゃない
Ain't it awesome, ain't it awesome, ain't it awesome to feel so good
みんながだいすき!!
I love you all!!
えねんぞっこうるらら miracle sing time
It’s our never-ending lu-la-la Miracle Sing Time
うたってうたってあいつたえるさいきょうしゅだん
I’ll sing, I’ll sing, it’s the absolute best way to express my love!
つたないきょくでもびみょうなかしでも
Even if the composition is clumsy or the lyrics are iffy
とどけたいせいぱいのsoulを
I want to convey my soul with all I have!
どんなほんもかいてないじゅぎょうじゃちょっとおそわんない
It’s not written in any book or taught even a bit in class
けどいっしょうわすれない
But I'll never forget it for the rest of my life
このよにないとおもってたきせきいっしょにねうたえば
If we sing together this miracle I thought didn't exist in this world
しんじられるんだつよくなれるんだ
I can believe, I can become strong
みんながだいすき
I love you all!!
えねんぞっこうるらら miracle sing time
It’s our never-ending lu-la-la Miracle Sing Time
うたってうたってあいつたえるさいきょうしゅだん
I’ll sing, I’ll sing, it’s the absolute best way to express my love!
つたないきょくでもびみょうなかしでも
Even if the composition is clumsy or the lyrics are iffy
とどけらいせいぱいのsoulとうしんだいのlifeを
I want to convey my soul and my life as it is!
きょうはきのうみたい？あしたはきょうみたい
Is today like yesterday? Is tomorrow like today?
だいじょうぶだいじょうぶたのしかったらだいせいかい
It’s okay, it’s okay, if it was fun then it’s a great success!
ろっかーはいつだってね「いま」やんちゃさかり
Lockers are always full of mischief "now"
すすめおとめだきしめて、きぼうを
Go forth, fair maidens, and embrace hope!
だいすきだいすきだいすきをありがとう
Thank you for all the love, love, love!
うたうようたうよこころこめてきょうもうたうよ
I’ll sing, I’ll sing, I’ll sing today as well with all my heart!
だいすきだいすきだいすきをありがとう
Thank you for all the love, love, love!
うたうようたうよあいをこめてずっとうたうよ
I’ll sing, I’ll sing, I’ll always sing with all my love!
Please hold.
We will soon be changing the channel.
We are about to switch the channel.
Please wait.
The channels will be changed soon.
Please stay seated.
As the channels are about to switch.
Don't change the channel.
Because we'll do it for you.
Do not touch the remote.
Because we will be doing it.