(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Dead Beats
Three
Two
One
Hello, Dead Beats!
Welcome to my birthday 3D karaoke!
I'm so glad you could join me!
Are you guys ready for this?
Let's do it!
Happy birthday to me!
Alright!
I'm a reaper, soul-taker, hell-raiser
I'm a non-believer, non-achiever, soul-bleeder
But the reaper, soul-searcher, hell-dweller
I'm a believer, overachiever, soul-leader
I'm a reaper, soul-taker, hell-raiser
I'm a non-believer, non-achiever, soul-bleeder
But the reaper, soul-searcher, hell-dweller
I'm a believer, overachiever, soul-leader
Happy birthday to me!
Whoo!
Hello everyone!
Welcome to my birthday 3D!
Thank you all for coming!
I'm so glad to finally be here
in 3D for my birthday!
It's been a long time coming, hasn't it?
We have a lot of fun songs planned for today.
So I hope you're ready to party!
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Alright, let's get into
the first real song of the night!
This one is a classic.
熱くなれ / 大黒摩季
Atsuku Nare / Maki Ohguro
熱くなれ
Feel the heat!
砂漠の真ん中で
In the middle of the desert
熱くなれ
Feel the heat!
真実を見つめて
Stare into the truth
冷めたハートじゃ
With a cold heart
愛せやしない
You can't love
この街の　人ごみにまぎれて
Lost in the crowds of this city
さまよえば　誰もが　孤独だね
If you wander, everyone is lonely, aren't they?
愛されたい　ただそれだけなのに
I just want to be loved, and yet...
不器用な自分に　苛立つよ
I get frustrated with my own clumsiness
夢を追いかける　背中を追いかけて
Chasing after the back of someone chasing a dream
気付けば　明日さえ　見失う
Before I know it, I've even lost sight of tomorrow
だけど　あきらめたくない
But I don't want to give up
まだ　あきらめたくない
I don't want to give up just yet
熱くなれ
Feel the heat!
砂漠の真ん中で
In the middle of the desert
熱くなれ
Feel the heat!
真実を見つめて
Stare into the truth
冷めたハートじゃ
With a cold heart
愛せやしない
You can't love
You can be free!
Believe in yourself!
Alright!
How are you guys doing out there?!
Are you feeling the heat?!
Whoo!
Let's keep it going!
あっ！聞こえますか？
Ah! Can you hear me?
聞こえますか！？
Can you hear me!?
えっ、Hello, are we live?
Eh, hello, are we live?
Yeah! Let's go, Gaikotsu-chan!
Yeah! Let's go, Skeleton-chan!
Everybody hi! It's my birthday, it's my birthday!
We're live! やった！
Okay, I'm- I'm seeing the chat now. We're live!
We're live! Yay!
Yeah, yay! Sorry for the little delay.
Everybody, Gaikotsu-chan is here to celebrate!
Everybody, Skeleton-chan is here to celebrate!
Unlucky Deadbeats, Gaikotsu-chan!
Kawaii, kawaii Gaikotsu-chan daisuki! Yeah!
Unlucky Deadbeats, Skeleton-chan!
I love cute, cute Skeleton-chan! Yeah!
寂しくないよ、寂しくないよ。
ガイコツちゃんいるからだ！
I'm not lonely, I'm not lonely.
Because Skeleton-chan is here!
Yeah, 超かわいいね。
Yeah, so cute.
Because, because my skeleton friend is here.
I don't feel alone. But, I also don't feel alone
because you guys, you guys are here with me!
Welcome, welcome to my karaoke room!
Check it out! It's made for me.
It's all made for me.
Bust it down, bust it down, bust it down,
bust it down, bust it down, bust it down!
Sorry, sorry, I'm really happy!
I'm happy because guess what everyone?
I'm officially No years old!
相変わらずね。
As always, right.
Yes, that's right. Happy Birthday everyone!
I'm reading the comments too.
Cute, cute. Thank you so much!
You guys like the balloons?
Balloons! 風船もあるね。
Balloons! There are balloons too.
そう、かわいいね。スカルみたいなやつも...
Yeah, it's cute. There's also one that looks like a skull...
あるから、ほら見て。最高ね。可愛いよ。
So look. It's the best. It's cute.
Happy Birthday Mori. Thank you so much!
You guys want to sing some songs?
We're in a karaoke booth, right?
So let's sing some songs!
I prepared a lot of songs today.
There are quite a few new ones too.
So get excited! みんな、ワクワクしてる！？
So get excited! Everyone, are you excited!?
ワクワクしてる！？
Are you excited!?
ガイコツちゃんもワクワクしてるよね。
Skeleton-chan is excited too, right.
Yeah, let's go Mr. Bones! Mr. Bones!
Bust it down Mr. Bones! Bust it down Mr. Bones!
No, it's okay. You guys...
You'll also see Gaikotsu-kun is a really good dancer.
Get ready, waku-waku?
Get ready, are you excited?
わくわくね？ね、ガイコツちゃん。
Exciting, right? Right, Gaikotsu-chan?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
あ、すごい。
Ah, amazing.
でも何か元気すぎるからちょっと...
But I'm a bit too energetic, so...
すぐにヘトヘトになっちゃうから...
I'll get exhausted right away...
ちょっと落ち着きます。
I'll calm down a bit.
は、はい。じゃあ、曲歌いましょう。
Ha, alright. Well then, let's sing a song.
Let's sing songs. You guys ready?
誰もが皆知ってる
Everyone knows it
消せやしない傷を
The scars that won't fade
どれくらい続くの?
How long will it last?
もういらないよ
I don't need it anymore
誰もが皆待ってる
Everyone is waiting
争いのない日々を
For days without conflict
戦場の兵士たち
Soldiers on the battlefield
思い出してよ
Remember
今母の温もりを
A mother's warmth now
この果てしなく広い世界に
In this endlessly wide world
自分だけの地図描いて
Drawing a map of your own
涙こらえて僕らは
Holding back tears, we
歩いてゆこう
Will walk on
立ち上がれ今ほら何度でも
Rise up now, as many times as it takes
眠れる獅子呼び起こして
Wake the sleeping lion
生きてゆくんだ
We'll live on
明日へ
Toward tomorrow
誰もが皆待ってる
Everyone is waiting
ひと欠片の愛を
For a tiny piece of love
憎んでも
Even if you hate
何ひとつ生まれないんだよ
Nothing will ever be born
そんなのも思い出してよ
Remember that too
この限りある時間の中で
In this limited time
まだ見ぬ楽園目指して
Aiming for a paradise yet unseen
どこまでだって僕らは歩いてゆこう
We'll walk as far as it takes
振り向かないで前だけを見て
Don't look back, just look forward
その身体朽ち果てるまで
Until that body decays
生きてゆくんだ
We'll live on
未来へ
Toward the future
Dako-chan, dance!
かわいい！
Kawaii!
かわいいね！いいね！
So cute! Nice!
思い出してよ
Remember
今母の温もりを
A mother's warmth now
この果てしなく広い世界の
In this endlessly wide world
まだ見ぬ楽園目指して
Aiming for a paradise yet unseen
どこまでだって僕らは歩いてゆこう
We'll walk as far as it takes
振り向かないで前だけを見て
Don't look back, just look forward
生きてゆくんだ
We'll live on
未来へ
Toward the future
Thank you.
Kawaii!
All right, let's do...
Let's sing something unexpected next.
『アイデン貞メルトダウン』
えなこ feat. P丸様。
Identity Meltdown
Enako feat. P-Maru-sama.
Woo!
アリ！？ナシ！？ナシ！？アリ！？
Yes!? No!? No!? Yes!?
どっち？どっち？
Which? Which?
アリ？ナシ？
Is it? Isn't it?
ナシ？アリ！？
No? Yes!?
ついてる ついてない あれどっち？どっち？
Lucky, unlucky, which one is it? Which?
アリ ナシ ナシ アリ
Yes, no, no, yes
自我が崩壊！
The ego is crumbling!
インドア系肥大した繊細な脳だ
An indoor-type, swollen, delicate brain
（バイバイ alright！ 一級在宅 allday！）
(Bye-bye alright! First-class stay-at-home all day!)
やる気のヤの字 どこに行っちゃったんだ
Where did the first letter of 'motivation' go?
（アイナイ 心技体 実家帰ります わーっ）
(Unseen soul and body, I'm going home, waa!)
ああ 未知なる世界と目が合ったよ
Ah, I've locked eyes with an unknown world
微笑んで 手招きしてるの
Smiling and beckoning to me
ねえ こっちの水はスウィーツパラダイス
Hey, the water over here is a sweets paradise
おしゃれ メイク ヘアアレンジ
Fashion, makeup, hair arrangements
乙女のその手 ダンスした
That maiden's hand danced
あれ わたし 誰 オレ お？
Wait, who am I? Me? Oh?
知らない 何 壊れそうなアイデンティティ
I don't know anything, a crumbling identity
生まれたばかり a sense of wonder
A newly born sense of wonder
そのまま maybe 溶けてゆく 深層心理
Just like that, maybe, melting away, deep psychology
目覚め たまえ 眠れるアイツ
Please wake up, that sleeping guy
いくとこまで いってみようか ハッピーエンド
Let's go as far as we can go, a happy ending
アリ？ナシ？
Is it? Isn't it?
ナシ？アリ！？
No? Yes!?
ついてる ついてない あれどっち？どっち？
Lucky, unlucky, which one is it? Which?
アリ ナシ ナシ アリ
Yes, no, no, yes
自我が崩壊！
The ego is crumbling!
お散歩調査隊 瀕死でおかえり
The walk investigation team, welcome back near death
（fall down！三流散策 weekend！）
(fall down! Third-rate stroll weekend!)
やる気を出した 結果が大変だった
I got motivated, but the results were a disaster
（実体 バイバイ いっせーの わーっ）
(Entities, bye-bye, all together now, waa!)
ああ マジカルウルトラ スーパーミラクル
Ah, magical ultra super miracle
抱きしめて 慰めてくれよ
Hold me, comfort me
ええ そんなの 夢さ ドリームワンダーランド
Yeah, that's just a dream, dream wonderland
地道 努力 コツコツ 正論マンガがパンチした
Steady, hard work, step by step, a logical manga punched me
やれ右！右！左！右！
Go right! Right! Left! Right!
いらない 愛 つよがりなアイデンティティ
No need for love, a bluffing identity
素直になりなさい catch on fire
Be honest with yourself, catch on fire
わがまま baby 溶けてゆく 固定観念
Selfish baby, melting away, fixed concepts
震え たまえ 内なる獣
Please tremble, the inner beast
自分自身を知るための 決闘だ
It's a duel to know yourself
ヘイヘイ！
Hey hey!
Check one, two
Mori Calliope! 超可愛いよ、可愛いよ！
Mori Calliope! So cute, so cute!
白か黒かで決めたい ゼロか100しかないの？（極論！）
Want to decide in black and white, is it only 0 or 100? (Extreme!)
生きづらいぞ クソったれだわ（諸行無常！）
It's hard to live, damn it! (Impermanence!)
神様 仏様 この私めに お導きを...（それでいいのか）
God, Buddha, please guide me... (Is that okay?)
YES! NO!
アイデンティティよ 目を覚ませ！
Identity, wake up!
知りたい どこへ行く 自意識
I want to know, where is my self-consciousness going?
ゆりかご 揺らされて どろんこごっこ
Rocked in a cradle, playing in the mud
このまま 永遠に 消えてゆく 世界の端っこ
Just like this, forever disappearing at the edge of the world
掴み もがいた
I grabbed and struggled
知らない 何 壊れそうなアイデンティティ
I don't know anything, a crumbling identity
生まれたばかり a sense of wonder
A newly born sense of wonder
そのまま maybe 溶けてゆく 深層心理
Just like that, maybe, melting away, deep psychology
目覚め たまえ 眠れるアイツ
Please wake up, that sleeping guy
自分自身を知るための 旅路
A journey to know yourself
ひとりのようで ひとりじゃなかった
Seemed alone, but wasn't alone
観測上で 成り立つ 存在X
Existence X that exists on observation
研究対象です
It's a research subject
アリ ナシ ナシ アリ
Yes, no, no, yes
ついてる ついてない あれどっち？どっち？
Lucky, unlucky, which one is it? Which?
アリ ナシ ナシ アリ
Yes, no, no, yes
自我が 自我が アイデンティティは崩壊中！
My ego, my ego, identity is collapsing!
デモン！
Demon!
Yeah!
I did my own backing vocals, you guys. Did you like them?
I shouldn't dance so much while singing...
Arigatou. Unexpected, ne?
Thank you. Unexpected, right?
I freaking love that anime. Anyway...
Oh, I think we have a guest?
Do we have a guest here?
Eh?
誰か？
Who is it?
Oh my God!
Whoa!
Happy Birthday to you...
ちょっと、ちょっと
Wait, wait
あ、忘れ物をしました！社長、お待ちください！
Ah, I forgot something! Boss, please wait a moment!
はい、はい
Okay, okay
Happy Birthday to you...
すげー！
Awesome!
Happy Birthday to you...
Happy Birthday dear カリ先輩...
Happy Birthday dear Calli-senpai...
モービー！サンキュー！サンキュー！
Morry! Thank you! Thank you!
Happy Birthday to you...
Me! That's so nice!
素敵なケーキ！ありがとうございます！
Wonderful cake! Thank you very much!
ヤミーヤミーケーキを持ってきました。
I brought a yummy yummy cake.
食べたーい！食べたーい！
I want to eat it! I want to eat it!
可愛いでしょ？
Isn't it cute?
すげー！
Amazing!
カリオペ先輩仕様スペシャルは...
This Calliope-senpai special version...
Wow, many special details.
すごーい、めっちゃ素敵。ありがとう。
Amazing, it's so wonderful. Thank you.
今食べますか？
Shall we eat it now?
あーどうかなー、まあ実は...
Ah, I don't know, well actually...
なんかライブ中...
During a live...
...あまり食べたくないね、たぶん。後で。
...I don't really want to eat, probably. Later.
じゃあ後で食べましょうね、一緒に。ね？
Then let's eat it later together, okay?
ねー！じゃあちょっと...
Yeah! Then for now...
置いときますんで、後で食べてください。
I'll put it over here, please eat it later.
めっちゃうまそう。すごい。
It looks delicious. Amazing.
じゃあこちらに。
Then, over here.
はい。
Yes.
いいね。めちゃめちゃ最高。ありがとう。
Nice. It's the best. Thank you.
Thank you for inviting me.
いえいえ、めちゃ嬉しいルイちゃん。
No no, I'm so happy Lui-chan.
本当に一緒に歌いたかったからね。
I really wanted to sing with you.
Happy Birthday today!
Thank you so much.
Congratulations, you are real birthday.
Congratulations, it's your real birthday.
Yes, that's right. That's right.
みんなね、すごいみんなめちゃめちゃワクワクしてるね。
Everyone is really, really excited.
嬉しい。
I'm happy.
はぁ〜はい。
Phew... yes.
すごい。
Amazing.
めちゃ熱かった、なんか外まで聞こえてましたよ。
It was so hot, I could hear it from outside.
そうだね。あ、ほら見て、あの骸骨くん、骸骨ちゃん？
Right. Oh, look, that skeleton-kun, skeleton-chan?
あ、初めまして。
Oh, nice to meet you.
可愛いね。
Cute.
Nice to meet you.
めっちゃ可愛いです。
Very cute.
Nice to meet you.
そう、踊りがめちゃ上手いよ。
Yes, they're really good at dancing.
じゃあ私も一緒に踊ります。
Then I'll dance too.
いいね、いいね、素敵、素敵。
Good, good, wonderful, wonderful.
Rolling, rolling. Rolling, rolling...
いいね、ちょっとセクシーすぎる。あ、
Nice, a bit too sexy. Ah,
いやー見えない見えない、ちょっと待って。
No, I can't look, wait a second.
いや無理無理無理。カリオペ無理よ。恥ずかしすぎる。
No, no, no. Calliope, I can't. It's too embarrassing.
なんかね、今日はあの、めちゃ低い曲、歌いたかったけど、
Well, today, I wanted to sing a very low song,
ホロライブで誰が低い声で歌えるかなと思って、
And I wondered who in Hololive could sing with a low voice,
あのルイちゃん、確かにルイちゃん。
And Lui-chan, definitely Lui-chan.
Voice is so low, yeah.
JPメンバーの中で一番低いですからね、声が。
Among the JP members, her voice is the lowest.
That's right. Yeah, yeah...
I decided to ask Lui to come sing with me...
...because I wanted to sing a really low song.
And she has the lowest voice I know in Hololive...
...aside from Towa-senpai who I'll have to do next time.
But I love Lui's voice.
あ、そうそうそう。あ、少々お待ちくださいね。
Ah, yes yes yes. Ah, please wait a moment.
Please wait a moment. Oh, you need a mic.
そうだね、座りましょう。
Right, let's sit down.
You need a mic.
Oh my God, ちょっと忘れちゃったね。
Oh my God, I kind of forgot.
Oh my God.
Okay, we gotta switch mics for a second.
可愛い。みんな可愛い。可愛くない？可愛い。
Cute. Everyone's cute. Aren't they cute? Cute.
チャットのデッドビーツのみんなも超可愛いね。
The Dead Beats in chat are super cute too.
Thank you.
Wonderful. Well, let's sing, yeah?
うん、はい。
Yeah, yes.
Alright, I have a good song. Enjoy.
Exciting. What do you think it is, chat?
骸骨ちゃんも一緒にダンスしてくださいね。
Skeleton-chan, please dance with us too.
What are we singing? Oh well, let's see.
歌いましょう。BLOODY STREAM!
Let's sing. BLOODY STREAM!
BLOODY STREAM / Coda
静寂の底から
From the depths of silence
目覚めるその柱たち
Those pillars awaken
時を越え
Transcending time
真紅の血潮が
The deep crimson blood
立ち上がる勇気を
The courage to stand up
引き合わせる
Brings them together
受け継ぐ愛を
Inherited love
宿命と呼ぶなら
If you call it fate
微笑む目で
With a smiling eye
次の手を
The next move
闇を欺いて 刹那をかわして
Deceive the darkness, dodge the moment
刃すり抜け奴らの隙を突け
Slip through the blades, strike their openings
つらぬいた思いが 未来を拓く
Piercing thoughts open up the future
Like a Bloody Storm, 熱く Like a Bloody Stone
Like a Bloody Storm, hot Like a Bloody Stone
血脈に刻まれた因縁に
In the fate carved into the lineage
浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
The bond of pride emerges and won't fade
握りしめて
Grip it tight
素敵！
Wonderful!
めちゃ最高！
It's the best!
骸骨ちゃんこっち来て！
Skeleton-chan, come over here!
ダンス、ダンス、ダンス！
Dance, dance, dance!
可愛い！
Cute!
すごい！
Amazing!
チャットのみんなもすごいワクワクしてるね。
Everyone in chat is really excited too.
こんな素敵な曲歌ってるからね。
Because we're singing such a wonderful song.
Yeah!
JoJo!
Go, Lui!
漲る力に
With overflowing power
打ち付ける鼓動は証
My pounding heartbeat is proof
友の声
Of my friend's voice
Woo! Woo!
滲んだ痛みと
With the blurred pain
今生き抜く意味を交わしながら
While exchanging the meaning of surviving now
Calli! Yeah!
おまえの意志が
Your will
夜明けを導く
Shall lead the dawn
まばゆいほどに気高く
So dazzlingly noble
Yeah!
光射す丘へ灼熱の空へ
To the hill where the light shines, to the scorching sky
魂がぶつかり合う旅路へ
To the journey where souls collide
悲しみに塗られた未来を救え
Save the future coated in sadness
Like a Bloody Soul 燃やせ Like a Bloody Star
Like a Bloody Soul, burn it up! Like a Bloody Star
炎裂き風を断ちその先へ
Tearing through flames, cutting through the wind, beyond that
怖れずに何も留まらずに進め
Without fear, without stopping for anything, move forward
流れの中
In the flow
共鳴する
Resonating
運命の波紋
The ripples of fate
心に...
In my heart...
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, come on!
闇を欺いて切なをかわして
Deceive the darkness, dodging the moment
刃すり抜け奴らの隙を突け
Slipping through the blades, strike their openings
貫いた思いが未来を拓く
The piercing feelings will open up the future
Like a Bloody Storm 熱く Like a Bloody Storm
Like a Bloody Storm, passionately Like a Bloody Storm
血脈に刻まれた因縁に
In the destiny carved into the lineage
浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
Rising up, the bonds of pride that will never fade
握りしめて
Grip it tight
Woo! JoJo!
いいねー、ジョジョポーズ！
Yeah!
Nice JoJo pose!
素敵！
Perfect!
Lovely!
いや、やっぱりめちゃめちゃ上手かった！
いやいやいや。
Man, you were really good after all!
No, no, no.
いや、でも今日2回目...
Two times, second time is 3D collaboration!
But this is our second 3D collab today...
...の3Dコラボだもんね。
...right?
そうだね。First time is いじめっ子 Bully.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right. The first time was the 'Bully' collab.
超楽しかった！
It was super fun!
いや楽しかった、今日はお呼びいただきましてありがとうございました。
It was fun, thank you so much for inviting me today.
いえいえ、こちらこそ！超楽しかった、本当に！
No problem, same here! It was really fun, truly!
これからも続くのでね。
The show will continue after this.
そうですね、Please enjoy!
That's right, please enjoy!
はい、エンジョイします！後でね、ケーキ一緒に...
Yes, I'll enjoy it! Let's eat cake together later...
...食べよう。
はい！
...let's eat.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes. これね、食べましょう。
Yes, yes, yes. Let's eat this.
そうだね、食べましょう。めちゃめちゃ上手そうだから。
Have a nice day today!
Right, let's eat. It looks delicious.
It looks so good! Thank you, I'll do my best!
And Dead Beats, see you!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye Dead Beats!
Bye-bye!
じゃあ、また！
バイ、ルイ姉！
Well then, see you later!
Bye, Lui-nee!
See you!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
There goes Lui.
Lui-nee, saikou. I knew that she was gonna sing that song so good.
Lui-nee is the best. I knew that she was gonna sing that song so well.
I knew it! I knew it!
She like, wasn't super, super familiar with it before, but like...
...she knocked it out of the park. I knew she was gonna be amazing.
Saikou, it's like a blessing for my ears. That's why I chose Lui-nee.
She's the best, it's like a blessing for my ears. That's why I chose Lui-nee.
Because I knew she would bless my ears with her low tone. Suteki datta, hontou ni ne.
Because I knew she would bless my ears with her low tone. It was lovely, truly.
God, she is so amazing.
Now that, she's a busy lady, so I'm gonna let her go.
Now then, she's a busy lady, so I'm gonna let her go.
Ah, it's a bit lonely. But that's okay, that's okay.
I'm gonna show you something. I want to show you a thing.
You both slayed it. Thank you so much! You guys are very sweet.
Really amazing indeed. That was straight fire. Her voice is beautiful. Agreed, so much.
So, we're gonna watch something so I can sit down for a second, right?
We're gonna watch a video.
Now, you guys know it's my birthday, right?
It's Mori Day!
You can tweet out #happymoriday with your screenshots...
...and to show your appreciation for your Mori if you'd like. Should you be so inclined, right?
If you'd like. So...
Additionally, there's something I want to show you guys.
It's a video.
A video of things you can buy!
That's right! Do you guys want to buy things?
骸骨ちゃん、ほら見て。一緒に見よう。
Skelly-chan, look. Let's watch together.
Check it out, everyone!
...never use, because you got lured in by that
low, low price of 19.99?
Well fear not, because on today's shopping program,
"Shop Till You Drop Dead", featuring Calliope Mori.
None of our items are 19.99. Ha ha!
Ho no!
Get ready to feast your eyes on some premium
tier items you'll literally want to gouge your eyes out
if you don't own them out of sheer FOMO
and additional existential dread of the
emptiness of your life without them.
You need these items! You need them!
Why not get a sick poster of your one and only boy
to display at work and assert your dominance
over your friends?
That's right folks, Mori Calliope's special birthday poster
features Mori Calliope rocking out at a concert
she definitely did, with an outfit she definitely wore!
You won't want to miss this premium item because
once it's gone, it's gone for good!
Fuck you scalpers, get it now!
Ever wanted to bathe yourself in sweet-smelling,
delicious purple liquid? Well, I sure can't relate.
But if you do, then you better get your hands on
this special dual set of bath bombs from
Mori Calliope's favorite premium underworld onsen!
They come in two scents: Mori Rose and
Death Sensei Purple Mist. Get yours today,
you smell like shit!
Thirsty? Surrounded by hot e-girls?
Who the hell isn't! But too bad for you,
that's no e-girl on your mug, it's your dad!
Your Mori-dad! With an exclusive design by
Mori Calliope, father to all!
You'll be feeling like number one as you sip
your stress, anxiety, and existential dread away!
Don't miss your chance to grab it, dummy!
Lil' swag merch-u,
get Lil' swag Mori-kun,
don't want to half-sie Deadbeat,
don't want to save trees Deadbeat,
Lil' swag merch-u,
got to get yours-u.
Plush comes with one outfit, design details different from final version. No trees are guaranteed to be saved by the making of this plush.
So what are you waiting for, Deadbeat?
If you get the whole set, a limited number
of Deadbeats will get a hand-signed postcard!
They're gonna sell out fast because I really like
my hand! But never fear, if you buy the full set,
you get a duplicated autograph postcard!
Remember Deadbeats, shop until you're dead...
beats! Get it? Deadbeats? Like the name
of the fans! Ha ha ha!
Yo, shut the fuck up, no one's laughing at that shit.
Wait Mori, no, I'm sorry!
Mori, I'm sorry, no! Mori, no!
Please, stop that shit, stop that shit out! No!
Mori, please, take it down! Oh god!
Oh! It hurts! I feel faint...
Don't worry about the ending part, that was just a little bit.
It wasn't real, it wasn't real.
Anyway, anyway! What about it, you guys?
What do you think of the merch?
Pretty cool, right? Pretty cool. Love some good violence...
no, no violence here. No, no, no, no.
Well, I hope you guys will be excited about this
and enjoy the many wonderful... bath bombs! Woah!
Crazy! Plush of my own... I hope you guys will get it.
Yeah, it'll be really cool. I swear you'll use
the things every day, you'll use the things every single day.
And... it's not that bad of a price? I don't know
your financial situation, so be careful.
Additionally, additionally, additionally...
um, there's something else I wanted to talk about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! I've already talked about this before
but I'm going to talk about it again because
I need more time to rest and also just because
it's really important to me that you get it.
Because if you buy this, my dreams will come true.
So, what else do we have here? I'm going to show it
to you again, it's the Blu-ray! P-chow! P-chow!
みなさん！
Everyone!
WHAT'S UP!!!!
MAJOR DEBUT CONCERT - NEW UNDERWORLD ORDER
2023/05/03
LIVE Blu-ray Release!!!
NEW UNDERWORLD ORDER - JULY 21, 2022 - TOYOSU PIT
Yeah! Blu-ray, Blu-ray!
And if you get it, you get lots of nice things too.
Or I mean that... look, it's behind me.
Right here, look.
Look at all the nice things you get depending on the store you buy it from.
There are like all kinds of different little things that you can get.
In addition, the only way to get them all is to buy the Blu-ray many many times, I don't know.
If you'd like to, you certainly can.
Because like I said, if you buy this Blu-ray, all my dreams come true.
Yay Mori store, yay Mori store, yay!
Um, yeah, it would make me really, really happy...
...because I'm super proud of this, of this release.
So yeah, check out the Blu-ray.
And don't go anywhere, because I still have one big announcement...
...or a couple of announcements, but one really big announcement at the end of the stream.
So don't go anywhere, okay?
We still got more to do.
But yeah, buy the Blu-ray, it would make me really happy.
Yeah, that'd be really great.
Another really big show might happen someday.
Well, I guess the surprise is kind of ruined, but just kidding, here it is.
Yatta—!
We did it—!
大丈夫、you didn't see anything. You didn't see anything.
It's okay, you didn't see anything. You didn't see anything.
You didn't see anything. You saw nothing.
Oh god, da... No, don't look there. Don't look there.
No, no, no, no, it's fine. You pretend like you didn't, pretend like you didn't see anything.
There's still another, there's still another announcement, okay?
Just pretend like you didn't see.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hey, I think someone's here. Oh my gosh.
What is this? Perhaps the sound of a phone that's about to ring?
あ、電話、電話かな。電話ありますね。
Oh, a phone, I wonder if it's a phone? We have a phone here.
ほら見て、we have a phone over here.
Look, we have a phone over here.
Isn't that great?
It would be awesome if it were to ring at some point.
Oh! It's ringing!
Oh my gosh, no way!
All right, let me see if I can grab it. Watch this.
もしもし？
Hello?
Hi, it's Calli. I heard you're lonely...
...at a karaoke booth by yourself on your birthday. Is the phone okay?
Yeah, no, I can hear you perfectly well. I... don't worry about it, it's fine, it's fine.
Hold on, let me hold on, let me just T-pose real quick.
大丈夫かな？
I wonder if it's okay?
Okay, let's see. Oh hello, okay, sorry, I can hear you perfectly now, IRyS. Hey, what's going on?
Hi, Calli! Hey!
I heard you were lonely and I was wondering if you wanted a visit from a certain Nephilim or so.
I'm not lonely, I...
But wait, no, no, no, you don't want me to come?
No, please, come! I don't have to come, you know.
No, no, no, I want to sing with you. IRyS, please, come here.
Yeah, let's karaoke party! I'll run there right now. I'll teleport there, yeah.
Are you sure you can run?
You have legs to run with?
Uh... it'll be something. I'm sure I might go too fast, I might... I might lose some dimension on my body.
Okay, well, good luck. I'm just going to go ahead and put the phone away then.
All right! I'm hanging up now. Bye!
There it goes, I put the phone away. Hi!
Okay, looks like IRyS is going to come and join us. We're going to maybe sing together.
Does that sound cool?
All right, well let's wait and see when she's going to be here. Me and Gaikotsu-kun are waiting.
Calli—!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Oh my god, what happened to you?
Why are you flat?
Oh, no, I just... I came too fast, I couldn't process my whole body into... into the room.
Stop... Oh my god.
Wait, what's wrong? Do I look different? Do I look different from usual?
As beautiful as usual, right?
Well, yeah, of course, naturally. I mean, you're always very pretty.
But you are, you are definitely flat.
I think that's okay, because it just means more people can get excited for your official 3D debut, right?
Yes! It's Flat-RyS! It's Flat-RyS!
Wow, I mean, hey, you know what? As long as you can still sing, I'm happy to have you here.
I am happy too!
And you know one thing that's good about being flat? What?
Is that, you know, since I'm basically just a piece of cardboard, I can touch Calli, I can do no matter what I'm doing to her right now...
Hold on... Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But you can't tell because it's not full body tracking!
No, no, no, stop that. Stop, stop, stop! Why are you being weird?
Stop, you're like a... you're like a fly.
I'm going to swat you... Stop doing that!
No, no, no. 意地悪！
No, no, no. How mean!
こいつ！
This girl!
All right, well, it's fine, it's fine. You know what? I'll allow, I'll allow your little...
...your little shenanigans as long as we can sing together.
Yay! Are we going to sing?
Of course!
I was thinking maybe we should sing a song from an anime that we both have seen...
...and we both have talked about on the chat before.
Yes! That anime.
That anime with the... with the bad ending.
Oh, that anime itself was... was a good anime, but man, the ship...
Best girl lost, and so I'll never forgive that anime. But that's okay.
She was robbed. She was robbed.
We're going to sing, we're going to sing the opening of True Tears.
True Tears, yeah! It is the opening.
It's the opening. Okay, it's the opening. We're going to sing...
リフレクティア！
Reflectia!
Let's do it. Yay!
虹色の回路に
To the rainbow-colored circuit,
無数の言葉たち
countless words,
半分だけでも ここならば
even if it's only half, if I'm here,
進んで行ける
I can move forward.
突然のメロディ
A sudden melody
また加速して行く
accelerates once again.
心を掴んだ 一片の
Capturing my heart, a single fragment
影も消し去る
even the shadows are erased.
まなざしキラキラ
A sparkling gaze,
あまり大きくない
even a road that isn't
道でもいいね
very big is fine.
そして駆け出す 飛び込む 奇跡へ
Then I start running, jumping into a miracle,
見上げる 手を振る 光へ
looking up, waving my hand toward the light.
止まらない気持ちを つないで行く
I'll connect these unstoppable feelings.
リフレクティア 揺らめく 近づく 明日へ
Reflectia, swaying, drawing closer to tomorrow,
奏でる 夢見る 未来へ
playing, dreaming toward the future.
まっさらな空 どこまでも連れて
Taking the brand-new sky everywhere,
涙の終わり合図に
as the signal for the end of tears.
Fading sharing yet say lovely
Your turn!
無意識のメロディ
An unconscious melody,
風になるように
so as to become the wind.
記憶の隙間が 一瞬を
The gaps in my memory
求め続ける
continue to seek a single moment.
まぼろしフワフワ
A fluffy illusion,
踏み出せるなら
if I can take a step forward,
きっと大丈夫
I'm sure it'll be fine.
そして重ねる 促す 願いを
Then stacking, urging my wishes,
導く 追い越す 時間を
guiding, overtaking time.
ガラスに通せば 浮かんでくる
If I pass it through glass, it appears,
螺旋の模様
the spiral pattern.
数える 束ねる 思いを
Counting, bundling my thoughts,
広げる 彩る 笑顔を
expanding, coloring my smile.
透明な空 包まれる度に
Every time I'm enveloped by the transparent sky,
生まれ変わって行くから
because I'll keep being reborn.
Now I'm sad.
Because our ship sank?
Yeah.
I'll always be bitter.
It's true tears, right?
Yeah.
少しの空想に
In a little daydream,
いつか打ち明けたい秘密
a secret I want to reveal someday.
流れて 描いて 開いて 映して
Flowing, drawing, opening, reflecting,
鳴らして 回って
ringing, turning.
小さな嘘さえ 指の先を
Even small lies
通り過ぎる
pass through the tips of my fingers.
隔てて 壊して 走って 帰って
Separating, breaking, running, returning,
満たして 歌って
filling, singing.
淡くて遠い 日々を救い出し
Rescuing the faint and distant days,
反射したなら
if they're reflected...
駆け出す 飛び込む 奇跡へ
I start running, jumping into a miracle,
見上げる 手を振る 光へ
looking up, waving my hand toward the light.
誇り成すオーブで 私を呼ぶ
Calling me with a prideful orb.
リフレクティア 揺らめく 近づく 明日へ
Reflectia, swaying, drawing closer to tomorrow,
奏でる 夢見る 未来へ
playing, dreaming toward the future.
まっさらな空 どこまでも連れて
Taking the brand-new sky everywhere,
限りなく舞い上がるよ
I'll soar infinitely high.
Fading sharing yet say lovely
Think of a really messed up English sentence.
Tear did Falling are reed feel
Yeah, that works.
Yeah! That was fun.
I'm jumping right now by the way.
She is, believe.
Believe she's doing it.
I am jumping!
Yeah. Together, together!
Just kidding. I'm not trying to tire you out.
We still have another song to sing.
Let's find that other song...
Something really hype.
We should sing a really hype anime song.
Such as...
One that like everybody knows and gets really excited about.
Like um... Like they want to... They want to shout the first part of the song.
Ah, ah, that song.
Yeah, the one that starts with a...
G... G... G... G... G...
Ji... Ji... Ji... Ji... Ji...
JIBUN WO!
いきましょう！COLORS!
Let's go! COLORS!
Let's go!
COLORS / FLOW
ASAGAWA TAKESHI / KOHSHI ASADA / FLOW, KO-KI
Yeah, yeah, bring it down!
Hey, hey, here we go!
自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな
I feel like I could change myself and even the world
瞬間は いつもすぐそばに...
The moment is always right by my side...
隠せぬ苛立ちと
With an irritation I can't hide
立ち尽くす自分を
And my standing self
見つめ 迷いながら 悩みながら 悔やみながら
I watch as I wander, worry, and regret
決めればいいさ
It's okay to just decide
君がくれた言葉ひとつ 戸惑いは消え去り
With a single word you gave me, my confusion vanished
空っぽだった僕の部屋に光が射した
Light shone into my empty room
見上げた大空が青く澄み切って行く
The sky I looked up at is becoming clear and blue
閉ざした窓を開くこと決めた
I've decided to open the closed window
自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな
I feel like I could change myself and even the world
瞬間は いつもすぐそばに...
The moment is always right by my side...
満たせぬ日常に在るはずの答えを探して
Searching for the answer that should be in my unfulfilled daily life
朝陽に一人 やわらかな声に振り向けば
Alone in the morning sun, if I turn towards that soft voice
眩い陽射しの中 ふと君が微笑む
In the dazzling sunlight, you suddenly smile
閉ざした窓が開きそうになる
The closed window seems like it's about to open
自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな
I feel like I could change myself and even the world
存在は 僕の目の前に
The existence is right before my eyes
見上げた大空が青く澄み切って行く
The sky I looked up at is becoming clear and blue
閉ざした窓を開くこと決めた
I've decided to open the closed window
自分を 世界さえも 変えてしまえそうな
I feel like I could change myself and even the world
瞬間を感じる 今ここに...
I feel the moment right here, right now...
光へと両手を伸ばして
Stretching both hands towards the light
心を吹き抜ける 空の色 香る風
The color of the sky and the scented wind blowing through my heart
What is going on?
That was a perfect camera shot, wasn't it?
The perfect meme ending to a perfect meme song.
Yay! Very nice. That was fun.
That was a good time. Thank you so much.
Thank you, Calli, for invit—
No, actually, I invited myself, what am I talking about?
Yeah, she's kind of flying around right now...
...like she owns the place. Oi, oi, oi!
What happens if I lie down?
Let's find out.
Oh god, oh god!
Wow, she's clipping through the... Oh lord!
Gosh, she's gonna see something yabai.
Oh no, oh no!
がんばれ、がんばれ！
Hang in there, hang in there!
We knew this would happen.
You want to T-pose and fix it?
Oh yeah, sure.
But before that, let me kick you once.
Preeee!
Wait, no, stop! Stop it! Stop!
Feel the legs!
おい、おい、お前！ Hey!
Oi, oi, omae! Hey!
Please, please...
fix me, Kami-sama.
fix me, God.
T-pose?
Little T-pose for IRyS as she gets... gets fixed.
Anyway, they're gonna... they're gonna fix IRyS now.
They're gonna fix her. She got a little crazy.
It's fine. We did this to ourselves.
This was our bad.
But it's fine. It was worth it to watch...
to watch IRyS clip into the ground, so...
I'm happy to do it. It's fine. It's fine.
It's fine. It's all good in the neighborhood.
Hold on, she's getting fixed now.
You guys want to hear a joke?
I want to hear it.
Uh... I don't... I don't have any jokes, sorry.
I was just asking.
I wasn't gonna tell a joke, I was just asking if
you wanted to hear one.
It's fine.
There she is!
There we go!
IRyS! Shall we...
oh wait.
You got a... oh no, no, no, no, no.
It's fine, it's fine.
Anyway...
Okay.
Oh, someone's calling!
Oh!
Hey! Hold on a minute. Who is this?
もしもし？
Hello?
もし... もし... もしもし？
Hello... hello... hello?
もしもし？
Hello?
え、もし... もし... もし？
Eh, hello... hello... hello?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
大丈夫です。
I'm okay.
あ、もしもし？
Ah, hello?
カリオペです。
This is Calliope.
誰かいる？
Is someone there?
Must be a prank call.
Somebody there? Hello?
Hello?
Oh! Oh, oh! Hold on a minute.
I'm here to inform you guys...
have 10 minutes remaining until you are get the f...
out of this... I'm kidding!
Oh my god! Bae!
I'm gonna beat you for that, Bae!
Happy Birthday!
Thank you, Bae!
Thank you, Bae! I appreciate you.
Hi!
Oh my god, IRyS.
Bae-bae!
Bae!
Bae-bae, how do you like me in this form, Bae?
Oh no! Oh no, I disappeared into the ground again!
It's okay, I'm uncovering you.
Oh wait, I don't know...
Look at her swim! She's swimming now.
It's okay, no, I'm making the same pose that Kaworu-kun
made when he was floating with Shinji-kun.
You can't be doing that! You can't say something
like that!
Oh! Wait, I'm sorry.
Bruh.
Anyway, Happy Birthday Calli!
Oh, thank you, Bae!
Hey, you know, when you do a ChadCast, it might be
something like this.
Oh, there we go.
I'm doing great.
Thank you for making some time to call.
Of course! Anytime for you!
I was so excited! Yay!
Yay! Bruh.
Bae, I have a question for you, Bae.
A little birthday question.
Yes!
What do you want to see me do this year?
It could be anything.
What do I want to see you do this year?
Oh, that's a good question.
Yeah.
I want to see you... wait, is this like a promise
that you'll do it?
Kind of.
We'll see, that depends. Depends on some factors.
I see. Um...
As your sister, I actually would want to see you
take an actual break.
Oh.
I was waiting for...
I was...
I would like to see you...
that's what I would like to see, period.
I appreciate that.
Thank you. Hold on, I'm T-posing.
Thank you.
I thought it was going to be something cool like, oh
we should like maybe learn to breakdance or something.
No, okay, look, you said...
okay, that was my sisterly answer.
Thank you.
If... okay, something that I would want to
see you do this year...
something cool.
Let's see. Um...
If... okay, something that I would want to see you
do this year, something cool. Let's see.
You know what I would actually want to see you
try and do a...
Oh! We should learn how to do a freeze together!
A freeze? What's that?
It's a breakdancing move.
It's when like you do like a breakdancing move
and then you freeze...
...in like a position. Yeah!
Oh, okay! Yeah, definitely! I mean, that sounds cool.
Wait, so like, you mean like, super cool like Matrix
kind of thing?
Like maybe like we swivel on our heads and then like
stop?
Um...
Maybe?
Yatta! Okay, the phone is fixed.
Hurray! Okay, the phone is fixed.
Oh, okay.
Okay, yeah. You said you wanted to freeze together?
Yeah.
What's a freeze?
A freeze... a freeze is like when you like stop...
it's like a pose but like you're suspending yourself
off the ground.
It's like a breakdancing pose. Yeah, something like that.
That's kind of advanced, but there's things like a
baby freeze.
I think that's the first thing beginner
breakdancers try and learn.
Cool!
Yeah, I'm down.
Alright then, let's do it.
I mean, if we ever do like a big ChadCast like live
performance or something, I want to try a
freeze with you.
Yeah.
Oh... yeah, I don't know how to do...
You don't know how to do it!?
Wait, you don't know how to do it!?
I don't... it's been a very long time...
since my body's not like it used to be, okay!?
Then how are we gonna learn!?
Alright, alright.
Well, I'll give you some time to learn and then...
I'll learn as well, okay?
Okay.
Oh my god, that'd be so much fun. My heart stopped when I heard Rakuen earlier.
Oh, see, I thought of you. I thought of you singing that song.
Yeah, 'cause you know, we're all Inuyasha gang here, so...
Yeah... Yeah, that... that makes me really happy.
Well, speaking of songs that I'm doing, what would you...
All right, I'm gonna give you the ability to ask me for like a dance move or pose request
for the next songs that I'm gonna sing. You don't know which songs they are, but...
but I'll insert it. Even if I'm singing a sad slow one, if you want me to do the worm, I'll do it.
Don't choose that, by the way.
All right. Um, do you perhaps know... Okay, there's a...
Okay, I would like to see a pepper grinder move in there.
What is that? What's that one?
Okay, so put your two hands in front of you. Okay.
One... and then pretend you're grinding pepper.
Yeah! Pepper grinder!
That's actually... That's pretty cool. Okay, I'll do that.
All right, I'll do... I'll do your pepper grinder.
Yeah! Do the pepper grinder! And I'd like to see a Holo squat for a song.
Squat? Okay, yeah! Whatever you want, Bae! All right, sure, squat! I'll do it for you.
All right, well I gotta... I gotta get going. You see these eyebags I've got under my eye?
They're from you. But I love you very much.
I love you too! Happy Birthday, Calli!
Thank you for the birthday wishes! You're the best, Bae!
You're the best! I'll talk to you later!
Love you! Bye-bye! Bye, Bae!
Bye, Bae! Bye, Bae! Why are you still there?
Bye! I'm still here! Bye, Bae!
There we go, that was... that was Bae. Bae gave me a call on my birthday. Wasn't that sweet? Wasn't it sweet, IRyS?
Yeah! It was very sweet. Sorry, I'm... I'm probably either in the ground or invisible right now.
It's okay. She's become a ghost, but she's still among us.
Don't... Chat, never mind. All right, well I wonder if somebody else will call.
ほ、他の誰か電話するかな？
I wonder if someone else will call?
誰が電話するのかなー？
I wonder who's calling?
Oh my gosh, someone's calling! Someone's calling! Someone's calling! All right, let's go pick up the phone again! Let's see what happens!
I got it! Oh, it worked!
もしもし！ Kitty, Kitty, もしもし！
Hello! Kitty, Kitty, hello!
It's Wawa! Kiara! Wawa's here!
Hello! What's up? You've got like a super special themed karaoke room!
I do! I wanted to do something special this year, you know?
Oh my god, what... eh? But it's like... normally you get these super boring karaoke rooms if you go to karaoke.
You gotta pay extra for the special ones. So how much did you pay for this special one?
You don't want to know, Kiara. You don't want to know how much I paid. But you know what? I'm happy.
Twelve bits! Sometimes you gotta treat yourself to something nice!
That's true, that's true. You know what, that's... that's the spice of life, honestly, that I get to do this kind of stuff.
I'm really happy, I'm lucky, you know?
Yay! Happy Birthday, Kewie!
Thanks so much, Kiwawa! I appreciate you calling in to wish me a happy birthday.
I gotta wish you a happy birthday too! I have it in my calendar.
Oh, yeah, thank you! Well, it's still a long time to go... but I was so surprised when I realized...
wait, what? Calli's birthday already? Now? What? It felt like just yesterday when you had your last one.
I know! Time really flies. Well, I'm gonna eat lots and lots of KFP on your birthday.
Nom nom nom nom...
I have a question! But I would prefer... like a... a cake that looks like fried chicken, but it's actually a cake.
You know those fake cakes? That is a real thing. People do know how to do that. Yeah, that's crazy.
Well, I have a question for you, Wawa. What do you want to see me do this year?
This year in general? Yeah, don't say 'take a break' because Bae said 'take a break'.
I want you to realize some plans that you have on the... you know, what do you call it? Backburner?
Or like, not backburner, I don't know, but... Oh yeah!
Plans that you have had since like maybe a year or so.
And just make them a reality this year. You know what I mean?
I know what you... I think I know what you mean. Definitely. Wink wink, wonk wonk.
Wink wink, wonk wonk! I like that idea. Okay, well you've inspired me now, Kiara. Okay, I'll do it! I'll do it!
Okay! Just do it! Just do it! Can you give me like, with the hand poses, like, you know,
walking around and then with the finger onto the hand?
Just... Oh, yeah, wait, hold on. The finger onto the hand? Yeah, maybe you can't take the props off, that's okay.
Just do it! Don't let your dreams be dreams! Do it!
Do it! Something like that. Yeah! I'll do it too! I'll do whatever!
You should do it too! Hey, also, you get a request for the next song that I'm singing.
What kind of like dance move or pose do you want to see me do?
Do you know like roughly what the vogue dance style is?
Um, can you give me an example? Vogue?
I think... Oh, hi IRyS! That's the first word I hear!
I said hi, Kiara! I was like, 'Hi Kiara!'. I'm here, I'm invisible!
IRyS, you can vogue too! Do you know how to vogue?
What is that? What is that? You don't know? Well, it's like...
...I mean, there's like several
parts to voguing,
but I think like what I want to see you do
is like over your head, like frantically
move your arms over your head like,
you know, like swirl and twirl
and then one hand to the left, one to the right and so...
舞踏（ダンス）の方、
Dancers,
ヴォーグ（Vogue）してますか？
are you voguing?
Oh!
Oh, she's doing it!
Yeah!
Kind of copy... kind of copy what she's doing.
Oh yeah!
Oh yeah, she's showing you!
Yeah!
She is a pro dancer after all.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, if you could vogue together with your dancer
doing the- maybe during every chorus, vogue.
Okay.
Every chorus.
All right, I'll try.
浴びるほどに、ヴォーグ（Vogue）お願いします。
Please vogue as much as you can soak in.
As much as I can, I will.
よろしく！
Best of luck!
よろしくね。
Best of luck to you too.
Oh gosh, she's giving me a hard one.
All right, I'll do my best.
Thanks, Kiuawa.
Have fun!
Talk to you later, Kiara. Bye!
Bye!
Yeah.
Oh, hold on one second, everybody.
We're gonna fix IRyS for a second
and I'm gonna put away the phone really quick.
Can you fix me?
I love you, Kiuawa! Bye!
I love you too, bye bye!
Bye, Kiara!
Bye!
There we go.
We're fixing IRyS.
She doesn't need to be fixed in my opinion, but that's okay.
I'm perfect the way I am!
Exactly.
Hold on, let me try the vogue thing.
Yeah, you're doing it!
You're doing it!
I see it!
I'm trying.
It's beautiful!
Thank you.
ありがとう。
Thank you very much, Gaikotsu-chan.
Thank you.
Gaikotsu-chan is very cute.
She's scared of me though, I think.
Oh no, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
She's just a little shy, but she's very outgoing around me.
Yeah.
Okay.
Cool, cool, cool.
Well, I wonder what we should do after this.
Here, let me sit down for a second.
I still have a couple songs I want to sing you guys.
I want to sing some more songs.
Um...
I'll do my best.
We got some emotional ones in there too.
Oh boy, oh man.
And also we have some announcements, so don't go anywhere.
But I really hope you guys have enjoyed the show so far.
I know that this is a lot more like casual and like cozy and whatnot.
It's not like a really big grand showcase or anything like that.
But I think that's okay.
You know, you guys always tell me that I should have more fun
um, you know, just having a good time singing
and worry less about like how high quality everything is all the time
and stress myself out over it, you know?
I'm fixed!
She's fixed.
Speaking of which, looking very high quality.
Thank you!
I'm a high-quality PNG floating around.
Oh, well I can't wait for your 3D!
Thank you, Calli.
It's gonna be fun.
Very fun, too.
I want to sing with you in 3D again.
We'll do it!
Just like we did at the Fest, yeah?
Yay!
Definitely.
Alrighty then,
well since my body is fixed now,
I think I should be heading off to do my Nephilim duties,
maybe perhaps an idol meeting.
An idol meeting?
Maybe perhaps an idol meeting
that I've been- that I've been getting an emergency alert for, for a bit.
Stop!
Get out, IRyS!
Not in my karaoke room!
Oy!
I need to go!
I'm a fly!
Get out!
Bye, IRyS!
Get out, IRyS!
Bye-RyS!
Get out!
She's leaving now.
Yay.
I was- I was really quite-
I was lonely.
I mean, I know that I have my Dead Beats here
...but it's even better with friends, right?
Yeah.
Huh.
Anyway, I guess we should sing some more songs.
Is that okay?
I think I've sufficiently rested enough.
Okay.
Well let's sing.
Let's continue singing, that's what we're here for, right?
I've got a couple more songs in me.
So let's go!
歌いましょう！
Let's sing!
イカサマライフゲイム
Ikasama Life Game
Yeah!
明日の午後は雨が降ると
They say it'll rain tomorrow afternoon...
ぽつり
...with a drip.
忌々しい啓示そんな何かに
To such an annoying revelation...
気をつけて
...be careful.
既定の終束には金も
In the pre-determined end, neither money...
標的たちは
...nor the targets...
誰も知らないこれはつまり
No one knows, which means...
運命の地（エライオッチ）
...a terrible fate.
『明日バスに乗るな』
"Don't get on the bus tomorrow."
事故が起こるから
Because an accident will happen.
最適な温度で
At the optimal temperature...
僕は生きていく
...I will live on.
イカサマライフゲイムが
The Ikasama Life Game...
手首を添えたジョーカーは
...the Joker with a hand on his wrist...
笑う
...laughs.
やがて
Eventually...
...感情を消し去った
...erased my emotions.
いつか見た憧憬
The longing I once saw.
穢れていく夢はマガイモノ 笑う独り
The tainting dream is a sham, laughing alone.
祈りの導きのままに
Following the guidance of prayer.
「明日のデートには行くな」とぽつり
"Don't go on tomorrow's date," he murmured.
影をさす寒気 おしこんで 札を引いた
Pushing down the chill pointing to shadows,
I drew a card.
過程の収束には敵わぬの 標的たちは
The targets can't compete with
the convergence of the process.
何も知らない僕がそれを選んだんだ
I, knowing nothing, was the one who chose it.
誰かが言ってた あの子独りで
Someone said, "That girl is all alone,"
帰りのホームから足を滑らせ
slipping from the platform on the way home.
イカサマライフゲイム 雁首そろえたジョーカーは
Cheating Life Game, the Jokers lined up
side-by-side...
笑う やがて
...laugh. Soon...
感情を消し去った
...they erased my emotions.
それでも存在理由など あとで決めるもの 笑う独り
Even so, things like a reason for existence
are determined later, laughing alone.
祈りの導きのままに
Following the guidance of prayer.
気づいた代償 答えに隠れた
The realized compensation, hidden in the answer.
さよなら愛しき日々 戻れないのは
Goodbye, beloved days.
The reason I can't return is...
僕だけでいいから
...because I'm the only one who needs to.
イカサマライフゲイム 雁首そろえたジョーカーは 笑う
Cheating Life Game, the Jokers lined up
side-by-side laugh.
やがて惨状は訪れる
Soon, the disastrous scene will arrive.
最後の通達 嫌に明快に
The final notice is disgustingly clear:
「明日君はどう頑張ったって死にますよ」
"Tomorrow, no matter how hard you try,
you're going to die."
イカサマライフゲイム 雁首そろえたジョーカーは 笑う
Cheating Life Game, the Jokers lined up
side-by-side laugh.
笑え
Laugh!
ババ抜きじゃ仕方ない おかえり感情
In this game of Old Maid, it's no use.
Welcome back, emotions.
死ぬほどの不安が愛しくて 笑う独り
The deathly anxiety is so precious, laughing alone.
祈りの導きのままに
Following the guidance of prayer.
明日雨は降るかな
I wonder if it will rain tomorrow.
一番の宝物
My Most Precious Treasure
裾が濡れたなら
If the hem of my clothes gets wet,
乾くの待てばいい
I'll just wait for it to dry.
水音をたてて
Making the sound of water,
跳ねた
it splashed.
きみが教えてくれたんだ もう怖くない
You were the one who taught me.
I'm not afraid anymore.
生きていてくれた
You stayed alive for me.
この手を離さなきゃだめだ
I have to let go of this hand.
ひとりでもゆくよ
Even alone, I will go on.
たとえ辛くても
Even if it's painful.
みんなで見た夢は
The dream we all saw together,
必ず持ってくよ
I'll definitely take it with me.
みんなとがいいな
Being with everyone would be nice.
みんなとがよかった
Being with everyone was good.
でも目覚めた朝
But on the morning I woke up,
誰もいないんだね
there was no one there.
もう振り返っても
Even if I look back now,
だれの影もない
there's no one's shadow.
水たまり
A puddle...
...だけが 気があった
...Only that, I noticed
生きていくこと それは立ち向かっていくこと
Living is about facing forward
それがわかったなら
Once you understand that,
あとは踏み出す勇気だけ
all that's left is the courage to take a step
どこまでもゆくよ ここで知ったこと
I'll go anywhere, with what I've learned here
幸せという夢をかなえてみせるよ
I'll show you that I can make the dream of happiness come true
みんなと離れても どんなに遠くなっても
Even if I'm separated from everyone, no matter how far away I get
新しい明日に この僕は生きるよ
In the new tomorrow, I will live
一人でもゆくよ 死にたくなっても
I'll go even alone, even if I feel like dying
声が聞こえるよ 死んではいけないと
I can hear a voice saying I must not die
たとえ辛くても 闇に閉ざされても
Even if it's painful, even if I'm shut in the darkness
心の奥には 灯りがともってるよ
In the depths of my heart, a light is burning
巡って流れて 時は移ろい
Circling and flowing, time changes
もう何があったか 思い出せないけど
I can't remember what happened anymore, but...
目を閉じてみれば みんなの笑い声
If I close my eyes, I hear everyone's laughter
なぜかそれが今 一番の宝物
For some reason, that is my greatest treasure now
Now, I'll sing one more song.
離れる頃 桜散る 全てが愛おしい
When we part, cherry blossoms fall, everything is precious
セピアの心情を 開いては また想い耽る
Opening up my sepia emotions, I lose myself in thought again
SAKURA Days
賑わいと 温もりを
They brought bustle and warmth
運んでくれた
they carried me through
おかげで 色づいた花
Thanks to that, the flowers bloomed with color
ある者は焦がれて
Some long for it,
ある者は皆で分かち合い
some share it with everyone
羨望の眼差しを 向ける者も
Some even cast looks of envy
舞い散る夜風に 秘めた切な愛おしい
In the dancing night breeze, a hidden painful endearment
サヨナラとありがとう 共に贈るよ
I send both my goodbyes and my thanks
おかげで また好きになった
Thanks to you, I've come to like it again
去る者を追えるはずなく
No way to chase those who leave,
来る者は拒めるわけない
no way to refuse those who come
故に尊い 桜色の 日々よ
Thus, the precious cherry-blossom-colored days
離れる頃 桜...
When we part, cherry...
葬らされる全てが愛おしい
Everything that's buried is so dear
セピアの心情を
These sepia-toned feelings
開いてはまた思い耽る
Opening them up, I'm lost in thought again
SAKURA Days
遥か彼方響く君の声に耳を澄ませば
If I listen closely to your voice echoing from afar
少なからずその温もり思い出せるように
So that I can remember at least a little of that warmth
凛とした寂しさも風情と成る
Even this dignified loneliness becomes part of the scenery
SAKURA Days
少なからずその温もり思い出せるように
So that I can remember at least a little of that warmth
麗しき SAKURA Days
Beautiful SAKURA Days
La la la la SAKURA Days
Woah SAKURA Days
SAKURA Days
Thank you.
Everyone, thank you so much for coming to my karaoke party.
I have one more announcement, two more announcements, but one really big one.
One really big announcement, okay?
Everybody...
It's my one-year anniversary with Universal Music as a major artist.
やった！パチパチパチパチパチ！やったやったやった！
Yatta! Clap clap clap clap clap! We did it, we did it!
Yay!
So everyone, I would like to introduce to you...
SINDERELLA LP!
That's right everybody, we've got a vinyl release coming out.
That's right, and orders are gonna open up tonight!
So if you don't want to wait six months to get my merch,
you can go ahead and get this, or you can get both, that's good too.
But if you don't want to wait... Yay Mori Store, yay Mori Store!
You can add SINDERELLA to your vinyl collection.
Yay! More merch, more merch, more merch!
Of course I wasn't gonna leave you guys without a vinyl, no no no.
I'm a big fan of records myself, so yatta!
I'm a big fan of records myself, so we did it!
It's out now. Oh, looks like it's out! Okay, it's out, you guys can get it.
Check the link in the description if you want to grab it.
The vinyl's out! You can go purchase it! Yatta!
The vinyl's out! You can go purchase it! Yay!
Yes, so you guys can check it out.
Yatta! I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
Yay! I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
I hope you guys get it. I can't wait to play it on my little phonograph,
my little turntable. I'm very excited, so I hope you guys will get it as well.
LP, LP! Already bought? Oh my gosh, you guys are fast! Wow!
You guys are really fast. はやーい！
You guys are really fast. So fast!
すごい、買ってくださいね、LPね。
Amazing, please buy the LP, okay?
そう、めちゃめちゃかっこいいこれ。
Right, this is really, really cool.
そうね。れいちゃん、あの素敵なアートね、ありますね、このジャケット。
Right. Rei-chan, that lovely art is on this jacket.
Yeah, it's also super limited in quantity, they are now telling me.
It's very limited, um, 'cause we can't make a million of these.
You guys know that there's, you know, kind of...
there's some... I don't know. You should get it now. You should get it now is what I'm trying to say.
Is what I'm trying to say! I'm so happy, I'm so excited.
CHECK THE LINKS IN DESCRIPTION FOR MORE DETAILS!
Um, so yeah, please grab it. Thank you so much everyone.
And I have one last thing to announce. I have a cover coming out.
Um, I don't know exactly when, 'cause it's being checked.
It should be within the next day or two days or so.
ちょっとサムネ見せてください。
Please show the thumbnail for a bit.
What song is it? What song is it? What song is...
サラマンダー！
Salamander!
Salamander! So please, 楽しみにしててくださいね。
Salamander! So please, look forward to it.
Please look forward to it. I'm really, really proud of this one.
It turned out super good, and I think you guys are gonna love it. So yay, please look forward.
And with that being said you guys, um, I'm your Mori.
I hope that you remember me. This was a really fun stream.
Thank you so much you guys. Thanks for spending time with me, thanks for singing with me.
And I guess I'll catch you guys on the flip side, okay?
Everybody take care. Be sure to grab the merch again, that would make me happy.
And yeah, with that being said everyone, I'll see you later.
Thank you for coming! Bye bye! ガイコツちゃんここに。
Thank you for coming! Bye bye! Skeleton-chan, over here.
Bye bye! See you everyone! またね！
Bye bye! See you everyone! See you later!
Peace out! Bye bye!
Mori Calliope SINDERELLA 2023.06.07 Vinyl Release!!
MAJOR DEBUT CONCERT NEW UNDERWORLD ORDER 2023.05.03 Blu-ray Release!
Mori Calliope Sinderella
2023.06.07 Vinyl Release!!
Tired of owning useless items you'll never use...
...because you got lured in by that low, low price of 19.99?
Well, fear not!
Because on today's shopping program, Shop Till You Drop Dead...
...featuring Calliope Mori.
None of our items are 19.99!
Haha! Oh no!
Get ready to feast your eyes on some premium tier items...
...you'll literally want to gouge your eyes out...
...if you don't own them out of sheer FOMO...
...and additional existential dread of the emptiness of your life without them.
You need these items.
You need them!
Why not get a sick poster of your one and only boy...
...to display at work and assert your dominance over your friends?
That's right folks, Mori Calliope's special birthday poster...
...features Mori Calliope rocking out at a concert she definitely did...
...with an outfit she definitely wore!
You won't want to miss this premium item...
...'cause once it's gone, it's gone for good.
Fuck you scalpers, get it now!
Ever wanted to bathe yourself in sweet smelling, delicious purple liquid?
Well, I sure can't relate.
But if you do, then you better get your hands...
...on this special dual set of bath bombs...
...from Mori Calliope's favorite premium Underworld Onsen.
They come in two scents:
Mori Rose and Death-sensei Purple Mist.
Get yours today, you smell like shit.
Thirsty?
Surrounded by hot e-girls?
Who the hell isn't!
But too bad for you, that's no e-girl on your mug.
It's your dad.
Your Mori dad!
With an exclusive design by Mori Calliope, father to all...
...you'll be feeling like number one as you sip your stress...
...anxiety, and existential dread away.
Don't miss your chance to grab it, dummy!
Lil' Swag Lord!
Plush comes with one outfit, sign details differ from final version...
So what are you waiting for, Deadbeat?
If you get the whole set...
...a limited number of Deadbeats will get a hand-signed postcard.
They're gonna sell out fast 'cause I really like my hand...
...but never fear, if you buy the full set...
...you get a duplicated autograph postcard.
Remember Deadbeats, shop until you're dead...
...beats! Haha, get it? Deadbeats!
Like the name of the fans! Haha!
Yo, shut the fuck up. No one's laughing at that shit.
Wait, Mori, no, I'm sorry!
Mori, they're laughing, I'm a Deadbeat!
No, wait, stop!
Mori, please don't!
Mori, please, take it out!
Oh god, it hurts!
I feel faint...
皆さん...
Everyone...
What's up!
Better better burn it out...
...灰になるまで...
...until it turns to ash...
MAJOR DEBUT CONCERT
NEW UNDERWORLD ORDER
JULY 21, 2022 IN TOYOSU PIT
99?
Ha ha ha!
Oh no!
Get ready to feast your eyes
on some premium tier items
you'll literally want to gouge your eyes out
if you don't own them out of sheer FOMO
and additional existential dread of the
emptiness of your life without them.
You need these items.
YOU NEED THEM!
Why not get a sick poster
of your one and only boy
to display at work
and assert your dominance over your friends?
That's right folks,
Mori Calliope's special birthday poster
features Mori Calliope
rocking out at a concert she definitely did
with an outfit she definitely wore.
You won't want to miss this premium item
'cause once it's gone, it's gone for good.
Fuck you scalpers!
Get it now!
Ever wanted to bathe yourself
in sweet smelling delicious purple liquid?
Well, I sure can't relate,
but if you do,
then you better get your hands on this
special dual set of bath bombs
from Mori Calliope's favorite premium
underworld onsen.
They come in two scents:
Mori Rose and Death Sensei Purple Mist.
Get yours today!
You smell like shit!
Thirsty?
Surrounded by hot e-girls?
Who the hell isn't?
But too bad for you,
that's no e-girl on your mug,
it's your dad.
Your Mori dad.
With an exclusive design by Mori Calliope,
father to all,
you'll be feeling like number one
as you sip your stress,
anxiety, and existential dread away.
Don't miss your chance to grab it,
dummy!
Lil' Swag Lord, woop, yeah!
Lil' Swag Lord, woop, woop!
Don't want to have stinky dead beats!
Don't want to stay trashy dead beats!
Lil' Swag Lord, woop, yeah!
Gotta get yours!
Plush comes with one outfit,
design details differ from final version,
no trees are guaranteed to be saved by the making of this plush.
So what are you waiting for, Dead Beat?
If you get the whole set,
a limited number of Dead Beats
will get a hand-signed postcard.
They're gonna sell out fast 'cause I really like my hand.
But never fear,
if you buy the full set,
you get a duplicated autograph postcard.
Remember Dead Beats:
SHOP UNTIL YOU'RE DEAD BEATS!
Ha ha!
Get it? Dead Beats?
Like the name of the fans!
Ha ha ha ha!
Yo, shut the fuck up.
No one's laughing at that shit.
Wait, Mori, no!
That shit is classic, man!
Everyone's laughing at it!
No one's gonna be... No, wait, stop!
Please!
Please don't hurt me!
Stop!
Cut that shit out!
No, Mori! Aah!
Mori, please! Cut it out!
Oh god!
Oh, it hurts! Aah!
I feel faint!
皆さん！
Everyone!
WHAT'S UP!
メラメラ Burn it up now...
Mera mera, burn it up now...
...say hey!
Jump! Jump! Jump!
2023/05/03 LIVE Blu-ray Release!!!
JULY 21, 2022 in TOYOSU PIT
2023.06.07 Vinyl Release!!