(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
同じ未来を 見ていたい
I want to see the same future
あの夢 手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
それぞれ 違った 心で
With our each different hearts
走り出そう
Let's start running
Shiny Smily Story
Lyrics: 金丸佳史 (onetrap)
Lyrics: Yoshifumi Kanamaru (onetrap)
Composition/Arrangement: 中野領太 (onetrap)
Composition/Arrangement: Ryota Nakano (onetrap)
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
It sprouted in a place where it was pitch black
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われた
This eye was stolen by a just a tiny hope
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Tuning well my heart shaking with anxiety
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I was squeezing out just a tiny bit of courage
諦めの街 手に手をとって進む
In the city of giving up, let's take each other's hands
苦しい時も私は一人じゃないから
Because even in painful times, I am not alone
だからもっと 夢追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dream more
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
世界を変えていく
Changing the world
輝き捧げてあげる
I'll give you a brilliance
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try to access
後悔なんて想像させない
I won't let you imagine any regrets
それぞれ 違った 心で
With our each different hearts
走り出そう
Let's start running
仮想の空に輝くこの眩しい思いは
This dazzling feeling shining in the virtual sky
見たことのない光をリアルに届けるよ
I'll deliver a never-before-seen light to reality
いつも聞こえるエールはここにキャプチャーして
Capture here the cheers I always hear
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
I'll want to search for new light again
君の笑顔は 保存して進む
Saving your smile, let's move forward
悲しい時に 見返すよ
I'll look back at it when I'm sad
力がわくから
Because strength will well up
胸を張って 夢追いかけたい
With my chest held high, I want to chase my dream
奇跡のストーリー
The story of a miracle
一緒に作ろう
Let's make together
終わらない夢を
An endless dream
誰一人欠かせない
Not a single person can be missed
愛が待つこの世界
In this world where love waits
それぞれ 違った 心で
With our each different hearts
彩れ
Color it
フレーズにこの鼓動を鳴らし続けたい
I want to keep ringing this heartbeat in the phrase
終わらない世界に溢れ出す笑顔たち
Smiles overflowing into the endless world
Shiny Smily Story
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage I've longed for
らしく輝きたい
I want to shine like myself
時に涙して
Sometimes shedding tears
また笑い合いたい
I want to laugh together again
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
踏み出した奇跡の一歩を
That first miraculous step we took forward
息切らせ夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams until I'm breathless
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement doesn't stop
空を超えていく 世界に見せてあげる
I'll show the world that goes beyond the sky
アクセスしてみない？
Why don't you try to access?
後悔なんてここにない
There's no such thing as regret here
それぞれ誓った心で進むわ
We'll move forward with the hearts we each pledged
We're here!
We're finally here!
I'm so glad we're here. It feels like that sometimes.
It's okay, it was still cute. Yes, it was cute.
Hi everybody!
Hi everyone!
Myth is here!
We're finally all together in 3D!
Welcome everybody...
...to the HoloMyth 3D Collab Showcase!
Let's start with some greetings. Gura, go!
どうも、サメです！
Domo, same desu!
It's me, Gawr Gura! Thank you everybody for coming!
Hi guys! Hello! Is it on?
Next to Calli!
死神ですです、破滅の加護ですです...
Shinigami desu desu, hametsu no kago desu desu...
...森カリオペですです。All right, Dead Beats!
...Mori Calliope desu desu. All right, Dead Beats!
Inaness go!
Wah! Let me hear a "wah"! Wah!
Wah! Wah! Wah!
Hi everybody, it's Ninomae Ina'nis. Yay!
Next to Ame!
Ame, come on! Show us what you got.
Bubba-bubba! Bubba-bubba!
Amelia Watson, number one detective! Hup-hup-hup!
Kiara, introduce yourself too! I forgot!
Hi hi hi! I'm Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English!
And I forgot to do one thing that I really want us to do!
Everybody, I want your hands to go to the middle!
One by one. Let's do our best today! Takanashi Kiara!
Gura! Mori Calliope! Ina!
Ame! せーの... イェーイ！
Ame! One, two... Yay!
So, everybody, this is our special showcase!
We just performed the classic, "Shiny Smily Story"!
How was that? I liked it! It was fun!
Nervous, but we made it. It was difficult though...
...practicing that one. We had to practice so many things.
I know! But I liked this part! I love this part!
We can see the chat! We're reading all your comments.
Oh my god, they're so fast! I love the hype!
I love the charms! Kiara... Heart, heart, heart!
Look at the spaceship in the back. Myth spaceship!
Oh yeah, look at the space! We're here!
Please look at this beautiful stage! Look at the satellite!
Whoa, pretty! We have good reception here.
Yes, this is the official Hololive English stage...
...as you may have already seen it in our individual showcases.
Look, it's an alien! What's over there? Is that Earth?
Earth! It's Brazil! Hi! Everybody watching! Konnichiwa!
Speaking of our individual showcases, up until this day...
...everybody has done them. The first one was Ina!
How was it to go first? I was so nervous!
I wanted everything to go, you know, perfectly...
...so it kind of set a really good mood for everyone.
You did great! You did awesome!
And then the weekend after, yeah, was our Takamori weekend!
Yes! I feel like we rocked the stage!
It wasn't me this time, chat. It wasn't me! I'm just saying.
But we did, didn't we? We did! That was amazing!
So much fun! And the week after was Gurame!
Hey! It went first, Gurame weekend!
Yeah!
I feel like Gura's showcase was very different from the usual stuff, right?
I was a pain in the butts to the studio, but studio team,
ありがとうございました、thank you for making it happen! Thank you!
thank you very much, thank you for making it happen! Thank you!
Yeah!
Too much math. I hope everybody enjoyed it. Yes, I was a pain.
It's okay though.
And then Ame, Ame. You had so much fun!
Yeah!
It was really fun, I'm glad I was able to do it.
So many balls!
But now I'm excited for this stream.
Yeah!
So excited! We have so many things planned.
What are we doing today?
Well, well, wait. First...
I don't know...
This is a special occasion, isn't it?
We're in 3D together properly for the first time! Right?
Look at these bodies, these beautiful bodies!
We sang and danced together! If you guys want to,
welcome to use the hashtag up there!
#Myth3Dkitaaa!
Yes! Take screenshots! Take screenshots! Yeah!
Take screenshots!
Do it, do it! Post them on Twitter or Facebook, I don't know.
Take screenshots! Yeah!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
It's not often that we get together like this, so we're gonna make the most out of this occasion with...
We have two games that we'll be playing!
Games!
And also... you want more like that Shiny Smily Story, right? You want more? Yes, yes, yes!
More! More! More!
So if you wait until the very end of this stream, you might see more of those performances!
It's worth it!
Yeah!
Okay! Well, then I think we should start with the first game, shall we?
Yeah! Let's go!
Game! Game! Game! Game! Game!
What, are we going somewhere?
No.
Huh?
Yes, we have to go! Game time! No, no, no!
Wait, no, this way! This way! Okay, let's go!
This way! Yeah, why not?
A game? Not game? Okay. Games!
Erh, no. Hey!
Why are we here? Why are we here? Welcome!
What do you mean welcome? We're not supposed to be here!
You guys are under arrest! No!
For the 3D Investigation Redux!
The Investigation 3D Redux / 聞き取り調査ショー
The Investigation 3D Redux / Inquiry Investigation Show
What? What investigation?
If there's a logo that means it was actually planned. I didn't know about this!
I didn't know about this either! What's going on?
All right, well, I need to investigate all of you closely, because now we're in 3D...
...and now we can't hide anything!
Did you do something? That wasn't supposed to be a game!
No! No! No! No!
Over against the wall! You're the first in the dock!
What... what did I do?
What did you do? What did you do?
The crimes! There's something here. Hold on, I gotta look closely.
もしもし、メガネ... [mumbling].
Moshi moshi, megane... [mumbling].
Hey! Oh!
Oh! Now you want to look closely?
Yeah, yeah, I heard you got an update or something.
Something changed recently. No, I have to protect myself.
So let me just get something to protect myself.
Oh! You guys remember seeing Kiara's behind?
On guard! Ha! Ah!
She has a weapon! What's with the sword?
No, no, no, no, that's fake.
That's... that's not real. It's optical.
How do I turn around? Turn around! Look at that, look at that.
Damn!
Oh my god!
I'm not hiding any crimes in here, oh my goodness.
You got a permit for that, don't you?
Yeah, do you have a permit for this, ma'am?
Kiara's the one that's gonna get this channel banned.
No, no, no, no! Ame!
I need to archive this so we'll take a picture of the front first.
Okay, okay. All right.
A photo for all the crimes you've committed. All right, side profile.
Okay, enough, enough. The back?
Yes, the back!
All right, all right, all right. Another close look.
Okay, okay, all right, get out.
All right, you got it, you got it. Good angle.
Kikiriki!
Okay, okay, thank you for the photoshoot.
Who's next? The small one. You.
The small short one. That's you.
Go shorty, go shorty. That's you, Shark. Get in there.
Who, me? わたし？
Who, me? Me?
She definitely has crimes on her. You've committed many crimes.
Me?
Yeah, being too short. That's what it is.
What you talking about, shorty?
Short stack, yeah you want to go? I'm taller than you!
You want to go?
Pretty good.
All right, let me have a closer look at that thing.
It's in violation.
What thing? What violation?
That thing back there. It's a kind of smelly.
Smelly!
It's not smelly!
All right, let me... I'm going to take a picture of this.
But let's take a picture of the front first.
Okay, front.
Oh, my mugshot, okay.
Yeah, mugshot time.
All right, side profile. Turn please.
She looks guilty.
Guilty!
Guilty of crimes.
Guilty of committing more than one!
Too cute.
Vicious. Possibly.
All right, now stay right here. All right.
Calliope Mori, come into the frame, please.
Wait, Calliope Mori? Why am I involved in this? I did nothing.
Is she a lost child? I need to compare heights, size.
Oh, wow, sorry about that.
Kind of morphed into you for a minute there.
Look at that height difference! Wow! Over-proves!
All right, all right, Shark, get out of here.
All right, see you later guys.
Out of the frame. I gotta take a nap.
You've committed crimes.
What did I do?
Every Calli crime! Oh yeah!
Well, I guess I did kill everyone on the planet but...
So you admit to it!
Okay, but that's my job, okay?
All right, let me inspect around here. Excuse me.
Oh! These shoes, these are nice. What are you...
What are you doing with these?
What size are these bad boys? Like dogs are barking!
The doggy's barking!
Step on me! Step on me!
No, Kiara, please! I didn't do anything.
All right, you did something. You're being booked.
And we're gonna take your picture first.
So face the front please.
I'm the most innocent one here.
I think she has a weapon. Is it a weapon?
No weapon. I didn't bring it today.
Guilty! Guilty for not having eyes! I caught her! Look at that!
All right, the side profile.
All right, all right, get out of here. You're going downtown.
It's an act, it's all an act!
Okay, last.
The most offensive crimes against humanity.
Ina-san! Your turn! Inanis, please! Face the front.
She's definitely the most guilty. Look at that face.
Wait, what? I'm innocent. Really!
Really? That's why you're booked because too many puns! Your crime!
Ah, but you guys enjoyed it! I know you guys enjoyed it!
Yeah, yeah.
Also she's not giving out enough cookies.
She promises cookies and she doesn't give them.
I want cookies!
It's rough times, okay? I can't... I can't make them all.
She gave us cake!
Are you hiding something back here? Let me pat you down.
Is there something there? Let me see.
Okay, wait, every... for a second... はずかしい...
Okay, wait, every... for a second... It's embarrassing...
What's going on? Oh, wait, what's that?
Oh my god!
Tentacles! They're coming out!
Oh, I got it, I feel yucky.
I'm innocent. Nothing wrong.
Put that away!
Okay, okay. はずかしい...
Okay, okay. It's embarrassing...
That's dangerous! So dangerous!
My crime...
I almost lost my breath because she's so cute.
Get back!
All right, all right, get her! Put them away!
Oh, no! Put them away!
Get them away! Don't get too close!
Maybe close your eyes.
Oh, they're fine now. She looks normal.
見ちゃだめ！ Are we good?
Don't look! Are we good?
Are they gone? Are they gone?
They... okay.
All right, that feels... Ina's back.
Okay, they're gone.
All right, that was disgusting. Oh, I'm scared.
Oh my!
All right, we're gonna take your picture. Come on.
It's okay. I'll free you after this, I swear, I swear.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean that. That's cruel.
あ、チュ！
Ah, chu!
All right, side profile please.
All right, I need to test something for science. Give me a moment.
Let me put my 虫眼鏡 away.
Let me put my magnifying glass away.
Hic!
Okay.
What are you gonna do? Oh boy.
Hic, hic, hic, hic, chat!
What is that?
Uh, I need to do a scientific dunk.
No, Ina, stay... I need you to stay still.
I'm trying!
It's not gonna work. It's not gonna work.
Gonna do a dunk... Hyah!
One more try! All right, one more, one more.
Do the dunk! Slam dunk!
She shoots... she scores!
Very nice! Okay, okay.
All right, that concludes the investigation. I'll free you for now.
No it doesn't!
Not yet! We have one more left!
We have to investigate her!
I don't think so!
You're not getting away from us!
Wait! Oh! Be careful, be careful.
Come here! Get her! Get her!
Take it away! Take it away!
I'm going to be the authority here! Take the 虫眼鏡!
I'm going to be the authority here! Take the magnifying glass!
No! I have the camera! You can't do it like this!
We gotta keep it professional.
We have to investigate her professionally.
Okay, fine, fine.
Tada!
Where'd you guys get those?
Amazon! Amazon! Amazon!
Let me look at you. You guys got into my stash?
Let's see. Hmm... Detective Watson, what are you doing over there?
I've committed no crimes.
What are those? Suspicious! Suspicious!
You committed many crimes. 30 seconds ago.
She's a liar.
なるほど。
I see.
Why don't we arrest you?
What are you guys looking at? Interesting.
Oh, nice shoes! They're pretty good.
Yeah, they're so shiny. Detective steppers.
Don't hide! Don't hide! What's in there?
What are you hiding under the cape?
She's hiding the Watson concoction!
No! There's nothing there. They can't see it.
I can't see it. But they wish they could.
Well, we should take some mugshots really quickly.
Yeah, let's take some photos.
Get against the wall, yellow one! Against the wall!
Oh, she's guilty! Look at that face!
Look at the face! Sideways! What are we booking her for, chat?
All right.
And the side! I would never commit a crime.
Investigating us without a warrant. I think we have illegal substances.
Okay, what's Watson concoction, of course?
Well, we'll have this... this footage investigated later in the back.
But for now, we have to actually go by the script, okay? Enough of this.
Go by the script. Okay, fine.
We have some games prepared, so let's do this! All right, let's go!
Get rid of those. Okay, I'll put this back in the 虫眼鏡 stand.
Get rid of those. Okay, I'll put this back in the magnifying glass stand.
Yeah, put those back where you found them, okay? Okay.
I need those.
So, everybody! Are you ready for some fun?
Yes! Sure! I'm up for anything!
The first game that we're playing today is...
Telephone Charades!
Telephone Charades / ジェスチャー伝言ゲーム
Telephone Charades
Well, since we're here in the highest quality of 3D, we want to show it off to you guys with this special game.
I will explain the rules to you guys.
Okay. Rules, rules, rules. I love rules. Rules are my favorite.
Right, right. So, the first person... we're gonna stand in a line, okay?
Standing in a line.
And the first person on the either the most right-hand side or the most left-hand side will get a clue that everybody else doesn't get to see.
We have to close our eyes, yes.
And then the person taps on the next person's shoulder, and they may open their eyes and they act out...
...well, for example, if Calli's first...
...she will act out to the other person. Yes.
And then, we only have 30 seconds for that, and there's no talking allowed!
So, how will that go? I wonder. You gotta do your best to show everything with your body.
Okay.
So we'll go by the order of: Calli, please, at the right over there, you're perfectly in the spot.
And then Ame, please. Okay.
Then Ina. That's me.
Gura. Gura-gura-gura-gura.
And then it will be me! Let's see how that goes! Okay.
All right, everybody close your eyes! Okay, let's start! No looking! Don't look, don't look, don't look!
For real, don't look! Show it to me.
Answer: Octopus / タコ
Answer: Octopus
Oh boy... This is going to be interesting. Got it.
No talking! 30 seconds. Ready? Can I turn around? Can I turn?
I think so! All right, Ame. Oh, okay.
Check this out. What the... what is that supposed to be?
Oh, okay, okay. Oh, that makes... okay.
I think I'm ready. I think I'm ready.
Okay. Can I look? Yeah, Ina look.
Do your best! がんばれ, がんばれ! Oh yeah!
Do your best! Do your best! Oh yeah!
Very nice! Yeah, keep it up! Oh, I think I get it!
You ready to go on? I don't know!
I'm just doing what she did! Okay, okay, okay. Gura!
Put your back into it, Ina!
Put your back into it!
What is happening?!
I don't know what's happening!
You gotta really move with it.
Okay. Okay.
You got it?
You got it.
Ina, nice legs.
Hi!
Oh, pretty good.
Okay, pretty good.
Those moves!
Oh, okay!
It's moving!
Wow, wow, wow!
Okay.
I feel things I've never felt before.
Can I stop now?
Oh yeah, you can stop.
Yeah, you can stop.
Well, I-I would say that is a mating dance?
Well, I would say that is a mating dance?
Are you serious?
Yes.
What part of that looked anything like a mating dance?
It was a mating dance! Does it attract you?
Was my... was I...
What did you think it was, Gura?
What do you think, Gura?
Yeah, what did you think it was?
I thought it was... interpretive dance.
Oh, okay.
She doesn't know either!
Well, okay, I thought it was swimming.
That's what I thought.
With the arms more like drowning.
But then she did this, I was like "what's that"?
I was talented!
I interpreted it!
Okay, okay. So yeah. Well, shall we look at the real...
The real answer!
The answer is...
Octopus!
Answer: Octopus / タコ
Answer: Octopus
You should've seen the way I was moving my legs. It was insane.
I see it now, I see it now.
Maybe...
It's difficult with only four limbs, alright?
No, it's not!
Shut up, Ina!
I did my best out there! Only four limbs!
Well, okay, okay. That was okay, I guess, but let's do a second round, alright?
We can try again! We'll switch up the order, so who wants to go first?
I'll go first! I'll go first!
Okay!
I'll fix what you couldn't do, Takanashi.
I don't want to be last!
I'll be second-to-last!
Oi, oi, oi!
I'll be after her.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
Who's in the front?
No, you be like...
Give me a sec, I'm at a FamilyMart.
The next one, however, will be more like a situation rather than an animal or whatever.
And you guys will not see the answer either until the end, so have fun guessing with us, alright?
Everybody! Chat, get it right!
Close your eyes!
I'm trusting you, Ina! I'm trusting you!
Do your best, Ina. I'm counting on you.
Ah, wait.
I think I got it. I think I got it.
Okay, okay. You can turn around, Calli.
Okay! What do we got? Not talking...
Oh, what is it this time? Oh, got it!
That's kind of cute! Okay, aww.
Wow, wow! Open your eyes!
Hi!
Ohhh! I mean, you were making noises though.
I'll forgive that one since it's not talking.
I mean, okay! Can I turn around?
Hi! Hello!
Hello!
What are you doing to me? Is that it?
Oh, that's cute! That's cute! Okay, alright.
I think Gura's gonna guess it! Alright.
Oh, that's easy! That's easy!
Okay, yeah, it seems easy! One of us is a genius!
Hmm-mmm-mmm, sleepy. Sleeping? Taking a nap?
Okay.
Oh! There's a little more to it!
There's a little more to it! Who messed up?
Well, I guess it was sleeping on someone's shoulder, right?
That's what I thought!
Because that's a situation!
I didn't know it was supposed to be on a shoulder!
That's why I was so close to you!
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, well, okay, so the correct one is...
Falling asleep on someone's shoulder!
Answer: falling asleep on someone's shoulder / 人の肩で寝る
Answer: falling asleep on someone's shoulder
Aww! I saw it in chat!
That was so easy! We did so well!
See? See? I told you, chat! Not bad, right?
We didn't mess up. Okay, so we got both wrong.
Hmm, shoot. Now, on which shoulder would you like to sleep tonight?
Which shoulder? Which shoulder would you like to sleep on?
I got plenty!
Isn't it nice to sleep on somebody's shoulder?
Anytime, Calli.
I got two pillows right here.
Ina...
Right here.
Comfortable. Pretty comfortable.
It's pretty much a blanket.
You don't want to sleep on Gura's hat? It's gonna be really soft.
Just like a thin outside... Stop being cute!
That thing is hard and squishy. What are you talking about?
It's squishy!
That fits firm.
Well, good try, everybody! That was fun! Yay!
Yeah! We didn't get it in the end, but it was pretty close the second one.
Yeah! I would say half correct. We have 0.5 points.
Not bad. Pretty good.
Hey, did you guys enjoy it in the chat?
Did you guys have a good time? Yeah?
Was it alright?
Yeah, well that was insane.
Anyone saying no?
I will find you, don't you dare.
You, and you, and you. I'm kidding.
Well, with that, I think we're gonna play
the next game right away because we're excited!
Oh my god!
Yay!
Where are we going? Where are we going?
Games, games, games!
For the next game, we're gonna go to another room though!
Bye guys!
See you in the next room!
New room! New room! Exciting!
I'm coming as well!
Let's go, team! Goodbye!
Ta-da-da-da!
Ohhh!
I know this place!
Tatami!
It's Fubuki-senpai's room!
Ah, so fun, so fun!
Wow, it's nice in here!
Mmm, yummy!
Welcome back everybody, thank you for waiting.
Yes, this place, you got it right,
it's Fubuki-senpai's place.
Thank you for lending it to us!
Wait a minute, is this her persona?
No, no, no, no. That's Orona, that's Orona.
Cute!
She's currently out buying milk,
she'll be back soon probably.
I hope she comes back.
So since it is a Japanese inspired room,
the game of course is also Japanese inspired.
But before we get started with that,
I want to hear some episodes from you guys!
Oh, oh?
Because we are all now together in Japan.
Some of us for the first time,
some of us maybe for the second time,
some of us like for the hundredth time.
But I think we all kind of felt
some kind of culture shock, right, until now?
That's true, surely we all have something like that.
Japan is very different.
So, anybody got something?
Oh, I do! I do!
Sometimes I gotta take a taxi, for various reasons.
Whenever I do though, the taxi dude is always like...
“Okay, so what's our route?”
I'm like “Huh? What do you mean what's our route?
I'm gonna leave it up to you.”
He's like “Well, we'll take this street,
and then we'll take this highway, is that okay?”
Yeah, that's fine.
“And then when you get off, we'll take this street,
but this street is a little far,
so we're gonna take this street instead. It's a shortcut.
Is that okay?”
Yeah, just drive the car, it's cool, it's cool.
He's trying to be polite.
I understand it, it's just that I guess maybe foreigners
are just so go-go-go, you know,
we don't usually care how we get there, it doesn't matter.
Speaking of taxis, you know how,
you know when you try to open the door for the taxi
because normally you do that in my country?
They say like “No, no, please don't touch it,
we're opening it automatically.”
So please stop, don't touch!
Also when you want to get out, same thing,
it always opens automatically.
So I'm like “Oh, okay.”
I got used to it now, but...
It's nice when you have a lot of stuff in your hands though,
because you don't have to touch the door.
That's true, that's true. Very free.
Oh the trains here are insane! They're crazy!
電車はすごい！
The trains are amazing!
All the train stations are like dungeons, they're crazy.
Oh yeah, lots of stairs. I get lost.
Yeah, you get lost a lot.
Oh yeah, you try to...
...it was like... and then suddenly you're like...
I remember that one time you walked too far ahead...
...and we were like, "Wait!"
Oh yeah, you didn't even check!
We walk in one line a lot.
You gotta keep up there!
I was like, "Oh no, I think the express is leaving!"
You gotta keep up.
Speaking of trains, another thing I noticed with the trains is that...
...in my country everybody's like loud...
...and they all walk and they scream and listen to music.
But in Japan, they're all quiet...
...and they're like, they're sleeping.
Yes.
Yeah, it's really, really quiet.
Right? I'm almost scared to talk.
And how do people not hold onto the things?
They just stand there on their own power stance.
Right? Power stance.
Well, I can't really. I wish I could hold onto Ina.
Yeah.
Surfing practice.
Hold onto me, Gura. I got you!
Any other episodes?
Oh, there's lots of...
...there's lots of text everywhere, like there's lots of advertisements and signs.
And it's crazy, and it's fun to test to see what I can and cannot read.
I wish I could read all of it because I want to know what it says.
It's very overwhelming though, right?
It is, but it's also fun because it's something I've never experienced.
I'm sorry, I took her on one of her first days...
...I took her to the most overwhelming stores ever.
Bic Camera and Don Quijote and the music!
I was also following you like a baby chicken.
Yeah.
I felt like a happy chicken mother, I guess.
Anyone else?
Oh, well, I have one!
I mean, I've tried not to, but I ordered a lot of Uber Eats while I was here.
And realized every time I'm like... they ping-pong on my door...
...and like open the door for them, they like... do a little bow.
I'm just like, "Oh, they're so polite, even like... even I'm not in front of them."
And like, you know, they usually have like a little message they can send...
...when they say like, "Thanks for the tip!"
Like, everyone says "Thanks for the tip!" and I'm just like, "I've never seen this before!"
They are so polite!
Every time, yeah. Sugoi!
Every time, yeah. Amazing!
Heh heh, Japan.
Well, those are some nice stories you got for me. Thank you very much.
But now, we're gonna play a game to hopefully learn even more about Japanese culture.
So, the game's name is... what's it called?
What is it called, Kiara? Ame, help her out!
It's not written there anymore!
Queen of... Queen of Japan... Tada!
日本の作法王決定戦
Queen of Japanese Etiquette
Queen of Japanese Etiquette!
Yatta! So, the rules are...
Hooray! So, the rules are...
...we get one theme, one situation or something like that...
...and then with the theme comes four different choices...
...that could be either wrong or correct. There's one wrong one.
And we'll have them be acted out by...
Who's really good at acting? Everyone!
We can all act! How about we all do it?
Okay, okay. Everyone together!
And then, once we're done acting, we'll decide together...
...we'll put our heads together and we'll think which one is wrong.
Alright! So, YouTube chat, let's go, let's go!
Yeah, you can guess too, chat!
First choice, first theme is... tada!
日常生活
Daily Life
Daily Life! Slice of Life!
Slice of life. Nichijou Seikatsu. Hmm.
Slice of life. Daily life. Hmm.
Alright, alright. Then let's look at the first one.
The first thingy... who's acting? We all could do it.
家では靴を脱ぐ
Taking shoes off indoors
Oh! Taking shoes off indoors. We're definitely not doing that right now.
Definitely. Oh, this is really bad, actually.
I hope Fubuki-senpai won't get mad at us for stepping on her tatami mats...
...I mean, with shoes on here. So, I'm sure it's fine, right?
Sorry! Suimasen!
Sorry! Excuse me!
They're slippers, right? Sumimasen.
They're slippers, right? Excuse me.
Yeah, but normally there's like a genkan...
What's genkan in English?
Entranceway, entrance door, doorway, something.
And there's a little, little... what do you call that? The stair?
The one stair. And before that, you always have to take off your shoes.
Shoes off! And in a lot of buildings, too.
They usually have like spare slippers that you can wear.
Yeah. You take shoes off even in like public buildings sometimes.
It's crazy!
Slippers! Or the recording studio!
Yeah, yeah. I've actually tripped on one of those...
...where it's got like the indent, like the ledge.
I was coming for the first time and I tripped on it.
Got too excited!
Yeah. So that sounds pretty good. Okay, next up...
相手の話の合間に「なるほど」をはさむ
Interjecting when someone's talking with short phrases such as "Yes," "I see," etc.
...is... interjecting when someone's talking with short phrases...
...such as "Yes", "I see", etc.
Yes, yes. Uh-huh. Hum-hum.
Naruhodo.
I see.
Ah, sou desu ne.
Ah, that's right.
Yeah, sou desu ne! Hai, hai.
Yeah, that's right! Yes, yes.
You can do it to me, because I want to say...
...what... after living in Japan...
...more and more I noticed that...
...I was, you know, getting that into my body.
And when I came back home to Austria...
...my... all my family, my friends, they noticed.
Kiwa-wa-wa-wa!
They were like, "You keep on reacting to what I'm saying!"
So, so, so. Yes, yes.
Right, right, right. Yes, yes.
So, but actually, I can't get rid of it anymore.
Wakaru. It's active listening. You're showing them you're listening.
I understand. It's active listening. You're showing them you're listening.
Especially when you're talking on the phone and stuff,
like they don't know if you're still listening, right?
Is that why you have to say like, "un, un"?
Un, un.
Just like "un" on the phone...
...like most people do.
Oh, yeah. True.
So did you girls also start doing that on your own by now?
Oh, yeah. I do it.
Definitely.
I do it. Oopsie.
Ame, what about you? You haven't been here for that long but...
Sometimes, I feel like it's something I would do anyways.
Oh, really?
うん、うん。なるほど。
Uh-huh. I see.
But I've been told that it's pretty cute, so...
I'm keeping it.
It is cute!
I agree.
Okay, next up!
Separating tissues depending on usage.
Alright Kiara, this one's all you.
What! Why?
You're the one who's been blowing your nose for the past 15 minutes.
This is true.
Exposed!
But, I'm not sure about this. I don't think this is...
Is this like separating the trash, like the garbage and recycling?
They separate the trash a lot, yeah.
But then like, not the tissues?
But then like...
Why aren't you guys playing this game?
Are we doing something wrong?
No, no, we're all doing it.
I'm separating the tissue. Pyun, pyun, pyun!
And then also in different trash bags? No way.
No way.
I mean, we can... we can put this one aside and kind of...
...look at what the last option is.
No, no, yeah. Let's look at the last one.
Last option. Last-o.
Expressing your gratitude before and after meals.
Ahhh, okay.
いただきます！
Let's eat!
ごちそうさまでした！
Thank you for the meal!
That was so synchronizing!
So "Itadakimasu" means "I'm digging in"...
...and "Gochisousama deshita" means "Thank you for the meal".
They do indeed say that. We all know that.
We know that!
Easy peasy. Easy answer.
Do we even have to think?
I don't think we have to think.
I've already forgotten them, so...
It's okay.
I think I remember. Yeah.
So the wrong one is number three!
Yaaay! やった！
Yaaay! We did it!
We did it!
そんなことやらない、right?
They don't do things like that, right?
Right, right.
That'd be too much work.
It's like, "this one I wiped my food with, you know?"
"And this one I blew my nose on." Like...
That's too... too much.
No one would play this game.
It all gets burned.
Yeah, I think so. Exactly.
That was... that one was pretty wild. Hmm.
So... what shall we do next?
Okay, notes. Okay, so with that...
...I think we all did so perfectly, we don't even need a second round!
Yaaaay!
Okay, but... there's something important...
...that everybody needs to pay attention to.
What? I'm listening.
We want to show off our merchandise one more time.
Oh, yeah! Alright!
Everybody in their individual showcases already showed up their individual merch.
We'll take a look at it another time, we'll start with Ina!
Okay! Ina-na-na-na!
My merch was... the Takodachi Ramen Stopper!
Basically, I think there's a few people who don't know how to use it.
Basically, when you, you know, cook cup noodles...
...the lid kind of like always like lifts up.
You put that little Takodachi Ramen Stopper on top of it, so that the lid doesn't lift up.
And then you get like the most perfectly cooked ramen, you know, cup noodles.
Or you know, you can just keep it as a figure.
That's helpful actually.
Next up! Kiara!
Yay! So my merchandise was...
...the Hot Phoenix Thermo Bottle and Bottle Case Set!
I'm so happy for this one, because it's thermos.
Everybody can use it. You can keep your hot things hot and your cold things cold.
It's perfect! And it even has a little Blue Buddy!
Is it thermal?
Yes, it's thermal!
Inside, yeah. And you can basically use the cap as a cup too!
Big brain!
I can put spaghetti in there.
Next me was... Calli!
Calli! Hello, there she goes.
Are you looking for a lovely gift for your significant other?
Perhaps you just want to look cool wherever you go.
Anyone can wear this cool piece of ice.
What is it? It's the Mori Calliope Pendant, baby!
You can also just display it in your house, because why not?
I'm genuinely asking you, why not? Buy it, or I'll hurt you.
Pretty please!
Buy one!
Thank you everyone! Appreciate you.
Okay, next after me was...
Goobidy boobidy booba! Googoogoogoo!
What was your merch?
It's a...
...bag. There it is.
Tell us about it.
Bag.
What kind of bag is it?
Blue bag.
Blue bag. The shoulder bag.
With strap!
Bag with strap.
It's so cute!
You can fit so much power in here. Bag.
I want one.
And what is it inspired after?
It's my... my bag.
Yama yama yama yama yama! I'm in my casual outfit!
That's right!
Wait, is that the thing you're wearing now?
No, not this!
That's just my uniform!
It looks like someone stole your sweater and made a bag out of it.
Yeah, that's not the worst thing they've made out of it.
Recycling!
That's a good point.
Okay, and a tissue... a tissue!
Who is next?
Last but not least, we have...
...Amelia Watson! Come over!
Hey! Ta-da!
There we go!
Oh my god, you have the hat I'm wearing right now!
On sale today!
Can I take it off and try it on?
No!
I'm gonna have to snatch it!
I want to sniff it!
But I like hats!
No! You guys are gonna do weird stuff with it, like smell it!
I want to wear hat!
The hat does not smell like Amelia Watson, okay?
That's a lie!
It's authentic!
Make it smell like you.
They all look so good! Make it smell like you!
They haven't been on sale yet, but they will go on sale...
...after this stream! Yes!
So exciting! Wait, there's one more thing.
One more?
But wait, there's more!
Ta-da!
What do we got?
Ta-da! It's time!
Wow! Of course, we have acrylic stands too!
These will be out on sale March 5th right after this stream.
Please check the shop page for details. Let's take a look at them!
一緒に見ていきましょう。
Let's take a look at them together.
Ta-da! These are so cool!
We can all do our poses!
Oh yeah, I'm holding an invisible book.
Okay, pose, baby, pose!
Wait! Give it your best, ladies! Do it!
Nice!
Yay!
So, if you want these at home, you can buy them together...
...or you can buy them separately, however you want!
Wow, they look really cute! Indeed!
So, what do you guys think of these?
They look so great, I want one! I think they're pretty cute.
Okay, how was it so far, guys?
It's so fun! I'm having a lot of fun!
I'm so happy we got to collab!
Yeah! Yay!
We're together! We're together! We're together!
We're together! Finally we're together!
Can we... can we have a little request?
なに なに?
What is it?
It depends... Can we... can we hug?
Hug! Hug!
Ame, you smell good!
I love everyone!
Yay! Happy!
Cute! Yay! So that was really healthy!
Everything! We actually wanted to talk a little bit...
...about our... our... this collab...
...maybe pick up some comments?
How's it going, guys? Did you post some screenshots?
#Myth3Dkitaaa! I hope you did!
I hope you did! Sniff sniff!
Group te-te, yes!
What was your favorite part so far?
Darn it! I'm asking you guys too, what's your favorite part?
What's your favorite part? Gura, what's your favorite part?
Finally being together... and game fun! Game fun!
Game fun! I like beating up Amelia!
Oh! In... I did not like that!
Yeah you did! You're lying to us, she liked it!
She liked it, yeah! She really liked it!
She liked it, yeah! She's lying, she liked it!
She wanted it! I did not like it!
She wanted it! Her dream came true!
Yay! Done it, done it!
As for performance, they liked the song, they're talking about the music.
Oh yeah, the SFX... I only wish we had more...
...more dancing!
You wish we had more? Oh!
I think they want some more.
There might be more... That is very possible.
Of course, I promised you, pinky promise, that there will be more!
That's right! Now a performance, one or two, who knows?
It's coming up! All right!
But we gotta go to the stage for that. Okay!
We're going already. Which way is it?
Thank you for the guests and for letting us do this!
Thank you for everyone! Thank you so much!
It went by so fast, we had such a nice time!
Yay yay yay!
All right! We love you! Love you!
Which way should we go? Which way are we going?
This way? This way? I don't know, this way!
いくぞ!
Let's go!
Loading screens too, we love the loading screens!
Come on Gura, this way Gura!
Now Loading
Non-Fiction
Lyrics: Mori Calliope/Elliot Hsu
Composition・Arrangement: Elliot Hsu
Somewhere's upon a time is not where Myth belongs
Through the faded lines of word and rhyme is a hidden song
Though fractured deeply, warped by sorrows, time and time again
Take my hand and enter our pretend
My silent skies, the moon's still shining, enlightening those alone
Lost souls who hear a song when gone astray
Those stripes upon our lives stay in the light now
When forced to behave, we stay and say
Be brave!
In a non-fiction, we souls reach out
And pen toward every page
We ignite, come alive, let the starry night
With the fire, no doubt, and take our way
Like a fairy tale where love prevails
The painful now we move relentlessly on by the light
Your spark has burst into the dark
Someone's upon a time is not where a voice gets heard
Will the faded lines of speeding time make us slight? Less words.
When kindness runs dry, a soul on fire is driven to react
And when burning flames attack
We will never be to black
No fate it seems, not a dream or a trick of light
Always make us see, take a seat, it's our glorious time
Who crossed the line, the voice inside that is real as they say
Kind of souls who choose the fate
We could never lose our way
My starlit skies, and the moon's shining
Inviting those along
Lost souls who hear a song when gone astray
Those stripes upon our lives stay in the light now
When forced to behave, we stay and say
Be brave!
Defiant 'til the end as the screaming begins
A brand new burning ember, so unyielding
Your love's giving me wings
While wading through the mud for the best time
I’ll let my soul be for our life
Set every fiber in motion, now we ride
In a desperate shout, our souls reach out
To fathom forever space
We ignite, come alive like a starry night
With a fire, no doubt, you can’t take away
Rise above any care, what the world may bear
Cause today, maybe we will joyfully hover by
Despite hopeless days or just far off ways
Nothing breaks, we will lead with all of our hearts
And smile...
...side by side...
...among the stars
Take off and fly, the longer we wait
The stronger it makes us as we fight every fate
Strength, to finally defeat
This journey of a thousand years to me
Journey Like a Thousand Years ~千年の旅~
Journey Like a Thousand Years
All right, all right!
Hands up, hands up!
Okay!
Songs unknown, enchanted by rhyme
Hidden wishes granted by time
Our longest hopes connecting the dots
Feel like echoes of ages gone by
Made a splash, but found I was free
A fish out of water, bound to the sea
Then reckless I dived, but you're right by my side
I bet this moment is how we can ride
Connecting songs across the sky
Take off and fly, the longer we wait
The stronger it makes us as we fight every fate
Strength, to finally defeat
This journey of a thousand years to me
Witness the fire in our minds, burning inside
Rising again from the ashes
Every bruise and the scratches makes us feel more alive
We never give up, never give in no matter what’s ahead
Instead we’ll crush the worries aside
If there's no world for us to touch or to see
We'll make it ourselves and make the memories
There ain't a mystery our brains cannot solve
We just shine brighter, grow tired, evolve
Connecting songs across the world
Take off and fly, the longer we wait
The stronger it makes us as we fight every fate
Strength, to finally defeat
This journey of a thousand years to me
At the end of this world, where's our fighting chance?
Nothing's changing, it's always the same story
Staged with a difference
Seek out a happy end, for me and my friends
And don't you give up on us just now
I want to see you smile
Find my way to you somehow
Take off and fly, the longer we wait
The stronger it makes us as we fight every fate
Strength, finally defeat
This journey of a thousand years to me
Let’s try, it can’t be denied
The wish in my heart is you right here by my side
Strength is all that we’ll need
I won’t wait a thousand years to be...
MYTH 3D STREAM
Mar. 5 12 PM (JST) / Mar. 4 7 PM (PST)
#Myth3Dkitaaa
Hoo!
See you then, guys!
Bye!
MYTH 3D STREAM
Mar. 5 12 PM (JST) / Mar. 4 7 PM (PST) #Myth3Dkitaaa
HOLOLIVE ENGLISH -MYTH- MORI CALLIOPE TAKANASHI KIARA NINOMAE INA'NIS GAWR GURA WATSON AMELIA