(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Hi.
Aha! Aha, I thought...
...I thought I was going to burp,
and then I thought,
imagine if the first thing I say when I'm here...
...is just a burp.
That would have been quite...
...that would have been something.
Anyway, hi! Hi!
Hi!
Hi.
I was... can you hear me over this...
...jazz band? Let me calm down...
...let me calm down the brass real quick.
Oh, is it fine? You hear me.
Ah! Hello!
It's my birthday today!
What was I going to say?
Oh, I was going to say,
I was so nervous before the start of the stream.
I was just saying "Ah" into my microphone like that,
but like really quietly and like sensually.
Well, not sensually, I was just saying it quietly.
And I was listening to my heartbeat so loud and so hard.
You can hear it. I can like hear it in my throat.
That's kind of gross, isn't it?
Ew, did you know there's a skeleton inside you right now?
And next to the skeleton, there's like hearts and stuff.
Did you know there's like squishy pieces inside of you?
There's a skeleton living inside you,
and he has a collection of other squishy things. Ew.
I'm also incredibly fidgety today because I'm so nervous.
Anyway, today's my birthday.
What was it?
Happy birthday to me.
I'm 9,303.
I look like a baby...
...um, but I...
...I can't rhyme with "E".
Dooba-dooba-doom. Ah.
Okay, just making sure. Is this pre-recorded? No.
Sucks to suck.
I'm sorry, I can't say that.
I can't be... I can't be...
...I can't be like that already. I'm sorry if I'm a bit on the...
...um, I'm gonna bite you.
Don't say anything mean to me. It's my birthday.
Do you see this face? When you're bullying me...
...this is the face you're bullying. Do you see this?
How could you? How could you?
This is what you're being mean to.
I can't bully the birthday girl. It's not fair.
Or is it that you can only bully someone on their birthday?
Or... Well, technically bullying, I guess, is... it hits a bit harder when it's your birthday.
Oh my goodness, do we have stuff to do!
Do I have this... not the brain for it.
So much to do, so little brain space. So little brain activity.
I can't hear over the jazz band, but you guys seem to be okay with it.
I just want to say thank you guys for coming.
Thank you for being here. Thank you for all of my birthday wishes that I saw on Twitter.
And all of you here saying "Happy Birthday". Thank you so much.
Alright, chill out, jazz.
Thank you guys. I really do appreciate it.
It makes me feel very warm and fuzzy.
I was having a chat with...
...uh, Staff-san, Ma-Man-san, management...
...and I was talking about how... how easy it is for me to cry, especially on my birthday.
I was like, "Oh boy". Because they came to me and they were like, "Girl, you know..."
...we got a... we got a gift for you from quite a few EBIs."
And I said, "Oh no. Is this..."
...is this going to be my... my big cry?"
"My big unconsol- unconsolable... my big unconsolable cry session on stream?"
It's like almost every year I have at least one.
At least one big cry-fest because I'm a big baby.
I'm a big cry baby. And that's okay. That's A-OK.
Oh my god, I forgot to tell you about my birthday cake!
So, my birthday cake... can you guess what kind of cake it is? Hmm?
I got a... don't guess, I'm gonna tell you.
I got a strawberry cake. It's got like whipped cream and strawberries.
Did you guess? Yeah, strawberries.
My favorite. My favorite. I could eat my weight in strawberries in like two hours.
Give me two hours and I'll eat an entire thing of strawberries.
Yeah. Also, do you see your little... do you see this? The little emojis on the side?
I can see all your emojis. So if all you guys put in the poopoo emoji...
...it would just be a stream of poopoo.
But I'm seeing a lot of... what do I see? Hearts, hundred... likes stuff.
I don't think the custom emojis go through though.
But yeah, hello! Thank you! Thank you for the hellos and the happy birthdays.
Happy birthday, happy birthday.
Ah, one year older. Isn't that weird to think about?
See, the problem around my birthday is I start to do a little too much deep think... and next thing you know I'm spiraling.
Like, "Oh! I'm birthday!" And then you think about the planet, and then the spinning of the planet...
...and then all of the planets... and then I start thinking about UFOs.
And then I freaked myself out really bad and I had to go to bed.
You ever do that? Don't let the brain run too fast.
Because sometimes it runs down really scary places. UFO!
Oh boy, what do we have planned for today?
I guess we could... we could take a peek at the birthday gift that a big group of you worked on for me.
I won't cry, I promise I won't cry. Pinky promise.
And then afterwards, I have some gifts for you.
...is, uh...
It's like, think of it like a goody bag.
Do you guys remember getting goody bags
when you went to birthday—
Oh wait! Oh my god, I forgot to tell you about that.
Do you remember...
Do you remember when you were a little babby
and you would get catalogs in the mail,
and they would have themed character
birthday party packs?
I was looking—I was looking them up
because I really wanted to do one.
Don't judge me, but I really wanted to do one.
And I was thinking like,
"Oh, kids these days, I bet you see like..."
"...uh, you probably still see like princesses
and like Barbie..."
"...and like Hot Wheels." And I was thinking,
"Oh, Bluey and stuff like that."
And you know what? They still have them!
I didn't do it this year,
but maybe next year...
...I'll throw myself a Bluey birthday party.
Bluey the dog. Yeah.
Because I can. And that's the magic of it.
So if you want to do that for your birthday,
I think you should do it.
You should get a piñata too, and beat it up.
All's I'm sayin'. Oh! Oh yeah, remindin' me.
Because yours used to do like goody bags
when you went to birthday parties...
...like in school and stuff. That was like the best part.
Is you go to the birthday party, and you give a gift,
but then you get the goody bag at the end
that's got like a tattoo and a slap bracelet.
So think of my gift to you as your...
...goody bag.
Yeah.
Also, I always for—I like—I keep forgetting
that I have to let myself breathe,
but I don't like the silence of when I'm breathing.
It makes me wildly uncomfortable.
But if I don't swallow and I don't breathe,
then I won't be able to talk anymore.
Somebody—somebody flick me in the forehead
and tell me, "That's—just don't do that. Just breathe."
Ah! A Gura bag? A Goo—a Goobi bag?
I put my goo in it.
Hmm.
Tasty, I guess.
Tasty, I think. Uh, okay!
So a gift to me from a very large group
of you is...
...here, I have it here. We're gonna take a—
we're gonna take a walk through it.
It is nearly 200 pages, from what I can see.
I don't think we have time to go through
all 200 pages, but...
It's—it's called "Nyuman Around the World:
Wish You Were Here".
And these look like all postcards.
Can you see my cursor? No. Okay.
Oh, sorry by the way, I had to cover you guys up.
I apologize.
So I want to see what this is.
I went this far because it told me how to view it.
Thank you very much.
This is actually really helpful. So...
"Hello, Hola, Bonjour, Guten Tag, Ciao,
Konnichiwa, Ni Hao, and Howdy Gura!"
"Chumbuds from all around the world braved
the most difficult challenge just for you."
"They touched grass!"
Wow!
Did you bring me back any? Mmm, grass.
"It was no easy feat, but with a little Gura
by their side, they gathered the courage..."
"...to make this one-of-a-kind book."
A group of dedicated Ebis were able to take
the valiant efforts of your international
community and make this travel journal
be filled with breathtaking scenery,
interesting attraction spots,
and silly Goomba sightings.
I'm very excited.
"We hope we can give you the feeling as if
you actually traveled to these places..."
"...perhaps even give you motivation and ideas
for your next trip. Let's enjoy this world..."
"...together, the GG team."
Travel journal and message screeners...
...by Zanme, Pommes, Afree, and Remu.
Communication and translation...
...Zanme, Afree, Pomme, and Lzmt.
Hi guys! Our graphic design, book logo...
...is by Shskr. Front and back covers by Advvcr.
This is pretty cool.
North America.
Is it like postcards? Gosh!
Artwork based on Lake Louise.
Louise? Or is that a V?
See, the problem is now is you're gonna really
get to see how much I can't read.
It's cute, it's based on a real lake in Canada.
Right, that was Canada.
Okay, okay.
By the way, I'm very worldly.
"New York, New York, submitted by Marcinie."
Oh please tell me I said that name right.
Marcinie? So did you guys like—wait.
Calgary—Oh my god!
Okay wait, we're gonna read a couple pages.
"Nendo Gura and the view from the tallest
building in the United States." It was the—
Oh, excuse me, "It was the third time I ever
came back to NYC..."
"...but it will never lose its magic."
I like heights and tall buildings, so for me the number one thing is to go...
...to all the observatory decks to the public and taking pictures of the breathtaking skyline.
I've been here! This big pointy building, I've been here!
Yeah, I wanted to use the bathroom at the top, tippy-tippy top...
...because then I could say that I went to the bathroom in the world's tallest building.
Which is not something that... current me... past me thought that was really funny...
...but current me thinks that's not exactly something... that's not a topic you bring to the dinner table.
Uh... so I didn't actually do it, so I can't actually even say that I... haha!
I, I... did you know? Did you know that I...
I... anyway...
The variety of different kinds of museums is fascinating and one of my favorites is the American Museum of Natural History where I took photos with those sharks.
OMG NYC!
I've not been... I don't think I've been to the Museum of Natural History.
I don't think I'm a very good museum-goer. I get really bored...
...really easily, which is really bad.
I need to go to like... like museums for children because they have all the stuff you can touch.
If a museum has touchy stuff then I'm fine, but if it's just a bunch of little placards...
...I probably wouldn't be okay. I'd be a little itchy.
Do I touch grass often? No. No.
It's good for you though.
So from Calgary, Alberta, which is Canada, did you know that? By Kilderan.
I'm so sorry, the text hurts my eyeballs, I can't really see... uh...
Hey Goob, allow me to introduce Fish Creek Provincial Park in Calgary, Alberta, Canada...
...one of the largest urban parks in North America, America!
I feel like... I feel like I'm being chosen to popcorn read but in school, and I'm really bad at reading in front of the class.
Um, it stretches 12 miles east to west coast, across the city and covers an area of around 5.2 square miles.
I can't visualize that. Can you give me that in... uh... how many hot dog... how many Fenway Franks is that?
How many hot dogs is that?
The park contains 62 miles of trails for walking, hiking, biking, picnic areas, fishing spots, and even an artificial lake for swimming.
Do you mean like a man-made lake? Because calling it artificial makes it sound... it makes it sound like a swimming pool.
Technically a swimming pool is an artificial... it's an artificial body of water. Alright, touché.
Much of the park is forested and is home to a wide variety of wildlife including at least one pack of ravenous wild Dino Gura.
Be cautious, especially during mating season.
I hear they are very unsafe. Um... beware ravenous packs of Dino Gura. Look at these terrifying beasties.
Don't want to get cornered by a bunch of these. They're not particularly good at stalking, but they are very cute.
And can convince victims to part with their food. Yes. Don't let them near your ankles.
Orlando, Flor... Wait, is there chapters in this? Holy moly.
Orlando, Florida and Rosarito, Mexico. Pokifan went to Orlando, Florida.
I knew Gura liked Disney a lot. Uh, yeah.
So I had to take her with me on a trip to Disney. Well, almost. It's not quite Disney, but Disney Springs of Orlando instead.
We came with a group of friends for a Pokémon Go event and had lots of fun catching Pokémon, eating tasty sweet treats, finding sea monsters, and seeing a fight between a dragon and a knight.
In Disney? They got medieval fights in Disney? Medieval joust fights in Disney?
Gura also tried to eat some of the fish at the Rainforest Cafe, saying 'Just one tiny bite, please' with a cute face...
...as well as meeting some of her dino ancestors at T-Rex Cafe.
Man, that is so cool that you actually brought Dino Gura to all these places, or your Nendoroid.
Pokifan! Also, I didn't know people still played Pokémon Go. I thought that was done, did, and no longer done in 20... what was that? 20...
...teen or something, but then again,
when I was in Japan,
I went to this place,
I don't remember who I was with,
I think I was with Ame.
But we went to this place... was it Ina?
It might have been Ina.
I don't remember.
I don't remember, but they had like
the life-size Pokemon GO trainers
in this really brightly lit room. It hurt my eyes,
but it felt like I was transported to another place.
It was pretty cool.
And then Esteban went to Rosarito, Mexico.
Puerto Nuevo is a fishing village
right next to the beach in Rosarito.
It's famous for serving some of
the best fried lobster in the world.
Legends say that sometimes you can spot
a big fish at this location.
Oh yeah?
Which one? This one?
Listen, when we migrate,
we just end up in different places.
That's just what fishies do.
We went to... oh god,
Ciudad de México?
Oh my god, I wish I could pronounce these better.
Oxford, Ontario.
Wait, I see meat stick.
I see flowers.
Somebody's going to be tortured medievally.
M... M... Maine.
Minnesota.
Massachusetts.
Oh god, Dino sighting on the east coast.
South Carolina.
The Goobs! In Tennessee. Are you kidding me?
There's literally a place called The Goobs.
I'm getting sidetracked. I've gotta keep going, but
I love this. Thank you guys so much.
Alberta, Canada. That's so pretty.
Look at the color of the water.
It looks like my bath after I put
a bath bomb in it.
It's so blue. Lake Astor?
Is it Astor or Oster?
I'm stupid, don't answer that.
Baja California, Mexico.
Wait, is it Baja or Baja?
See... this is embarrassing.
New York.
La Rumorosa.
Southern Maine. Vernon.
Buffalo, New York.
Coastal...
It's the- it's the shark girl.
I've seen her on stream before.
Chihuahua, Mexico.
New Orleans.
Oh my god.
Minnesota, Hawaii, Illinois.
So this means that a bunch of people,
if you guys brought out your Guras
around other people,
that means that maybe like
the government started tracking all these sightings.
Imagine if they really registered me as a cryptid.
Or not me, but technically Gura.
Because people kept saying,
"Hey, what is this thing?"
"This thing we keep seeing everywhere?"
And now you're on a government watchlist.
Pizza time!
Cute!
Wait, Europe?
You guys went to Europe too?
England?
Oh, definitely government watchlist.
100%. This is amazing.
This is...
I feel... I feel...
I'm feeling things.
I'm getting emotional.
Asia, Oceania.
We have cosplay Guras!
We have Mumei. We have Muna.
We actually have Moom and Kro-id as well.
Thank you guys. This is amazing.
It's like 200 postcards
to me, from you.
Oh my god, I went to Brazil!
I literally went to Brazil
thanks to you guys.
Fishtival!
And then there's messages.
This is where I'm gonna cry.
Oh... this is it.
This is where I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna cry.
I can't though, because we have...
Oh my god, the tractor!
Is that a John Deere?
I didn't realize how expensive these things were.
John Deeres?
I don't know why, I watched a tractor comparison video...
...and it was like, woah!
Is that Danny DeVito in a shark hood?
That's amazing. Thank you guys.
This is incredible.
Every year, you guys spoil me so much. I just...
I'm very excited. I'm very excited to read all of these.
Thank you so much, everyone.
Thank you so many of you...
...so many of you put so much work into this. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thank youuu~
Now.
I do believe it's time for your goody bag.
If you'll have it... um...
If you would like a goody bag, I have a goody...
...a bag of goodies for you.
It's a goody bag of goodies for you.
Um, so the first... I'm gonna open the goody bag for you.
So don't worry. One...
...the first goody in the goody bag is...
...uh, um, where is it? There it is.
Well, here's the first one.
Here's the first little something.
Emotes! Thank you Maerie!
It's new emotes.
New emotes!
A bit of a birthday tradition, but still...
...I think it's nice.
We have some fresh new emotes from Maerie. Thank you!
Let's see what we got.
I didn't really think the transparent background through did I? No.
We have an unamused Ebbi.
We have Dino Gura.
We have... looks like Elmo on fire meme.
Ebbi is on fire, but everything is fine.
Then we have a big ol' thumbs up.
Big ol' thumbs up.
Yeah, I think you should be able to use them... use them sooner than later.
But yeah, we have some emotes just for you.
Where'd I put these emotes?
Okay, emotes. Um...
Oh god, I didn't... I didn't think the rest through.
Okay, I didn't really... I didn't really think this through.
Um, but I hope you like the emotes...
...and also thank you Maerie for once again doing an amazing job with the emotes.
I'm sorry, I'm scatterbrained.
Um, okay, the next one is the big one.
It didn't fit in the goody bag, so I didn't really...
I don't really... um, anyway...
Um, so do you remember a long time ago...
...when I kind of in passing just...
...I mentioned like, uh...
Hey, wouldn't it be... wouldn't it be funny...
...if I made like a animated...
...a fully animated OP...
...but for myself?
It's done!
It's all done!
I'm freaking out! Do you want to see it?
It's all done. I didn't animate it of course, don't get that idea.
It was a big team project once again.
But hey, we did it! Woo!
And I would like to show you now.
It's pretty much what I have to say.
I'm very nervous... the nerves are getting worse as I go.
But yeah, I'd like to show you that now.
Chotto matte. Chotto matte.
Wait a moment. Wait a moment.
Please hold.
Let me prepare that for you very quickly.
Oh, which one is it? I don't know.
I have two here.
Okay, I would like to present to you...
...my very own animated anime OP!
Because why not? For you!
Okay!
Okay, how do I... um... br-br-br-br-br-br-br-br-ah!
Can you still hear me? Hello.
Okay.
I'm nervous. Okay, enjoy.
Always keep your eyes on the line of the horizon
Come on chumbuds climb on board and sail the brighter days
Rain's gonna bring you down and currents pull you out, ah
Blindsided with the 404
Try to make a splash but every streamer's crashed on you
But still we keep on spinning
Shabu shabu shabu shabu shabu shabu
Chop 'em up, stir 'em up, slice 'em up, and cook 'em up every day
次まだよーよーよー
The next is yet to come...
Shabu shabu shabu shabu shabu shabu
It's almost time to sail the ocean
9000 years gives you a perfect armor
With a hand to hold we're not alone
That heart of gold will lead us home
No one's ready, we've just begun
Hydra's setting's just more fun
So hang on both of us across
Help me finish the songs. Hydra setting!
Come sail away with me
I'm set to sea, I'm at the sea
The sun will shine on our eyes
They say dreams will carry
So no matter how we go just always go
I'm the same Same-desu!
I'm the same shark!
Always keep your eyes on the line of the horizon
Come on chumbuds climb on board and sail the brighter days
Aaaaah!
...eeee-ya... oh God.
Well!
Yay!
Okay, and what did we think?
I'm shaking. I'm shaking...
...and shaking and shaking and...
I really quickly would like to say a big thank you...
...to the team that made that possible.
You're going to be seeing it a lot, so... yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, okay, so I have a photo here...
...with all the names I would like to do a quick thank you for...
...because it would not have been possible without everybody involved here...
...minus myself. But we have the Hololive English team.
We have Jared, we have DuDu, 1211...
...we have Beast, we have Julius, we have Anna...
...Why am I shaking so bad? Kyun, we have Ruan...
...we have Richtou, we have Wiki and we have Wonder.
Uh, these are the fantastic people working with Tonari. Thank you very, very much Tonari.
Um, I'm so happy to have been able to work with everybody at Tonari again.
I'm such a big fan of Tonari. I hope you enjoyed... I did.
Aaaah! Maybe... maybe, maybe we watch again and...
Oops, wait, hold on... we watch again...
...and we can go frame by frame another time, 'cause there's a lot of little Easter eggs in there.
That's the thing I love about Tonari is that they are... they're Hololive fans.
So they always put a lot of little, little teeny tiny Hololive things...
...little Easter eggs in there that you wouldn't necessarily recognize if you weren't an avid Hololive fan.
Oh nice, we have the emotes working. That's pretty good.
The thumb is very cute. Like for example, one of the... one of the things that caught my eye...
...was when I did the heart and the 'U' was backwards...
...from the Christmas VR Chat stream. Like something like that would have probably gone over some people's heads, but...
...no! No! No! Thank you Tonari!
Oh, also funny story. Uh, there's a part where I'm shaking my butt...
...during the Shabu Shabu Shabu and it was funny trying to portray how I wanted that to look.
I had a meeting with Tonari, the team, and I was like, 'Hey, for this part right here...'
two different dances that...
uh I was going to do during those sections
and I said, can we replace this one with me shaking my...
my... my butt?
And the Tonari team was like, "What do you...?"
"I don't... I can't visualize that. What do you mean?"
I said, "I'm like bent over sticking my tail in your face and I'm shaking."
And then I remembered that it was reference from the... the New Year's stream
when I sent that and they were like...
They were like: "Shaking your..."
"Shaking your what? At the... what?"
"Shaking your ha-?"
I said, "Like this!"
And they like, "Oh, okay."
So just... just literally you... butt to the camera?
I said, "Yes!"
Exactly that.
It was very yabe but it was very comical.
It was very risky but it was very comical.
Very funny.
Uh I'm very, very happy. I'm very happy.
I'm very nervous still.
But um...
Yeah!
And there was a lot of other Hololive members in there.
We had Council, we had Myth, we had...
oh god, we had Chloe, we had Ollie.
Who else did we have?
I'm having a brain fart.
Kanata? Choco?
So yeah.
Thank you Tonari!
Um... okay, let me see.
Let me just keep up with my brain.
Ah, okay.
Okay.
I'm going to sing now.
I just want to sing you a song.
I would like to sing you a song...
...because I need to calm down.
We're going to do karaoke now.
Hope that's alright.
Is it going to be shaky? Probably.
Am I a nervous birthday girl?
Yeah.
Um... what should we sing?
Let's do this.
I just want to sing this.
Eenie, meenie, miny...
...moe.
To you...
Sing a song to you.
私は私
I am me,
あなたはあなたと
and you are you.
ゆうべ言ってた
You said so last night,
そんな気もするわ
or so it feels.
グレイのジャケットに
On that gray jacket,
見覚えがある
there's a familiar
コーヒーのしみ
coffee stain.
相変わらずなのと
"You haven't changed a bit,"
ショーウィンドウに
as we're reflected
二人映れば
in the shop window.
Stay with me...
真夜中のドアをたたき
knocking on the midnight door.
帰らないでと泣いた
Crying for you not to leave...
あの季節が　今
that season is now
目の前
right before my eyes.
Stay with me...
口ぐせを言いながら
while saying your favorite phrase.
二人の瞬間を抱いて
Holding onto our moments,
まだ忘れず
still not forgetting,
大事にしていた
keeping them dear.
恋と愛とは
That passion and love
違うものだよと
are different things.
ゆうべ言われた
You told me last night,
そんな気もするわ
or so it feels.
二度目の冬が来て
The second winter came,
離れていった
and it drifted away,
あなたの心
your heart.
振り返ればいつも
Whenever I look back,
そこにあなたを
I've always felt
感じていたの
you were there.
Stay with me...
真夜中のドアをたたき
knocking on the midnight door.
心に穴があいた
With a hole in my heart...
あの季節が　今
that season is now
目の前
right before my eyes.
あの季節が 今 目の前
That season is now before my eyes
Stay with me...
寂しさ紛らわして
Distracting myself from the loneliness
おいたレコードの針
The needle on the record I placed
同じメロディ 繰り返していた
It was repeating the same melody
Stay with me...
真夜中のドアを叩き
Knocking on the door at midnight
帰らないでと泣いた
I cried, asking you not to go home
あの季節が 今 目の前
That season is now before my eyes
Stay with me...
口癖を言いながら
While saying your favorite phrases
二人の時間を抱いて
Holding onto our time together
温めていた
I was keeping it warm
Stay with me...
真夜中のドアを叩き
Knocking on the door at midnight
帰らないでと泣いた
I cried, asking you not to go home
あの季節が 今 目の前
That season is now before my eyes
Stay with me...
Did you hear that?
Who is that?
Interrupting my karaoke.
Looks like the poor little Red Gura has to stay behind.
Uh-oh, spaghetti-o.
You want a what?
You want a battle me in karaoke?
How you gonna do that when you look like Flat Stanley?
Somebody better have a balloon pump,
'Cause I'm winning just by being 3D.
You still want to battle me? Okay.
What do you guys think?
Should we battle the Red Gura in karaoke?
What'd you say?
Did you hear that?
She said she's cuter than me.
What do you mean you're cuter than me?
I'm cute! I am Gura! I'm...
...this is... cuter than me!
Prove it!
What do you mean? Prove it? I can prove it!
I can prove it, but we're gonna have to step up the game, I think.
I think I want to squish this little challenger even flatter than they already are.
Do you hear me? You little red flat thing.
Let me get ready.
I'm bringing the big guns of cute, okay?
Give me two seconds, I'll be back.
You're gonna eat it, you little shart-stain.
語れない 眠れない 止まらない
Unspeakable, sleepless, unstoppable
あなたの見てる正体
Your true form that I see
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart no one can read
不可思議 知りたいだけ
I just want to know the mystery
嘘も 現実も
Whether lies or reality
どっちも 真実だったの
Both were the truth
本当よ
It's true
ひとりぼっち 何も無理強いしないで
All alone, don't force anything.
私 愛されたい
I want to be loved.
有耶無耶 サヨナラ 軽い目眩
Vague goodbyes, a light dizziness.
あなたのいない化粧界
A world of makeup without you.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical record no one can read.
自意識 溢れ出した
Self-consciousness overflowed.
言葉 世界空 いつも噛み合わないの
Words, world, sky, they never quite fit.
痛くて
It hurts.
毎夜 願うこと 何も疑わないで
What I wish for every night, don't doubt anything.
混ざり 溶け合いたい
I want to mix and melt together.
可愛くない 分からない 不遇存在
Not cute, don't understand, an unfortunate existence.
あなたと残す後悔
Regrets left behind with you.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical record no one can read.
五百回 繰り返した
Repeated five hundred times.
正しい夢は
The right dream is...
悲しい声は
The sad voice is...
美しい 疑わしい
Beautiful, suspicious,
羨ましいねぇ どれ
enviable, isn't it? Which one?
語れない 眠れない ドロメライ
Can't talk about it, can't sleep, Droomeray.
あなたが見てる正体
The true form you are seeing.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical record no one can read.
不可思議 知りたいだけ
Mysterious, I just want to know.
終わらない ことはない ドロメライ
It doesn't end, it never does, Droomeray.
あなたと跨ぐ境界
The boundary I cross with you.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical record no one can read.
一瞬時 傷口 舐めるの 知りたいだけ
Licking my wounds for a moment, I just want to know.
私は私のこと愛して何が悪いの? 嫉妬でしょうか?
What's wrong with me loving myself? Is it jealousy?
痛いだとか変わってるとか届きませんね そのリプライ
“You’re cringe” or “You’re weird” - those replies don’t reach me.
大好きなお洋服
My favorite clothes.
大好きなお化粧で
With my favorite makeup.
お決まりのハーフツイン巻いて
Styling my usual half-twin tails.
お出かけしよう 日傘持って
Let's go out, bringing my parasol.
ぼっちだって幸せだもん
Even alone, I'm happy.
チュ! 可愛くてごめん 生まれてきちゃってごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute, sorry for being born.
チュ! あざとくてごめん 気になっちゃうよね? ごめん
Chu! Sorry for being calculated, you're curious, right? Sorry.
チュ! 可愛くてごめん 努力しちゃっててごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute, sorry for putting in the effort.
チュ! 尊くてごめん 女子力高くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious, sorry for my high femininity.
ムカついちゃうよね? ざまぁ
You're getting annoyed, aren't you? Serves you right.
あなたはあなたのことだけどうぞ 私に干渉しないで
You should just worry about yourself, please don't interfere with me.
…ください
…please.
意味深なモノ 登るよ 結局
Climbing up something meaningful, in the end,
届きませんね その勝ち組
It won't reach those winners, will it?
その影口 重いヤツ底物
Those bad-mouthers are just heavy bottom-feeders.
お気に入りなら降るぐらい
If you like it, let it rain.
崩せない前髪 櫛で解いて お出かけしよう
Combing my unshakeable bangs, let's head out.
軽いオンナ 吹くな 負けんな
Don't talk like a flighty woman, don't lose.
重すぎるツノ
The horns are too heavy.
ちゅ! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
この時代生きてごめん
Sorry for living in this era.
ちゅ! 目立っててごめん
Chu! Sorry for standing out.
意識しちゃうよねごめん
You're bound to notice me, sorry.
ちゅ! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
自分磨きしてごめん
Sorry for working on myself.
ちゅ! ぶりっ子でごめん
Chu! Sorry for being a goody-goody.
虜にしちゃってごめん
Sorry for making you fall for me.
ムカついちゃうでしょ? ざまあ
It's annoying, right? Too bad!
趣味の違い 変わり者とばかりされても
Even if I'm called a weirdo for my different tastes,
負けたくない 怖くもない アンタらごとき
I won't lose, and I'm not afraid of the likes of you.
自分の味方は自分でやりたい
I want to be my own ally.
一番大切にしてあげたい
I want to cherish myself most of all.
理不尽な我慢はさせたくない
I don't want to endure unreasonable things.
それが私
That's just who I am.
ちゅ! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
生まれできちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born.
ちゅ! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so calculative.
人生 楽しんでごめん
Sorry for enjoying my life.
ちゅ! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for putting in the effort.
ちゅ! 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious.
女子力 高くてごめん
Sorry for having high femininity.
ムカついちゃうよね ざまあ
It's annoying, right? Too bad!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay...
Yeah, fine. That was cute.
It was fine. Whatever.
I was cute too.
Wasn't I?
Nemurenai... toroi mai... mmm mmm mmm
I'm not getting shown up in my own birthday stream!
Okay, fine. Whatever.
If you... blah. Whatever.
I still have a trick up my sleeve.
You've seen me be cute.
But how about a taste of...
...cool?
Can you do cool, you little red snot?
Wow, 25 points? Thank you.
All right, fine! Fine, you want some Cool Gura?
I'll do Cool Gura.
Cool...
...power activate!
I have copied you...
...and made of myself so crash and splash.
I play with my obsession...
...I feel the tension...
...I need percussion.
I would like to show...
...cut open my skull, look into my head.
I don't know why I'm so harsh...
...I could be so brash, I'm going to crash...
...'cause I feel...
I can always show my everything to you...
If this moment was for me...
I try to hear, lend my ear...
...for voices inside one link to join it all...
...together.
All the things I knew...
...the world I trusted would be the same.
If I remained inside my protective castle and cave.
I've had my eyes closed
Words are just a toy that people play with, it's superficial
I know the proof is out there, the hidden answer that someone left there
'Cause I feel...
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment works for me
I'll try to hear, blend my inner voices
Since I'm willing to join it all
If I can go travel back in time, start it all over again
Follow a calculated path to live
But one day I will come across the same feeling again
And know that it will carry over...
'Cause I feel...
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment works for me
I'll try to hear, blend my inner voices
Since I'm willing to join it all
So it goes again
ミラクルが崩す箱
A miracle breaks the box
秘宝に香るアズなでだ
Sweeping over the scent of treasure
デンジャラス マリンズ丸
Dangerous Marine's Maru
Ahoy!
さぞやデートのあと
Surely after a date
極上の海賊の秘宝
The finest pirate treasure
それは私
That's me
雨が船漂う
Rain drifts on the ship
香り元辿り笑わないで
Don't laugh while following the scent
ああ 来てみて
Ah, come and see
席次世界一 スーパーピチピチ
Ranked number one in the world, super fresh
むちゃくちゃ少女 捕まえたくない？
Don't you want to catch this crazy girl?
Yo-ho-ho get the treasure, maybe tasting me?
私の甘さが欲しいでしょう？
You want my sweetness, don't you?
Ahoy! Treasure Boy...
秘宝のにお...
The scent of treasure...
Ahoy! Treasure Boy...
優しく射して...
Pierce me gently...
Ahoy! Treasure Boy...
奔放の扉
The door of wildness
あ、あ、あ、な... まじで早く開けて！
Ah, ah, ah, na... Seriously, open it quickly!
あー、宝箱...
Ah, treasure box...
Showing my knee.
We will sail the seven seas.
七つの大海を。
Across the seven seas.
Summer sun's smiling with glee.
また、帆を懸け進むべ！
Once again, set the sails and move forward!
Shining your shore, marine.
また出会えるか、何想像してんの？
Will we meet again? What are you imagining?
Now please grant my dearest dream.
Open up this box.
Open it right now or I will scream!
Screamo-na-ocean!
Namae mo tamanyu-nori no Sasubee.
Kimi-tachi mo moga-man deki-nai.
You guys can't resist it either.
Yo-kara on the pleasure, maybe love of me.
Watashi no subete wo te ni irete.
Take everything of me.
Ahoy! Takarabako, kimi no saihou.
Ahoy! Treasure Box, your treasure.
Ahoy! Tabishite-go, hashitage deshou.
Ahoy! Let's travel, isn't it hashitage?
Ahoy! Sagashite-go, sashi wa nina-chau.
Ahoy! Let's search, it's becoming sashi.
Ah, ah, ah, ah! Dareka tasukete!
Ah, ah, ah, ah! Someone help!
Maji de eien no shizugi.
Seriously, an eternal drop.
Kimi-tachi nani kaba-itteru no.
What are you guys talking about?
Bakade-ru daru-wa katsuro.
Dakara ima sugu akete yo.
So open it right now.
Takara-bako...
Treasure box...
Anatara no sugu akete yo.
Open your soon.
Kimi, kimi-tachi, akete!
You, you guys, open it!
My, my, my... I mean, it's my birthday, I won, right?
You can't hear me, right? Okay, fair enough, fair enough.
A little red, where are you? Come here, you can join the stream now.
You've been nice enough. On one condition.
Okay. Oh. You did fine. You did great.
Whatever. Really pulling out treasure box. Okay, I see how it is. Fine.
Anyway, that was a fun little contest, wasn't it?
We have some merchandise to talk about.
Would you like to help me, Red Gura? I don't think she's gonna help me.
So I guess it's just on me, you guys.
So, we're gonna talk about, it is the time, it is the birthday merchandise time.
The link has been posted, I see, thank you, thank you Staff for helping.
So we're gonna go over the merchandise. Yay!
I'll let you out of the jar if you behave, you stinky little minnow thing.
Get out of here! What do you want? Where are you?
Why are you so... Oh, I did that wrong, that's why.
Merchandise! There's no link... Oh, maybe it's not live yet. My bad.
Birthday Celebration 2023. What do we got? Let's take a look.
Gura's PC/Tablet Case, featuring the birthday art this year.
Cute! My fellow iPad kids, it is time for us to have Gawr Gura themed tablet case.
It's cute though, it's got Gura sticker on it too. It looks like I did it by hand.
Cable Spaghetti Collector (Cable Tie).
It's funny because I was asked, what do you call this? And I said, 'Oh, it's the spaghetti collector'.
Because they asked me what I want to call this, and I said 'spaghetti collector'. So they literally named it Cable Spaghetti Collector.
It's a cable tie, it wraps up all your cables or your headphone cables or whatever's all tangled up.
...pencils, whatever you want to do really.
It'll help you clean up.
I desperately need these because I am the number one culprit...
...of cable spaghetti.
They're cute though, they have Ebi and Bloop on them.
And they're blue, the most important part.
What's next?
guRED and BLUera Glass Set!
Featuring today's competition!
Red Gura...
guRED versus BLUera.
Whose side are you on? Hmm?
Whose side are you on?
Is this gonna be like a Twilight thing all over...?
No, because at the end of the day, Gura is Gura.
And Gura cute...
...ish.
Kind of smelly though, a little bit.
Team BLUera!
They're cute though, they're by Same-anko.
I love Same-anko's stuff.
And it might be hard to see from the stream, but if you zoom in...
...the Red Shark and stuff has like an angry face,
and then the Blue Shark has a cute happy face. It's really cute.
Yeah.
You can drink the blood of your enemies...
...or your morning strawberry smoothie.
Whatever you desire.
And then, the item that I am most excited about,
that I... I am so excited about is...
He's real.
Ebi-chan is real!
You can get your hands on a big fat Ebi-chan!
Perfect for squeezing.
He's pocket-sized.
Or as I like to compare it...
Ebi-chan here is about the size of a healthy dill pickle.
A whole dill pickle. Nya.
And I scribbled my name on the bottom, just so you remember.
I mean, you could put your name on it if you really want to,
but I put my name on it.
I guess that technically means you're mine.
I can share though.
We have Ebi-chan.
I want to get a bunch and stack them on top of each other.
Yeah, he's like the perfect size to grip tightly in your hand,
so you could use him as a stress ball if you want.
Or, I don't know, hit it with a baseball bat.
Or... um... I don't know.
Whatever. If you need a little bit of pocket motivation...
He'll fit in your pocket.
If you have him. Or on the top of your head like me.
Thank you.
Ebi-chan. Ebi, Ebi, Ebi...
Put it in a jar.
You don't have to put it in the jar.
I mean, you could, but...
I would put Red Gura in the jar before I put Ebi-chan in the jar.
Ebi doesn't deserve it. Ebi doesn't deserve being put in the jar.
In the jar. No, chat, no!
No, my lovelies, please.
Think before you act.
What has this poor creature done to you?
What if he's too heavy and he can't even support his front side?
You wouldn't put a creature like that in a jar.
You must nurture him and caress his tall antennae.
And make cute heart shapes with it and send pictures to me.
Fry it? Mmm, it's gonna taste like...
...polyester and copper. Mmm, tasty.
Put some butter on that. Mmm.
Elevensies.
Alright, I see. Caress, you can caress the Ebi gently though.
He's very sensitive.
They're a sensitive crustacean.
Happy Birthday, Gura. Thank you!
Yummy yummy. Nani?
Yummy copper. No! Don't put... Don't put it in your mouth!
It's not meant for your mouth. Your mouth hole.
I love this little combo you guys can do now with the Ebi.
The Ebi thumbs-up affirmation.
The thumb-up affirmation Ebi emote. It's very cute.
Yes, this one.
I like it.
Let's see what else. And we're gonna be doing illustration!
Thank you, thank you. Sena, Sena-san!
Thank you. Otsuki! I'm gonna be hand-signing, again.
Let's everybody say a prayer that I can actually spell my name correctly.
For those of you that got my incorrectly spelled name last time, I apologize.
But hey, now you have proof that I'm a dum-dum.
Physical proof.
But yeah, I'm gonna be doing some more signy-signy-sign.
And try really hard not to, yeah, spell the name wrong.
Also... oh nevermind, I probably shouldn't say that one.
Yeah! Ta-da!
Plus a bonus for limited edition.
So those are limited.
I hate to say that...
...but they are limited.
Unfortunately, for now.
Maybe someday I'll just be able to give out whatever, whatever everybody wants in unlimited quantities.
The unlimited quant...
Is there a spelling mistake?
They always ask me...
...they sometimes they ask me, they're like, "Hey Gura, can you, can you guess this for, or can you look at this for spelling mistakes?"
And I say, "Yeah."
And then I don't really do it because I am the worst person to do that with.
I'm... don't, please don't ask me that.
It's sold out. Is it actually sold out, or is it just the website having to update?
Cause that, that is the thing that happens with like merchandise websites is that they usually just go, "Oh, we sold out," but it just takes them a bit.
It's not... is it actually? I don't think it's actually sold out.
Nah...
It's gone. Why?
Boo!
Limited is sold out. I'm so sorry.
Well, hmm... I'm gonna hold out hope that the website was... is being smelly.
The website's being smelly.
Well, um... maybe, maybe I know. I'll pull management aside and I'll say...
..."Because I'm the birthday girl..."
...as my birthday girl wish, I would like to ensure that everybody gets exactly what they want.
As I... since I am the birthday girl, I therefore would like everybody else to be a birthday person and get their birthday wish as well.
Yeah, let's see if that passes.
Pretty please, I have a thing of sprinkles right here. Because I eat them.
I just eat sprinkles out of the jar.
Pretty please, with sprinkles on top!
Pretty, pretty please!
Gawr Gura Birthday Celebration 2023 Merch List
Birthday Celebration 2023: On Sale June 21st
Why? Because. Do you guys remember when I used to drink maple syrup right out of the jar?
I used to do that. For those of you that don't know, I used to have a jar of uh, sugar-free maple syrup...
...that had like a baby bottle nozzle on the top and I would just pop it open...
...and take like a slurp in between the stream or something.
Ooh, yummy! Mmm, maple syrup! Mmm!
If only I had a mouthful of butter. "Isn't it too sweet?" No, not at all.
It's like baby food. Well no, I wouldn't give, I wouldn't give a baby sugar-free maple syrup. I'm just a big baby, that's all.
A baby bottle pop of maple syrup and yummies.
Whoa! Thank you guys, thank you everybody. Thank you for making this an amazing birthday.
A very, very amazing birthday.
Also, it's kind of funny. The theme was originally for my birthday like blues and, and yellows and cozy like that.
But then last minute I was like, "I need pink!"
I require pink and yellow and purple and polka-dot...
...and a cute birthday hat with cupcakes and like really cute everything and sparkles and stuff.
It's kind of... I don't know, I just think that's kind of funny. Oh well, still cute though.
Should we let Stinky out of the jar? Do you think she's been behaved?
I have her labeled as "Red Devil" in my, in my stream. Let's let you out.
I'll let you out just this once since you... you can come and hang out with everybody.
Oh, you're so cute when you're up close! Wow!
That's pretty cool. Sorry, she's talking to me, but you can't hear her.
Trust me, she's talking to me. Little goblin. Little goblin, little tiny little thing.
Little, I don't know. Little baby?
Little baby says she wants to sing another song. Is she whispering evil? No, no, no.
She wants to sing some more because she's feeling very proud of herself for winning... winning over the chat.
Winning, she says, she says she's just been winning.
Superior song choices. Okay, okay, okay.
We can sing one more song together, what do you guys think?
An encore! The winner was chat. Chat wins all along.
Everybody wins. Everybody a winner.
I like the "everybody a winner." Should we do an encore? Stinky smelly little fishy? Yeah?
Should we do it together? I think we should do a song together, what do you think?
I think that would be cute.
I think that would be a cute reminder that at the end of the day, we're all in...
...us together.
God, I'm so awkward. Maybe you should take over, Red Gura...
...'cause then maybe you won't be as awkward as I am. This is painful. Okay.
We're going to go ahead... We're going to go ahead and then sing something.
We'll figure it out behind the scenes, 'cause I don't... I know what we're going to sing.
I know exactly what we're going to sing.
Okay. You ready, Gur?
Gur... uh... Okay, she's ready.
All right. Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
Encore!
Always keep your eyes on the line of the horizon.
Come on, chumbuds, climb on board and celebrate our days.
Yeah!
Waves will knock you down, and currents pull you out, ah-ah.
Life hits you with the ocean...
Tryna make a splash, but every stream is crashed, oh no!
But still we keep on swimming!
鮫 鮫 鮫 鮫
Shark, shark, shark, shark
ちょっともくさつ 誘って 走り出そう 準備は Every day
A little silence, let's head out together, preparing every day
鮫 鮫 鮫 鮫
Shark, shark, shark, shark
吸いまで世 起きは浮きよう 良い商い 一緒に
To the edge of the world, life's transient, good trade, together
It's almost time, just give me a sec.
A thousand years to hook in a net...
With a hand to hold, we're not alone.
Got a high of go then head above... no wait...
The fun's just begun, being hydro-dynamic is just more fun!
So hang on, 'cause the water's dropped, here we go, down, down, down!
Come sail away with me!
Our future's beyond the sea, the sun rise shine on our lives.
This old dream we carry each.
So no matter how we grow...
...just always know.
あ、あ、鮫々です！
A, a, Am-same-same desu!
Always keep your eyes on the line of the horizon.
Come on, chumbuds, climb on board and celebrate our days!
Okay, everybody, that's it for...
...my birthday stream of 2023! Pew! Woohoo! Yeah!
I hope you enjoyed your time today with me.
Thank you very much for spending time with me and for saying hey after all this time.
I really appreciate it.
I hope you had fun. I hope you were entertained...
...even just a little bit. I hope... I hope your days are going well and your...
...your life is going well, honestly.
Thank you so much again for the support.
I hope you enjoyed everything that I've shown you today.
Huge thanks to everybody that has helped to make today's stream possible.
Thank you very much. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
And thank you to Manessan as well for helping me through all of this. I really appreciated it.
We have more fun stuff coming in the summer.
It's a big summer, you guys. I hope you're strapped in and ready.
Strap in, buttercups. It's going to be a big one.
I'm very excited, and you should be too.
Yahoo!
Also, there might be another bigger Gumba 3D live on the horizon...
...mmm, perhaps? Mmm, perhaps? It'll probably be quite a bit of ways from now...
...but just so you know, just another thing to look forward to.
Wahoo! Yippee-yippee-yippee!
Thank you though, guys. I'm excited.
Thank you as always. Thank you for everything. Thank you as always and forever.
Um, I'll see you around, okay?
Happy Birthday to me and to any of you if it's your birthday!
Happy Birthday. I'm sweating.
Thank you, guys. I hope you have a lovely day. I will see you...
I'll see you... trying to think of like a fun ocean word.
I'll see you in the, in the... ocean. I'll see you...
I'll swim by!
...at least not on this bed.
I'll see you.
Happy birthday to me!
Gooba, gooba-gooba, gubba-gubba-gubba-gubba, gooba!
Goodbye! Say bye, Gurura.
She said... Oh, I can't repeat that.
Bye!
Say bye, Gura. Say bye, Gura.
Bye-bye! Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
Bye... Bye...
See you!