(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Okay, we've reached the destination.
Right on time.
Is everyone ready?
You bet. Let's go.
Alright then!
Ready... set... Jump!
Havin' a blast!
We're ready to greet the world
We're voyaging forward with courage to run
toward a brand new start
Let's go live,
bridging the distance across the sea
Endlessly, cheerfully
meeting heart to heart!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah!
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far, but we're
striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the new dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll create every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
Smashing barriers left and right
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
So get together, let's reunite
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright!
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways
Discovering highways to everywhere
Step by step (Yeah!)
Gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation,
A dream unfurls
Let's make friends (Yeah!)
Making a moment of history
Joyfully, follow me
We'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now, setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question we'll break through!
Don't retreat! We'll keep aspiring to excel
That's our Myth! It's awe-inspiring going well
Represent! So light the fire and let's rebel
The future's brighter, we can tell!
We're ready to...
We're ready to change the world!
Medley, medley, medley, medley, medley!
What are you doing?
Oh you too? Both of you guys are acting a little strange.
We're doing crazy poses!
Why are they being so silly?
We got a show to do!
You guys have a show to do!
Ina, come on, come on!
頑張れ！
Go for it!
I know the floor is nice, but...
It is really nice!
It's smooth!
Minna-san, thank you for coming to the show today to celebrate Myth's...
Everyone, thank you for coming to the show today to celebrate Myth's...
...you guessed it, fifth anniversary!
That was the medley, a nice throwback. We've made so many songs together.
Nostalgic!
Putting it all together like that is like really emotional.
And it's not just like our fifth anniversary, it's also hololive English as a whole, five years!
We're so old!
Senior!
We're all yippee!
We're oldies, we also achieved so much in the last five years, you know?
We had three EN concerts.
My voice cracked, sorry about that!
And we had a lot of friends join us over the years.
And this, you know, in the end I'm just really happy to be performing with you guys. It's so much fun!
We can't get too emotional just yet, though, because we have a show to do!
Anyways, anyways, anyways, there's a hashtag right here, right here!
Take lots of pictures, screenshots and post them on social media. #Myth5years!
Make us trend!
If you want, you don't have to if you don't want to.
If you don't do it we'll be sad. We'll be angry.
We'll get you!
Also, besides that, everybody, this is important!
I'm just checking...
...making sure you guys are all here legally.
Did you guys all receive a ticket-sama? Hmm?
Did you guys all receive a ticket? Hmm?
Ah, it's me! It's me! That's me!
We look so cool!
Yeah, I think I gave you mine at the bar. It was kind of spicy, remember?
I... I accosted you on the street, if you remember correctly.
Oh! Oh! That's what you're up to.
I... I... I might have trespassed.
Ina wouldn't do such a thing!
Well... my Ninomae Ina'nis...
Nothing! I did nothing illegal!
Fine, don't tell me, keep your secrets. It's fine. I'm used to it in five years.
Now that we know that everybody's here with their tickets and they're allowed to be here...
...we'll be singing a lot on this stage today in different combinations and different fun songs and so on.
Floor!
Okay! Beautiful stage!
お洒落！
Stylish!
Fancy!
There's a chair! Test it out, test it out!
How much does that cost?
Couch! Can I lie on it?
Oh my god! The chandelier!
I really like that one.
Are we stealing that?
Is that a heart?
What's the heart for?
Looks expensive.
It does.
Wait, did it just change color?
It just gained some color.
Oh, why, I wonder?
Could it be that it's reacting to
everybody's reactions in the chat
and their feelings? It's changing color
according to that!
Are you guys getting excited?
So you guys have an important job to do now, right?
Yeah, it's just they're always doing something.
You guys are always doing things.
It must be their power...
...and their energy!
It's flowing through us.
Thank you.
Well, I look forward to seeing
how it develops from here out.
So, you know what you're gonna do, right?
You're gonna get out your keyboards,
and you're gonna type some things.
[Myth Typing Noises]
Hackerman! Yeah.
Give us your energy!
Give it to us!
Yeah, not like we're trying to
shake you down or anything.
I feel it! I'm shaking them down!
Oh, okay. All right,
we're choosing violence again today.
Why are you so violent?
It's supposed to be wholesome and...
...just really happy to be here.
Five years later, she's done.
Oh no, they know the real me now.
Sorry, I'm sorry!
Why am I always the one
that makes things awkward?
It's all Ina's fault!
I apologize.
Yeah, 'cause there's not a lot of time
for yapping too much today, it seems.
We're gonna dance our hearts out
and sing our hearts out for you guys.
And oh man, we've been doing
a lot of that these days.
I think everybody in Myth deserves a trophy.
A little reward.
A treat, perhaps?
Cookies!
Cookies?
Cookies are good too.
Maybe a cookie-shaped trophy?
Or a trophy made out of a cookie.
Or a trophy-shaped cookie.
Yes!
Yes please.
You hear that management?
You better be having some rewards for us.
So demanding.
Yeah, well, that's okay.
In any case,
I know how we can kick this off.
Kick it off?
Yeah.
So, maybe it's like a little cheesy,
but I thought maybe the three of us
could like jump in the air and go "Wheee!"
Like "3, 2, 1, jump!" and then
the camera goes "Vrooom!" we like fly
into the air and go to the next song.
I get it, I get it.
I get you.
I've done it before.
Okay! Then let's do it.
No punching, no violent thoughts, Ina.
Don't punch the camera. I know what you're thinking.
Just one uppercut?
Not one! Zero!
Nice.
Okay, let's do it.
Here we go! On my count.
Ready?
Okay.
Next song start!
3, 2, 1, JUMP!
ビビデバ
Bibideba
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: ツミキ
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Tsumiki
つまんないデイズ 散々だね
Boring days, they're terrible
奇跡願ってるだけの人生
A life just wishing for miracles
Watch me do-to-do-to-do Hit you 研ぎ澄ましのマジック
Watch me do-to-do-to-do, hit you with refined magic
One, two, three だってまだフリーダム The party ain't started
One, two, three, because it's still freedom, the party ain't started
ヘイタクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey taxi, take me to space
夜空は音を立てて 夜を急かす魔法みたいだ
The night sky makes a sound, like magic hurrying the night along
人生は一瞬にして 解ける魔法
Life is magic that unravels in an instant
恐れなんかないわ かけてみて 魔法 今宵のストーリー
I've no fear, try casting it, magic, tonight's story
邪魔な馬車飛び乗って Driving
Jump into that pesky carriage, driving
私を大変身 Make up
Give me a complete makeover, make up
我儘のマニマニ 煌めきに注意注意
As I please, beware, beware of the sparkle
Shut up な街で Dancing サヨナラ Goodbye劣等感
Dancing in a "shut up" town, farewell, goodbye inferiority complex
Please go かっさらって Dirtyな皆々 ご注目あれ
Please go, sweep them all away, dirty everyone, pay attention
Bibidi-Bobidi-Boowa
Bibidi-Bobidi-Boowa yeah
あの子が履いたガラスの靴で踊る Tonight
Dancing in the glass slippers that girl wore tonight
Bibidi-Bobidi-Boowa
Bibidi-Bobidi-Boowa yeah
あんなに浅はかなら 私を連れ去ってよ 我儘少女
If it's that shallow, take me away, selfish girl
Dance だりだりだん どんな問題も会話ひとつ
Dance, dari-dari-dan, any problem is just one conversation
白紙も正解も間違いも 愛せ本当の私の理想
Love the blank pages, the right answers, and the mistakes, my true ideal
なんだか世界は限界の気配がしてうだうだだ
Somehow the world feels like it's at its limit, just droning on
安心じゃ心配 歩きましょう Jumpin' Jumpin' out
Security is worrying, let's walk, jumpin' jumpin' out
ギリギリばっか 正味ばっか 今は発散してしまおうか
Always at the limit, always just the net amount, shall we let it all out now?
まだまだビビッとキミにダンシング 夜っ端じゃ物足りないわ
Still dancing to you with a spark, the start of the night isn't enough
ついに導き出したキミへのアンサー ハイになるまで踊ってよ
Finally derived the answer for you, dance until you're high
Bibidi-Bobidi-Boowa
Bibidi-Bobidi-Boowa yeah
あの子が履いたガラスの靴で踊る Tonight
Dancing in the glass slippers that girl wore tonight
Bibidi-Bobidi-Boowa
Bibidi-Bobidi-Boowa yeah
あんなに浅はかなら 私を連れ去ってよ 我儘少女
If it's that shallow, take me away, selfish girl
Hooray!
Let's get started.
Easy breezy down.
Hey 頭の中でのこのCremaは 私のPersonaに繋がる
Hey, the crema in my head connects to my persona
生まれたてのアイデアと情熱があるが 疑う事もなく冴えある者が群がる
With freshly born ideas and passion, those who are sure to shine flock together
What about you 誰だ？狂妄膨らます
What about you? Stir up those delusions
ひと時たまらない分かちきろの先に待つ 結末は麒麟児大器晩成玉だがる
The end that awaits beyond the fleeting, undeniable moments is the late bloomer’s magnum opus
選ぶのは自分景気づけ先に景気飲め
A segment of one's peak, a cake that comes before a break
怒涛に如く数多貸して 研いだ言の葉ここで息高し
Accompanied by the sweet heights of nostalgia, that's where I'll live
Come on hurry どこまでも
Come on hurry, let's go together
今夜の事推しあつま
To the other side of tonight's fleeting dream
Live it with no hesitation
時間を忘れ焦がれる炎の情
Forgetting time, the roar of the fire
Keep it back coming up next level
The future's only colored by the cleverest of rebels
飽和せし情を糧に正気
Feeding off of saturated passion, stay sane
狂気乱舞種が芽出し入り乱れ賞鼓
A wild dance of madness, the seed sprouts and the prize is heralded
乱れ咲い等謳歌ビルホー
Enjoy the blooming, chaotic days to the fullest
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
Just a little madness, you could take the drive out of me
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
Can't hide it's a new generation creation
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
Tearing up the canvas, won't be watching what you want me to be
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
Too rough, too loud, unburned, unrefined
Find out that flood of noise is only in our minds
Right now, it's time, no doubt we're moving on
I'm drawing my ideal world at each and every dawn
狂い出した瞬間
The moment things went crazy
感じきれば悩みも昇華
If you notice, your worries will be sublimated
Breaking all expectations, time to forget and burn with the passion
反芻するならし
No need for rumination
罪過の眼差し
The gaze of guilt
解き放とう情熱を今
Release the passion right now
Never hitting the brakes to prove I got what it takes
To manifest a world you've never discerned as real or fake, so come on
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
Just a little madness, you could take the drive out of me
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
Can't hide it's a new generation creation
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
Tearing up the canvas, won't be watching what you want me to be
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
ああ 人様よこれっぽっちも
Ah, people don't even have a bit of it
自分の背中預けるような夢があればそれでいい
As long as you have a dream that you can entrust your back to, it's fine
誰れに笑われようよりもひたすらにあがき
Keep struggling no matter who laughs at you
やまない雨はないと信じ今に様変わる
Believing that there's no rain that won't stop, everything will change now
Words are gifted, prolific, you bet to be specific
Brushstrokes blowing smoke blink and you can miss it
These words elicit visions of a future so exquisite
Some masterpiece you never seen wait a few commit it
知らない事があれば研究 出来ない事があれば練習
If there's something you don't know, research it. If there's something you can't do, practice it.
姿勢を前のめり 我を熱中
Lean forward and get absorbed in yourself
成功の真反対にある失敗が 一番の近道だ You can do it 最高峰は道だ
The failures on the opposite side of success are the shortest path. You can do it, the peak is the path.
Stars align and all design I'm already on my way
ほとばしる情熱 瑞々が震える鼓動の銃弾まで
Gushing passion, until the moist pulse of the bullets
Focus finding all this blind risk I'm already on my way
This is some vivid and striking my NEKKYOU!
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
This is some vivid and striking my NEKKYOU!
熱狂！
NEKKYOU!
誤解すんなよ こんな滑稽な
Don't misunderstand, it's laughable
サッと過ぎ去る毎日（エブリデイ）
How time flashes by every day
Another prisoner of fate no one could fake out
Stay awake now, you know you wanna fire away
Now there's no question where the fault lies
These days I struggle just to empathize
もう戻らないって分かっているんだろう
There's no going back, and you know that
Cast a blessing on my cursed role
And feed this bleeding egotistical soul
Before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい 青い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
身分不相応の嫉妬に塗れた
Dripping in jealousy that's a bit too daring
ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
An ecstasy that's just a little bit lacking
誤解も解けないまま私 人を傷つけて
I hurt somebody without ever opening my eyes
一粒の才すらないわ
But there's no talent here, it's clear to see
転がり落ちたジロゴロサイ
The rigged dice falls and rolls
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I ever notice your love and affection
Cast a blessing on my cursed heart
Why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか神様 教えてくれますか
Pray tell me, God
...すか
...?
言葉少なに貴方に捧ぐ
I give to you silently
今に消えてしまいそうなこの命を
My life that's about to burn out
鳴呼 愛おしいセピア色した
Ah, and these sepia-toned sights
何より大事なこの景色を
they're most precious of all
もう少し見ていたいよな
I wish I could see them a bit more...
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
If I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The devils on my shoulder never let me be
Obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
Somebody save me
My world is caving in cuz I thought I deserved it all for free, yeah yeah
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
鳴呼 美しい蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くなりたいとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
晴れあらり 今踊り踊れ 恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny spell, now dance and dance, play in love's yearning, clap your hands like cherry blossoms
はねにまぎれ 今音り戻せ 粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Mingled in petals, now dance back, play whimsically, come dance right here
ひゆるりらぼっぱ
Lyrics, Music: tuki
Hiyururira Boppa
いざやお立ち また時が過ぎてく よりどりみどり 祭り囃子
Now stand up, as time passes again, a plethora of choices, festival music
あれのごらん 籠も放り込み よく身を見に行きたいた
Look at that, throw in the basket too, I really want to go and see for myself
人生より道まわり道
Life is a detour, a roundabout way
行きたいように生きられや
Live as you wish to live
晴れあらり 今踊り踊れ 恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny spell, now dance and dance, play in love's yearning, clap your hands like cherry blossoms
はねにまぎれ 今音り戻せ 粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Mingled in petals, now dance back, play whimsically, come dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらぼっぱ
Yuru yururira, yururira boppa
ゆるりお立ち また時は過ぎ去る 酸いも甘いも 祭り囃子
Leisurely stand up, as time passes away again, both sour and sweet, festival music
味わい尽くしてしまいましょう さあ何から平らげよう
Let's taste it all to the fullest, now, what shall we devour first?
人生気付けば山の如し
Before you know it, life is like a mountain
命の花を打ち上げましょう
Let's set off the flowers of life
晴れあらり 今踊り踊れ 恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny spell, now dance and dance, play in love's yearning, clap your hands like cherry blossoms
はねにまぎれ 今音り戻せ 粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Mingled in petals, now dance back, play whimsically, come dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらぼっぱ
Yuru yururira, yururira boppa
花よ花よ 誇りなさい
Oh flower, oh flower, be proud
まごうことなく君のまま
Unmistakably as you are
上を向いてごらんなさい
Please look up
最後の日まで花であれ
Be a flower until the final day
晴れあらり 今踊り踊れ 恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny spell, now dance and dance, play in love's yearning, clap your hands like cherry blossoms
はねにまぎれ 今音り戻せ 粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Mingled in petals, now dance back, play whimsically, come dance right here
晴れあらり 今踊り踊れ たれかれも遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny spell, now dance and dance, let everyone and anyone play, clap your hands like cherry blossoms
はなれ離れ でも花びら上げて 粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Separated from each other, but let the petals rise, play whimsically, come dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらぼっぱ
Yuru yururira, yururira boppa
caramel ribbon cursetard
Lyrics: meg rock / Music: ミト (クラムボン)
Lyrics: meg rock / Music: Mito (clammbon)
ああしたい　こうしたい　どうしたい
I want to do this, I want to do that, what do I want to do?
まるで死んでるみたい
It's as if I'm dead
石の上にも三年
Three years on a stone
でもそんなんじゃ　エイ！　サーキュレーション
But with just that... Hey! Circulation
どん底から始まるストーリー
A story that begins from rock bottom
まるで掌の上のイモーション
Just like emotion on the palm of a hand
カラカラ飛び出しイイ気分だなんて
Jumping out rattle-rattle, saying it feels good
君は決め顔でせーの
With a look of determination, you say, "Ready, go!"
永遠を願った夢に
To the dream that wished for eternity
終わりを告げる朝が来た
The morning that signals the end has come
嘘でできたその涙
Those tears made of lies
見つめ見つめ見つけた心
Staring and staring, I found a heart
甘くほろ苦いキャラメルのように
Like sweet and bittersweet caramel
絡まるリボンは呪いの鎧だけど
The entangled ribbon is armor of a curse, but...
この気持ちはそう
This feeling is, yes...
この気持ちにしか
Only in this feeling...
きっとわからないから
...will it surely be understood
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you
ひとつひとつ叶えていこう
Let's make them come true one by one
僕らの物語は
Our story...
今日も続く約束
...is a promise that continues today
彩りどりの真っ黒な歴史
Colorful, pitch-black history
愛おしいわたしの歴史
My precious history
誰も知らない真っ白なページ
A pure white page that nobody knows
更新してゆく
Is being updated
綻びたくない綻びは
The flaws I don't want to unravel...
放したくない喜びで
...with the joy I don't want to let go of
継ぎ接ぎだらけのこの心
This heart full of patches
噤み紡ぎ繋いだところ
Where I kept silent, spun, and connected
憧れこがれまちこがれ
Longing, yearning, waiting impatiently
全部全部全部全部
All, all, all, all
プリンみたいにひっくり返して
Flip it over like a pudding
キャラメルキャラメル my favorite
Caramel, caramel, my favorite
いたいいたいどこいった
Ouch, ouch, where did it go?
切り離したままの僕はパズルのピース
Disconnected, I'm a puzzle piece
でもそんなんじゃやだ
But I don't want it like that
僕ら決め顔でせーの
With looks of determination, we say, "Ready, go!"
次の切り札は
The next trump card...
自分でお選ぶの
...is chosen by yourself
運命の赤いリボンを手繰り寄せて
Reeling in the red ribbon of fate
この気持ちはそう
This feeling is, yes...
この気持ちにしか
Only in this feeling...
きっとわからないから
...will it surely be understood
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you
ひとつひとつ叶えていこう
Let's make them come true one by one
僕らの物語は
Our story...
今日も続く約束
...is a promise that continues today
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hands with you
ひとつひとつ叶えていこう
Let's make them come true one by one
僕らの物語は
Our story...
今日も続く約束
...is a promise that continues today
彩りどりの真っ黒な歴史
Colorful, pitch-black history
愛おしいぼくらの歴史
Our precious history
残さず食べて全部糧にして
Eat it all up and make it all nourishment
更新してゆく
Is being updated
Yeah!
What... what are we doing?
Welcome back, Calli!
Oh, hi! Hey.
You guys look a little tired.
I thought we were posing for the Myth album cover,
which is not coming out, by the way.
Misunderstanding! Misunderstanding.
Well, we have a mixtape, though.
Someday, someday.
Did you guys enjoy the song so far?
What did you think?
Yeah, pretty fun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
We did a really cute one, Ina.
Yeah!
caramel ribbon curstard.
Yeah, you guys's voices... "you guys's"?
Your voices fit really, really well with that.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, it's a really cute song.
Yeah. I... me and Ina were like,
"What song should we do together?"
And I was like, "Ha! I wonder if Ina
would let me do a Monogatari song?"
I was like, "Monogatari please!"
And she's like, "Yeah! Sure!"
You're talking to Ninomae Ina'nis, you know!
Of course I'm gonna say yes!
But we all like Monogatari.
We do, yeah! We all could have done it too, huh?
Sure, yeah, I would have done it.
We could have had her doing the...
(Sings bits of song)
Now I wanna see that!
I can do it now. I can do it now.
We should have done it as three people because it was cute!
But I'm gonna be as cute as I can.
That was everybody's solos, though.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
Except mine, that was amazing.
You guys know I could rap that fast?
Oh my god, I was so surprised!
Kind of crazy. Impressive.
Yeah, mama!
かっこいい、カリ！
You're so cool, Calli!
I did my best. It was like, enough,
enough of this. Oh, you know, she did it.
And then plus the dancing was pretty cool too.
Oh yeah!
頑張った！ Good job!
You did your best! Good job!
And Ina too, very impressive!
Oh my goodness, I really challenged myself.
The dancing has leveled up so much.
Yeah!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Cute, beautiful.
Yeah, demure.
It was a lot of fun, it was difficult,
of course my heart rate shot through the roof.
But we did it.
We did it.
And then me and Ina did some air guitar.
Yeah.
My original song, Sepia, was a...
very close song to my heart.
And Ina played guitar by the way.
Yeah, I loved the purple guitar.
Yeah, so cool.
But what's still missing now?
Oh, there are a couple songs missing, aren't there?
Like WAWA's song, my song...
A lot of unit songs...
And mine and Calli's combination song...
I wonder why...
I wonder, I wonder.
I will just say that the song for me and Calli
was also chosen, kind of suggested by me.
Thank you for... thank you for being okay with it.
It's a nice song. I don't want to spoil anything,
but it was pretty good.
And my solo will be...
eh... epic and hyped! So look forward to it.
What's the music? Can you give a hint?
I know it's about to happen pretty soon here, but...
No! No! No hints!
Alright, alright.
Why? I'm a toddler, why?
Yes, we still have a lot of our show left over,
so don't tune out. There's lots more! Stay with us!
Stay right here.
Don't move.
Wait and continue to watch until the end.
And use the hashtag! Don't forget that.
Okay, hashtag.
Are we ready to move on? Move on?
Okay.
What should we do?
No, what should we do?
We should play with the camera.
What do you want to do, Ina?
What do you want to do the most?
I know what to do...
Oh?
What are you going to do?
Not something violent, right?
Oh! She's going to do something violent!
She's doing something violent!
Hee-yah!
Confessions of a Rotten Girl
Dear God, I've come to repent my sins.
Let your blood wash me clean, for I'm...
I'm...
I'm a rotten girl!
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
Temptation's flowing through my veins
And bounded by the shackles of shame
I promised I'd indulge no more
But my heart I can't ignore
In my dreams they're turning up the heat
I'm a dirty rotten girl
I'm locked underneath the bleachers
Just watch, look beyond the smoke and mirrors
Hearts struck, shun the unbeliever
Our reparation would never be complete
Red hot tension in each whisper
Snapshot, quiet moans and muffled whimpers
Come on, can't you feel the fever
Rising up, rising up to the sky
And as the realm of toxic fear slips beneath my skin
The Lord sayeth, 'Help my child, don't give in to sin'
It's driving me crazy, the urge to forsake
The incense of shifts within this wicked play
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
Student Council breathing down my neck
I wonder if they're hiding from me
Forbidden fruit before my eyes
And a taste that solidifies
My regret, regretting history
I'm a doubtful rotten girl
Someone please tell me what to do
Because honestly, I just can't stop
I've been trying so hard and I can't stop
What would God think?
And I, I know I'm supposed to be a good girl but
Somehow I just can't control myself
Every time I see them, touching skin to skin
My mind goes, my mind goes...
AAH!
Could he be right, am I pushing leaders for the light
With all of these disciples of romance driven blind
Cuz somebody save me, the urge to forsake
The incense of shifts within this wicked play
The power of resting in my hands
Oh my God, it's a perfect plan
And salvation, I can live my life
as an ordinary girl
I can't resist them anymore
Cuz I smell strawberries galore
All the trauma from a couple's soul
Could never be the devil in me
And I'm a sinner 'til I die
What's the harm if I don't mind
Cuz the power within empowers me
I can live a sinful life
チェックワンツー！
Check one, two!
チェックワンツー！イェーイ！
Check one, two! Yay!
あーもう無理！文化祭
Ah, I can't take it! The school festival
言葉にダンスに…キャパオーバーです
Words, dancing... I'm over capacity
心配無用のおまじない
An incantation so you don't have to worry
きっと報われるその努力
Your hard work will surely pay off
笑顔になぁれ
Put a smile on your face
ドキドキしてる
My heart is racing
ありえないくらい本気だし
I'm seriously giving it my all
まほうがかかる
A magic spell is cast
今日限りヒーロータイム
Hero time, just for today
何とぞね？
Okay?
baby kiss 照れないで
Baby kiss, don't be shy
気持ち伝えてよ！
Tell me how you feel!
（好き！）
(I love you!)
好き！
I love you!
相思相愛好き
Mutual love, I love you
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup runs
髪が乱れても
Even if my hair gets messy
（好き！）
(I love you!)
好き！
I love you!
絶対忘れない青春の1ページ
I'll never forget this page of our youth
あー超きもちー！文化祭
Ah, it feels so good! The school festival
隣で笑ってる君のおかげだ
It's all thanks to you laughing by my side
弱気な私変えてくれた
You changed my weak self
絶対最強のパートナー
The absolute strongest partner
マジでありがとう
Really, thank you
カクセイしてるファン力の力マシマシで
Awakening, with the fans' power increasing more and more
まほうつよまる終わりかけヒーロータイム
The magic strengthens as hero time draws to a close
延長、ね？
An extension, okay?
baby kiss 隠さずに
Baby kiss, without hiding it
気持ち伝えてよ！
Tell me how you feel!
好き！
I love you!
（好き！）
(I love you!)
相思相愛好き
Mutual love, I love you
おやつ食べたいし
I want to eat snacks
帰宅いいですか？
Is it okay if I go home?
（ダメ！）
(No way!)
ダメ？
No way?
（ダメ！）
(No way!)
ごめん嘘嘘こちらこそ帰さない！
Sorry, I'm kidding, I won't let you go home either!
TakaMori for five years!
Can you guys keep it going?!
いくよー！
Here we go!
かりちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Calli-chan super cute?
（かりちゃんは超かわいい！）
(Calli-chan is super cute!)
きあらちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Kiara-chan super cute?
（きあらちゃんは超かわいい！）
(Kiara-chan is super cute!)
Big Ups! Everybody!
Danke schön!
Are you ready?
3, 2, 1, Go!
まほう解けちゃうね…
The magic is going to wear off...
最後に聞かせてよ
Let me hear it one last time
好き？
Do you love me?
大きな声で好き！
With a loud voice, I love you!
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup runs
髪が乱れても
Even if my hair gets messy
（好き！）
(I love you!)
好き！
I love you!
絶対忘れない青春の1ページ
I'll never forget this page of our youth
な×7 Yeah!
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na Yeah!
鼻っ面を割りゃ　八から十　あんたらなんじゃ　多分納得も可能
If you break your nose, it's eight to ten. What are you? Maybe it's possible to be satisfied.
クワバラ　クワバラ　クワバラ
Kuwabara kuwabara kuwabara
目にも留まらぬ速さ　生きた煩悩　たまらん　逆らわず　押し通す　我が儘
A speed that the eye can't keep up with. Living worldly desires. Unbearable. Without resisting, I push through my selfishness.
そこどけ　大蛇か　またわらわ　もといのあなた
Get out of the way. Is it a giant snake? Or is it me? Or rather, you.
さぁどっちだいい？　どっちもいいさ　ヨミナヨ
Well, which one is it? Both are fine. Read it.
今日さながらど真ん中
Today just like the center
積み上げていくタパタパ
Stacking it up, tappa tappa
四時四十四分待ったら
Waiting for 4:44
昼夜昼夜風様が
Day and night, the wind
構わん待った番外編
Didn't care, waited, the extra edition
やっぱ声貸したんなら 文字通りお疲れ様やん
If you lent your voice, then literally good job
晴れた晴れた晴れた晴れた 晴れた晴れた
It's cleared, cleared, cleared, cleared, cleared, cleared
眠り飽きた先で 君を待った
After getting tired of sleeping, I waited for you
タコと頬が重なり合ったら
When the octopus and cheek overlap
瞳が重なったら
When our eyes meet
心体頭 脈打っていくなんだか
Heart, body, head, somehow pulsing
背中に今 羽が生えたならば
If wings were to grow on my back now
暗闇からさらば
Farewell to the darkness
飛び出していく彼方
Flying off to the beyond
心体頭 懐かしい温かさ
Heart, body, head, a nostalgic warmth
足元に今 花が咲いたならば
If flowers were to bloom at my feet now
暗闇からさらば
Farewell to the darkness
飛び出していく彼方
Flying off to the beyond
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
Living over and over within you or your heart
まぶたの裏 闇の中
Behind the eyelids, in the darkness
胸の奥に居ついてる メロディ リズムに
Forever in the depths of the heart, to the melody and rhythm
今日さながらど真ん中
Today just like the center
積み上げていくタパタパ
Stacking it up, tappa tappa
オニとチャンバラ the lyrical is a massacre
Sword fighting with demons, the lyrical is a massacre
渡る大海原 花唄うしゅららら
Crossing the vast ocean, humming tra-la-la
祓いたいのなら 前祭毎度のサスタバ
If you want to exorcise, the usual sustaba of the festival
誰が拓いたかパンドラ あとは何があっても知らんがな
Who opened Pandora? I don't care what happens next
八百万年待ったか チョー久しぶりのシャバだ
Have you waited eight million years? It's been a super long time in the outside world
ガキや若造は まだこっちくんじゃねえよ バカが
Kids and youngsters, don't come over here yet, you fools
今確かに目が合ったな こういう顔しちゃおしまい
Our eyes definitely met just now, making a face like that is the end
晴れた晴れた晴れた晴れた 晴れた晴れた
It's cleared, cleared, cleared, cleared, cleared, cleared
眠り飽きた先で 君が待った
After getting tired of sleeping, you waited
たったと頬が 肩を抱き合ったら
When just cheek and shoulder embrace
怒りが消え去ったら
When anger disappears
心体頭 脈打っていくなんだか
Heart, body, head, somehow pulsing
背中に今 羽が生えたならば
If wings were to grow on my back now
暗闇からさらば
Farewell to the darkness
飛び出していく彼方
Flying off to the beyond
心体頭 懐かしい温かさ
Heart, body, head, a nostalgic warmth
足元に今 花が咲いたならば
If flowers were to bloom at my feet now
暗闇からさらば
Farewell to the darkness
飛び出していく彼方
Flying off to the beyond
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
Living over and over within you or your heart
まぶたの裏 闇の中
Behind the eyelids, in the darkness
胸の奥に居ついてる メロディ リズムに
Forever in the depths of the heart, to the melody and rhythm
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the Muses whisper "truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
A wild chase, a frantic pace
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
Ah... da da da da da da da
I'm always spinning fate
Whoah yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I spin back 'round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance, a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
Ooh la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoah, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
New song, new song, new song!
Yatta!
It's our first song as a trio, you guys!
Yeah! Oh, true!
So now that I'm thinking about it...
Yeah! It's only like 2 minutes.
That's a good workout.
Yeah. I guess it's because of all the Zoomers and like it's short nowadays, huh?
That's what everybody says.
They say you.
Not me!
Certainly not.
But yeah, unfortunately, this was also the last song for this live!
えー？
Ehhhh?
But...
Yes, but!
But the music video for our 5th anniversary song
Fortune Spinner will premiere on
the Hololive English official YouTube channel
right after this concert!
So make sure you stick around, okay?
Don't miss it!
Don't you dare!
Don't miss it.
Make sure you watch it a lot
and loop it a lot, please.
Yeah! Yeah.
そうですね！そうですね！
That's right! That's right!
Stuff some celebrating to do, right?
That's right. I think it's time because it's the end
that we kind of celebrate ourselves here. 5 years!
Are we ready for that? Yes!
Yes, we are ready! Okay, let's do it!
Let's do it! Let's do it!
Oh! What is that cake over there that is not mine?
Hey! Oh, come on!
Be-be-be careful! Come on, come on!
Can we... can we... talk about how delicious it looks?
Yeah! Now I can't see it properly
because of the way you're talking about it.
It's big though. It's almost bigger than Ina!
Oh yeah. Hey!
Hey, stop stop stop. Not now, not now.
Eh! Don't pick off the strawberry!
Hold your horses. Let's eat it later
and celebrate later, later, later.
And look, there's trophies!
Yeah! I saw that! We can do an award show, right?
Staff somewhere actually got us trophies!
Yeah, they were listening! Thank you!
They followed our shopping list accordingly.
Okay, 5 years, we deserve an award.
Yeah. We had so many meaningful accomplishments,
so let's see what they all are, okay?
Okay! Who's it gonna be? Yeah!
Should I start? I'll take mine.
Hshyuu! Our awarding... God bless you.
God bless you. Sorry. Jya-jya-jya-jyan!
Hshyuu! Oh! God bless you. Sorry,
I'm not trying to disrupt your award ceremony.
What did you get? What did you get?
High! I have... my award is... let's see... uh...
Most Meals Cooked Award ~Takanashi Kiara~
I think it says 'Most Meals Cooked Award' ~Takanashi Kiara~.
She's cooking in Holo EN! Let her cook!
Let her cook! Let her cook! Let her keep doing it!
She has been cooking a lot. She has a lot of meals.
Yeah, thank you. I think that's what that's about,
mostly it's about me living a healthy lifestyle
and then cooking many meals at home.
Yeah. I wish I could cook for you girls someday.
Someday! I hope you guys
enjoyed my performances today!
I am so proud to stand here with my gen-mates
even on this day after so many years.
I will continue to work hard, of course,
so that I can maybe gather even more awards.
I will put this on my shelf at home where my cats
will also probably put a lot of fur on it.
Or knock it down. Meow, meow, no!
Meow, meow! They like to do that.
Is it out of real glass? It's kind of heavy,
I have to be careful. Careful. Yeah.
Thank you guys so much! I love you girls!
(Mwah mwah mwah) It's been an honor so far,
so let's do our best together!
Thank you for this award!
Woo! Who's next? Who's next?
Is it Ina'nis?
Me? Oh, could my award be, let's see...
yoi-sho! Yoi-sho! Most violent? Yikes.
100% not violent. You do it to yourself.
You do it to Ina. All right.
My award is... oh yes... oh yes... I already got... It is...
Most Time Spent on the Floor Award ~Ninomae Ina'nis~
It is 'Most Time Spent on the Floor Award' ~Ninomae Ina'nis~.
Oh, that I believe! Yay!
おめでとう！Congratulations!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I know you guys probably think I would never get this award,
but you know, I worked so hard this year
to stay on the floor. Very unprecedented.
And uh, yeah. Not only did I stay on the floor,
I really did my best to practice dancing
and singing this year to perform well with you guys.
And I hope that you guys see that as well.
Thank you so much for all your support.
I'll continue to do my best with these girls.
Yeah! Let's keep doing it! Thank you! Myth! Myth!
And last but not least... Calliope-mon.
Oh, what could it be? Oh, what could it be?
Our sneezier... the most sneezes today.
The most sneezes in the Myth 5th anniversary showcase.
Most blessed. Okay, well, actually,
my trophy is for... jya-jya-jyan!
Best Worst Luck Award ~Mori Calliope~
Best Worst Luck, especially in games
where there are microtransactions.
Hehe! That's not so boss. Yeah, I mean,
I've seen it happen in real time. But the dedication,
the determination to pull a signed card...
I'm not gonna give up yet. (Singing slightly)
I'm gonna be very sappy. Okay.
I really like that line, I'm not gonna give up.
...gonna give up yet because, because
I'd like to think that we're not gonna give up yet
because there's still so much that I want to do...
...the three of us together. Together!
Together!
You know!
And I didn't think that I would be here
five years from the start with you guys.
Same!
Yeah.
I really thought I'd be out of here.
Same!
But now I can't... I can't see a future where
I'm not here with you guys. So for now...
Oh, so nice!
That's it!
Oh, shucks!
Okay!
So because of that, I'm not gonna give up yet.
I don't want to give up yet.
So let's do our best!
Oh yeah, the wrapping-up jingle is playing!
I'm just gonna start talking about nothing because it
annoys me when they play the jingle to tell me to stop.
This morning I ate a bagel and I had cream cheese on it.
It was delicious but it went over my budget.
I'm in big trouble with my trainer.
Safe!
But anyway, I'm not... you can't get rid of me!
All right!
You can't get rid of any of us, hopefully!
Everybody, all good things come to an end, unfortunately.
But thank you so much to the hololive English community
for supporting us continuously for five years.
Thank you to the girls today and all the staff
and sound guys that supported us also for this celebration,
who gave us the trophies!
Yeah!
Once again, congratulations to us! To us!
Yeah! Five years of hololive English -Myth-!
Yay! Thank you! Thanks for coming!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Peace!
Yeah! Thank you guys for the merch!
Buy the merch!
Merch, merch please!
Merchandise!
Next is the merchandise announcement!
We have hololive English -Myth-'s 5th anniversary
celebration merch being released!
Let's look at the details. Check it out!
First up, we've got the Mirror Acrylic Panel!
It's designed so that the surroundings and background
of the illustration have a metallic mirrored vibe.
Oh, so cool!
I absolutely love this illustration. Hope you guys do too!
Next up, we have the collection cards!
These cards feature a shiny metallic finish
and you can choose from three different designs.
Also, the backside is matching for us all.
Make sure to get the one from your oshi for sure!
Next up, we have the coin medals!
Our shiny 5th anniversary commemorative coin medals!
There's one design for each member, and the backsides
also have a common design.
They come in an antique gold-plated finish
inside the original packaging.
Ooh, so shiny!
Oh man, everything looks so good!
But I'm especially interested in what we have
to show you guys next.
Next up, we have the Anniversary Hats!
So first up, Anniversary Hat - Mori Calliope!
This one uses a soft fluffy fabric.
The Death-sensei part is removable so you can also
rock it without him. Make sure that you check it out.
It's super stylish!
I love the shape so much and...
all of my members (Deadbeats) voted on it together.
So hope that you guys will enjoy!
Next up, we have mine!
The Anniversary Hat from Takanashi Kiara!
Looks like this!
Decorative parts are removable.
It can be worn reversibly, inside out,
so you'll have a different color then!
And it's a bucket hat style design, which we
didn't have before for me. Very fashionable, I must say!
Last but not least, we have my hat!
The Anniversary Hat - Ninomae Ina'nis!
The ribbon part is removable and the patches are
super cute too. You can wear it to become Takodachi!
Yes!
And yeah, you can mix and match with or without
the ribbon for different looks.
So everybody, be sure to check our merch out!
And that concludes our 5th year anniversary stream!
OtsuMyth!
Thank you for an unforgettable 5 years!
I can't wait for even more amazing fun things...
...in the future!! Buckle in!!
It's going to be an exciting ride up ahead!!
GO NEXT!! INA
Thanks for 5 years together everyone!!
Are you ready for 5 more??
I've already been the best journey a Reaper
could ask for but let's run towards...
...the future together!! We can't wait
and I love my Myth girls!! Goodbye, Calli
KIKKERIKI!
These 5 years were super crazy!
It was up's and down's but in the end we stayed
together and I grew and learnt so much!!
Every moment shared with you guys is forever in
my heart and I'm looking forward for more...
...years together!! Love, Kiara