(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Okay, we reached the destination.
Right on time.
Is everyone ready?
You bet. Let's go.
All right then! Ready?
Set...
Jump!
Coming in hot!
We're ready to greet the world
We're voyaging forward
with courage to run toward a brand new start
Let's go live
bridging the distance across the sea
Endlessly
cheerfully
meeting heart to heart!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivot of the moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah!
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up!
Big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far
But we're striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
(This is it!)
It's smashing barriers left and right
(That's our Myth!)
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
(It's endless!)
So get together, let's reunite!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright!
We're ready to seize the day
traversing the pathways
discovering highways to everywhere
Step by step
Yeah!
gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
with this generation
a shining sensation, a dream unfurls
Let's make friends
Yeah!
making a moment of history
Joyfully
Follow me!
We'll connect the world!
You'll hear our song
ringing out
over hills and oceans
Our legend grows
and continues!
We'll carry on
starting now
setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question we'll break through
(Don't relent!)
We'll keep aspiring to excel
(That's our myth!)
It's awe-inspiring, going well
(Represent!)
So light the fire and let's rebel
The future's brighter, we can tell!
We're ready to...
We're ready to change the world!
Yay!
Uh uh uh uh uh
Myth medley! Myth medley! Myth medley! Myth medley!
What are you doing?
I... I...
Oh, you too?
Both of you guys are acting a little strange right now.
We're doing crazy shapes!
Why are they being so stiff?
Come on, those shoulders too.
You gotta shoulder too.
Ina come on, come on!
頑張れ！
Do your best!
I know the floor is nice but...
It is really nice.
It's smooth.
皆さん！
Everyone!
Minna-san thank you for coming to the show today...
Everyone thank you for coming to the show today...
...to celebrate Myth's... you guessed it...
5th Anniversary!
Woo! Yippee!
It was a medley... a nice throwback.
We've made so many songs together.
Yeah, 懐かしい.
Yeah, nostalgic.
Putting it all together like that is like really... emotional.
エモエモ.
Emo emo.
And it's not just like our 5th year anniversary...
It's also Hololive English as a whole, 5 years!
Yeah!
Don't do that!
We're old!
We're all... 5!
You know?
We also... we also achieved so much in the last 5 years you know?
We had three EN concerts...
My voice cracked, let's go!
Let's go!
And we had a lot of friends join us over the years...
...and in the end I'm just really happy to be performing with you guys.
It's so much fun.
Yeah!
Can't get too emotional just yet though because we have a show to do.
Mmh, mmh. It's true.
Yes, anyways, anyways, anyways...
There's a hashtag right here, right here.
Yes yes.
Over here. Take lots of pictures, uh, screenshots and post them on social media.
Hashtag #Myth5years!
Make us trend!
Trending, get it trending.
Number one!
If you want, you don't have to if you don't want to.
Just kidding, if you don't do it we'll be sad.
We'll be angry. We'll get you.
Do it.
Okay.
Besides that everybody... this is important. I'm just checking.
Making sure you guys are all here legally.
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
あら！
Oh my!
Did you guys all receive a ticket?
Oh I remember that.
Ah, it's me! That's me!
We look so cool.
Yeah I think I gave you mine at the bar...
It was kinda spicy, remember?
Whoa. Spicy?
I accosted you on the street, yeah if you remember.
Ah right...
Oh that's what you were up to.
Yeah, yeah, I... I might have tres... trespassed?
What?
おやおや？
Oh my?
Wait what did you do?
Ina would do such a thing!
Don't worry about it don't worry about it!
That was our alter egos.
That's right, that's right.
Okay. Well... Ninomae Ina'anis?
What? Sorry.
What did you do? You want to share?
Nothing. I did nothing illegal.
Fine. Don't tell me, keep your secrets.
Wow.
That's fine. They're used to it. It's been five years.
Now that we know that everybody is here with their tickets and they're allowed to be here...
We'll be singing a lot on this stage today...
in different combinations and different fun songs and so on.
But speaking of the stage...
Oh yeah!
Look at this stage!
Look smooth floor.
Beautiful stage.
Gorgeous.
おしゃれ！
Stylish!
Look at the chairs, that's fancy.
How much does that cost?
Couch, can I lie on it?
Get your priorities straight.
Whoa look at that chandelier!
Can I swing on it?
No!
Do not swing on the chandelier!
What's the heart for?
Looks expensive.
Wait, did it just change color?
If we could just gain some color.
Ah, why I wonder?
Could it be that it's reacting to everybody's reactions in the chat?
And their feelings, it's changing color according to that?
Are you guys getting excited?
Chat, you guys have an important job to do now, right?
Which is doing things, they're always doing something.
It must be their power...
...and their energy.
It's flowing through us!
Well I look forward to seeing how it develops from here out.
So, you know what you're gonna do right?
You're gonna get out your keyboards and you're gonna type some things.
Type-o-man!
Give us your energy!
Give it to us!
Not like we're trying to shake you down or anything.
I feel it, I feel it.
I'll shake them down.
Okay, alright, we're choosing violence again today.
Why are you so violent?
In a violent mood.
We should be wholesome and teetee.
I'm just really happy to be here.
Five years...
Five years later she's done.
Oh no they know the real me now.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Sounds eager though, I apologize.
Well, there's not a lot of time for yapping too much today it would seem.
We're gonna dance our hearts out, sing our hearts out for you guys.
Oh man, we've been doing a lot of that these days.
I think everybody in Myth deserves a trophy.
A little reward perhaps?
A treat perhaps?
Cookies?
Cookies are good too.
Cookies sound good too.
Maybe a cookie shaped tro... or a trophy made out of a cookie?
Or a trophy shaped cookie.
Oh!
You hear that management?
You better be having some rewards for us!
We demanding!
Yeah, so demanding.
Wow, that's fun.
That's okay, in that case I know how we can kick this off.
Kick it off?
Yeah, so maybe it's like a little cheesy.
But I thought maybe the three of us could like jump in the air and go 'Weee!'
Like 3, 2, 1, jump! And then the camera goes 'Vwoom!'
Like flying in the air and go to the next song.
I get it, I get it.
I get you.
Done it before.
Then let's do it.
No punching, no violent thoughts Ina.
Don't punch the camera, I know what you're thinking.
Just one uppercut?
Not one, not... at zero!
Let's do it, okay?
On my count.
Ready? Okay.
Next song start!
Three, two, one, jump!
つまんないDays
Boring days
無惨残念
Cruel regret
奇跡願ってるだけの人生
A life just wishing for a miracle
Watch me do-do-do-do
Juju-juicy-juicy
トリック無しのmagic
Magic with no tricks
I wanna be free
だってmotherfucker
Because motherfucker
The party ain't started
Hey taxi
ちょっと宇宙まで
Take me to space for a bit
用心は 音を立てて
Carefully, making a sound
夜を急かす ママの事
Rushing the night, about Mom
人生は 一瞬にして
Life is but an instant
溶ける魔法 それならば
Melting magic, if that's the case
駆け抜けて 思い通りよ
Run through it, just as you wish
お邪魔なバッシュ飛び乗ってdriving
Jump on those pesky bash shoes and driving
あたしは大変身makeup
I'm doing a huge transformation makeup
わがままのまにまに
At the mercy of my selfishness
きらめきに チューチュー
Kiss kiss to the sparkle
Shut up な街で dancing
Dancing in this shut up town
さよならgoodbye劣等感
Farewell goodbye inferiority complex
カッとなって甲斐性無し
Getting mad and good for nothing
涙 皆 召し上がれ
Everyone, eat up your tears
ビビデバ ビデブーワ
Bibidi-ba-bidi-boowa
怖がってもしょうがない
It's no use being scared
ガラスのシューズで踊る tonight
Dancing in glass shoes tonight
ビビデバ ビデブーワ
Bibidi-ba-bidi-boowa
こんなに朝度ないなら
If morning is nowhere near
うちらにとっちゃ文句なし
Then we have no complaints
お邪魔なバッシュ飛び乗ってdriving
Jump on those pesky bash shoes and driving
あたしは大変身makeup
I'm doing a huge transformation makeup
わがままのまにまに
At the mercy of my selfishness
きらめきに チューチュー
Kiss kiss to the sparkle
Shut up な街で dancing
Dancing in this shut up town
さよならgoodbye劣等感
Farewell goodbye inferiority complex
カッとなって甲斐性無し
Getting mad and good for nothing
涙 皆 召し上がれ
Everyone, eat up your tears
ビビデバ ビデブーワ
Bibidi-ba-bidi-boowa
Hurry, hurry
Let's get started
耽溺で結構 Easy peasy pow
Indulgence is fine, Easy peasy pow.
Busy, busy, down
頭の中でこねくり回す
Kneading thoughts in my head,
後のペルソナに繋がる
connecting to a future persona,
産まれたてのアイディア
a newborn idea.
多少ムラがあるが
It's a bit inconsistent,
疑うこともなく才ある者が群がる
but the talented gather without doubt.
What about you?
ただ探求 妄想膨らます
Just seeking, expanding delusions.
居た堪れない
Can't stand it,
分かつ岐路の先に待つ結末は
the ending waiting beyond the fork,
麒麟児 大器晩成
a prodigy, a late bloomer,
はたまた臥竜鳳雛の末端
or the tail end of a sleeping dragon.
選ぶのは自分
The choice is yours,
血気盛ん
full of vigor.
かしましい喧噪に飲まれるな
Don't be swallowed by the noisy clamor.
Don't be late
しくじれば Anarchy
If you mess up, Anarchy,
Anarchy, Let you know my name
Calliope!
The music Junkie Junkie,
It was me, Calliope!
未だ本領発揮発揮
Still showing my true colors,
Let you know my name
Calliope!
This is Calliope!
Kick it back, coming up next level
The future's only colored by the cleverest of rebels
飽和した時代を駆け抜け
Running through a saturated era,
狂気断絶 種が芽吹く
cutting off madness, seeds sprout.
歪む脳症候
Distorted brain syndrome,
乱れ咲いた桜花
cherry blossoms blooming wildly,
浴びる Hope
bathing in Hope.
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Just a little madness
you can take the drive out of me
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Can't hide it's a new generation creation
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Tearing up the canvas
won't be what you want me to be
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
Too loud, too loud
unbalanced and unrefined
Find out the flood of noise
it's only in our minds
Right now, it's time
no doubt we're moving on
I'm drawn, my ideal world outside their lines
萌え立ったその瞬間
Wait for that moment it sprouts,
誰も気付けないマシーン感
a machine sense no one notices.
Breaking all expectations
初心忘れず蹴る
kicking without forgetting beginners' mind,
鬼が出るか蛇が出るか
will a demon or a snake appear?
排出マナ
Ejecting mana,
罪過の眼差し
gaze of sin.
高田症と情熱を維持
Maintaining high spirits and passion,
半端ない
it's insane.
Never hitting the brakes
the proof of God, what it takes
To manifest the world
you never discern as real or fake
So come on
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Just a little madness
you can take the drive out of me
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Can't hide it's a new generation creation
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Tearing up the canvas
won't be what you want me to be
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
ああ 一つも汚れても
Ah, even if it gets a little dirty,
自分の背中押せるような
if it's a dream that pushes my back,
夢があるならそれでいい
then that's enough.
タラレバで終わるよりも
Better than ending with 'what ifs',
一頻りもがき
struggling for a while.
止まない雨はないと信じ
Believe that no rain lasts forever,
今に様変わる
things will change soon.
Words are gifted, prolific
you have to be specific
Broad strokes blowing smoke,
blink and you can miss it
These words elicit visions of a future so exquisite
Some masterpiece you've never seen and wait until the few commits it
知らなきゃ怖いことがある 研究
There are scary things if you don't know, research.
出来ないことがあれば 練習
If you can't do it, practice.
姿勢は前のめり言わぬ 熱中
Posture leaning forward, silently engrossed.
成功の真反対にある失敗が一番の近道だ
Failure, the opposite of success, is the shortest path.
You can do it, Psycho
後は未知だ
the rest is unknown.
It's about you!
Starts aligning all designing heart
I'm already on my way
音走るトゲ潜む
Sound running, thorns hiding,
五感震える体中が自由になるまで
until my whole body shivering senses becomes free.
Force of blinded all this blindness hard
Gotta go with my own way
Vicious and vivid and striking my Nekkyo!
熱狂!
Nekkyo! (Frenzy!)
Vicious and vivid and striking my Nekkyo!
誤解すんなよ
Don't get me wrong,
こんな滑稽な
it's just laughable.
サッと過ぎ去る毎日(エブリデイ)
Everyday flashes by in an instant.
Another prisoner of fate no one could fake out
Stay awake now
you know you wanna fire away
Now there's no question where the fault lies
These days I struggle just to empathize
もう戻らないってわかっているんだろ。
You know there's no going back, right?
Cast a blessing on my cursed role
And feed this bleeding egotistical soul
Before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of distant days,
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I end up thinking about the meaning of my birth.
嗚呼 美しい青い日々だな
Ah, what beautiful blue days they were.
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
Should I burn them into my eyes?
もう少し強くならないとな
I need to become a little stronger.
身分不相応の嫉妬に塗れた
Smeared with jealousy unsuited to my station,
ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
an ecstasy that's a bit lacking.
誤解も解けないまま私
Without resolving the misunderstanding,
人を傷つけて
I hurt people.
一粒の才すらないわ
I don't even have a grain of talent,
転がり落ちたジロロサイ
the rolling dice falls.
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I even notice your love.
Cast a blessing on my cursed heart
Why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか神様教えてくれますか
Please, God, will you tell me?
言葉少なに貴方に捧ぐ
I give to you silently
今に消えてしまいそうなこの命を
My life that's about to burn out
嗚呼 愛おしいセピア色した
Ah, and these sepia-toned nights
何より大事なこの景色を
They're most precious of all
もう少し見ていたいよな
I wish I could see them a bit more...
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
If I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The devils on my shoulder never let me be
Obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
Somebody save me
My world is caving in cuz I thought I deserved it all for free yeah yeah
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい青い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
春嵐 今 踊り踊れ
Spring storm, now dance, dance
恋焦がれ遊べ 桜って歌え
Yearn for love and play, sing of cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今を取り戻せ
Disappear into the flowers, take back this moment
水興に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with whimsy, come now, dance right here
沈む夕日 待ち人が過ぎてく
The setting sun, the person I wait for passes by
色とりどり緑 酸いも甘いも祭囃子
Colorful greenery, sour and sweet, the festival music
あれもこれもカゴを放り込み
Throwing this and that into the basket
欲にまみれ生きて痛い
I want to live covered in desire till it hurts
人生より道 回り道
Life is a detour, a roundabout way
行きたいように生きなはれや
Live however you want to live
春嵐 今 踊り踊れ
Spring storm, now dance, dance
恋焦がれ遊べ 桜って歌え
Yearn for love and play, sing of cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今を取り戻せ
Disappear into the flowers, take back this moment
水興に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with whimsy, come now, dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらっぱ
Yuru yururi rara yururirappa
散るは丁度ときは過ぎ
Scattering perfectly as time passes
酸いも甘いも祭囃子
Sour and sweet, the festival music
味わい尽くしてしまいましょう
Let's savor it all until the end
さあ 何から平らげよう
Well, what shall we devour first?
人生気付けば矢の如し
Life flies like an arrow before you know it
命の花を打ち上げましょう
Let's launch the fireworks of life
春嵐 今 踊り踊れ
Spring storm, now dance, dance
恋焦がれ遊べ 桜って歌え
Yearn for love and play, sing of cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今を取り戻せ
Disappear into the flowers, take back this moment
水興に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with whimsy, come now, dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらっぱ
Yuru yururi rara yururirappa
花よ花よ
Oh flower, oh flower
誇りなさい
Bloom proudly
迷うことなく君のまま
Without hesitation, just as you are
上を向いてごらんなさい
Look up and see
最後の日まで花であれ
Be a flower until the very last day
春嵐 今 踊り踊れ
Spring storm, now dance, dance
恋焦がれ遊べ 桜って歌え
Yearn for love and play, sing of cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今を取り戻せ
Disappear into the flowers, take back this moment
水興に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with whimsy, come now, dance right here
春嵐 今 踊り踊れ
Spring storm, now dance, dance
誰彼も遊べ 桜って歌え
Everyone play, sing of cherry blossoms
花離れでも花火上げて
Even if the flowers scatter, launch the fireworks
水興に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with whimsy, come now, dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらっぱ
Yuru yururi rara yururirappa
愛したいこうしたいどうしたい
I want to love, want to do this, what do I want to do?
まだ天真爛漫みたい
It seems I'm still innocent and naive.
石の上にも三年
Perseverance prevails.
でもそんなんじゃ
But with just that...
AIサーキュレーション
AI Circulation.
やっと始まるストーリー
Finally, the story begins.
だって棚ぼたのようなエモーション
Because it's an emotion like a windfall.
殻から飛び出し
Jumping out of the shell,
いい気味だなんて
saying "Serves you right."
君はキメ顔で
You, with a posed look...
永遠を願った夢に
In the dream that wished for eternity,
終わりを告げる朝が来て
the morning that announces the end comes.
お砂糖でできたその涙
Those tears made of sugar...
見つめ 見つめ
Staring, staring,
見つけた心
the heart I found.
甘くほろ苦い
Sweet and bittersweet,
カラメルのように
just like caramel.
絡まるリボンは
The entangling ribbon
呪いの鎧だけど
is a cursed armor, but...
この気持ちはそう
This feeling is, yes,
この気持ちにしか
only this feeling
きっとわかんないから
can surely understand.
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hand in hand with you,
ひとつひとつ叶えてゆこう
let's make them come true one by one.
僕らの物語は
Our story is
今日も続く
a promise that continues
約束
even today.
色とりどりの
Colorful,
真っ黒な歴史
pitch-black history.
愛おしい私の
My beloved
歴史
history.
誰も知らない
A pure white page
真っ白なページ
that no one knows,
更新して
I will go on
ゆく
updating it.
話したくない
The tear I don't
綻びは
want to talk about...
離したくない
With the joy I don't
喜びで
want to let go,
継ぎ接ぎだらけの
this heart full of patches,
この心
I spun and spun,
紡ぎ紡ぎ
the place
繋いだ所
I connected.
憧れ恋焦がれ
Admiring, yearning,
待ち焦がれ全部全部全部
waiting impatiently, everything everything!
プリンみたいに
Flip it over
ひっくり返して
like a pudding.
Caramel caramel my own flavor
どこ痛いそこ痛い
Where does it hurt? It hurts there.
切り離したままじゃ僕はパズルのピース
Left separated, I am just a puzzle piece.
でもそんなんじゃやだ
But I don't want that!
でもそんなんじゃダメ
But that's no good!
僕はキメ顔でせーの
I pose with a cool face, ready set!
好きの切り札は
The trump card of love,
自分で選ぶの
I choose it myself.
運命の赤い
Pulling in the red
リボンを手繰り寄せて
ribbon of fate.
この気持ちはそう
This feeling is, yes,
この気持ちにしか
only this feeling
きっとわかんないから
can surely understand.
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hand in hand with you,
ひとつひとつ叶えてゆこう
let's make them come true one by one.
僕らの物語は
Our story is
今日も続く
a promise that continues
約束
even today.
君と手と手繋いで
Holding hand in hand with you,
ひとつひとつ叶えてゆこう
let's make them come true one by one.
僕らの物語は
Our story is
今日も続く
a promise that continues
約束
even today.
色とりどりに
Colorfully,
真っ黒な歴史
pitch-black history.
愛おしい僕らの
Our beloved
歴史
history.
残さず食べて
Eat it all up without leaving any,
全部糧にして
turn it all into fuel,
更新して
and go on
ゆく
updating it.
Welcome back Calli!
Oh, hi. Hey.
You guys look a little tired.
I thought we were posing for the Myth album cover...
...which is not coming out by the way.
Don't misunderstand.
Did you guys enjoy the song so far?
Yeah...
Was pretty fire.
Yeah yeah yeah.
We did a really cute one Ina.
Caramel Ribbon Cursetard.
Yeah...
You guys's voices...
...fit really really well with that song.
Oh thank you.
Yeah, it's a really cute song.
Yeah. I...
...me and Ina were like "What song should we do together?"
And I was like...
..."Oh, I wonder if Ina would let me do a Monogatari song?"
I was like "Monogatari please!"
And she's like "Naisu!"
Wait wait wait wait.
You're talking to Ninomae Ina'nis you know.
Of course I'm gonna say yeah.
Right right. Cause we all like Monogatari right?
We do. Yeah.
Calli would have done it too huh?
Sure, yeah I would have done it.
We could have had her doing the...
I can do it now. Uh.
Ah, I should have done it as three people.
Then you got even more cute.
But we also tried to be cute as we can.
We got everybody's solos though.
Yeah. Except mine. We don't know anything about those.
You guys know I could rap that fast?
Like, I was surprised.
Impressive.
Yeah. Maa maa maa.
Kakkoii Kiara.
I did my best. It was like enough...
...enough to... I was like "Oh, you know, she did it."
And plus the dancing was pretty cool so.
Oh yeah.
Gambatta.
Good job. And Ina too, very impressive.
Oh my goodness, I really challenged myself.
The dancing has leveled up so much.
Yeah.
Through the roof... but...
We did it.
And then, me and Ina did some air guitar.
Yeah, bringing out the guitar!
My original song, Sepia.
Very close song to my heart.
Yeah, I love the purple guitar.
What's still missing now?
Well there are a couple songs missing, aren't there?
Like the Wah-Wah... So... My So... So...
Mine and Calli's combination... song?
I wonder...
What you guys are gonna sing?
I wonder... I wonder...
I will just say that the song for me and Calli was also chosen...
kind of by... suggested by me.
Thank you for being okay with it.
It's a nice song.
I guess, yeah, I don't wanna spoil anything but...
That was pretty good.
And my solo will be... uh... epic.
And hype.
Why did you choose it?
Can you give a hint?
I know it's about to happen pretty soon, but...
No! No! Damn it!
No! Alright, alright.
Why?
Yes, we still have a lot of a show left over, so...
Don't tune out.
There's lots more.
Stay with us.
Stay right there.
Don't move.
Wait!
And continue to watch until the end.
And use the hashtag, don't forget that.
Okay, hashtag.
Are we ready to move on?
Move on.
Okay.
What should we do?
We should...
We should play with the camera.
I know what to do.
What do you want to do the most right now?
I know what to do!
Bam! Bam! Bam! Bam!
Not something violent, right?
Okay.
Bam! Bam! Bam! Bam! Hey!
Dear God,
I've come to repent my sins.
Let your blood wash me clean for I'm...
I'm... I'm...
I'm a rotten girl.
I swore I'd never sin again.
But my patience running thin...
Such a temptation flowing through my veins.
Bounded by these shackles of shame.
I promised I'd indulge no more.
But my heart I can't ignore.
In my dreams they're turning up the heat.
I'm a dirty rotten girl.
Unlocked, underneath the bleachers.
Just watch, look beyond the smoke and mirrors.
Heart struck, shun the non-believers.
Our reparation would never be complete.
Red hot, tension with each whisper.
Snapshot, quiet moans and muffled whimpers.
Come on, can't you feel the fever,
Rising up, rising up to the sky.
As venom injects the fear, glistening in my skin.
The Lord says love thy child, don't give into sin.
It's driving me crazy, the urge to forsake the answer.
Something shifts within this wicked bliss.
I swore I'd never sin again.
But my patience running thin...
Student council breathing down my neck.
I wonder if they're hiding from me...
Forbidden fruits before my eyes.
And a taste that's so divine.
My regrets rewriting history.
I'm a sad, pathetic girl.
Someone please tell me what to do.
Because honestly I just can't stop.
I've been trying so hard and I can't stop.
What would God think?
And I, I know I'm supposed to be a good girl but...
Somehow I just can't control myself.
Every time I see them, touching skin to skin,
my mind goes... my mind goes...
Ahhh!
Could Eve be our idol?
Could she lead us through the light?
With all the disciples of lemon-driven vice.
Cause somebody save me,
the urge to forsake the still,
Something shifts within this wicked bliss.
The power resting in my hands.
Oh my god is such a plan.
Until salvation, I can live my life
as an ordinary girl.
I can't resist it anymore.
Cause I smell sulfur galore.
All the drama from a couple's role.
Could never beat the devil in me.
And I'm a sinner till I die.
What's the harm if I don't mind?
But the thought that empowers me,
I can live a sinful...
Check, one, two!
Check, one, two! Yeah!
あーもう無理！文化祭
Ah, it's impossible! The culture festival.
言葉にダンスに…キャパオーバーです
Words, dance... it's over capacity.
心配無用のおまじない
A charm for no worries.
きっと報われる その努力
That effort will surely be rewarded.
笑顔になぁれ
Become a smile!
ドキドキしてる
My heart is pounding.
ありえないくらい本気だし
I'm unbelievably serious.
魔法がかかる
Magic is cast.
今日限りヒーロータイム
Hero time just for today.
何卒ね？
Please, okay?
Let's go!
Baby kiss 照れないで
Baby kiss, don't be shy.
気持ち伝えてよ
Convey your feelings.
好き！
I like you!
相思相愛 好き
Mutual love, I like you.
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup falls apart,
髪が乱れても
even if my hair gets messy.
好き！
I like you!
絶対忘れない青春の1ページ
A page of youth I'll never forget.
Hai!
あー超気持ちいい！文化祭
Ah, feels so good! The culture festival.
隣で笑ってる君のおかげだ
It's thanks to you smiling next to me.
弱気な私変えてくれた
You changed the weak me.
絶対最強のパートナー
Absolutely the strongest partner.
マジでありがとう
Seriously, thank you.
覚醒してる
I'm awakening.
ファンサの効力マシマシで
Fan service efficacy increasing.
魔法強まる
Magic strengthens.
終わりかけヒーロータイム
Ending hero time.
延長ね？
Extension, right?
Let's go!
Baby kiss 隠さずに
Baby kiss, without hiding.
気持ち伝えてよ
Convey your feelings.
好き！
I like you!
相思相愛 好き
Mutual love, I like you.
おやつ食べたいし
I want to eat snacks.
帰宅いいですか？
Can I go home?
ダメ！
No!
ごめん嘘嘘 こちらこそ帰さない
Sorry, lie lie! I won't let you go either.
TakaMori for five years!
Can you guys keep it going?
いくよー！
Here we go!
カリちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Calli-chan super cute?
カリちゃんは超かわいい！
Calli-chan is super cute!
キアラちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Kiara-chan super cute?
キアラちゃんは超かわいい！
Kiara-chan is super cute!
Big ups everybody!
Danke schön!
Thank you!
Are you ready?
Three, two, one, go!
魔法解けちゃうね
The magic will melt away.
最後に聞かせてよ
Let me hear it one last time.
好き？
Do you like me?
大きな声で好き！
With a loud voice, I like you!
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup falls apart,
髪が乱れても
even if my hair gets messy.
好き！
I like you!
絶対忘れない青春の1ページ
A page of youth I'll never forget.
Hai!
Na na na na na na na, yeah!
ダンダダン ダンダダン ダンダダン ダンダダン
Dandadan dandadan dandadan dandadan
人目も悪い輩 あんたらなんかじゃ束なっても適わん
Evil spirits in the public eye, even if you bunch together you're no match.
クワバラ クワバラ クワバラ
Kuwabara kuwabara kuwabara
何にも止まらぬ速さ
Speed that nothing can stop.
ええ？ 来た！わらわら
Eh? They came! Swarming.
だんまり？
Silence?
下らん押し通す我儘
Pushing through stupid selfishness.
其処退け 代打だ
Move aside, I'm the pinch hitter.
童はもう一人の貴方
I am another you.
8時44分回った
It's past 8:44.
解釈 4寸4分様が構わなくちゃバグらん
If Mr. Interpretation doesn't care, it'll crash.
ええ 藪から明日なら文字通り お疲れ様やん
If tomorrow's a surprise, then literally, good job.
這い出た 這い出た 這い出た
Crawled out, crawled out, crawled out...
必死で這い出た先
Desperately crawled out ahead,
で霧は晴れた
and the fog cleared.
過去と僕が
If the past and I...
うまく噛み合ったら
...mesh well together.
痛みが重なったら
If the pain overlaps.
心 体 頭
Heart, body, head...
みなぎっていく 何だか
...somehow filling up with power.
背中に今 羽が
If wings have grown...
生えたならば
...on my back now,
暗闇からサラバ
farewell to the darkness.
ええ
Yeah,
飛び立っていく彼方
flying off to the distance.
ええ
Yeah.
心 体 頭
Heart, body, head...
懐かしい温かさ
...a nostalgic warmth.
足元に今 花が
If flowers have bloomed...
咲いたならば
...at my feet now,
暗闇からサラバ
farewell to the darkness.
ええ
Yeah,
飛び立っていく彼方
flying off to the distance.
Hoo!
何度だって生きる
I'll live again and again,
お前や君の中
inside you and you.
瞼の裏や
Behind the eyelids,
耳の中
and inside the ears.
胸の奥に
Deep in the chest,
居着いてるメロディ
the melody settled there.
リズムに
Into the rhythm.
Yeah!
Dan da dan dan...
今日 明日 何か変わらぬど真ん中
Today, tomorrow, something unchanging in the center.
積み上げてく Top of top
Piling up, top of top.
鬼とチャンバラ
Sword fighting with demons.
The lyrical chainsaw massacre
渡る大海原
Crossing the great ocean.
鼻歌 過ぎ去り シャララ
Humming a tune, passing by, sha-la-la.
祓いたいのなら
If you want to exorcise,
待った 今際の際だわ
wait, it's the brink of death.
誰が開いたかパンドラ
Who opened Pandora's box?
あとは何が出ても知らんがら No way
I don't care what comes out after. No way.
何百年待ったか 超久しぶりのシャバだ
Waited hundreds of years, ages since I was out.
Whoo!
ガキや若葉
Brats and greenhorns,
まだこっち来んじゃねえよバカ
don't come over here yet, idiot.
今確かに目があったな
Our eyes definitely met just now.
こういうことかよ しょうがない
So that's how it is? Can't be helped.
這い出た 這い出た 這い出た
Crawled out, crawled out, crawled out...
眠り飽きた先で
Tired of sleeping,
君が待ってた
you were waiting there.
縦と横が
If vertical and horizontal...
片抱き合ったら
...embrace one side.
光が差したら
If the light shines in.
心 体 頭
Heart, body, head...
みなぎっていく 何だか
...somehow filling up with power.
背中に今 羽が
If wings have grown...
生えたならば
...on my back now,
暗闇からサラバ
farewell to the darkness.
ええ
Yeah,
飛び立っていく彼方
flying off to the distance.
ええ
Yeah.
心 体 頭
Heart, body, head...
懐かしい温かさ
...a nostalgic warmth.
足元に今 花が
If flowers have bloomed...
咲いたならば
...at my feet now,
暗闇からサラバ
farewell to the darkness.
ええ
Yeah,
飛び立っていく彼方
flying off to the distance.
Hoo!
何度だって生きる
I'll live again and again,
お前や君の中
inside you and you.
瞼の裏や
Behind the eyelids,
耳の中
and inside the ears.
胸の奥に
Deep in the chest,
居着いてるメロディ
the melody settled there.
リズムに
Into the rhythm.
Yeah!
Dan da dan dan...
There's an answer out there somewhere,
When the Muses whisper truth or dare.
The hands of fate play tug-of-war,
But no one's keeping score.
Stay the course and be tenacious,
'Cause the future is a game of chance.
The chips are down but I'm all in,
I play until I win.
I'm not gonna give up now,
The wheels of fortune circle back around.
A new turn in the betting ring,
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string.
And through this tangled thread,
I see what's up ahead!
A wild chase,
a frantic pace,
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate!
Ah la da da da da da da...
I'm always spinning fate.
Whoa, yeah.
Spin the roulette,
see where it falls,
Testing the limits and betting it all.
Round and around,
jumping into the circle,
Over and over, a test of will.
Oh, the game is never easy,
and the outcome is a mystery.
But these are fates worth betting on,
their threads unbroken.
Called to life
by flaxen strings.
Casting lots together
at the start of everything.
I'm not gonna give up yet,
I spin back 'round with every chance I get.
The wheel turns and the die is cast,
The time has come for fate to change at last.
And if it's black or red,
I'm moving up ahead!
A perfect chance,
a daring dance,
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands!
Ooh la la la...
I'm taking fate into my hands.
Whoa, yeah.
And through this tangled thread,
I see what's up ahead!
New song, new song, new song!
New song!
Yay!
It's our first song as a trio, you guys.
Oh, really?
Oh, true!
Thanks.
That was a good workout.
Yeah.
I guess that's because all the zoomers like it short nowadays, huh?
That's what everybody says.
Not me.
Certainly not.
But yeah, unfortunately this was also the last song for this live.
Ehhh?
But!
The music video for our 5th anniversary song, Fortune Spinner...
...will premiere on the hololive English official YouTube channel right after this concert!
So make sure you stick around, okay?
Don't miss it.
Don't miss it!
Make sure you watch it a lot.
And loop it a lot.
Please.
Yes.
Very much.
そうですね。
That's right.
That is right.
We still have some celebrating to do though, right?
That's right, I think it's time, because it's the end, that we kind of celebrate ourselves here.
Five years!
Are we ready for that?
Yeah.
Yes, we're ready.
Okay, let's do it!
Let's do it!
Oh!
What is that cake over there? That is not mine.
Hey!
Oh.
Wait wait wait wait wait!
Come on! Come on!
Wait can we eat it?
Let's talk about how delicious it looks.
Yeah!
No no I can't see it.
It's big too.
It's almost bigger than Ina.
Oh yeah.
Hey stop stop stop not now not now!
Don't pick off the strawberries!
Hold your horses!
Let's eat it later and celebrate.
Later, later.
And look, the trophies!
Yeah!
That's true.
Wait do we actually get trophies?
Yeah, and awards show, right?
Is that some of this?
They were listening. Thank you.
They followed our shopping list accordingly.
Okay.
Five years, we deserve an award.
Yeah.
We had so many meaningful accomplishments, so let's see what they all are, okay?
Okay.
Look at it be!
Should I start?
I'll take mine.
Achoo!
Oh bless you.
Sorry.
I'm not trying to disrupt your award.
Cha cha cha cha!
What did you get? What did you get?
はい！ Er...
Yes! Er...
My award is...
Uh let's see... uh... I think it says...
Most... Cooked... Cooked the Most?
She's cooking.
In HoloEN.
Let her cook.
Let her keep doing it.
She has been cooking a lot. She has a lot of meals.
Yes, thank you.
I think that's what that's about. Mostly it's about, uh, you know...
...me living a healthy lifestyle...
...and then cooking many meals uh at home.
I wish I could cook for you girls someday.
Someday.
I hope you guys enjoyed my performances today.
I am so proud to like...
...stand here with my genmates...
...even on this day after so many years.
Um, I will continue to work hard, of course.
So that I can maybe gather even more awards.
Um, I will put this on my shelf at home...
...where my cats will also probably put a lot of fur on it.
Oh yeah.
Yum yum.
Or knock it down.
Meow meow.
No no!
They like to do that.
Is it out of real glass?
I gotta be a little bit careful but...
Careful.
Thank you guys so much! I love you! Mwah mwah mwah mwah!
It's been an honor so far, so let's do our best together.
Thank you for this award!
Congrats!
Who's the next one?
Who is next?
Is it... Ninomae Ina'nis?
Me?
Oh, could my award be, let's see...
Most violent.
What? Violent?
No.
100%.
You do it to yourself.
Alright. My award... is...
Oh!
Oh! Oh yes. I already guessed.
It is... Most Time Spent on the Floor.
That I believe.
Thank you thank you thank you.
I know you guys probably think I would never get this award, but you know...
I worked so hard this year to stay on the floor.
Very unprecedented.
And uh yeah, not only did I stay on the floor...
I, you know, really did my best to uh practice dancing and singing this year...
...to perform well with you guys.
And I hope that you guys see that as well.
Thank you so much for all your support.
I'll continue to do my best with these girls.
Yay!
Let's keep doing it!
And last but not least.
Mori Calliope.
Oh what could it be?
Our sneezer?
Look at this.
Don't sneeze today.
Most sneezes in the Myth 5th anniversary showcase.
Most blessed.
Well, actually my trophy is for... じゃじゃーん！
Well, actually my trophy is for... Ta-da!
Best Worst Luck.
Especially in games where there are microtransactions.
Ehhh? That's not so pop!
Yeah, I mean I've seen it happen in real life.
But the dedication, the determination to pull a signed card...
I'm not gonna give up yet.
Real quick, I'm gonna be very sappy.
Well okay. Go ahead.
I really like that line. 'I'm not gonna...'
I'd like to think that we're not gonna give up yet,
because there's still so much that I wanna do...
uh, the three of us together.
Together.
You know, um...
and I didn't think that I would be here five years from the start...
...with you guys.
Same.
Yeah.
I really thought I'd be out of here.
Same.
But now, I can't... I can't see a future where I'm not here with you guys.
Awww.
That's so romantic!
So... shut up.
Okay.
So because of that, I'm not gonna give up yet.
I don't want to give up yet.
So let's do our best together.
Oh yeah, the wrapping up jingle is playing.
I'm just gonna start talking about nothing because that annoys me...
...when they play the jingle to tell me to stop.
This morning I ate a bagel and it had cream cheese on it.
It was delicious, but it went over my calories.
I'm in big trouble with my trainer.
Okay, wrap it up! Wrap it up!
Anyway!
Five years! Five years!
You can't get rid of me!
Alright.
You can't get rid of any of us, hopefully!
Hopefully.
Hehehe.
Well everybody, all good things come to an end, unfortunately.
But thank you so much to the hololive English community for supporting us continuously for five years.
Thank you to the girlies today and all the staff-san that supported us also...
...for this celebration, who gave us the trophies!
Yeah!
Once again, congratulations to us!
To us!
Yay!
Woo-hoo!
Thank you!
Thanks guys!
Bye bye!
Peace!
We forgot our merch!
Merch! Please!
Merch time!
The merchandise!
Next is the merchandise announcement!
We have hololive English -Myth- 5th Anniversary Celebration merch being released!
Let's look at the details. Check it out!
First up, we've got the Mirror Acrylic Panel.
It's designed so that the surroundings and background of the illustration have a metallic mirrored vibe.
Ooh, so cool!
I absolutely love this illustration.
Hope you guys do too.
Next up, we have... the Collection Cards!
These cards feature a shiny metallic finish...
...and you can choose from three different designs.
Also, the backside is matching for us all.
Make sure to get the one from your oshi, for sure!
Next up, we have the Coin Medals!
Our shiny 5th Anniversary commemorative coin medals.
There's one design for each member.
And the back sides also have a common design.
They come in an antique gold-plated finish inside the original packaging.
Ooh, so shiny!
Oh man, everything looks so good!
But, I'm especially interested in what we have to show you guys next.
Next up, we have the Anniversary Hats!
So first up, Anniversary Hat - Mori Calliope.
This one uses a soft, fluffy fabric.
The Death-sensei part is removable...
...so you can also rock it without him.
Make sure that you check it out. It's super stylish.
I love the shape so much.
And, uh, all of my member Deadbeats voted on it together.
So hope that you guys will enjoy.
Next up we have mine! The Anniversary Hat from Takanashi Kiara.
Looks like this!
Decorative parts are removable.
It can be worn reversibly, inside out...
...so you'll have a different color then.
And it's a bucket hat style design...
...which we didn't have before for me.
Very fashionable, I must say.
Last but not least, we have my hat!
The Anniversary Hat - Ninomae Ina'nis.
The ribbon part is removable and the patches are super cute too.
You can wear it to become a Takodachi.
Yes.
And yeah, you can mix and match with or without the ribbon for different looks.
So, everybody, be sure to check our merch out!
And that concludes our 5th year anniversary stream!
Otsu-Myth!
Thanks for 5 years together everyone! Are you ready for more?! It's already been the best journey a Reaper could ask for but let's run towards a future we wanna see! I ain't done yet! Love ya! Calliope Mori
Thank you for an unforgettable 5 years! I can't wait for even more amazing, fun things in the future!! Buckle in!! It's going to be an exciting ride up ahead!! Go Next!! INA
Kikkeriki!! These 5 years were super crazy with many ups and downs but together we conquered every hurdle, together we will forever stay locked in my heart and I love you all so much! Cheers to more with my myth girls! Kiara