(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
INA'NIS 3D SHOWCASE #TakoTimes3
Wha...
Hi everyone!
Oh, I see all of your comments! Hi!
How are you?
Ah, what time is it?
It's Tako Time!
Ah, hi, hi!
How are you guys doing?
Are you excited? Good.
Well, first of all, one thing I, you know, promised you guys...
...was to kabedon as soon as I got the 3D showcase, so...
Kabedon!
Oya oya Takodachis, what are you doing here?
My, my, Takodachis. What are you doing here?
Oh no... Ah, I was so, so, so, so nervous...
...but you know, let's just, let's just do it normally. Normally. Hi!
Hi! Hi everyone! Isn't it so exciting?
We waited so, so long for this to finally happen.
And it's finally here! It's finally here!
I can't, I can't contain my excitement. I'm sorry.
But you know, I'm going first. You know, usually for relays we ended up with, you know, the debut order...
...but this time for special, special event I'm the first one to go. So I'll do my best...
...but make sure you check out the other three showcases coming up in the upcoming weeks too! Yay!
But yeah.
So, first of all, I guess I can show you guys around the place?
Maybe? Maybe? Yeah.
Okay, come here, so follow me. Follow me. Yeah.
So, you guys have maybe a little bit familiar with this place.
So, you guys might be a little bit familiar with this place.
You know, there's some art supplies, you know, my little drawing workspace. Oh!
I guess I haven't really shown you guys how I do traditional art, but...
Someone familiar! Could it be?
AO-chan!
このネクロノミコンがすごい！ 第1位！
This Necronomicon is Amazing! No. 1!
このネクロノミコンがすごい！ 1st
This Necronomicon is Amazing! 1st
Al-chan...
...in the flesh.
Al-chan's sleeping right now but I guess...
...you heard of Ina's back, how about Al-chan's back?
TVドラマ化決定！！
TV Drama Adaptation Confirmed!!
I guess you don't really see Al-chan's back that often, hey?
But apparently the TV drama has been decided on but...
...you know, I think it's still in the works.
But yeah, this is Al-chan.
And I guess you can look around the rest of the room.
Well, here's my little bookshelf area. It's not full of books yet but...
...there's a couch over there I usually like to sleep on, you know, I sleep everywhere.
And yeah, some miscellaneous things and of course, can't forget...
...my streaming desk.
That's right, I stream from here, you know, I go...
Tututututu...
Hi guys!
And you guys see, see the, you know, the view behind me. Yeah, yeah.
And then if we walk over a little more this way, you get to see...
...more books! I love books.
But then there's like a beautiful garden out there, you guys don't really get to see this often, right? Yeah.
And of course, can't forget this angle of the room...
...which you guys are very familiar with. Yay!
This is my little studio. What do you guys think? Isn't it great? Yeah.
So exciting!
Yeah, you know, I really want to show you guys, you know, this full space and...
...finally after what, two, two and a half, maybe two and a half, two years ish? Yeah.
Um, yeah, I'm so, so happy.
I'm losing my vocabulary here because I'm so, so nervous and happy and...
...just flooded with emotions.
But I guess there's one thing you guys have been looking forward to when it comes to 3D streams, so...
...something I haven't shown you guys yet.
I mean, I've appeared in lives, I've appeared in different shows and programs in my 3D.
There's one thing, one thing I've asked to be kept secret until today.
What do you think it is? What could it be?
That's right! My tentacles. Ina-boinboins.
But you know, it's a little, just a little embarrassing so look away...
...maybe look away a little bit. Just look away a little bit. Okay.
Are you guys ready? Wait. Doon! Tada! Ina-boinboin!
Ina-boinboin! That's right, I told you guys, it's not...
...it's not attached to my back, there's like a void gate in there somewhere that they're summoned from, but boinboin!
I take so... I'm going to touch them. Don't you just want to squeeze them? You can't.
But they're boinboin! Wee!
Boinboin boinboin boinboin boinboin boinboin!
Okay, calm down Ina, calm down. It'll be okay.
Hmm, what do you guys think? Yay!
Oh? I got a call? Ah, tentacles, you're kind of in the way. Okay, look away for a second.
Look away for a second. Poi! Are they gone? Okay, we good.
CHALLENGE
We got a message from Myth! Oh my goodness!
A challenge! Hmm, what could they have cooked up for me?
Well, they sent some messages for me, so let's see, let's see what they have.
Okay, start with Kiara. Pop pop pop!
Uwa! Oh, Kikiriki! Hello everybody, this is Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth!
Hi Kiara! Your gen-mate. First of all, congratulations on being number one for the range!
Thank you! So case, let's go! I'm doing fine right now. No, hopefully. I'm scared.
Well, I am here to request a pose or two from you. Okay. So let me start...
I want two things. Let me start with I want your best or your cutest idol pose that you can think of in 5 seconds.
Idol pose, idol pose! I'll give you 5 seconds to think. 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, go!
Cute! Jeez! Oh, cute! Okay, okay, here we go again.
Next one! Next one's next! Okay, okay, okay, next one next. お客みなさん、上から目線でお願いします。
Next one! Next one's next! Okay, okay, okay, next one's next. Everyone, please look from a top-down perspective.
イナちゃんは下の方に。
Ina-chan, please be at the bottom.
Instructions for camera?
Yeah, and now Ina...
...put your hands together like you're praying.
Okay, and do a pouty face.
As if you're asking the viewer for some... something.
Yes, cookies, like "Onegai"? "Onegai"?
Yes, cookies, like "Please"? "Please"?
Credit card number, please!
Keep on doing that. Alright.
Bye-bye!
Bye Kiara! Thank you!
CHALLENGE
Yeah, Kiara flew over to, you know, somewhere else for now.
But yeah, thank you Kiara.
Oh, Idol pose, Idol pose is always tough, you know? But I'll try.
Okay, who do we have next? Ame!
Hi Ina!
Ame!
I'm so proud of you!
Oh, thank you Ame!
I know it takes a lot of courage to get up and do this stuff in front of a lot of people.
You finally made it! Yay!
Yay!
I love watching you move and wave around, the thing you do with your arms, the Wiggle!
You know, I already know, you look so cute doing it too.
So my pose request is first, you gotta plank.
That's right, you gotta get down on the ground and do that trend that people did a long time ago.
This is just the first step, okay?
Okay, okay.
I'll wait. Are you there yet?
No...
Okay, okay. Then, if staff doesn't yell at you...
...you gotta do the worm!
Oh no, staff already is yelling at me, it seems I cannot do the worm.
Okay, I can do this though, I can... yes.
Is it more of like a full body wave?
Yeah, yeah. Ina and her waving arms, tentacles always.
She does it too! And back... and back.
Well, hopefully that wasn't too difficult of a pose.
Thank you Ina.
Thank you Ame! Love you!
Goodbye! I love you Ame! I love you!
Oh Ame... Oh Ame is so cute.
I can't wait to see her showcase as well!
Okay, who do we have next? Oh, from Calli!
Hello there Ina, Ina, Ina!
Hi Calli!
It's me, your boy, your reaper, Mori Calliope of the Myth generation, same one as you! Wow!
Oh man, I have a lot to say, but I feel like it might end up being redundant or unnecessary.
So I'm just gonna say thanks for being a shoulder for me to lean on, quite literally sometimes.
We've had so much fun together between Guilty Gear Strive and playing recorders together...
...and hopefully soon we can do the ukulele thing.
Oh yeah!
But until then, I just want to let you know that you're a great friend that I can always depend upon...
...and I never feel weird talking to you ever.
Like, it's always really chill and laid back, and I think it's 'cause you remind me of my art friends from the past.
So you're a very important person to me.
And so, since I feel so comfortable around you, I'm gonna ask you to do some poses...
...that make you feel uncomfortable. But not in like a weird way...
...like in like a way where like it's hard for you to do them.
Because everybody here is gonna be asking you to do like cute things, I'm sure, right?
Well, I'm here to dish out the real challenges, 'cause life is full of challenges, you know?
So... I'm gonna ask you to do the worm.
Can you do the worm, Cali... Ina?
Calli! I can't do the worm!
I can only do this! I can only do this!
I'm guessing the worm might be a little difficult for you, but I want to see you put your back into it, you know? Give it your all.
But in the event that you can't do the worm, that's okay, I've prepared a second choice.
You may choose between the worm or the splits.
She's gonna get me back for this one, isn't she? Oh god.
Just you wait Mori Calliope!
You should have been nicer to me!
I should be nicer to her today because she's the first one debuting 3D, oh man, I'm gonna be in big trouble.
Okay, look, Ina. Splits are good for you.
They can be good for you. For your health.
Make you flexible, right?
That's not in my dictionary.
You'll thank me later. Okay, I'll try not to stretch your muscles too bad, whichever one you choose, okay?
I'll try, okay.
If that happens, I'll give you a massage to make up for it, okay? That's a good deal, though.
Not quite as good as Gura, but still.
You can count on me, just like I can count on you. Good luck!
Thank you Calli! Oh, she disappeared.
Alright. Well, I can't do the worm, so I'll try the splits. I'll try the splits.
Okay, I think that's it.
This is... this is as far as I go.
You see, I'm not that flexible.
See, I can't... oh yeah, I can touch my toes.
Okay, that's as far as...
That's as far as I go.
I'm sorry, I tried! I tried, chat, I tried.
I practiced, but I just can't touch my toes.
But okay, we have... I think we have one last...
One last message...
...from Goombah, Gooba!
あっ、
Ah,
あーっ！
Ah!
Hi Ina!
Gooba!
Ina!
I want to watch you do the...
...Houshou Marine desu!
Okay.
Good luck with the rest of your...
...3D showcase.
Love you, Ina.
Love you, Gura.
Heart!
Houshou Marine desu!
Ah...
Uh...
How do I do this?
How does it go again?
Chat...
I don't know how.
ホロライブ3期生、
Hololive 3rd Gen,
宝鐘マリンですー！
Houshou Marine desu!
船長、すみません。
Sencho, I'm sorry.
すみません。
I'm sorry.
宝鐘マリンですー！
Houshou Marine desu!
Yeah!
Okay, I'll practice this later.
Thank you!
Sorry, sorry, Sencho!
But yeah, that was the call from Myth.
Oh, they're honestly...
Without them, I really...
I mean, WE couldn't be here without each other.
So I'm really, really happy they're my genmates...
...and that we can finally show you guys our 3D showcases.
Thank you!
And you guys too.
Without you guys, you know, this would not have been possible.
So thank you very much! Thank you, thank you!
Well, you know, we've kind of warmed up now.
I think we can probably move on to something special I prepared for you guys.
So you guys are curious how I, you know, craft things from the void?
This time, to make it easier for you to understand,
I prepared a magical canvas where I can draw something...
...and I can use it as a catalyst.
That's right, catalyst, to summon whatever I draw!
Surprise!
Okay, let's go over there and bring the canvas over.
Tan-tan-tan-tan-tan...
Here is my canvas, yoisho!
Woah!
It's pretty heavy, but I've been practicing.
Alright, blank canvas. Isn't that so scary?
Number one things artists fear.
But let me just grab this magical brush here.
Hoick!
Hehe, isn't this brush really big?
I don't know how well I can draw with this, but...
...how about we test out the canvas for a bit, okay?
Actually haven't tested if it works, so...
I'll just draw something really quick.
Tan-tan-ta...
...and a smile...
...and the ring, and done!
Speed paint!
Who's that?
Who's that cutie on the canvas?
It's you!
Okay, okay, let me just put down my brush.
Yoisho!
I've prepared a special summoning room just for this occasion.
So I'll just bring you guys right on over.
Yoisho, yoisho, okay, let's go!
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho...
Alright, I'll put you guys on...
Yoisho!
Okay, are you guys ready?
There's a saying amongst artists:
If you draw what you want from the gacha, you shall get it.
So it's also called 'Kakkebaderu'.
So it's also called 'Kakkebaderu' (If you draw it, it will appear).
So that'll be our magical spell today.
Are you guys ready?
描けば出るー！
Kakkebaderu!
Woah!
That was...
Wah! T-Tako!
Tako... Tako... Tako... Tako...
Tako, you made it!
Oh, I have to be careful I don't step on any of you.
Tako, oh, you're so cute!
You know, that was my dream, you know?
To have you guys join me on this special day.
Tako!
Ah, you're so cute!
Hi!
Oi!
Face!
Say hi!
Ah, you guys are so cute!
Look at you!
Ah...
Wait.
Seems... seems a little empty.
Hmm, odd.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Yeah, Tako!
It succeeded!
Okay, so the canvas works.
The magical canvas works.
So, I'll just... whew!
Actually, I'm kidding.
I'll let you guys go.
There you go.
Hmm, since that worked...
You know, special occasion...
Maybe, just maybe, if we draw...
a Hololive member, do you think...
they'll be summoned as well?
Well, we can give it a try.
Okay, okay, okay.
Get my special brush.
Hoi!
All right, huh, who should I draw first?
Oh, I know, I know, I know!
I mean, there's no mistaking this member.
I'm sure you guys will guess right away.
Hmm...
Just to make sure, I'll write this.
Okay...
Done with my brush.
ん、どや！
Ta-da!
Who could it be, chat?
Who could it be? Can you guess?
Can you guess?
Well, we have a cup here.
And some wings.
And the word "BANO". Hmm...
Who could it be? Well...
Take you to the summoning room.
あたたたたたたたた！
Atatatatatatatata!
Hah, I should have built the summoning room a little closer...
to the...
to the studio, but...
Okay, here we go.
おっけばでる！
Okkebaderu!
Oh!
Is it working? Is it working?
やほー！
Yaho!
メル先輩！
Mel-senpai!
メルです！
It's Mel!
こんかぷー！
Konkapuu!
先輩！
Senpai!
嬉しい、嬉しい！
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
あのところで、これ何？これ。
By the way, what is this?
何ですかこれ？
What is this?
カップですね。
It's a cup.
これメル？これメルってこと？
Is this Mel? Does this mean it's Mel?
カップ。
Cup.
先輩じゃなくて、なんか先輩を召喚するために作った...
It's not senpai, it's something I made to summon senpai...
It's something I made to summon senpai.
メルの似顔絵かと思っちゃったよ。
I thought it was a portrait of Mel.
うん、うん、うん。 Don't worry about the letters.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Don't worry about the letters.
文字はちょっとあの大丈夫です。気にしないでください。
Don't worry about the letters. Please don't mind them.
BAN...
や、BANダメでしょう！
Hey, BAN is bad!
BANダメでしょう！
BAN is bad!
イナのせっかくの披露目なのに！
Even though it's Ina's special showcase!
BANはダメだよ！
BAN is bad!
メル先輩もちょっと...
Mel-senpai, just a...
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ！
No, no, no!
ダメ、ダメ！ はあ...
No, no! Ha...
Yeah, thanks for joining me today, Mel-senpai. 来てくださってありがとう。
Yeah, thanks for joining me today, Mel-senpai. Thank you for coming.
こちらこそありがとう。イナおめでとう！
Same here, thank you. Congratulations, Ina!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
You know, Mel-senpai was the first senpai I met...
when I visited Japan, so you know...
when I met her I was like, "Senpai please, please..."
"you know, I would love you to take part in the 3D ohirome stream."
And she said yes right away, I'm so happy!
せっかくだからなんか一緒に撮ろうよ、写真。
Since we're here, let's take a photo together.
あ、写真！ うん！
Ah, a photo! Yeah!
Screenshot time! Screenshot!
えーと、どうします？ こ... こんな感じ？
Uh, what should we do? Like... like this?
可愛いBAN！
Cute BAN!
BANダメですよ。
BAN is not good.
可愛いBANって何だ？
What do you mean by "cute BAN"?
でも可愛い。先輩可愛い！
But it's cute. Senpai is cute!
イナ、イナ可愛い！
Ina, Ina is cute!
嬉しい、先輩ちゅー！
I'm happy, senpai kiss!
先輩カップ！
Senpai cup!
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
Senpai so soft...
ああ、ソフト！
Ah, soft!
So soft!
柔らかいってこと？ うん、うん。
You mean soft? Yeah, yeah.
めっちゃ、めっちゃ可愛い。
Really, really cute.
イナ、イナも可愛い。
Ina, Ina is cute too.
Smile!
可愛い、イナ。
Cute, Ina.
Ah, thank you so much for joining me today.
Let's collab again! Let's play while I'm still here!
うん、うん、また遊ぼうね！
Yeah, yeah, let's play again!
Thank you!
めっちゃおめでとう！ Thank you!
Congratulations! Thank you!
それじゃ！
See ya!
メルは魔界に帰るかな。
I think Mel's going to head back to the demon world.
Yeah.
Bye-bye!
Inasuke, I love you!
I love you too!
またね、みんなも。
See you later, everyone too!
Bye-bye!
Thank you! Bye!
うわあ、メル先輩そうキュート。
Uwaa, Mel-senpai is so cute.
I can't handle it. My heart is melting.
Since we know that we can successfully summon some other members,
there is another member I do want to try and summon, you know?
Maybe you guys will know who she is right away.
Grab my brush. (Oof!)
All right, I'm ready. Speed paint time.
There's no way I can get this wrong, right?
So, so, so easy to draw.
Okay, done!
ドドン！
Ta-da!
Can you guys guess who it is?
Who could it be? Who could it be?
We'll see. All right, all right.
To the summoning room!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
かけばでる！
If I draw it, she will appear!
ホ？
Huh?
Yukihana Lamy? / 雪花ラミィ？
Lamy? Ina? Lamy?
Lamy? I'm Lamy?
Lamy? Oh, what? Lamy? Lamy? Oh, wait...
Hug me, hug me! Hug me!
Chu chu chu! My Ina, Ina, chu chu chu!
ダメ！ダメ、ダメ、ダメ！ラミィ、ラミィ、ノー！
No! No, no, no! Lamy, Lamy, no!
Okay, okay, I'll try again. I think I messed up. I think I messed up.
I messed up here. Okay, go back down. Okay.
Seems like I have to be a little more specific when I draw.
All right, let me try again. Let me try again.
Grab my brush. I'll actually be more specific when I draw this time.
Draw Lamy's cute face here, right here,
her flowers, smile, and done!
Okay!
How's the speed paint? I think I stepped up my speed painting.
All right, let me just put this down.
I gotta save Lamy from being stuck in another form.
All right, let's go! Lamy!
I'll save you Lamy!
Surely, surely it'll work. I drew her more detailed this time, so...
かけばでる！
If I draw it, she will appear!
わああ！いなーたん！
Waaa! Ina-tan!
Yukihana Lamy / 雪花ラミィ
Lamy! Lamy!
I love you Lamy! Whoo!
さっきの何？
What was that earlier?
え、さっきちょっと、あの、失敗した...
Uh, earlier I just, well, failed...
失敗したね、ちょっと、大福がちょっと、あの...
I failed, the Daifuku was a bit, well...
ごめん、ごめんなさい。
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Waaa, Lamy! Arigato! Thank you for coming!
Tako-dachi! Tako-dachi da yo! Hello!
Tako-dachi! Tako-dachi! Hello!
Oh, do you want to say your jiko-shoukai in English?
Oh, do you want to say your self-introduction in English?
I'm Hololive JP fifth generation,
Elf-face Lamy!
Wamy! Waaa! Thanks for coming!
Congratulations on your 3D debut!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとう！会いたかった！
Thank you! I wanted to see you!
私も！
Me too!
ちゃんとハグ。Hug me, hug me.
A proper hug. Hug me, hug me.
Mmu mmu mmu! Ina, Ina! チューもらった！
Mmu mmu mmu! Ina, Ina! I got a kiss!
嬉しかったよ！Thank you! 嬉しい。
I was so happy! Thank you! I'm happy.
Okay, next collab, next collab!
うん、うん、しようしよう。日本酒。
Yeah, yeah, let's do it. Japanese sake.
そうそう、ラミィのあの...
That's right, Lamy's...
飲む？飲みたい。
Drink? I want to drink.
飲みたい、飲みたい！
I want to drink, I want to drink!
日本酒！
Japanese sake!
Wow, 飲みたい。
Wow, I want to drink.
Come home. Oh, come home.
行く、行く、行く！
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go!
あ、じゃあバイバイね！
Oh, then bye-bye!
バイバイねー！またねー！
Bye-bye! See you!
Thank you, Lamy!
おおー、ラミィ...
Oh, Lamy...
Oh, she's so cute. I can't handle it.
She's adorable, adorable.
I can't wait. I really want to try her sake, you know?
But, you know, you can't really buy it anywhere 'cause it's so popular.
But since, you know, I-I can just shimmy over to Lamy's place... hehe.
Alright, alright, alright.
How about one more? One more, one more member summoning.
I realized I need to draw a lot more details, you know,
in order to summon them.
So maybe, you know, I can do a special summon this time.
I can do this. Okay.
Grab my brush.
よいしょ。
Yoisho.
Alright. Oh, okay.
Okay. I can already imagine her. Yeah.
Okay. Oh yeah, I can't forget the little accessories here.
Mmm. Like that, and that.
And... yup!
And done!
Alright. This one took a little longer, but...
hehe. Definitely detailed enough.
Who could it be? Hmm. Hmm. It's not YAGOO.
Hi YAGOO.
Let me put away my brush. よいしょ。
Let me put away my brush. Yoisho.
Who could it be?
There's a Watamelon, mmm, mmm,
and some horns, flower in her hair...
our fluffy fluffy Senpai.
Okay, let's go, let's go call her
in the special summoning room.
よいしょ。
Yoisho.
Alright, a little far, gotta run.
Okay, okay, a little closer this time.
Too much running.
よいしょ。 Alright. Yeah.
Yoisho. Alright. Yeah.
Okay, good.
Okay, we got this.
描けば出る！
If you draw them, they'll appear!
えっ？わっ？えっ？わっ？えっ？
Eh? Wha? Eh? Wha? Eh?
Tsunomaki Watame
たこ焼き食べてたんだけど！えっ？えっ？
I was eating takoyaki! Eh? Eh?
あ、えっ、わため先輩！
Ah, eh, Watame-senpai!
I ate takoyaki now.
お、たこ焼き食べたんですか。
Oh, you ate takoyaki?
食べた。
I ate them.
たこダチ、たこ焼き...
Takodachi, takoyaki...
たこダチたこ焼き... あれ？
Takodachi takoyaki... Huh?
誰だ？誰がわため先輩に食べられた？
Who? Who was eaten by Watame-senpai?
Who got eaten by Watame-senpai?
食べてないよ〜。
I didn't eat them~.
へへへ。先輩！
Hehehe. Senpai!
イエーイ！3D！うわ、3Dおめでとうございます！
Yay! 3D! Wow, congratulations on 3D!
おめでとうー！
Congratulations!
ああ、嬉しい。
Ah, I'm happy.
Wow, big fluffy. Oh, small face.
No, no, no, cute face.
Cute.
比べてみようよ。
Let's compare.
うん。アドーラブル（Adorable）。
Yeah. Adorable.
いや、もう、同じじゃないですか。
No, they're the same, aren't they?
同じだねー。
They're the same~.
同じですよ。えー、嬉しい。
They are the same. Oh, I'm happy.
やったー！ありがとうございます、わため先輩。
Hooray! Thank you, Watame-senpai.
ね、これ、わため先輩悪くない。
See, this, Watame-senpai isn't wrong.
わため先輩悪くないですよね。
Watame-senpai isn't wrong, right?
わためろんも、やっぱり、嬉しい。
Watamelon too, as expected, I'm happy.
そして、わため先輩も、あの、ライブの衣装で、
And Watame-senpai too, uh, in that live outfit,
なんか、なんかゴージャスみたい。えー！
she looks, like, kind of gorgeous. Wow!
なんで呼んでくれたの？
Why did you call me?
え、ちょっと、なんかスペシャルな日なので、
Well, it's kind of a special day,
あの、できればわため先輩と会いたくて。
so, um, I wanted to meet Watame-senpai if possible.
へへへ。
Hehehe.
嬉しい。大好き。
I'm happy. I love you.
Please show me Waki-pie. Waki-pie.
Waki-pie. Show me Waki-pie! Yeah!
わため先輩のWaki-pieも！
Watame-senpai's Waki-pie too!
Thank you! Thank you forever!
イエーイ！Thank you forever!
Yay! Thank you forever!
さすが、わため先輩はWaki-pieでした。
As expected, Watame-senpai was Waki-pie.
Thank you forever! 嬉しい、嬉しい。
Thank you forever! I'm happy, I'm happy.
今日誘ってありがとうございます。
Thank you for inviting me today.
こちらこそ。遊びましょう。
Same here. Let's play.
また今度たこ焼き食べようね。
Let's eat takoyaki again next time.
たこパしましょう。楽しみ。
Let's have a takoyaki party. Looking forward to it.
待ってるよー。またねー！
I'll be waiting! See you!
バイバイ、わため先輩！
Bye-bye, Watame-senpai!
おおー。わため先輩、
Oh. Watame-senpai,
she's so fluffy and cute.
I can't handle it. Ah...
why are they so cute?
My heart... haaa...
My heart's beating not from the running but from how cute they are honestly.
I can't believe I finally got to meet them...
...and at such a special day too!
But yeah, you know, um... I think the summoning canvas, special magical canvas worked really well.
But, you know, what if we also drew something different...
...like maybe a new stage? New place?
Do you think it'll work?
Well, we'll never know until we try, so...
...let's give it a try, shall we?
All right, heave-ho...
...get my brush.
This might take a little longer 'cause um, I'm not very good at drawing backgrounds yet.
All right, oh... I hope the brush was a little smaller but...
...I think I got this. Yeah.
Okay, as detailed as possible...
...and done! Ta-da!
Um... can you guys guess? Guess the stage?
It's pretty good. I mean, it's the best I can do with this brush.
That's right, that's right. Okay, let me just put down this brush.
Ha... okay. Well, we'll see where this takes us. I don't know if it's gonna work but...
...we'll see. All right, shall we?
Walking over to the summoning room... [humming]
I... I shouldn't have...
Okay... whew. Running up the stairs is such a work.
Okay...
One last time.
Kakikebadiru!
TIPS
Takodachis are crafted from the void by Ina.
They have the ability to shape-shift into anything,
including daily utensils, food, and animals including humans.
Research suggests that they taste like switch cartridges when licked.
LOADING..
if ～ひとり思う～
Lyrics・Composition: 株式会社インテリジェントシステムズ
if ~Hitori Omou~
Lyrics・Composition: Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.
揺らり 揺るれり 泡沫
想い 巡る秤
Gently swaying, floating like bubbles
A scale where memories revolve
伝う...
Flowing...
伝え見なす地
The ground you walk upon,
その背が拓く明日は
tomorrow revealed by your path.
光へと手を伸ばす
Stretch out your hand towards the light.
汚れなき銀の剣
A pure silver sword.
まどろみ想いを
Severing through your thoughts
断ち切りて
of slumber.
歌う静謐
Singing in the tranquility,
聖者
a saint.
柔く光散りて
The soft light scatters,
闇去りゆく暁
dawn as the darkness fades.
独り想う
Lost in thoughts all alone.
ルラリラ ルレリ
Luralia, Lureli.
うたかた想い巡る計り
Transient thoughts spinning in balance.
伝え見なす地
The ground you walk upon,
その背が拓く明日は
tomorrow revealed by your path.
闇へと進みゆく
Heading into the darkness.
虚ろな雲の御座
The empty throne of clouds.
己をすべて欺いて
Deceiving everything about yourself.
責める終わり
The blaming end.
虚無よ
O emptiness.
鈍く崩れ落ちて
Crumbling down dully,
光去りゆく黄昏
dusk as the light fades.
独り想う
Lost in thoughts all alone.
選びしは正しき道
The path chosen was the right one.
すべてが...
Everything is...
嘆きも笑顔も
The grief and the smiles,
悔いも夢もきっと
the regrets and the dreams, surely.
昏す目に
With darkened eyes,
迷い疲れて
tired of wandering,
たゆたい
swaying,
未だその身に刻む詩を
the verse still carved upon that body.
きっと
Surely.
あざなえ
Intertwine.
沈みゆく
Sinking down.
彷徨いたゆたう
Wandering and swaying.
面影求め探してた
Seeking and searching for a vestige.
移りゆく
Shifting,
暁から
from the dawn.
震え果てて
Trembling until the end.
水面に映る
Reflected on the water's surface.
惑いを誰が知るや
Who can know the confusion?
ルラリラ ルレリ
Luralia, Lureli.
うたかた想い巡る計り
Transient thoughts spinning in balance.
伝え見なす地
The ground you walk upon,
その背が拓く明日は
tomorrow revealed by your path.
Lura lali, lura li...
Haa, haa, ha...
I guess we succeeded in
summoning the new stage! Yay!
How was the song?
Isn't this stage so so pretty?
Haaa...
Yeah, oh my goodness.
I was very nervous, but pulled it off. I did it, yay!
Well, I have another song for you here,
but we're going to have to change things a little bit.
So the next song... hold on, let's do this.
Huuu... yiii... hyu!
It worked! Okay.
Um, this place might be really familiar for you guys.
I hope you like the next song.
Yeah. Okay.
教えて 教えてよ その仕組みを
Tell me, tell me the way it works.
僕の中に誰かいるの？
Is there someone else inside of me?
壊れた 壊れたよ この世界で
Broken, it's broken, within this world.
君が笑う 何も見えずに
You laugh, without seeing anything.
unravel
Lyrics: Composition: TK
壊れた僕なんてさ 息を止めて
A broken person like me, holding my breath.
ほどけない もうほどけないよ
It's unravelling, I can't unravel it anymore,
真実さえ freeze
even the truth is frozen.
壊せる 壊せない
Can break, can't break.
狂える 狂えない
Can go mad, can't go mad.
あなたを見つけて
I found you.
揺れて歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は
In this shaking, distorted world, I'm gradually
透き通って見えなくなって
becoming transparent and invisible.
見つけないで 僕のことを
Don't find me.
見つめないで
Don't look at me.
誰かが描いた世界の中で
In a world drawn by someone else,
あなたを傷つけたくはないよ
I don't want to hurt you.
覚えていて
Remember
僕のことを
me.
無限に広がる孤独が絡まる
Infinitely spreading loneliness entangles me.
無邪気に笑った記憶が刺さって
Memories of innocently laughing pierce me.
動けない 動けない 動けない
Can't move, can't move, can't move,
動けない 動けない 動けないよ
can't move, can't move, I can't move!
変わってしまった 変えられなかった
It's changed, it couldn't be changed.
2つが絡まる 2人が滅びる
Two things entwine, two people perish.
壊せる 壊せない
Can break, can't break.
狂える 狂えない
Can go mad, can't go mad.
あなたを汚せないよ
I won't let you be tainted.
揺れて歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は
In this shaking, distorted world, I'm gradually
透き通って見えなくなって
becoming transparent and invisible.
見つけないで 僕のことを
Don't find me.
見つめないで
Don't look at me.
誰かが仕組んだ孤独な罠に
In a lonely trap set by someone,
未来がほどけてしまう前に
before the future unthreads itself,
思い出して
Remember
僕のことを
me,
鮮やかなまま
vivid as it is.
忘れないで 忘れないで
Don't forget, don't forget,
don't forget, don't forget.
変わってしまったことに paralyze
Paralyzed by what has changed.
変えられないことだらけの paradise
A paradise full of things that can't be changed.
覚えていて 僕のことを
Remember me.
教えて 教えて
Tell me, tell me.
僕の中に誰かいるの？
Is there someone else inside of me?
TIPS
Dr. Oopsie does not, in fact, fix any mistakes in your life.
However, it could definitely create new ones, so please drink responsibly.
- Tentacult Health Department
舞いゆくは　星のかけら
Falling are fragments of stars
天体に　手を伸ばして
I reach my hand out to the celestial bodies
行き交う願い　感じているね
I can feel the passing wishes, can't I?
すべては今　モノクロームの　なか
Everything is now within the monochrome
モノクローム 〜 version de l'apprivoiser
Lyrics: こだまさおり Composition: 神前 暁 Arrangement: 高田龍一
Monochrome 〜 version de l'apprivoiser
Lyrics: Saori Kodama Composition: Satoru Kosaki Arrangement: Ryuichi Takada
白く　こぼれだす吐息
A white breath spilling out
消えかけた　言葉の形
The shape of words that were about to fade
きゅっと　ぬくもりの分だけ
Just by the amount of warmth tightly held
空はほんのり　明るくなった
The sky became slightly brighter
悲しみに　濡れた翼
Wings soaked in sadness
重なりあう　純白へ
Towards the overlapping pure white
渡しあった　未来への　やさしい勇気
The gentle courage for the future we passed to each other
誰も知らない　世界の
Of a world that no one knows
夜明けを待っている鼓動
A heartbeat waiting for the dawn
痛みをつれて　旅だつ私
Carrying the pain, I set out on a journey
はじまる明日へ
Towards the tomorrow that begins
舞いゆくは　星のかけら
Falling are fragments of stars
天体に　手を伸ばして
I reach my hand out to the celestial bodies
行き交う願い　信じているよ
I believe in the passing wishes
すべては今　モノクロームの　なか
Everything is now within the monochrome
凍えた　記憶を溶かす
Melting the frozen memories
手に入れた　愛とともに
Together with the love I've obtained
振りむかずに　風あおぐ空の彼方
Beyond the sky where I look up at the wind without looking back
それぞれが　たどる軌道
The orbits that each of us follows
たとえもう　逢えなくても
Even if we can't meet again
光が見せる　銀河のどこかで　つながっているね
We are connected somewhere in the galaxy that the light shows
散る星は　砂のように
The falling stars are like sand
まなこを　あまく撫でる
Gently stroking my eyes
静かに眠る 夢の残渣
The residue of dreams sleeping quietly
全てはまだ モノクロームのどこか
Everything is still somewhere in monochrome
Haa...
Yay! I did it!
What'd you guys think? I prepared three songs for you guys!
Yee! Thank you, thank you!
Haa... It's finally almost over, huh?
We waited over... twoish years.
We planned it out... but then you know, we had to wait so long, but...
you know, I worked so so so hard to make this happen, and...
to actually dance it and sing it, like, like live, live!
Haa... It was all worth it, it was all worth it.
What'd you guys think? Did you guys like it? Do you guys like the stage?
Oh, isn't this so cool? We're in space! We're in space!
Yeah, this is a special stage for a special occasion, so. Hope you guys like it.
Thank you, thank you everyone! Thanks for coming to watch today.
Haa... Yeah, oh, I can't believe...
you know, I'm still processing it in my head how... it's finally today.
Oh, I'm gonna cry.
Don't, don't cry Ina, don't cry. No, no leaking ceilings, it's okay.
Phew.
But yeah, you know, without everyone, you know, you guys, Myth...
all the staff, all the studio staff, thank you so so much for...
making this happen.
Don't cry. Thank you for making this happen.
But yeah, thank you, thank you so so so much! Yee!
But you know, um... (clears throat) No, no leaking ceilings. We got, we got business here.
For a special occasion, you know...
um, I believe it's time to maybe announce some, you know, goods and stuff, maybe maybe maybe!
You guys ready? Hmm? Ready? Hmm? Ready?
Oh, Tako!
Tako, what are you doing here, Tako?
Oh, you're not supposed... oh, you're not supposed to come up here on the stage, Tako.
Yeah, oh, you were worried? Oh, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay. Don't cry, Tako. Be happy.
Wait, what? You want to become the merch?
Are you sure about that?
Are you sure? You sure?
Okay, I mean, if you're fine with it. Moto Tako! Yoisho!
Well, with this noble Tako sacrifice, we shall create new merch for this special occasion.
Are you guys ready? Alright, Tako, are you ready?
Piece of cake, you know. Okay. Okay. Se-no!
Piece of cake, you know. Okay. Okay. One, two!
Hoi!
Oh, I think I... yeah, I think I did it. Okay.
Alright! You guys ready? Are you ready?
And tada!
That's right!
Tako! You're squished! What happened?
Tako, are you okay? Tako's okay. Stuck on my hand.
Wait, a bit... get off, get off. Maybe not. Okay.
This Tako's stuck on my hand.
But! The goods for this special occasion will be...
Don!
Oh! A Takodachi Ramen Stopper!
Woo! Okay, Tako, you can go back now.
Wee... Blah!
Haa! That's right!
For all you cup noodle enjoyers,
you can now have a personal Takodachi to help you hold the lid down in place.
Or it can be a cute little figure too. That's also possible!
Isn't this so cute?
Yeah, I actually, you know, played around with it and you can kind of like push it,
push the Tako down and it like sticks onto your hand. It's very nice.
But yeah, this will go on sale, not today, not today, remember that.
This will go on sale starting... March 5th.
モノクローム 〜 version de l'apprivoiser
Monochrome ~ version de l'apprivoiser
Takodachi Ramen Stopper "Let's TAKO a break"
And that's not all. It's HoloMyth 3D collab.
So after that, after everyone's is over,
it's gonna be on sale, so please look forward to it.
I hope you guys like it. Oh, it's so cute!
But yeah, one more thing, one more thing, one more thing.
It is actually tonight.
Tonight!
Around what, five hours or so from now,
it's gonna be my real holographic debut! Woo!
I'm gonna be on hologram! Eeee!
Yeah, apparently there's gonna be a lot of tentacles,
so I hope you guys look forward to it. Yes.
Ah, it's been... it's been an amazing time, everyone.
Thank you so much again.
And make sure you check out everyone in Myth's 3D showcases too.
Next up is Kiara. Kiara, that's you. That's you. Yeah.
But yes, and then it's gonna be Calli, and then Gura,
and then Ame, and then the collab. That's right.
It's gonna be such a fun month! Eeee!
Anyways, thank you so much again everyone
for being patient and waiting.
It's finally here.
And I'll continue to do my best. Yes.
Thank you! Bye bye!
This is it! Bye bye!
A few more minutes until the 3D showcase is over.
So what happens when the 3D showcase is over?
You don't know?
That's when 3D showcase begins.