(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Aaah, the good old days
when I was performing with my friends at the jazz club.
It was so much fun!
Everyone was having their BEST time dancing, singing,
and just having the best time of their lives.
Haaa... good memories.
Now I kinda wanna watch old tapes...
Hmm...
not this one.
Not this...
Okay, this one!
Yeah yeah yeah!
This one was a blast!
I had so much fun on this one!
Hmm-mm-mm...
You Make Me
作詞：Monday 満ちる / 作曲：Monday 満ちる
Lyrics: Monday Michiru / Composition: Monday Michiru
(Vocalizing)
You make me wanna get up in the morning
You make me wanna stay up all night long
You make me wanna get up to be dancing
You make me wanna reach up to the sky
I feel so high
When I first met you
I already knew
Something special has begun
...than I've ever knew before.
...than I've ever known before.
Was it in your eyes, feelings you can't disguise?
Something telling me that destiny knocked on my front door.
It's better to believe than to let by the happiness I feel inside.
Don't let go, I know you feel the same, let passion grow...
...and it gets better day by day.
You make me wanna get up in the morning.
You make me wanna stay up all night long.
You make me wanna get up to be dancing.
You make me wanna reach up to the sky, I feel so high.
Universal love from heaven above.
Fundamentally the truth I've been searching for.
Secret rendezvous in my dreams, me and you.
Brand new feelings warm my soul like a blaze more and more.
Like a shield protecting me from night.
Your love makes me forget those times I was alone.
There's nothing that can touch me, oh-oh...
...the beauty of this love to the world.
You make me wanna get up in the morning.
You make me wanna stay up all night long.
You make me wanna get up to be dancing.
You make me wanna reach up to the sky.
You make me wanna get up in the morning. Let's go!
You make me wanna stay up all night long.
You make me wanna get up to be dancing. Yeah!
You make me wanna reach up to the sky, I feel so high.
Can you feel this energy? Whoa-oh.
Synchronizing you and me. Whoa-oh.
Power of positivity. Whoa-oh.
Your electricity. Whoa-oh.
It's better to believe than to let by the happiness I feel inside.
Don't let go, I know you feel the same, let passion grow...
...and it gets better day by day.
You make me wanna get up in the morning.
You make me wanna stay up all night long.
You make me wanna get up to be dancing.
You make me wanna reach up to the sky, I feel so high.
You make me wanna get up in the morning.
You make me wanna stay up all night long.
You make me wanna get up to be dancing.
You make me wanna reach up to the sky, I feel so high.
Dance break, let's go!
jazzeta
Yay! Hello everyone!
Welcome to Jazzeta! Welcome to my birthday party!
Sorry, I'm out of breath.
Welcome to Jazzeta. If you guys are watching...
...Jazzeta is something I've always been dreaming of.
I've always wanted to perform in such a big stage like this.
I've always wanted to perform on such a big stage like this.
How did you like it? The moves had a bit of hip-hop dance moves in it.
Was it cool? Was it cool? Was it cool? Was it cool?
Um, yeah. So...
...last time I was also in a jazz club as well, but this is special.
Because tonight's performance... I would say tonight, today...
...today's performance is all jazz.
So yeah, I hope you like that one. It's very groovy.
Ooh, I hope you guys like this!
So yeah...
Um, don't go anywhere because there will be the next performance.
Right, Bozo?
Bozo... Bozo can't answer so... (laughs)
Jadi masih ada lanjut performance berikutnya.
So there's still the next performance coming up.
次の曲はね...
As for the next song...
Do you guys know? Do you guys know?
Can you guess? Can you have a little bit of a guess?
I'll guess... um, okay okay.
I'll give you guys some clue.
Hmm... Hmm...
Huuh, we have a special guest so...
Who can it be? 誰だろう？
Who can it be? I wonder who it is?
Can you guess who?
JAZZ SHOW
SPECIAL PERFORMANCE BY NINOMAE INA'NIS
花が寝る夜 波に映った星
The night when flowers sleep, the stars reflected on the waves
唸れる月が足をくすぐる
The groaning moon tickles my feet
流れる光に沿って行ってみたら
When I try to follow the flowing light
耳に囁いた 君に届かない？
Does what I whispered in your ear not reach you?
今手を繋いでも
Even if we hold hands now
精一杯抱きしめても
Even if I hug you as hard as I can
空は秋に満ちるんだ
The sky is filled with autumn
指先でゆらゆらと
Swaying at my fingertips
その動きが止まった時計の針に飛び込んだ
That movement jumped into the hands of the clock that stopped
固まった願いさえ
Even the frozen wishes
離れたい今は その笑顔
I want to get away from that smile right now
知ってるよ
I know
光歌う夜 目に映った空
The night when light sings, the sky reflected in my eyes
爽やかな香りがくすぐる
A refreshing scent tickles me
足跡合わせて歩いてみたら
When I try to walk matching our footprints
私を見ていた 君に届かない？
Does it not reach you, who was looking at me?
ずっと手を繋いでも
Even if we hold hands forever
君について行ってみても 空は雨に染めるんだ
Even if I try to follow you, the sky turns to rain
君を呼び出した声
The voice that called out to you
の形が 渇いた色濡らして
Its shape wets the parched colors
強く叫んだ声が
The voice that screamed out loudly
散らばった今は その言葉を
Has scattered now, those words
知ってるよ
I know
君は分かってるかな 教えてくれた
I wonder if you understand? You told me
戻らない その幸せは
That happiness which won't return
I'm so... I'm so excited to sing this with you.
Thank you so much, Ina, for singing with me.
"Violet" has been one of my favorite songs, so I'm really happy...
...that I got to sing this, especially with you and in jazzy version as well!
I love Jazz, and I love you.
Thank you, Ina.
No, thank you for inviting me to sing with you, especially "Violet" too!
Inoseta- also I really love your singing voice, so it made me really happy...
...that you wanted to sing "Violet" with me.
Thank you again, love you too Zeta!
あながめる夜　波に映った星
A staring night, stars reflected in the waves
三日月が　消えてゆく
The crescent moon is fading away
指先で夜を揺らした
I swayed the night with my fingertips
その動きが　止まった時計の針に踏み込んだ
That movement stepped onto the hands of a stopped clock
蜘蛛が描いた列車　そよ風
The train drawn by the clouds, a gentle breeze
その笑顔を　知ってるよ
I know that smile
Da ba da da...
OH! What's this tape? OH! Ini kaset apa, ya? ん？このテープ、なんだろう？
OH! What's this tape? OH! What is this tape? Hmm? What is this tape?
I don't think I've ever seen it before. Kayaknya aku belum pernah lihat ini sebelumnya. 初めて見るな。
I don't think I've ever seen it before. It seems I haven't seen this before. I'm seeing it for the first time.
Wait, let me play it! Bentar, coba aku putar! ちょっと再生してみようかな...
Wait, let me play it! Wait, let me try playing it! I think I'll try playing it...
Full Story
作詞：進藤まゆり
作曲：進藤まゆり
Full Story
Lyrics: Mayuri Shindo
Composition: Mayuri Shindo
今宵　お邪魔をいたします
I will pay you a visit tonight
一つ　秘密を増やしましょう
Let's increase our secrets by one
あなたが悪い　心は火照り
It's your fault, my heart is flushed
航海先に佇まないよ　今更
I won't linger at the destination of our voyage, not now
唇　優しく重ねましょう
Let's gently press our lips together
指を　素肌に這わせましょう
Let's trace our fingers along bare skin
深まる吐息　身体を乗っ取り
Deepening sighs taking over the body
枯れない薔薇のような　私をあげる
I'll give you myself, like a rose that never withers
ああ
Ah...
Heeey! 地獄へ落ちてゆけ　そこで骨まで髄まで
Heeey! Fall down to hell, and there, until the very marrow of your bones...
愛せぬなら　一途なふりをして
If you can't love, at least pretend to be devoted
Heeey! 地獄を見るほどの　愛ならば惨めな癖に
Heeey! If it's a love enough to see hell, despite being miserable...
Towa-sama, let's go!
…虜に飢えてた時
...When I was starving for a captive,
夜の帳を狙いましょう
Let's aim for the curtain of night.
あいつはちょろい
That guy is easy,
この手に弱い
vulnerable to this hand.
欲の皮が張るのに見苦しすぎる
Even though he's blinded by greed, it's too unsightly.
Hey Hey Hey この世は蜃気楼
Hey Hey Hey, this world is a mirage.
噂も偏見も涙も幻でしょう
Rumors, prejudices, and tears are all probably illusions.
知らぬが仏たち
Ignorance is bliss.
溶けた手
Melted hands,
詐欺を働く 音沙汰もない
working a scam, not a word heard.
Towa-sama!
Yes!
Are you okay?
I'm okay, I'm okay!
Okay! Let's sing this part together!
Okay!
Hey Hey Hey この世は蜃気楼
Hey Hey Hey, this world is a mirage.
噂も偏見も涙も幻でしょう
Rumors, prejudices, and tears are all probably illusions.
Hey Hey Hey 地獄へ落ちてゆけ
Hey Hey Hey, fall into hell.
そこで骨の髄まで愛してるなら
If you love to the marrow of your bones down there,
いちずな振りをして
pretend to be single-minded.
Hey Hey Hey 地獄は見るほどないなど
Hey Hey Hey, there's no hell worth seeing,
満ち足りないくせに
even though you're never satisfied.
Thank you!
Bye bye!
Hi!
How was the performance too?
It was fall, right?
Fall, fall, fall-y.
It was strictly good.
It was really cool.
I tried my best to use my deep voice for that one.
Hope you guys liked it.
Towa-sama was so freaking cool.
I had so much fun singing with her.
Oh wow. Actually...
...not don't forget.
Actually, we still have a little bit of something.
Last time we had Zetamin...
...a bottle.
But today, we have many many cool stuff.
We have more cool stuff.
Even cooler than Zetamin.
What could it be?
Apa ya kira-kira?
I wonder what it is?
Masih ada lagi nih...
There's still more...
な！
Na!
Vestia Zeta Birthday Celebration 2024
Tada!
Wah!
Tentu saja, bukan birthday party kalau tidak iklan dulu, iya gak?
Of course, it wouldn't be a birthday party without an ad first, right?
Kita iklan dulu, guys.
Let's have an ad first, guys.
This is my merchandise! Yay!
Goods! Yay!
Isn't this really beautiful?
I really love the dress.
Do I look nice?
大人っぽいね。
It looks mature, doesn't it?
This is like, just like imagine like a spy...
...going inside a ballroom...
...having a glass of strawberry juice.
The concept is like jazz but also like spy...
...kind of like mixed together.
So, yeah!
アルテラママ、ありがとう！
Arutera-mama, thank you!
Thank you so much for making such a beautiful illustration.
So, of course, if you see here...
...it's very rare that my theme is like red...
...because you know if you see in the back...
...I mean the stage, everything, everything is super red.
So I hope you guys like this one.
And there's still more.
There's still more.
Okay, let's see the items one by one.
First one, はい！
First one, hai!
Fancy a dance with me-? Diorama Acrylic Stand
Oh!
A diorama acrylic stand.
アクリルスタンドか...
An acrylic stand, huh...
これいいな。
This is good.
Ini bisa ditaruh di meja.
This can be placed on a table.
Bisa ditaruh di mana aja.
It can be placed anywhere.
Di ranjang, di meja makan...
On the bed, on the dining table...
...meja tidur... gak ada meja tidur.
...bedside table... there's no bedside table.
Di mana aja.
Anywhere.
Lu bisa, guys. Gila keren banget acrylic stand.
You can get it, guys. This acrylic stand is crazy cool.
Beautiful. You can put this anywhere.
Um, you can have, you can have elegant, elegant Zeta accompany you in your room.
Or you can bring this around.
I usually bring my acrylic stand inside like a pouch.
So, if you find like an accessory for the pouch, it would be nice.
And it's something like, um, it says "Fancy a dance with me?" question mark.
Ooh, fancy, fancy, super fancy!
はい、次！ Next!
Okay, next! Next!
Bwah! Woah! It's a hoodie!
So this is something you guys... I feel like you guys wanted it for a long time.
Coz you guys were always like "Zeta, can you make us something to wear?"
And now we have a uniform!
Ya nggak sih? Masak Zecretary unit sama Zegethering nggak punya seragam?
Right? How can Zecretary unit and Zegethering not have a uniform?
Tapi ini bukan seragam ya. Ini kayak cozy gitu lho.
But this isn't a uniform. This is like cozy, you know.
Enak kalau mau di rumah santai.
It's nice if you want to relax at home.
Kalau mau ke luar juga bisa.
If you want to go out, you can too.
Soalnya nggak terlalu formal tapi nggak terlalu casual banget ya, in between.
Because it's not too formal but not too casual, in between.
Kalian bisa pakai. Ini hoodienya lumayan oversized ya buat aku.
You can wear it. This hoodie is quite oversized for me.
Tapi ini comfy banget. This is so good, ya.
But this is so comfy. This is so good.
Kakak-kakak silakan dibeli. Kakak-kakak ya.
Everyone, please buy it. Everyone, okay?
Ini aduh, bahannya halus ya. Udah gitu apa lagi nih?
This, oh, the material is soft. And then what else?
Um, ada gambar ilustrasinya di belakang. Uh, cantik sekali!
Um, there's an illustration on the back. Uh, it's so beautiful!
Uh, langsung, langsung, langsung checkout!
Uh, immediately, immediately, immediately checkout!
This is beautiful. Look at the illust.
This is beautiful. Look at the illustration.
可愛いでしょう？
Isn't it cute?
So the main point of this illustration is Zeta with like Bazo suit actually.
If you look at it, yeah. And it's gray, so we know it's Zeta.
Because it's gray. Anyways, yeah.
And then, um, it has a little bit of tag in it, and the tag says "Vestia Zeta".
So yeah, this is what it looks like.
Yeah, you can wear this in conventions, or meet and greet.
Or wherever you want to go, honestly. It's not tacky at all.
So wear it wherever. Okay, next!
Oh! It's a pocket size BaZeta plushie keychain!
So cute!
Wait, that's actually so cute. That's so cute!
That's like the drawing in, um, in the back of the hoodie, but except it's now in a plushie!
So we have Bazo plushie, we have the other Zeta plushie, the Friends one.
And now we have the pocket size.
これめっちゃ可愛い！
This is so cute!
It's like you can bring this to traveling...
旅行とか...
Like on a trip...
来たいならこれね、連れてきて。
If you're coming, please bring this with you.
You can bring this, or you can hang it on your bag, or you can have multiple of it and make an itabag.
Or, I don't know, this is a keychain.
So you can hang this anywhere.
Ini bisa digantung di mana aja.
This can be hung anywhere.
Mau jadi jimat keberuntungan...
Whether as a lucky charm...
Mau kalian gantung di celana, di tas, di tembok, di mana aja, di rambut, terserah ya.
Whether you hang it on your pants, your bag, your wall, anywhere, on your hair, it's up to you.
Ini keren banget. Ini lucu dan ini halus pokoknya.
This is so cool. This is cute and it's soft, basically.
Kelihatan sih dari fotonya.
You can tell from the photo.
This is really cute.
Dan ini pocket size, jadi tuh ukurannya lumayan ya, guys.
And this is pocket size, so the size is quite reasonable, guys.
Kalian bisa baca sendiri ukurannya.
You can read the size yourself.
Ukurannya lucu, jadi kalian tuh bisa bawa ini ke mana aja pokoknya.
The size is cute, so you can basically bring this anywhere.
Masuk, langsung masuk tas gitu, udah. Oke, next!
It fits, just goes right into the bag. Okay, next!
And this is the last item, it's Zecretary's Pin Me Down Pin Badge! Ooh!
So this is a badge as a Zecretary. So I wanted something... I wanted like a tie at first.
But then I decided on a badge because badge is more wearable.
So this badge you can put it, you can wear it um on your shirt.
You can wear it on your bags.
Because, you know, people wear pins on their bags. You can pin this on your shoe, your socks, wherever.
This is really nice. Um, also if you have like... the original idea is for it if you have a tie,
You can like pin the badge on the tie.
Jadi kalau kalian punya dasi, kalian bisa pin di dasi gitu misalnya.
So if you have a tie, you can pin it on the tie, for example.
Atau kalian bisa pin di mana aja.
Or you can pin it anywhere.
Aku juga sebenarnya punya nih pin-pin gitu nih nih.
I actually have these pins too, look.
Aku punya... I have a pin as well.
I have... I have a pin as well.
If you guys can see. I have the deer pin.
You can pin it in your um belt bag if you have that.
I mean I have thigh highs but...
Yeah, you can pin it anywhere. You can pin it in your shoes if you want and all that.
Or in your hairband? Do you have a hairband?
Ini pin kalian jadi ini serbaguna, oke.
This is your pin, so it's versatile, okay.
But of course, it doesn't end there, because I also...
...prepared three voice packs...
...for my birthday as well. Yay!
Voice Pack
Situational Voice Pack
“The Runaway Princess Who Found Herself in a Jazz Club?”
(Japanese)
Situational Voice Pack
“Behind the Scenes with a Singer”
(Indonesian)
Situational Voice Pack
“A Spy Hired to Track Down a Prince at a Ballroom, When a Mysterious Man Approaches Her”
(English)
So I prepared the stories for the three birthdays as well.
I wanted different stories for each language.
Sama yang bilang skip iklan, kalian nggak bisa skip.
To those of you saying to skip the ad, you can't skip it.
Karena kita lanjut terus!
Because we're keeping it going!
First one, situational voice in Japanese.
So これ日本語のボイスなんだけど...
So this is a Japanese voice pack, but...
The title is “The Runaway Princess
Who Found Herself in a Jazz Club?”
Yay! If you guys are unsure, there is a preview button to sneak peek the content.
So it's about a princess from a certain kingdom.
She sneaks out of the castle
to perform as a jazz singer at the club.
So this is really interesting. Next!
So, the second one is a different story in English.
It's called “A Spy Hired to Track Down
a Prince at a Ballroom,
When a Mysterious Man Approaches Her.”
Ooh, who could that be?
So this is about Zeta who infiltrates a ballroom as a spy on a mission...
...searching for the prince she is targeting. Yay!
Next!
Lastly, we have something a little bit familiar, maybe you're curious.
A different story in Bahasa Indonesia.
It's called “Behind the Scenes with a Singer.”
Wuih, behind the scene dengan seorang penyanyi, cie.
Whoa, “Behind the Scenes with a Singer,” ooh.
Jadi storinya ini tuh...
So this story is...
...ceritanya itu lagi backstage, terus...
...the story is about being backstage, and then...
...ngedenger Zeta ngomong.
...hearing Zeta talk.
This is too, if you guys want to hear me yap behind the scenes, basically.
And the voice pack is sold separately and not included in the full merch set.
Before, before I end this commercial break...
...I have one more secret to share with you guys.
There's a sneak peek of a special bonus you will get from buying the good set. Pam!
Wait, これね...
Wait, this...
Complete Set Purchase Bonus
Illustration: おめてる
Birthday Merch Complete Set Limited Edition
• Cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten autograph
Birthday Merch Complete Set
• Cheki-style bromide card with a duplicated foil-stamped autograph
Script data of voice recordings for both sets (Japanese, Indonesian, English)
Complete Set Purchase Bonus
Illustration: Ometeru
Birthday Merch Complete Set Limited Edition
• Cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten autograph
Birthday Merch Complete Set
• Cheki-style bromide card with a duplicated foil-stamped autograph
Script data of voice recordings for both sets (Japanese, Indonesian, English)
This is a cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten autograph.
So, I'm handwriting the autograph myself.
Remember, there is a limited quantity for the cards that are personally signed, so don't miss out.
You'll get my beautiful autograph.
Or my not beautiful autograph, whatever.
You'll get a rare one if I accidentally misspelled my name or something.
Please check the description for the links and details.
You can purchase the merchandise on Hololive Production site...
Birthday Merch Complete Set
• Fancy a dance with me? Diorama Acrylic Stand
• Comfy Bazzeta Hoodie
• Pocket size BazZeta Plushie Keychain
• Zeetarian’s I’m Me Down Pin Badge
• 3 Voice Packs
• Bonus items: Cheki-style bromide card, script data
You can purchase the merchandise on Hololive Production site...
...at 9 PM WIB or 11 PM Japan time...
...or after the streaming ends.
Or you can just click the link on the pinned chat. Yay!
Yeah, this will be PO...
...purchase order.
So for more details you should check the homepage.
Thank you! That's all. Yay!
Silakan skip ad.
Please skip the ad.
Have you guys heard of this story?
Once upon a time, there was a girl.
She got lost and she met new friends along the way.
And went on adventures with them. And... the rest is history.
お話しをしよう
Let's tell a story,
Alice in Musicland
作詞・作曲：OSTER project
Lyrics/Composition: OSTER project
昔話より
even better than old tales,
もっともっと素敵な
a much, much more wonderful
お伽話
fairy tale.
扉を開けると
When I open the door,
真っ白なうさぎ
there's a pure white rabbit.
お慌てで駆けてく
Hurrying along,
あとを追うの
I'll follow behind.
チクタク チクタク 急いで行かなきゃ間に合わない
Tick-tock, tick-tock, I have to hurry or I won't make it!
あぁ チクタク チクタク ぎくしゃくするのはもう嫌だ
Ah, tick-tock, tick-tock, I hate being so flustered.
そら チクタク チクタク 時間はどんどん減ってゆく
Look, tick-tock, tick-tock, the time keeps ticking away.
もう とにかく僕には時間がない
Goodness, anyway, I just don't have any time!
ねぇ そんなに慌てて一体全体どうしたの？
Hey, what in the world happened for you to be in such a hurry?
どこかの誰かといつかどこかで待ち合わせ？
Are you meeting someone somewhere at some time?
そう 彼女はチクタクとっても時間にシビアだよ
Yes, she is tick-tock, very strict about time.
そんなに？
That much?
そうさ！
Exactly!
だって彼女は女王様
Because she is the Queen.
覚々鹿々云々ともう
This and that and so forth, and...
どうにも時間がないから
...there's just no time left.
話があるならまたの機会にしておくれ
If you have something to say, make it another time.
それならひとつだけ教えて
In that case, just tell me one thing.
なぜそんな時でも陽気な歌を歌うの?
Why do you sing such a cheerful song at a time like that?
それはミュージックランド
That is Music Land!
ミュージックランド!
Music Land!
そうさミュージックランド
That's right, Music Land!
ワンダーランド!
Wonderland!
ここがミュージックランドだからさ
This is Music Land, that's why!
じゃ、お先に失礼
Well then, excuse me.
またお暇にバイバイさようなら
Until next time, bye-bye, goodbye.
待って!
Wait!
ああ、なんて不思議な世界なのでしょう
Oh, what a mysterious world this is.
この先は何が待ってるかしら
I wonder what's waiting for me ahead.
お嬢さん
Young lady.
え?
Huh?
お嬢さん
Young lady.
私?
Me?
そう、お嬢さん
Yes, young lady.
なあに?
What is it?
君は誰?
Who are you?
私の名前は...
My name is...
君は名前など...
You are not just a name...
そう、あなたは誰なの?
...so, who are you?
Who am I? 問いかけてみよう なぜ
Who am I? Let's ask. Why?
Who am I? わからないんだ
Who am I? I don't know.
Who are you? ねえ教えてよ
Who are you? Hey, tell me.
Who am I? 曖昧さ
Who am I? It's vague.
誰わかってるのは 歌ってる僕が
What I know is that the one singing...
最高にハッピーってこと
...is extremely happy.
You love music. 歌を歌えば
You love music. If you sing a song...
少しずつ見えてくる
...little by little, it becomes clear.
僕が生きる意味はきっとここにある
The meaning of my existence is surely here.
だってそう僕は/私も
Because that's right, I/we are...
最高のシンガーなのさ
...the best singer.
この風変わりなリズムはどこから聞こえてくるのかしら
I wonder where this strange rhythm is coming from.
それは私だよ。私。ことタラサ。さ、腰かけたら始めるぞ
That's me. Me. None other than the Hatter. Once you sit down, we'll begin.
お茶はいかが?
How about some tea?
楽しく飲めば世界も踊る
If we drink it joyfully, the world will dance too.
お茶はいかが? さあお嬢様
How about some tea? Come, young lady.
何て変なフレーバー
What a strange flavor.
普段の味になれちまったら すべてが退屈になっちまうもんさ
Once you get used to ordinary flavors, everything becomes boring.
ありきたりなものじゃつまらない
Ordinary things are just not interesting.
それを知った奴はみんなイカレちまうのさ
Everyone who knows that goes crazy.
ほら、お茶はいかが?
Look, how about some tea?
気を衒いたけりゃイカれちまえ
If you want to show off, just go crazy.
さあ、イカレた楽しいティータイム
Now, a crazy and fun tea time!
迷い込んだ森の中 私をいざなう声が
Inside the forest where I'm lost, a voice beckons me.
深い霧に木霊する 私の道はどっち
Echoing in the thick mist, which way is my path?
あっち、そっち、それともこっち?
That way, this way, or that way?
優柔不断なお嬢さん
Such an indecisive young lady.
だけどそれは私も同じ あっちもそっちも歩く道
But it's the same for me too. This way and that way, they're both paths.
喜びや 悲しみや 愛しさまで
Joy, sadness, and even love.
歌にしたい今も全部
I want to turn it all into a song, even now.
降り重なっていたら
If they were to fall and pile up,
最初にまとめて言ったものが 何か分からなくなって
I've lost track of what I said all at once
in the beginning.
最後に残されたものは
What was left at the end
透明な正体の知れない予感と
Was a transparent, unknown premonition and
個性の残骸
The wreckage of individuality.
それを芸術と呼べるのか
Can that be called art?
誰にも分からない
No one knows.
頭の中はごちゃごちゃで
My head is a mess,
不透明なままも悪くない
But staying opaque isn't so bad either.
さっき決めた私を決めた
The 'me' I decided on just now, I've decided.
私の道
On my path.
Ha~
幸か不幸か 感情を選んだ
Fortunately or unfortunately, I chose my emotions.
道は情へ 続く道
The path leads to emotion...
女王様のおなりー！
The Queen has arrived!
私が女王様さ
I am the Queen.
何か文句あるの？
Do you have any complaints?
私の歌えば誰もが釘付け
When I sing, everyone is captivated.
全てをひれ伏させるオーラ
An aura that makes everything bow down.
あなたが女王様 承知しておき
You are the Queen, keep that in mind.
美しい歌声 当たり前じゃない？
A beautiful singing voice, isn't that a given?
オーケストラさ 始めましょう
An orchestra, let's begin.
私のミューゼ
My Muse.
Hey know, yeah, one base
Oh ho! Drums! Whoo! Brass section!
皆言う事をお聞き 私のために奏でなさい
Listen to what I say, play for me.
全ては私のものよ 私は女王様だからさ
Everything is mine, because I am the Queen.
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute.
これはみんなで 奏でるミュージック
This is music we all play together.
へんてこでも まとまらなくても
Even if it's weird or disorganized,
どんな時でも ハッピーを感じてるのさ
Always feeling happy.
十人十色 だけど
Ten people, ten colors, but
重なれば ハーモニーになる
When layered, they become harmony.
理由は単純さ
The reason is simple,
だって We love music
Because We love music.
お話をしよう
Let's talk,
昔話より
More than old stories,
もっともっと 素敵な おとぎ話
A much more wonderful fairy tale.
それはありふれた 魔法のフィロソフィー
It's a common magic philosophy.
みんなのハートに 隠れた ミュージック
Music hidden in everyone's heart.
La~
Ha~
Alice in Musicland
How do you get to Musicland?
Under the pillow, another land?
Or just behind the tree?
Where clouds go rolling by
They roll away and leave the sky
Where is the land beyond the eye
That people cannot see?
Where do stars go?
Where is the silver crescent moon?
They must be somewhere
In the sunny afternoon
Alice in Musicland
Where is the path to Musicland?
Over the hill or here or there?
I really wonder where
Now we know the answer
When we're enjoying music
Always we're in Musicland!
Alice in Musicland
Yeah!
Gimana? Gimana? Gimana?
How was it? How was it? How was it?
どうでしたか？
How was it?
Oh, I can't believe it's almost ending.
Almost, because it still hasn't ended, right?
How are you guys enjoying it so far?
Are you watching it with popcorn?
Or are you watching it with something else? With coffee maybe?
Thank you everyone for coming to my birthday party because...
Ah, I am so excited, I am so happy that my...
...that my vision is coming to reality.
Ah, man, that was really nice, huh?
That was really nice.
I hope you guys noticed my love for all things like...
...retro, vintage...
...and like jazz, you know?
I've always wanted to create something like a little bit different...
...like slightly old-style jazz vibes.
Makasih semuanya udah bikin mimpi aku jadi realita, pokoknya...
Thank you everyone for making my dream a reality, basically...
Ah, seneng banget!
Ah, I'm so happy!
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
I'm so incredibly happy!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
Thank you to everyone and my guests that made this happen.
Amazing special guests!
And I am happy if you guys just had fun...
...grooved to the music and stuff.
So yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed watching it and thank you for always supporting me!
応援してくれてありがとう！
Thank you for supporting me!
Bye bye!
This will be a moment I will never forget!!
Thank you for all the support & amazing memories!