(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
TAN The Autofister Network 3D LIVE
[Title: TAN The Autofister Network 3D LIVE]
お気に召すまま / Lyrics & Music: Eve
[Song: As You Like It / Lyrics & Music: Eve]
淡々 言葉を吐いた
I spit out indifferent words
あんな思い出に泣いたのは
I cried over those memories
今日で終わりにしないか
Can't we put an end to this today?
1, 2 の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal
ユーエンミー手を取りあったのは
Holding hands, just you and me
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイズ＜1＞
An act of courage for me, Phase 1
立ち止まんないでいいんだからね
‘Cause we shouldn't stand still, right?
空々しいな この人生
Life is a sham
できないだなんて 言わないでね
Don’t say you can't do it
言わないでね
Don't say it
今更なんて 言わないでね
Don’t say it's too late now
僕ら今 さあさあ輪になって 回り始める
Come on, come on, now we form a circle and start to spin
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Bit by bit I come to hate it, but I come to like it
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, hey, I don't even understand the meeting of my selves
どんどん 中に寄って でも離れてく
We steadily close the gap, but we remain far apart
ぱっぱっ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Da-dum, carried by the music we start to dance
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Wretchedly, I come to hate it, but I come to like it
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, hey, I don't understand now or ever
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
Shake shake my heart, yay
大正解なんてないのさ
There’s no such thing as a right answer
じゃあ一体どこに向かえば
So, where the hell do I have to go
物語は終わりますか
To find the end of this story?
1, 2 の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal
ユーエンミー手が触れ合ったのは
Holding hands, just you and me
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイズ＜2＞
An act of courage for me, Phase 2
畏まったって 意味ないんだって
There’s no meaning to being humble and respectful
恥ずかしがった 夢にばいばいです
So bye-bye to my embarrassing dreams
この先ずっとよろしくね、よろしくね。
From now on, forever, let’s get along, let's get along.
君と今さあさあ交わって 目を逸らしあう
Come on, come on, we now avert our eyes from each other
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Bit by bit I come to hate it, but I come to like it
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, hey, I don't even understand the meeting of my selves
どんどん 様になって 崩れ落ちてく
I steadily become better, but I'm crumbling to pieces
ぱっぱっ 触れる前に 消えてしまうの
Da-dum, you disappear before I can touch you
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Wretchedly, I come to hate it, but I come to like it
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, hey, I don't understand now or ever
わかりあえるまで僕たちは
Until we can understand each other, we
今更なんて 言わないでね
Shouldn't say it's too late
僕ら今 さあさあ輪になって 回り始める
Come on, come on, now we form a circle and start to spin
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Bit by bit I come to hate it, but I come to like it
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, hey, I don't even understand the meeting of my selves
どんどん 中に寄って でも離れてく
We steadily close the gap, but we remain far apart
ぱっぱっ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Da-dum, carried by the music we start to dance
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Wretchedly, I come to hate it, but I come to like it
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, hey, I don't understand now or ever
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
Shake shake my heart, yay
さあさあ輪になって 回り始める
Come, come, now we form a circle and start to spin
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Bit by bit I come to hate it, but I come to like it
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, hey, I don't even understand the meeting of my selves
どんどん 中に寄って
We steadily close the gap
でも離れてく
But we remain far apart
ぱっぱっ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Da-dum, carried by the music we start to dance
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Wretchedly, I come to hate it, but I come to like it
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, hey, I don't understand now or ever
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
Shake shake my heart, yay!
Wooooo!
Oh my god!
Did you see us? We're so cute! All four of us are so cute together!
Now this is what I call a concert!
We should do more concerts!
This is where the money's at!
Yeah, the money's in the concert!
It's so nice to see everyone perform!
More concerts! More music!
If only there was a concert that was coming up...
If only there were tickets available right now for a concert...
Serendipity?
I don't know where that word came from. Seremunnity?
Wait, what if we invite even more people?
But if we invite more people, it won't be a concert anymore.
Because when there's more people, they start fighting.
Oh? You mean drama?
Drama!
It's just when you get too many girls in a room, drama happens.
But that sells!
Sometimes people like seeing girls fight.
Sometimes there's just too many girls, you know? And yeah...
And sometimes they just can't get along.
But that makes for good television.
Let's content farm them!
FOLLOWING UP ON THE HOLOLIVE-ENIANS
[Title: FOLLOWING UP ON THE HOLOLIVE-ENIANS]
LOS ANGELES
[Location: LOS ANGELES]
GINA'S CONDO
[Location: GINA'S CONDO]
Oh my god, girls! If you want to hang out with us, you have to step up your bag game.
Like, where do you even get your bag from? It looks bootleg!
You don't even recognize the bag I carried today?
Oh, you next-time we gotta have to take you to Bonel.
Bonel?
I own that company.
Oh, what? You own Bonel?
I own the sister branch of Bonel.
Oh my god!
What are you cooking?
Oh, it's my newest recipe. It's a zero calorie...
Oh shit!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, what the fuck!
What happened?
Are you going to pick that up?
Don't tell me what to do!
You literally threw it on the ground.
No I didn't!
You literally did it. You can't accidentally throw something on the ground.
No I didn't! You did! You put it there!
I put it there?
You put your ass in my stupid kitchen, you bitch!
You absolute bitch!
I did not do that!
You literally did! You always make shit up!
Is this happening right now?
Bijou! Bijou, did you see her do that?
Did you see that?
Oh yeah, I saw it! I saw you throw a frying pan!
I saw you throw a frying pan at her!
No! Excuse me!
Yeah, so I was making this totally delicious zero-calorie option dinner for everyone...
because I know that everyone needs to lose a little weight for the party tomorrow...
and I just can't believe that she would do such a thing.
Have you seen Celine? She's a total fucking bitch.
That food is going to be nasty, and you know it.
She's always on these like health trips, but it doesn't do anything for her figure.
Come, come here!
Don't tell me what to do!
Come here! Come here!
You're not my mom!
Look! Look at it! You threw that on the ground!
I've never seen that in my entire life!
You've never seen that in your entire life?
You got this for me for Christmas!
I would never get you something for Christmas!
What?
You got it for me for Christmas!
No, I don't know what you're talking about!
You always do this! Someone hold me back! Hold me back!
Hey, hey, hey! Labor!
Leave my friend alone!
Are you okay? It's okay, it's okay. Don't cry!
Oh my god, so dramatic!
So dramatic!
How dare you betray me! And she's crazy!
She's crazy!
Shut the fuck up!
Who even are you?
I don't know why the fuck I'm here!
I was just here to like promote my music and like...
all these, you know, really rich girls here.
I'm so honored to be here honestly, but...
I don't know what the fuck went on.
Like, what the fuck?
I think it's the water. There's something in the water.
I don't even know why IRene was here.
Who invited her?
She's sexy.
Why are you always so dramatic?
Me, dramatic?
Why do you always make shit up?
I don't make shit up!
You live for the drama!
You are a fake! You are a fake!
The only thing about me that's fake is my tits!
You [bleep]!
Yeah, her tits are fake.
I would know, I paid for them.
Well, I was really insecure about my chest, so you know, I got it, yeah.
You know, Daddy paid for...
No, wait!
Was it Shina?
Oh my God, I forgot about that!
I owe her, she's the best!
It's a vibe. Are you okay?
I'm not okay!
Breathe, breathe, girl.
I'm literally not okay!
Do you see what she did to me?
I saw! That was against everyone!
That was unbelievable! Our food, I was looking forward to that!
I was a new low-calorie option!
Excuse me? Like, you should stop acting like that, you know?
How old are you?
Excuse me? I'm sorry, I don't want to talk to her like that.
Excuse me? Don't talk to me like that!
Oh my God, Bijou always has my back, girl.
I know she'll throw down with me.
Are you getting my good side?
Make sure you get the right angle.
This is for TV, right? Yeah, check me out.
Anyway, Celine is a [bleep].
I don't know what kind of problems she has with my girl Shina, but...
If she continues with this, we're gonna have to throw hands.
She better catch me outside, how about that? If you know what I mean.
I think she needs a wake-up call.
Bijou is such a follower. She doesn't have a single thought in that empty head of hers.
If you were to take her head and rattle it, it would sound like a baby rattle.
You guys are so loud, we're gonna get a noise complaint.
And it's gonna be so embarrassing for you because...
The only noise complaint we'll get is when you're in your bedroom!
What? What does that mean?
Her bedroom?
You know what? Well, at least this apartment isn't under my name, so you're gonna get in trouble.
I will send you to jail! My daddy's a lawyer!
Oh well, you know what? My daddy owns your daddy!
My daddy might be under your daddy, but...
He's a lawyer!
I think your daddy's under my daddy in more ways than one!
Do you see what she's doing to me, Bijou?
I saw, girl!
Oh, so you have a problem with Shina and I, sis?
You have so many issues!
Don't you ever touch her again! You understand?
Oh! She pushed me!
She did nothing!
She pushed me!
Rachel threw herself on the floor. I saw it happen. She's just so dramatic.
Wait, she's such a pick-me girl. That Rachel, what a pick-me.
Kind of a [bleep].
I pick her though. Have you seen her thunder thighs?
Dang, I wanna bite that.
Don't tell her though. Cut that out! Cut that out!
Quella [bleep]! Dammi un'altra di quella [bleep]!
That [bleep]! Give me another of that [bleep]!
Sempre ancora quella [bleep]!
Always still that [bleep]!
Se mi tocca di nuovo, io non ce la faccio più! Basta, ho finito!
If she touches me again, I can't take it anymore! Enough, I'm done!
Rachel's so sweet. She always got my back.
Sometimes she falls down though, but, you know, it helps for my cause. So it's okay.
You are a problem! And you're a danger to society!
I got you, girl. I got you. Get up!
Get up! Right now, you're ruining your outfit!
Anyways guys, I'm kind of hungry. Do you want...
I want food! I came here for food and networking.
Oh, what are you making? I was making a new low-calorie recipe that I...
...you really need to slim down.
I was looking out for you!
If you are cooking, I guess everyone's going to lose their appetite. Not hungry anymore.
I thought Shina was trained by a Michelin chef?
I was!
No, she's just lying. She always makes up this shit.
Namaste, namaste, namaste...
Oh, I can expect something so nutritious. It's really nutritious.
How dare you try to ruin our perfect five-star meal?
Wait, it was really delicious.
I was really looking forward to it.
Five stars.
You ruined Thanksgiving.
No, Raora can do whatever she wants, and you are no one to tell her what to do.
Well I can say whatever I want! I lied!
Hey, leave her alone! Hey, hey, leave Bijou alone.
So what are we here for anyways?
Dinner! Dinner! Dinner!
Do we get to actually eat?
Yeah! Are we gonna eat?
That's right! We're gonna eat!
Oh my God! We're gonna eat!
We're gonna eat!
Anyways, I want to go back to the kitchen and I'm gonna finish cooking.
Yeah, where you belong!
You [Bleep]!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Who's gonna hold me back? Get off of her!
She's... back off! Hey! Animal abuse! Animal abuse!
Are you okay girl? Girl, are you okay?
Animal abuse! Animal abuse! Help!
Just because your dad is a lawyer doesn't mean you can do whatever you want!
The forks not suit you!
Make me look good in the edit, okay?
Check them out!
T.A.N. The Autofister Network
[Logo: T.A.N. The Autofister Network]
I feel like that was too many swear words.
I think they said too, there's too many beepings in there.
Yeah, it was almost like a Morse code.
They didn't even censor fuck!
Or shit!
I just... I don't know...
I would never swear on your channel by the way.
Yeah, you're so sweet. That's really nice of you.
I would never fucking do that. That's so messed up of someone to do.
Yeah, really fucked up.
I just wish they would have edited that out, you know?
Yeah, I just... I'm really uncomfortable right now.
I'm only five minutes old. I'm not allowed to hear those words.
I'm just really scared.
It's also... I don't think we're gonna make any money out of that because it's not gonna be allowed to be aired.
They're gonna demonetize our channel!
What if... what if we have a show but instead of like real people, it's scripted?
Yeah, then we can make sure that there's no curse words in it, and we'll take them all out.
Yeah, scripted... it can still be drama, right?
Yeah, just no... no cursing. No cursing, please.
Please, no cursing on our channel.
HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH
[Title: HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH]
PREVIOUSLY ON: HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH - THE TALE OF BEAVER AND THINKER.
[Recap: THE TALE OF BEAVER AND THINKER]
TWO UNLIKELY SURVIVORS FIND EACH OTHER IN THE MIDDLE OF THE APOCALYPSE, AND ALTHOUGH WARY, THEY'VE COME TO FIND COMFORT IN EACH OTHER'S PRESENCE.
Two unlikely survivors find each other in the apocalypse, and although wary, they've come to find comfort in each other's presence.
HAUNTED BY THEIR PAST, AFRAID OF A FUTURE THAT MAY NEVER COME, WILL THEY EVER BE ABLE TO OVERCOME THEIR STRUGGLES AND REACH MUTUAL UNDERSTANDING IN A DYING WORLD?
Will they ever be able to overcome their struggles and reach mutual understanding in a dying world?
FOR MORE INFORMATION, PLEASE WATCH SEASON 1 FIRST AIRED ON JULY 3, 2024
[Please watch Season 1 first aired on July 3, 2024]
So have you thought about it?
You just... you always say things, but in reality...
I love you.
No, you love your wife.
She's dead now.
You don't even remember...
Even if she's dead that doesn't mean that she's not there anymore.
And I've been thinking about it because I'm the Thinker. You, what are you even?
I'm the Beaver.
Oh man, if I was a beaver I'd be eating so good right now because I have wood.
Look at my wood. Check it out.
Pretty impressive wood.
So you'll want for nothing.
I can provide for you.
But you love your wife! You don't understand!
But over the past seven days...
...that we've learned to survive.
You just want me for my body.
You're not interested in my mind! But I'm the Thinker! I want you!
No, no, no, you have to understand! You're wrong! You're wrong!
No, please! It doesn't have to be like this! Look at my wood!
No, I don't want to look at your wood! Look at my wood!
I don't want your wood!
But you'll be so full!
No, ew, ew! Put that away! Look at my wood!
You don't even want me for my mind! You want me...
Ah! A skeleton! Run away, run away! I'll protect us!
I mean, Beaver! I'm the Beaver! I'm not Gigi, I'm Beaver! I'm the Beaver!
I'm the Beaver!
Beaver be careful!
Oh my God, where'd you get that weapon? I've never seen you use that before.
Yeah, I've used... I bought it from that one pawn shop owner, remember?
Oh yeah, that guy! With the first thing! With the one line! With the want me?
No.
Watch out! Look out! I'm so scared! That was so cool!
Oh my God, that skeleton is so cool! Whoa! What a dance! That skeleton is going crazy!
Oh, she's just... she's too strong! Too strong!
Ah! Ah! Ah! It's just so cool!
Magia / Lyrics & Music: 梶浦由記
[Song: Magia / Lyrics & Music: Yuki Kajiura]
宝鐘マリン、兎田ぺこら、セレス・ファウナ、七詩ムメイ
[Vocals: Houshou Marine, Usada Pekora, Ceres Fauna, Nanashi Mumei]
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
Someday, the light of love that you set aflame in your eyes
時を越えて
Will transcend time...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
...and surely destroy one dream
確かに一つ壊すだろう
of this world that hurries to its ruin.
躊躇いを飲み干して
Swallow down your hesitation.
君が望むモノは何？
What is it that you wish for?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
儚い明日はあるの？
will there be a transient tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
That I dreamed of when I was young,
古の魔法のように
something like the ancient magic,
闇さえ砕く力で
with power that can break through the darkness,
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to meet you and your smile.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の勇気
is courage made of handpicked flowers.
思いだけが頼る全て
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
光を呼び覚ます
a wish that will awaken...
願い
...the light.
いつか君も誰かのために
Someday, you will also wish for great power
強い力を望むのだろう
for the sake of someone else, I suppose.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
In the night when love captured your heart,
未知の言葉が生まれてくる
yet unknown words are born.
迷わずに行けるなら
If I can go without losing my way,
心が砕けてもいいわ
I don't mind if my heart is broken to pieces.
いつも目の前の哀しみに
I want a spell that can let me
立ち向かうための
fight against the sorrow
呪文が欲しい
that is always in front of my eyes.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are a memory that continues to dream.
私は眠らない明日
I am the sleepless tomorrow.
二人が出会う奇跡を
I will move forward in order to attain
勝ち取るために進むわ
the miracle of the two of us meeting.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の刃
is a sword of handpicked flowers.
思いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for,
心に振りかざす
a wish that I brandish...
願い
...within my heart.
囚われた太陽の輝く
When I used to like books about strange lands
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
illuminated by captive suns,
願いはきっと叶うと
I believed the fairy tales that
教えるお伽噺を
taught us that wishes would surely...
信じた
...come true.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Gently, magic from ancient times
古の魔法優しく
bloomed wildly in silence.
世界を変える力が
"The power to change the world
その手にあると囁く
lies in those hands of yours," it whispers.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let us have an unending dream.
君と行く時の中で
During this time I go through with you,
思いだけが生きる全て
my feelings alone are all that I live for.
命を作るのは
What will create my life is...
願い
...this wish.
They brought them back to kill them off?
They killed a main character!
Like, not—not it's not a big cast,
it's literally just two characters.
I can't believe that you would have
a finale of a show years ago,
and then you would do a reunion episode
to kill the main character!
That's so stupid!
Oh my god.
These writers don't know what they're doing.
That's not gonna make any money.
We should trash this idea!
This is a terrible idea.
You know what? Not my canon!
Not my canon!
This is not my show!
No, no, this is just a cash grab.
I hate it!
Okay, okay. You know what else is a cash grab?
What? What?
The Autofister merchandise!
If only we could have someone here
that could tell us about it!
Is this... is this thing on?
Okay, great.
皆さん、こんにちは！
Hey everyone, it's me,
Mori Calliope from Hololive English Myth,
coming here to you today to ask you
to please purchase this merchandise:
...the Autofister Net merch set!
Ever wanted a Gremtomo keychain?
Or a Gimimi or Cemimi?
Or better yet, an acrylic stand
with Autofister on it?
(noise of enthusiasm)
Oh, wow!
For the low, low price of 99.99...
[price will be beeped]
Sorry, sorry, sorry. I did it again.
This can be yours! This can be yours!
And if you purchase now!!
I will say this one super awesome word out loud!
(pregnant silence)
League of Legends.
That's... that's two words.
Wait, no, I... okay, I see what's under that.
That's three words. I'm not saying that.
Management, did you check the script beforehand?
Ooh, this was a bad idea,
this was a freaking bad idea.
League of Legends. Thank you.
And buy the merchandise.
Oh wow! Thanks, Calli!
She loves it! She loves our merch!
劣等上等
[Title: BRING IT ON]
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Rettou Joutou, BRING IT ON
Bring the house! Let's go!
ヘイ！ ヘイ！
Hey! Hey!
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Rettou Joutou, BRING IT ON
ヘイ！ ヘイ！
Hey! Hey!
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Rettou Joutou, BRING IT ON
子供騙しのマセマティカ
A kid's game, this Mathematica
バレてんだってそんなのって
It's so obvious, the tricks, but
プライドがないや
I've no pride!
ご立派警鐘気取りで
How grand, playing officer are you?
高みの見物ばかりじゃつまんねぇ
Just to play it safe up here, how dull is this
ほらもっと
Come on, more
間違って上等
Mistakes, Bring it!
退屈に手をかけて
And do something about this boredom,
ママ、やっぱあたしは
Mommy, after all,
こんなところじゃ終われない
I can't end in a place like this.
ぬるくて気が触れそう
It's so lukewarm, it's driving me crazy!
ごっこ遊びも芝居もさよなら
Farewell, to the plays and pretends,
ずっとこのままなんてさぁ
You know, staying like this for life
いられないよ
Fuck that!
ダッダッダあたし大人になる
Dun-dun-dun - I'm going to be a grown-up!
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Knowing the bitter, the sweet, and now
パッパッパ変わる時代
Pa-ppa-ppa - Times fly by so fast
悪いことばかりじゃないでしょう
It's not all terrible, now, is it?
過去も、罪も、罰も、すべて
The past, the sins, punishments, all of it
素手で、愛で、生き抜いてやり返すわ
With my bare hands, my love, I'll live through it all and serve a payback
yeah,挑発 あたし達はno doubt
Yeah, taunting are we, no doubt
緑のアイツにばっか構ってんね
See you're always tending to that green girl.
さぁburn up いつになったら貰える合格
Now, burn up, when's my certificate coming?
赤ペンいれてよどこがダメなんですか
Come on, grade it, where is it that I'm wrong?
酒女金XXXX(ドラッグ)やっちゃってコンプラ
Drinks, b-ches, money, XXXX (drugs) - Oops! Gotta comply
チルってaiight…
Chill aight...
冗談じゃんブラックジョーク
Take a joke man - just dark humor
中指立てたくなるような事情
Stuck in shit that just makes me want to flip the bird
ありすぎて指が足りねぇから
Hell, I'm in so deep I don't have enough fingers!
hands up
and what's up 最低？ もともとだろ
and what's up loser? You were always one, heh,
bring it on
「まあまあ」なんか要らない
Don't need that calm down
欲しがります死ぬまでは
I'll keep wanting it until I'm dead
伸びた背丈育った街に投げキス
Growing tall - a goodbye-kiss to my hometown
劣等上等
[Song Title: Rettou Joutou]
伸びた背丈 育った街に投げキス
Growing tall - a goodbye-kiss to my hometown
見せ場はこっから 覚悟しとけよ
Highlight reel's rolling now, get ready!
ダッダッダ 僕ら大人になる
Dan-dan-dan, We're going to be grownups!
カウンター狙い 最低な日々に
Aiming for the chance to counter those shitty days
眈々とかます一撃
With a swift strike
誰も読めない先 まだあいこでしょ
No one can read the future, we're still tied even here
バグも、ロスも、ズレも、すべて
The bugs, the losses, the fuck-ups, all of it.
素手で、生きて！生き抜いて覆すよ
With my bare hands, I'll live, live through it and overthrow it
くだらないことばっかが譲れない
It's always the small stuff I can't let go of
わかるか？あたしの美学
Get it? My aesthetic
この馬鹿正直な拳ひとつが切り札
This thick-headed fist alone is my ace up the sleeve
がなる劣等 一抜けよさらば！
Rings the inferiority, “I’m out!” "Peace!"
こんなもんじゃない
This is far from over!
ダッダッダ あたし大人になる
Dun-dun-dun, I'm going to be a grown-up!
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Knowing the bitter, the sweet, and now
燦々 交わるミライ
The brilliant, intersecting future
もう子供じゃないのわかるでしょ
You know I'm not a child anymore
時代 機会 待ってくれない
Times and opportunities won't wait for us
素手で、捨て身で、
With my bare hands, at the risk of my life,
生き抜いて上等だわ
I'll survive, and that's just fine.
愛ある時代
An era with love
それでは皆様お先に Bye, Guys!
Well then, everyone, I'll be going first. Bye, Guys!
Are you thinking...
...what I'm thinking?
I think I am!
Oh my god!
We have to bring this!
Write it down! Write it down right now!
Put it in the suit!
Yes!
Oh my god, they're gonna love this!
They're gonna love it!
They're gonna love us!
They love us!
This is path.
CANCELLED
[Stamp: CANCELLED]
I'm going to give up on my dreams.
D- Never give up on your dreams.
Really?
Yeah, I feel like you had half a good idea.
And you had half a good idea too.
And together...
...we'll...
...whole good idea.
That's a whole good idea.
We'll get the funding one day.
Well thank you very much everyone...
...that helped us work on all these shows together.
Oh, thank you to all...
...our beautiful wonderful guests.
And thank you to you grems and otomos at home...
...watching us today during our TV show.
Please sign our petition...
...and look at the credits...
...and don't forget there is something else...
...coming up in just a few minutes!
Right after this!
So don't change the channel!
Don't change the channel just yet!
Put down that remote!
Put it down!
Yes! Gun to your head, put it down right now!
Put down the remote right now!
There's something really really cool...
...coming up right after this!
Yay!
The Autofister Network 3D Live!