(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
お気に召すまま / Lyrics & Music: Eve
[Title: Okinimesumama / Lyrics & Music: Eve]
淡々 言葉を吐いた
Indifferently, I spat out the words
あんな思い出に泣いたのは
Crying over such memories
今日で終わりにしないか
Why don't we end it today?
1, 2の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal
ユーエンミー手を取りあったのは
You and me, holding hands
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイズ
It was my brave action, phase
立ち止まんないでいいんだからね
You don't have to stop
空々しいな この人生
It's so hollow, this life
できないだなんて 言わないでね
Don't say you can't, don't say it
言わないでね
Don't say it...
今更なんて 言わないでね
Don't say it's too late now
僕ら今さあさあ輪になって 回り始める
Now, come on, come on, we form a circle and start spinning
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Gradually I come to hate it, but then I love it
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, hey, I don't know, even my self-meetings
どんどん 中に寄って でも離れてく
More and more, we get close, but then drift apart
ぱっぱっ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Pa-pa, riding on the sound, we start to dance
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
I come to hate it so much, but then I love it
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, hey, I don't know, from here on out forever
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
Shake shake my heart, yeah
大正解なんてないのさ
There's no big correct answer
じゃあ一体どこに向かえば
So where on earth should I head to?
物語は終わりますか
Will the story end?
1, 2の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal
ユーエンミー手が触れ合ったのは
You and me, our hands touched
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイズ
It was my brave action, phase
畏まったって 意味ないんだって
Being formal, it's meaningless
恥ずかしがった 夢にばいばいです
Goodbye to the dreams I was shy about
この先ずっとよろしくね
Please be good to me from now on...
よろしくね
Be good to me
君と今さあさあ交わって 目を逸らしあう
Now, come on, come on, you and I intersect and avert our eyes
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Gradually I come to hate it, but then I love it
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, hey, I don't know, even my self-meetings
どんどん 様になって 崩れ落ちてく
More and more, it takes shape, but then it crumbles
ぱっぱっ 触れる前に 消えてしまうの
Pa-pa, before I can touch it, it disappears
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
I come to hate it so much, but then I love it
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, hey, I don't know, from here on out forever
わかりあえるまで僕たちは
Until we can understand each other, we...
今更なんて 言わないでね
Don't say it's too late now
僕ら今さあさあ輪になって 回り始める
Now, come on, come on, we form a circle and start spinning
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Gradually I come to hate it, but then I love it
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, hey, I don't know, even my self-meetings
どんどん 中に寄って でも離れてく
More and more, we get close, but then drift apart
ぱっぱっ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Pa-pa, riding on the sound, we start to dance
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
I come to hate it so much, but then I love it
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, hey, I don't know, from here on out forever
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
Shake shake my heart, yeah
[お気に召すまま]
[Title: Oki ni Mesu Mama]
Wow!
Oh my God! Did you see us? We're so cute!
All four of us are so cute together!
I loved that concert! Yay!
This is where the money's at! Yeah, the money is in the concert!
It was so nice to see everyone perform.
More concerts! More music! If only there was a concert that was coming up...
Ah, if only... If only there were tickets available right now for a concert!
Serendipity... I wonder where that word came from.
Wait! What if we invite even more people?
But if we invite more people, it won't be a concert anymore, because when there's more people, they start fighting.
No... You mean drama?
Drama! Drama! Yeah, when you get too many girls in a room, drama happens.
But that does sell. We love seeing girls fight.
Sometimes there's just too many girls, you know? And yeah, and sometimes they just can't get along.
Mm-hmm... But that makes for good television.
We should film them.
Let's content-farm them.
[FOLLOWING UP ON THE HOLOLIVE-ENIANS]
[Title: FOLLOWING UP ON THE HOLOLIVE-ENIANS]
[LOS ANGELES]
[Location: LOS ANGELES]
[GINA'S CONDO]
[Location: GINA'S CONDO]
Oh my God, girls, if you want to hang out with us, you have to step up your bag game. Like, where did you even get your bag from? It looks... budget.
You don't even recognize the bag I carried today?
Oh, you... Next time we're going to have to take you to Benella. Benella.
Benella? / Yeah.
I own that company. / Oh! You own Benella?
I own the sister branch of Benella. / Oh my God.
Oh my God, what are you cooking?
Oh, it's my newest recipe. It's a zero-calorie...
Oh shit.
It's a zero-calorie...
Oh my God! Oh shit.
Oh my God, what the—
What happened?
Are you going to pick that up?
Don't tell me what to do!
You literally threw it on the ground.
No, I didn't!
You literally did it. You can't accidentally throw something on the ground.
No, I didn't. You put it there! / I put it there?
You put your ass in my stupid kitchen, you—! You absolute—!
I did not do that!
You literally did! You always make shit up! I watched you do that.
Did you see her do that? Did you see her do that?
Did you see that? Did she seriously... Oh, yeah, we saw that, sis.
I saw you throw a frying pan, girl. / No, no! / Excuse me?
Yeah, so I was making this totally delicious zero-calorie option dinner for everyone...
...because I know that everyone needs to lose a little weight for the party tomorrow. And I just can't believe that she would do such a thing.
Have you seen Celine? She's a total fucking—. That food is going to be nasty, and you know it.
She's always on these like health trips, but it doesn't do anything for her figure. Come here!
Don't tell me what to do! / Come here! Come here! You're not my mom! Look! Look at it!
You threw that on the ground. / I've never seen that in my entire life. / How have you never seen that in your entire life?
I've never seen that in my entire life. / You got this for me, for Christmas!
I would never get you something for Christmas. / What?
You got it for me for Christmas! You always do this.
Someone hold me back, hold me back, hold me back! / Hey hey hey hey, leave her!
Leave my friend alone! It's okay, it's okay, don't cry.
You're going to ruin your mascara, girl. You guys are so dramatic.
So dramatic! How dare you! She's crazy!
She is fucking crazy! She is crazy!
Shut the fuck up! Who even are you? I don't even know why the fuck I'm here!
I was just here to like promote my music and like, all these, you know, really rich girls here. I'm so honored to be here honestly...
...but I don't know what the fuck went on. Like, what the fuck? I think it's the water.
There's something in the water. I don't even know why Irene was here.
Who invited her?
She's sexy.
Why are you always so dramatic?
Me dramatic?!
Why do you always make shit up?
I literally do not!
You live for the drama!
You are fake! You are fake!
The only thing about me that's fake is my tits!
Tits?!
You [bleep]!
Yeah, her tits are fake. I would know, I paid for them.
Well, I was really insecure about my chest, so you know, I got it. You know, Daddy paid for...
No, wait. Was it Shina? Oh my god, I forgot about that. I owe her, she's the best.
It's fine. Are you okay?
I'm not okay. I'm literally not okay.
Did you see what she did to me?
I saw.
That was unbelievable. Our food! I was looking forward to that.
I was making a new low-calorie option!
Excuse me, like, you should stop acting like that, you know. How old are you?
Excuse me?!
Don't talk to her like that.
I can talk to her how I want!
Don't you talk to me!
Oh my god, shut up! Yeah!
Oh my god, Bijou always has my back, girl. I know she'll throw down with me.
Are you getting my good side? Make sure you get the right angle. This is for TV, right? Yeah, check me out.
Anyway...
Cecilia is a [bleep]!
I don't know what kind of problems she has with my girl Shina, but...
if she continues with this, we're gonna have to throw hands.
She better catch me outside, how about that, if you know what I mean.
I think she needs a wake-up call.
Bijou is such a follower. She doesn't have a single thought in that empty head of hers.
If you were to take her head and rattle it, it would sound like a baby rattle.
You guys are so loud, we're going to get a noise complaint.
and it's going to be so embarrassing for you because this is your...
The only noise complaint we'll get is when you're in your bedroom!
(Gasp)
What, what does that mean?
Bedroom?!
You know what? Well, at least this apartment isn't under my name, so you're gonna get in trouble.
Uh-huh.
I will send you to jail! My daddy is a lawyer!
Oh, well, you know what? My daddy owns your daddy!
(Screams)
I might be under your daddy...
...but he's a lawyer!
He's a lawyer!
I think your daddy's under my daddy, in more ways than one!
Do you see what she's doing to me, Bijou?
I saw, girl.
Oh, so you have a problem with truth and analysis?
(Yelling/arguing)
(Yelling and charging)
Don't touch her ever again, you understand?!
Oh my god, who do you think you are?!
Don't touch her!
(Rachel falls down dramatically)
She threw herself on the ground!
I did nothing!
She pushed me!
Rachel threw herself on the floor. I saw it happen. She's just so dramatic.
She threw herself on the ground!
Oh my god!
Wow, she's such a pick-me girl.
That Rachel is a pick-me.
Kind of a [bleep].
I'd pick her, though.
Have you seen her thunder thighs?
Dang, I wanna... I wanna bite that.
Don't tell her, though! Cut that out! Cut that out!
Quella [bleep], m'ha toccato quella [bleep]...
That [bleep], that [bleep] touched me...
Sempre ancora quella [bleep]...
Always that [bleep] again...
Se mi tocca di nuovo, io non ce la faccio più, basta, ho finito!
If she touches me again, I can't take it anymore, that's it, I'm done!
Rachel is so sweet, she always got my back.
Sometimes she falls down, though, but you know, it helps for my cause, so it's okay.
You are the problem, and you're the danger to society!
I'm a danger?!
She fell! Oh my god!
She fell!
Watch out, watch out! You're gonna ruin her outfit!
Yeah, yeah, get away!
Stop! I mean, come on, join us, join us!
How dare you!
Stop touching each other. This is getting a little too far, I think.
I got you, girl. I got you. Get up, get up right now, you're ruining your outfit.
Oh my god...
Anyways, guys, I'm kind of hungry. Do you want...
I'm hungry, I came here for food and networking.
Oh, what were you making?
I was making a new low-calorie recipe that I... because you really need to slim down.
(Screams / gasps)
I was making it for you!
If you were cooking, I guess everyone's going to lose their appetite.
Yeah, not me anymore.
[bleep]!
I thought Shina was trained by a Michelin chef.
I was!
No, she's just like, she always makes up this...
Namaste, namaste, namaste...
Oh, I can expect something so nutritious.
It's really nutritious.
How dare you try to ruin our perfect five-star meal!
It was really delicious. We're so proud of it!
Five stars! You ruined Thanksgiving.
Bijou can do whatever she wants, and you are no one to tell her what to do.
Well, I can say whatever I want to!
She's my client!
Leave her alone, Gigi. Leave Bijou alone.
So, what are we here for anyways?
Dinner! Dinner! Dinner!
Do we get to actually eat?
Yeah! Are we gonna eat? That's right!
Are we gonna eat? Oh my god! We're gonna eat!
Anyways, I want to go back to the kitchen and finish cooking.
Yeah, where you belong.
You b**ch! Whoa! Oh!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hold her back! Hold her back off of her! Oh, you b**ch!
Help! Hold her back! Abuse! Animal abuse!
Are you okay, girl? Girl, are you okay?
Animal abuse? Animal abuse? Where?
Just because your dad is a lawyer doesn't mean you can do whatever you want!
That spork does not suit you.
Make me look good in the edit, okay? Check out my profile.
Mmm... I feel like that was too many swear words.
I think they said too... there's too many bleepings in there.
Yeah, it was almost like a Morse code.
Did they even censor "f**k"? Or "sh*t"?
Ah! I just... I don't know...
We must stop. I would never swear on your channel, by the way.
Yeah, you're so sweet. That's really nice of you.
I would never f**king do that. That's so messed up of someone to do.
Yeah, really f**ked up. I just wish they would have edited that out, you know?
Yeah, I... I just... I'm really uncomfortable right now.
I'm only five minutes old. I'm not allowed to hear those words.
I'm just really scared. It's also just... I don't think we're gonna make any money out of that because it's not going to be allowed to be aired.
They'll demonetize our channel! Nooo!
What if... what if we have a show, but instead of like... real people, it's scripted?
Oh! Yeah! And then we can make sure that there's no curse words in it, we'll take them all out.
Yeah, yeah! It can still be drama, right?
Mm, but just... just no curse words. No cursing, please! Please, no cursing on our channel.
Previously on Half a Fortnite Away from Death - The Tale of Beaver and Thinker:
Two unlikely survivors find each other in the middle of the apocalypse...
...and although wary, they've come to find comfort in each other's presence.
Haunted by their past, afraid of a future that may never come...
...will they ever be able to overcome their struggles in a dying world?
So, have you thought about it?
You just... you just always say things, but in reality...
I love you. No, you love your wife!
She's dead now. You don't even remember...
Even if she's dead, that doesn't mean she's not there anymore.
And I've been thinking about it, because I'm the Thinker.
What are you even? I'm the Beaver.
Oh man, if I was a beaver, I'd be eating so good right now.
Is that wood? Cause I have wood. Look at my wood, check it out.
Pretty impressive wood. So you would want for nothing. I can provide for you.
But you... you love your wife! You don't understand! But still, she's... she's your wife!
The past seven days... that we've learned to survive.
You just want me for my body. You're not interested in my mind.
I want you for your mind! I'm the Thinker! I want you! No, no.
No, you have to understand! You're wrong! No! No, please! Please!
It doesn't have to be like this! Look at my wood!
No, I don't want to look at your wood! Ah! Look at my wood! Oh, please!
I don't want your wood! I don't... But you'll be so full!
No, ew, ew, put that away, ew! Look at my wood!
You don't even want me for my mind, you want me...
Ah! Skeleton! A skeleton!
Run away, run away! I'll protect us!
I mean... I mean, Beaver! I'm the Beaver! I'm not Gigi, I'm Beaver! I'm the Beaver!
Beaver, be careful!
Oh my god, where did you get that weapon? I've never seen you use that before.
Yeah, I've used... I... I bought it from that one pawn shop owner, remember?
Oh yeah, that guy! That was a good thing. Was it So-Wamy?
No.
Watch out, Beaver, watch out! Watch out! Watch out!
Oh, that was so cool!
Oh my god, the skeleton! She's so cool! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! What's that? Best skeleton is going down!
Oh, she's just...
It's too strong! Ah!
It's just so cool! Ah!
Aaaaaah!
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
The light of love you'll one day ignite in your eyes...
(時を超えて)
...(will transcend time)
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を 確かに一つ
...will surely shatter the dream of a world rushing to its destruction...
(壊すだろう)
...(one by one).
躊躇いも飲み干して
Gulping down your hesitation...
君が望むモノは何？
...what is it that you desire?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
At the end of such a greedy longing...
儚い明日はあるの？
...is there a fleeting tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic...
古の魔法のように
...I used to dream of as a child,
闇さえ砕く力で
with the power to shatter even the darkness...
微笑む君に会いたい
...I want to see you smile.
怯えるこの手の中には
In these trembling hands...
手折られた花の勇気
...lies the courage of a plucked flower.
想いだけが頼る全て
Only my feelings are all I rely on,
光を呼び覚ます 願い
a wish that awakens the light.
いつか君も誰かの為に 強い力を
One day you too, for someone's sake...
(望むのだろう)
...(will desire strong power).
愛が胸を捉えた夜に 未知の言葉が
On the night love captured your heart...
(生まれて来る)
...(unknown words will be born).
迷わずに行けるなら
If I can go without hesitation...
心が砕けてもいいわ
...it's alright if my heart breaks.
いつも目の前の悲しみに 立ち向かう為の
Always, to face the sadness in front of me...
呪文が欲しい
...I want a spell.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are still a dream-seeing memory,
私は眠らない明日
I am a tomorrow that never sleeps.
二人が出会う奇跡を
To win the miracle of us two meeting...
勝ち取る為に進むわ
...I will move forward.
怯えるこの手の中には
In these trembling hands...
手折られた花の刃
...lies the blade of a plucked flower.
想いだけが生きる全て
Only my feelings are all I live for,
心に振りかざす 願い
a wish I brandish in my heart.
囚われた太陽の輝く
When I loved the book of Wonderland...
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
...where the trapped sun shone,
願いはきっと叶うと
I believed in the fairy tale...
教えるお伽話を信じた
...that told me the wish would surely come true.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Quietly blooming...
古の魔法優しく
...was the ancient magic, gently...
世界を変える力が
...whispering that the power to change the world...
その手にあると囁く
...is in your hands.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let's dream an endless dream...
君と行く時の中で
...in the time I go with you.
想いだけが生きる全て
Only my feelings are all I live for,
命を作るのは 願い
it is my wish that creates life.
They brought them back to kill them off?
They killed a main character... like, not...
it's not a big cast! It's literally just two characters.
I can't believe that you would have a finale of a show years ago,
and then you would do a reunion episode to kill the main character!
It's so...
...stupid!
These writers don't know what they're doing!
That's not going to make any money!
We should trash this idea. This is a terrible idea.
You know what? Not my canon. Not my canon.
This is not my show!
No, no. This is just a cash grab. I hate it.
You know what else is a cash grab?
What? What?
The Autofister merchandise!
If only we had someone here who can tell us about it.
Is this...
...is this thing on?
Okay, great.
みなさん！
Minna-san!
Hey everyone, it's me, Mori Calliope, from Hololive English Myth,
coming here to you today, to ask you to please purchase this merchandise...
...dot dot dot...
the Autofister Net merch set!
Ever wanted a gremtomo keychain?
Or, uh... a Gimimi or Cemimi?
Or better yet, an acrylic stand with AUTOFISTER on it??
Oh... wow!
For the low low price of 99.99... [beep]
...close bracket.
Sor- Sor- Sor- Sorry...
This can be yours!
And if you purchase now!!
Double exclamation point. I will say this one super awesome word out loud!
Open bracket, pregnant silence, close bracket.
That's... uh, that's two words.
Wait...
No, okay, I see what's on there. That's three words.
I'm not saying that.
Did you... did you check the script beforehand?
Ugh, this was a bad idea, this is a freaking bad idea, I don't know why I agreed to this, ugh!
League of Legends. Thank you, and buy the merchandise.
Oh wow, thanks, Calli!
She loves us. She loves our merch.
(Grow up! Nah mean?)
(Track Giga)
(Bring it on, bring it on, fumin Nippon)
Ah!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Bring it on!
子供騙しのマセマティカ
Childish trick of mathematics,
偉そうに御立派 継承気取りで
Acting all great, noble, and self-righteous,
高みの見物ばかりじゃ つまんねえ
Just sitting back and watching is so boring!
ほらもっと 間違って上等
Hey, bring on even more mistakes!
退屈に手をかけて
Destroy this boredom!
こんなところじゃ 終わらない
It won't end in a place like this!
ぬるくて気が触れそう保存
It's so lukewarm I'm going crazy.
ごっこ遊びも 芝居もサヨナラ
Goodbye to playing house and acting,
ダッダッダ あたし大人になる
Da-da-da, I'm growing up!
酸いも甘いも 噛み分けて今
Having tasted the sweet and sour,
パッパッパ 変わる時代
Pa-pa-pa, the changing times!
悪いことばかりじゃないでしょう
It's not all bad things, is it?
過去も罪も罰もすべて
The past, the sins, the punishments, all of it,
素手で愛で 生き抜いてやり返すわ
I'll survive with bare hands and love, and pay you back!
Yeah 挑発 私達は no doubt
Yeah, provocation, we are no doubt
緑のアイツにばっか かまってんね保存
Always paying attention to that green guy, huh?
さあ burn up
Now, burn up!
いつになったら もらえる合格
When will we finally get a passing grade?
赤ペン入れてよ どこがダメなんですか
Mark us in red ink, tell us where we went wrong!
酒 女 金 ドラッグ
Alcohol, women, money, drugs...
やっちゃってコンプラ
Breaking the compliance!
Chillって aiight
Just chill, alright?
冗談じゃんブラックジョーク
It's just a joke, a black joke!
中指立てたくなるような事情
Reasons that make you want to raise your middle finger
ありすぎて指が足りねえから
Are so many, I don't have enough fingers!
Hands up and what's up
最低？ もともとだろ
Terrible? I was like that from the start!
Bring it on!
「まあまあ」 なんかいらない
I don't need any "so-so" options!
欲しがります死ぬまでは
I'll crave for more until I die!
伸びた背丈 育った街に投げキッス
Blow a kiss to my taller height and the town I grew up in!
見せ場はこっから 覚悟しとけよ
The highlight starts here, prepare yourself!
ダッダッダ 僕ら大人になる
Da-da-da, we're growing up!
そこのけそこのけ 街になびく 秘め騒ぐ心から
Get out of the way, get out of the way! Fluttering in the streets, from my secretly clamoring heart...
覚悟しとけよ
You better prepare yourself!
段々々 ほら 音に鳴る カウントダウン
Step by step, look, the sound rings out, the countdown...
狙い 狙い 痛い 痛い 日々に
...aiming, aiming at these painful days.
燦々と かます 仁義
Brilliantly serving up justice!
誰も読めない 先も読めない これで勝負
No one can read it, the future is unreadable, this is the showdown!
バグも マスも ドレも すべて
Even the bugs, the masses, whichever it is, take them all along...
ツレて 満ちて 生きて 射ち抜いて 狂い咲きしよう
...and fill up, live, shoot through, let's bloom in madness!
We've got a very special show! Let's go!
かったるい 事はしない
I don't do tedious things.
言葉が かげり ズレない
My words don't shadow or slip.
解るか？ あたしの 美学
Do you understand my aesthetic?
この 場で 正直な
Right here, my honest...
拳 一つが
...single fist...
切り札
...is my trump card!
ガナる ラッタッタ
Shouting "rat-tat-tat"!
一撃 で K.O. するならば
If it's a one-hit K.O., then...
そら 行くぞ
Here we go!
Ow!
Alright, Otomos, and every single grem at home, put your hands up!
こんな もんじゃない
This isn't all I've got!
段々々 ほら 音に鳴る カウントダウン
Step by step, look, the sound rings out, the countdown...
酸いも甘いも 見分けて今
...telling the sour from the sweet now.
燦々 交わる 未来を
With no fear of...
恐れることもないよ 解るでしょ<
...the brilliantly intersecting future, you understand, right?
地平 線まで
All the way to the horizon...
届かない
...where we can't reach,
連れて行くよ
I'll take you with me,
息を抜いて 頂戴な 頂戴な
so please, take a breath, please.
それは皆々様、お先にバイバイっ！
Well then, everyone, bye-bye for now!
Gigi, I think we're done.
We are? Show is over. Yeah, we are finished.
Uuuugh...
Are you thinking...
...what I'm thinking?
I think I am!
Oh my god. We have to do this. Write this down, write this down right now!
Let's bring it to the suits! Yeah!
Oh my god, they're gonna love this!
They're gonna love it!
They're gonna love us! They love us. They love us!
This is bad.
This is bad. (Slow-motion)
I'm going to give up on my dreams.
Don- Never give up on your dreams.
Really?
Yeah. I feel like... you had half a good idea.
And you had half a good idea, too.
And together... That's a... We'll... ...whole good idea.
That's a whole good idea. We'll get the funding one day.
So, thank you very much, everyone, that has helped us work on all these shows together.
Oh, thank you to all of our beautiful, wonderful guests!
And thank you to you, grems and otomos...
...at home...
...watching us today...
...during our TV show!
Um, please sign our petition, and look at the credits!
And don't forget, there is something else...
...coming up in just a very few minutes!
Very special!
Right after this, so don't change the channel!
Don't change the channel just yet! Put down that remote, put it down.
Yes!
Gun to your head, put it down right now!
Put down the remote right now!
There is something really, really cool coming up right after this!
Yay!
The...
Autofister Network!