(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Terima Kasih!
Thank you!
Berkat kalian, kami bisa bersinar.
Thanks to you all, we can shine.
Beribu-ribu terima kasih.
A thousand thanks.
Terima kasih udah bikin stage ini...
Thank you for making this stage...
...& hidup kami lebih berwarna.
...and our lives more colorful.
Terima Kasih!!
Thank you!!
Terima kasih banyak!!!!!
Thank you so much!!!!!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank you!!
Kalian Semua Keren-BGT!!
You are all SUPER COOL!!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank you!!
Makasih ya!!
Thanks!!
terima kasih
thank you
Ayo mulai!!
Let's start!!
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も
My body and heart too...
この手で Make you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine.
Woah oh oh...
Oh baby I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby I need you, I need you forever.
君を見るたび
Every time I see you,
上書きされてく欲望に
I'm being overwritten by desire.
重なる Eyes, Eyes, Eyes
Overlapping Eyes, Eyes, Eyes,
Melt into your Smile, Smile, Smile
ねえ、その姿形
Hey, that appearance and shape,
全てが拍車かけてく
everything is spurring it on.
恋から Ai, Ai, Ai
From love to Love, Love, Love,
毎秒おかしくなってく
Every second I'm going crazy.
手を伸ばせばもう届く距離
If I reach out, it's within touching distance.
危険な Ecstasy 試したい
I want to test this dangerous Ecstasy.
穏やかに恋したい
I want to love calmly,
どんなシーンも私に見せて
but show me every scene of yours.
このまま Stay by my side
Just like this, Stay by my side,
どこにも行かないで
don't go anywhere.
Ah 100%
純粋な愛だから
because it's pure love.
Imitation? 止められない感情
Imitation? Unstoppable emotions.
その腕で抱きしめてよ
Hold me tight in those arms.
ちょっとそこからじゃ
From just over there,
ずっともっと近くで
I want to be always, much closer.
認め合いたい 昂る衝動
I want to accept each other, this rising impulse.
持て余すだけなら Fly
If you can't handle it, then Fly.
Hey tell me what's wrong with me
なにも問題ない普通だし
There's no problem, it's normal.
君の全部知りたい
I want to know all of you.
I do need you in my soul
最初は声を聞く
First, I hear your voice,
それだけでよかった
that alone was enough.
だけど次第に Why
But gradually, Why,
ワガママになった
I became selfish.
誰かに笑いかけ
Smiling at someone else,
その仕草に苛立ち
getting irritated by that gesture,
隠せない自分に気づいた
I realized I couldn't hide myself.
独り占めしたい
I want you all to myself.
いっそ鎖に繋いで
Rather, just tie me up in chains.
二人きりの部屋
A room with just the two of us,
接近距離
at close range.
行動発言監視したい
I want to monitor your actions and words.
想い全てぶつけたい
I want to throw all my feelings at you.
その吐息感じたい
I want to feel that breath.
永遠に Stay by your side
Forever Stay by your side,
どこにも行かせない
I won't let you go anywhere.
Ah 100%
暴れ狂う衝動
A raging impulse,
認め聞かせない絶対
I definitely won't let you ignore it.
Ah 私たち
Ah, as for us,
だとしても引き下がれない
even so, we can't back down.
歪んでく衝動
Distorting impulses.
後目引かせない絶対
I definitely won't let you look back.
Hey tell me what's wrong with me
なにも問題ない普通だし
There's no problem, it's normal.
君の全部知りたい
I want to know all of you.
I do need you in my soul
目を閉じたら
When I close my eyes,
止めどない愛が
endless love is here.
触れたい
I want to touch you.
私の方だけ
Just look at me.
このまま Stay by my side
Just like this, Stay by my side,
二度と離れないで
don't ever leave me again.
Ah 100%
純粋な愛だから
because it's pure love.
命令少女　そこで嗜めてよ
Commanding girl, reprove me right there.
ああ　僕からかい？
Ah, is it from me?
ずっともっと近くで認め合い
Acknowledging each other much closer forever.
暴れた少女
Rampaging girl,
だって甘そうだ　だけなら
because it looks sweet, if that's all...
Tell me what's wrong with me
何ももんないナイフ突き出し
Thrusting a dull knife with nothing to it,
君の全部知りたい
I want to know all of you.
I need you, need you 今すぐ
I need you, need you right now.
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever.
Oh baby, I need you...
逃げるなら今だ
If you're going to run, now is the time.
未だ見よ勝利を願っちゃって
Still wishing for victory to be seen.
Are you ready? もしかしての Sign
Are you ready? Possibly a sign?
揺れない去りに 15 minutes
Unwavering departure in 15 minutes.
Just face scanning
遊びでは Standby now
For play, standby now.
もう正直飽き飽きなのよ
Honestly, I'm getting tired of this.
どうなっても残酷
No matter what happens, it's cruel.
私には血の味ね
For me, it tastes like blood.
Day by day
Victory to the world
手に入れると
When I get it in my hands,
最高感度はきっと
the highest sensation must surely be
掛け替えのないはずよ
something irreplaceable.
逃したって止めないさ
Even if you miss it, I won't stop.
今夜　私の基本になる
Tonight, it will become my foundation.
Victory to the world
Haa... Siapa di sini yang lelah dengan kehidupan?
Haa... Who here is tired of life?
Kalau capek enaknya gimana nih Holohero?
If you're tired, what's good to do, Holohero?
Goyang aja!
Just dance!
Bukannya sudah biasa ditikam oleh kecewa
Isn't it already common to be stabbed by disappointment?
Pastinya oh oh...
For sure, oh oh...
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya
Maybe it's about time
Kau coba lepaskan saja
You just try to let it go
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
No need to ask why anymore
Jika memang
If indeed
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui
Don't cry over it, try to get through
teka-tekinya...
its puzzles...
Relakanlah
Let it go
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada
You are stronger than
yang kau kira
you think
Dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be
Jalani saja
Just live through it
Dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be
Jalani saja
Just live through it
Walau kadang mati rasa
Even if sometimes you feel numb
Bahkan hingga tak berdaya
Even until you're helpless
Dan usahamu terasa
And your efforts feel
sia-sia
pointless
Jika memang
If indeed
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui
Don't cry over it, try to get through
teka-tekinya...
its puzzles...
Relakanlah
Let it go
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada
You are stronger than
yang kau kira
you think
Lepas semua kendali
Release all control
Tancap gas dan berlari
Step on the gas and run
Terima dan sudahi
Accept it and end it
Jika memang
If indeed
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui
Don't cry over it, try to get through
teka-tekinya...
its puzzles...
Relakanlah
Let it go
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada
You are stronger than
yang kau kira
you think
Kau lebih kuat daripada
You are stronger than
yang kau kira
you think
Dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be
Jalani saja
Just live through it
Dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be
Jalani saja
Just live through it
Halo Comic Frontier!
Hello Comic Frontier!
Welcome to...
Hololive Indonesia...
5th Anniversary Live
Chromatic Future!
Yay!
Wah gila, gila, gila!
Wow crazy, crazy, crazy!
Makasih banyak semuanya udah pada dateng...
Thank you everyone for coming...
...ke konser 5 tahun kita ya!
...to our 5th year concert!
Wah gak berasa gak sih udah 5 tahun aja?
Wow, doesn't it feel like it's been 5 years already?
Kalau gitu kita mulai dari perkenalan diri dulu gak sih?
Then, shouldn't we start with self-introductions?
Mulai dari aku, aku!
Start with me, me!
Oke oke oke.
Okay okay okay.
Mission Starto!
Mission Start!
Aku Vestia Zeta dari Hololive Indonesia Gen 3.
I'm Vestia Zeta from Hololive Indonesia Gen 3.
Nice to meet you!
Next, Kaela!
Oke oke oke, Kaela...
Okay okay okay, Kaela...
Grinding every time, the blacksmith from...
...Hololive ID Gen 3.
I'm Kaela Kovalskia.
Nice to meet you all!
Next next next, Kobo!
Bokobokobo, Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
Nah bertiga kami dari...
So, the three of us are from...
Hololive Indonesia Gen ke-3
Hololive Indonesia Gen 3
HoloH3ro!
Wah gak nyangka juga deh konser 5th Anniversary...
Wow, I really didn't expect the 5th Anniversary concert...
...Hololive ID ini akhirnya ada juga.
...of Hololive ID to finally happen.
Dari lagu pertama aja...
Just from the first song...
...udah keren banget guys!
...it was already so cool guys!
Woe, woe, woe, woe, woe!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Nanti keringetan loh, nanti keringetan.
You'll get sweaty, you know. You'll get sweaty.
Kok Kaela gimana?
How about you, Kaela?
Aduh, seru banget.
Oh my, it's so exciting.
Aku enggak nyangka sih sampai aku bisa ada di sini ya.
I never expected I'd actually be able to be here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong konsernya masih panjang banget...
But speaking of which, the concert is still very long...
...jadi kalian tetap semangat ya sampai akhir!
...so you guys keep your spirits up until the end!
Semangat, semangat, semangat, semangat!
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Eh, tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi emang pada tahu judul konsernya apa?
Eh, but speaking of the concert, do you actually know what the title is?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah Chromatic Future!
Our concert title this time is Chromatic Future!
Ada yang tahu enggak artinya apa? Ayo absen.
Does anyone know what it means? Come on, roll call.
Nah ini, Kobo paling tahu.
Well, Kobo knows this best.
Yang... yang jelasin yang paling tinggi. Yuk, let's go.
The... the one to explain is the tallest one. Yup, let's go.
Segitu ya... ya udahlah, ya udah.
Like that, huh... alright then, alright.
Nih ya guys ya, buat kalian yang belum tahu...
Here guys, for those of you who don't know...
...Chromatic Future itu artinya tuh masa depan yang berwarna-warni.
...Chromatic Future means a colorful future.
Jadi karena Hololive Indonesia kan udah lima tahun nih...
So, because Hololive Indonesia has been around for five years...
...kita sama-sama dari hari satu sampai sekarang.
...we've been together from day one until now.
Nah, jadi itu untuk ke depannya...
So, for the future...
...harapannya tuh kita bisa nyiptain waktu dan memori yang berwarna-warni...
...our hope is that we can create colorful times and memories...
...sama seluruh fans dari Hololive Indonesia!
...with all the fans of Hololive Indonesia!
Ya gitu! Betul kayak yang dibilang Kak Ela!
Just like that! Correct, just like Kaela said!
Nah, kalian sekarang udah pada tahu kan karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
Well, now you guys know since it was explained by Kaela.
Kalau gitu konsernya kan udah mulai nih.
In that case, the concert has already started.
Kalian mau ngepost soal konser ini di medsos...
If you want to post about this concert on social media...
...jangan lupa hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture ya!
...don't forget the hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture!
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh...
Because we really want to see you guys...
...pengen lihat semangat kalian!
...want to see your excitement!
Betul banget, ya enggak?
That's right, isn't it?
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
Don't make a typo, don't make a typo!
Asik, share ke semua oke?
Cool, share it with everyone, okay?
Jujur deh, kalian tuh pas dibilang kita bakal konser lho di Indonesia...
Be honest, when you were told we were going to have a concert in Indonesia...
...kalian pada kaget enggak sih?
...were you guys surprised?
Betul, aku setuju juga. Aku merasakan empati.
Correct, I agree too. I feel the empathy.
Aku juga waktu itu enggak nyangka banget kayak 'Hah? Beneran? Ini real nih?'
I also really didn't expect it at that time, like 'Huh? For real? Is this real?'
Kayak 'Loh? Bisa gitu?'
Like 'Whoa? It can be like that?'
Akhirnya mana udah bersembilan di Indonesia pula ya kan.
Finally, and all nine of us are in Indonesia too.
Ini kan konser pertama Hololive Indonesia yang bersembilan.
This is the first Hololive Indonesia concert with all nine members.
Sebenarnya tuh enggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar dan terpenting juga...
Actually, this isn't just the biggest and most important moment...
...untuk fans Hololive Indonesia...
...for Hololive Indonesia fans...
...tapi seluruh dunia juga pasti bakal nonton enggak sih?
...but the whole world will definitely be watching too, right?
Tentu aja, ini pencapaiannya enggak bakal cuma sampai di sini aja kan.
Of course, this achievement won't just stop here.
Jadi next-nya mungkin kita bisa apa ya...
So for the next one, maybe we can, what was it...
...dominating the world! Gitu!
...dominating the world! Like that!
We ready! We ready ready ready!
Selain dari dukungan fans in this opportunity...
Aside from the fans' support in this opportunity...
...kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih untuk semua sponsor yang mendukung...
...we also want to say thank you to all the sponsors who supported...
...terjadinya konser ini!
...the realization of this concert!
Terima kasih!
Thank you!
Eh, tapi ngomong-ngomong di konser ini kayaknya ada yang beda enggak sih?
Eh, but speaking of this concert, don't you think something is different?
Yang beda tuh kali ini model kita.
The difference is our models this time.
Model baru nih.
It's a new model.
Gemes banget!
So adorable!
Kameranya deketin ke aku.
Bring the camera closer to me.
Keimutan Kobo nih, nih, nih.
Kobo's cuteness, here, here, here.
Eh sini sini sini, ini kamera diambil Kobo semua enggak sih?
Eh here here here, Kobo is taking all the camera time, isn't she?
Aku juga! Aku juga! Jangan Kobo doang!
Me too! Me too! Not just Kobo!
Stop, stop, stop, stop! Mulai, mulai, mulai!
Stop, stop, stop, stop! Start, start, start!
Jangan berebutan di depan konser!
Don't fight in front of the concert!
Hmph, syukurin loh ya.
Hmph, serves you right.
Itu main adu desibel penonton.
That was an audience decibel battle.
Kobo pengen deh coba kita teriakin penonton, karena kan tadi mereka sudah teriakin kita.
I want us to try shouting at the audience, since they shouted at us earlier.
Iya, iya, iya.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maksudnya kita teriakin intro kita bareng penonton-tachi!
I mean we shout our intro together with the audience!
Betul!
Correct!
Teriaknya bareng penonton, jangan teriakin penontonnya.
Shout *with* the audience, don't shout *at* the audience.
Iya gitu maksudnya.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
Soalnya kan habis ini kita harus nyanyi...
Because after this we have to sing...
...jadi kita harus simpen suara dulu gak sih?
...so we should save our voices first, right?
Betul, ya.
That's right.
Gak bakal selama itu ternya... tenang aja, gak bakal selama durasi stream Kaela gitu ya guys ya.
It won't be that long... relax, it won't be as long as Kaela's stream duration, guys.
Ya udahlah, mau teriak-teriak ya udah...
Whatever, if you want to shout then fine...
...aku gak masalah lah, aku ngikut, aku ngikut.
...I don't have a problem with it, I'm in, I'm in.
Gimana nih semuanya? Udah siap belum?
How is it everyone? Are you ready yet?
Siap Kak!
Ready Sis!
Siap nih kayaknya. Oke?
They seem ready. Okay?
Kobo dulu ya.
Kobo first, okay.
Aku mau kita sama-sama teriak...
I want us to shout together...
BO-KO-BO-KO-BO!
Oke? Siap ya?
Okay? Ready?
Satu, dua, tiga!
One, two, three!
BO-KO-BO-KO-BO!
Suka suka!
Like it, like it!
Giliran Zeta, giliran Zeta.
Zeta's turn, Zeta's turn.
Aku aku? Oke oke oke oke.
Me, me? Okay okay okay okay.
Pas aku bilang "Mission Starto", kalian bareng-bareng teriak...
When I say "Mission Starto", you all shout together...
..."Starto" ya!
..."Starto", okay!
Siap? A-a-a... Mission...
Ready? A-a-a... Mission...
STARTO!
Oke, habis ini Kaela.
Okay, after this Kaela.
Oke oke oke oke.
Okay okay okay okay.
Nah ini ya, buat semua penonton sama HoloHero juga...
Alright, for all the audience and HoloHeroes too...
...kalau misalnya aku bilang "HoloHero!", kalian bilang "Hu Ha!"
...if I say "HoloHero!", you say "Hu Ha!"
Gampang kan? Langsung langsung langsung.
Easy right? Let's do it, let's do it.
Oke ya, siap ya?
Okay, ready?
HoloHero!
HU HA!
Mantap mantap mantap mantap.
Great, great, great, great.
Keren keren keren.
Cool cool cool.
Akhirnya Gen 3 kompak juga.
Finally Gen 3 is in sync too.
Kompak lah!
Of course we're in sync!
Iya kompak.
Yeah, in sync.
Kelihatannya masih pada semangat nih ya.
Seems like everyone is still energetic.
Soalnya dari lagu pertama kita hari ini aja udah kerasa banget.
Because even from our first song today, it felt really intense.
Kalian tuh pada nyangka gak sih kalau lagu pertama kita tuh bakal "100%"?
Did you guys expect that our first song would be "100%"?
Beuh, mana ada yang nyangka. Aku aja sendiri gak nyangka juga.
Beuh, no one expected it. Even I didn't expect it myself.
Langsung dibuka dengan Hoshino... famoed gitu.
Opened straight away with a Hoshino... Hoshinova mood.
Keren banget kan?
Really cool, right?
Asik, asik.
Cool, cool.
Keren banget sih. Apalagi tadi Zeta sama... Zeta sama nyanyi...
Really cool. Especially earlier Zeta and... Zeta and singing...
Zeta sama Kaela nyanyi "100%" tuh udah kayak real 100% ya.
Zeta and Kaela singing "100%" was like a real 100% performance.
Itu tuh bisa gak sih gak sekeren tadi?
Can you guys not be that cool?
Aku tuh jadi ingin kayak "ugh! ugh!" gitu kan.
I just wanted to go "ugh! ugh!" like that.
Kalian pernah gak sih nyanyi lagu sekeren tadi? Aura farming ya.
Have you guys ever sung a song as cool as that? True Aura farming.
Aura farming sesungguhnya.
The true aura farming.
Keren banget emang lagunya Moona.
Moona's song is indeed really cool.
Emang kan Zeta kan soalnya biasanya lagu-lagu yang stylish...
Right, because Zeta usually does stylish songs...
...yang jazzy-jazzy gitu.
...jazzy ones like that.
Jadi tadi pas dinyanyiin tuh ya, "100%", rasanya jadi beda banget vibesnya.
So when it was sung earlier, "100%", the vibes felt really different.
Terus Kaela juga...
Then Kaela also...
...tadi ngerap ya, "sttt sttt sttt"...
...rapped earlier, "sttt sttt sttt"...
...kayak... apa tuh?
...like... what was that?
Tatatata... tatatata...
Iya pokoknya keren banget!
Yeah, anyway it was really cool!
Keren banget ya tadi.
It was really cool earlier.
Tapi habis ini tuh masih ada lagi.
But after this there's still more.
New Zombie!
Ayo, pada tahu dong ini lagu siapa?
Come on, you surely know whose song this is?
Tau lah, tau lah.
Know it, know it.
Senpai kita, senpai kita.
Our senpai, our senpai.
Iya tadi...
Yeah earlier...
Tadi tuh itu ya, HoloRo tuh performnya juga keren banget, kayak lagi di game gitu.
Earlier HoloRo's performance was also really cool, like being in a game.
Betul, setuju.
Correct, agreed.
Terus tadi ada back dancernya men.
And there were back dancers, man.
Keren gak guys? Keren gak?
Cool right guys? Cool right?
Keren!
Cool!
Ada apa lagi tuh tadi? Lampu laser...
What else was there earlier? Laser lights...
...terus ada efek kembang api segala.
...and there were firework effects and everything.
Terus, banyaklah ya gimik-gimik yang wow.
Plus, there were lots of gimmicks that were wow.
Itu back dancer nanti aku hire semua ya buat solo konser aku.
I'll hire all those back dancers later for my solo concert.
Wah, udah ngomong konser solo aja.
Wow, already talking about a solo concert.
Omongan adalah doa ya.
Words are prayers, yeah.
Iya, amin.
Yes, amen.
Tapi konser yang ini belum selesai.
But this concert isn't over yet.
Belum, belum, belum.
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
Eh, tapi kalian tahu gak sih sebelum ini tuh nyanyinya lagu apa?
Eh, but do you guys know what song was sung before this?
Eits, aku mah tahu banget lah.
Eits, I definitely know that.
Itu lagu terbaru aku.
That's my newest song.
Dahlah.
Whatever [Dahlah].
Iya.
Yeah.
Udahlah.
Whatever.
Gak usah dibahas.
Don't need to discuss it.
Dahlah.
Whatever.
Loh, kok gitu? Itu tuh maksudnya judulnya "Dahlah".
Wait, why like that? The title really is "Dahlah".
Lagunya judulnya "Dahlah".
The song's title is "Dahlah".
Oh... "Dahlah".
Iya iya iya, oh "Dahlah".
Yeah yeah yeah, oh "Dahlah".
Bilang dong.
You should've said so.
Abisnya kamu kan sering "dahlah, dahlah" gitu.
Because you often say "dahlah, dahlah" like that.
Jadi kirain emang beneran "dahlah".
So I thought it was really just "dahlah" [giving up].
Entar "Dahlah, dahlah", pulang dia.
If you say "Dahlah, dahlah", she'll go home.
Pulang nanti. Jangan, jangan.
Going home later. Don't, don't.
Kalau gitu "Dahlah" tuh maksudnya apa sih?
In that case, what does "Dahlah" mean?
"Dahlah" sama kehidupan.
"Dahlah" [Done] with life.
Hidup tuh berat ya guys ya.
Life is heavy, guys.
Kalau hidup berat, ya udah, "dahlah" aja.
If life is heavy, well, just say "dahlah".
Habis itu lanjutkan hidupmu.
After that continue your life.
Begitu.
That's it.
Iya betul, teman-teman.
Yes that's right, friends.
Di kehidupan yang dewasa ini...
In this adult life...
Jadi kita sambil keliling-liling kan nyapa fans gitu ya.
So we walked around while greeting the fans, right?
Asik banget ya tadi ya?
It was really fun earlier, right?
Aku juga suka banget tadi ada sebagian reff-nya ya.
I also really liked that there was part of the refrain earlier.
Da la da la da la da la...
Itu... Itu beda lagu gak sih?
That... isn't that a different song?
Ih gak gitu deh. Gak gitu kek.
Eh, not like that. Not like that, man.
Ya tapi pokoknya asik lah ya kalau nyanyi lagu chill santai-santai kayak gini.
Yeah but anyway it's fun to sing a chill song, relaxing like this.
Iya santai dong.
Yeah, relax of course.
Tapi... ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenernya belum bisa santai dulu. Heh, santai!
But... speaking of relaxing, we actually can't relax yet. Hey, relax!
Hehe, karena... kayaknya katanya gak boleh santai terus.
Hehe, because... it seems they said we can't keep relaxing.
Iya iya iya jangan santai-santai. Jangan terlalu santai.
Yeah yeah yeah don't relax. Don't be too relaxed.
Karena konsernya tuh masih panjang.
Because the concert is still long.
Jadi, sebelum itu, kalian ada gak yang mau kalian sampein dulu? Mulai dari ini nih yang gak bisa diem.
So, before that, is there anything you want to convey first? Starting from this one who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja.
Just three words.
I love you.
Keren.
Cool.
The best.
Sangat jelas ya.
Very clear, yes.
Tetap semangat. Tetap semangat menjalani hidup ya.
Stay spirited. Stay spirited in living life, okay.
Udah gitu aja. Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang. Semangat!
That's all. Anyway until the end it's still long. Spirit!
Sarangheyo~
I love you~
Gak mau yooo.
I don't want to yooo.
Oke kalau aku... Yah... Semangat selalu.
Okay if it's me... Well... Spirit always.
Semangat santai.
Relaxed spirit.
Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai ya?
Relaxed spirit huh?
Semangat santai.
Relaxed spirit.
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjut gak? Kita...
Okay in that case shall we continue? We...
Weits weits weits tunggu dulu.
Wait wait wait hold on.
Sebelum selesai... selesai ini nih ya... kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu gak sih?
Before finishing... finishing this part... shouldn't we shout together with the audience first?
Iya dong. Ayo ayo ayo!
Yes of course. Come on come on!
Oke oke. Jadi... kita teriak bareng ya. Dalam hitungan tiga.
Okay okay. So... let's shout together. In the count of three.
Kita sama-sama teriak Chromatic Future. Oke ya?
We shout Chromatic Future together. Okay?
Oke oke. Chromatic Future. Gitu kan ya?
Okay okay. Chromatic Future. Like that right?
Iya iya kayak gitu. Oke langsung ya. Sambil lihat sini sini sini. Sambil lihat.
Yeah yeah like that. Okay straight away. While looking here here here. While looking.
Aku ya aku... aku yang penonton ini nih.
Me, yes me... I'm the audience here.
Iya iya. Aku... aku ini deh, yang tengah yang tengah. Halo!
Yeah yeah. I... I'll be this one, the one in the middle. Hello!
Oke bareng-bareng ya. Satu, dua, tiga!
Okay together. One, two, three!
Chromatic Future!
Everything was easy, I did it all alone.
So effortlessly, I spread my wings and let my magic unfold.
Got all problems solved without any setbacks there is nothing uncontrolled.
But there's no way I can begin, dream life that I need to win.
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces.
I know I gotta soar a little higher.
Hope all turns to be the things I desire.
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap.
Like a winged peacock.
Kan ku taklukan gelap.
I will conquer the darkness.
Dengan sihir angin kan ku ajak.
With wind magic I will invite.
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit melawan dunia.
Everyone asleep to rise and fight the world.
We'll never give up.
As long as we got the strength in ourselves.
We could rise above the pain.
Walking step by step, trusting my own pace.
Giving me what I deserve to have.
Let it go! (Just believe me!)
They'll never bring me down, just believe me.
It'll never bring us down, just believe me.
Let it go! Won't let their cruelty stealin' my royalty.
And when the universe works against me I will just... Let it go!
If it's spicy, just sip some tea, let it go.
Let it go!
I've been living carefree.
There's no bitter words in the world that could affect me.
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold.
Not letting it show.
Stings but I'm bigger than my feelings so that will be enough.
There is no way I can begin, dream life that I need to win.
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces.
I know I gotta be better than ever.
Hope all turns to be sweeter than ever.
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap.
Like a winged peacock.
Kan ku taklukan gelap.
I will conquer the darkness.
Dengan sihir angin kan ku ajak.
With wind magic I will invite.
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves,
We could rise above the pain.
We're stronger than before.
Walking step by step,
trusting by our faith.
Giving me what I deserve to have.
Let's go!
Just believe me.
Let it go!
They'll never bring me down, just believe me.
It'll never bring us down, just believe me.
Won't let their cruelty
steal my royalty.
And when the universe works against me I will just...
Let it go!
Come on guys, know how to do this!
One, two, three, let it go!
Let it go...
hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE
Acrylic Panel
Acrylic Stand
Holographic Button Badge
Lanyard & Ticket Holder
T-shirt