(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
supported by Pocky ACL
Ayunda Risu
Kureiji Ollie
Vestia Zeta
Moona Hoshinova
Anya Melfissa
Kaela Kovalskia
Airani Iofifteen
Pavolia Reine
Kobo Kanaeru
TERIMA KASIH!
THANK YOU!
BERKAT KALIAN, KAMI BISA BERSINAR. BERIBU-RIBU TERIMA KASIH
THANKS TO YOU, WE CAN SHINE. THOUSANDS OF THANK YOUS
TERIMA KASIH UDAH BIKIN STAGE INI & HIDUP KAMI LEBIH BERWARNA!
THANK YOU FOR MAKING THIS STAGE & OUR LIVES MORE COLORFUL!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank you!!
TERIMA KASIH BANYAK!!!!!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!!!!!
Terima Kasih!! Kalian Semua Keren BGT!!
Thank you!! You guys are super cool!!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank you!!
Makasih ya!!
Thanks!!
terima kasih
thank you
Ayo mulai!!
Let's start!!
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も
Body and soul
この手でMake you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine
Oh baby I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby I need you, I need you forever
君を見るたびに
Every time I look at you
上書きされていく欲望に
In this ever-overwriting desire
重なる eyes, eyes, eyes
Our eyes meet, eyes, eyes
夢中すぎる smile, smile, smile
Infatuated with that smile, smile, smile
ねぇ その姿形
Hey, your appearance and form
全てが拍車かけていく
Everything is spurring it on
恋から 愛、愛、愛
From a crush to love, love, love
毎秒 可笑しくなっていく
Every second, I'm going crazy
手を伸ばせば届く距離
Within reach if I stretch my hand
1mm単位で確かめたい
I want to confirm every millimeter
穏やかに恋したい
I want to love you peacefully
どんなシーンも私に見せて
Show me every scene
このまま Stay by my side
Stay by my side just like this
どこにも行かないでね
Don't go anywhere, okay?
あぁ 100%
Ah, 100 percent
純粋な愛だから
Because it's pure love
止められない感情
Unstoppable emotions
その腕で抱きしめてよ
Hold me tight in those arms
ずっと 離さない
I'll never let go
ずっと もっと 近くで
Forever, even closer
認め合いたい
I want us to accept each other
狂おしいほど求めてるだけなら
If I'm just seeking you so madly...
Hey, tell me what's wrong with me
名前もない普通だし
I'm just a nameless ordinary person
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you right now
最初は声を聞く
At first, just hearing your voice
それだけで良かった
That alone was enough
だけど次第に
But gradually
我儘になった
I became selfish
誰かに笑いかけ
Smiling at someone else
その仕草に苛立ち隠せない
I can't hide my irritation at that gesture
自分に気付いた
I noticed myself
独り占めしたい
I want to have you all to myself
いっそ鎖に繋いで
Might as well tie you with chains
二人きりの部屋至近距離
In a room with just the two of us, close distance
強引な発言阻止したい
I want to stop those pushy remarks
思い出で眠りたい
I want to sleep in memories
鋭い吐息感じさせて
Let me feel your sharp breath
永遠に Stay by your side
Forever by your side
どこにも行かせない
I won't let you go anywhere
あぁ 100%
Ah, 100 percent
私だけに依存してね
Please be dependent only on me
いいでしょう？
Is that okay?
響き合う合図
Signs echoing each other
丸ごと受け止めてよ
Accept all of me
あぁ 私たちなら
Ah, if it's us
例えとしても息ができない
Even as a metaphor, I can't breathe
行かせてよ
Let me go
狂おしいほど 止めさせない絶対
So madly, I'll never let it stop
Hey, tell me what's wrong with me
名前もない普通だし
I'm just a nameless ordinary person
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you right now
目を閉じたら 止められない I can... 触れたい
If I close my eyes, I can't stop, I can... want to touch you
Oh you! 私の声だけ
Oh you! Only my voice
このまま Stay by my side
Stay by my side just like this
二度と離れないで
Don't ever leave again
あぁ 100% 純粋な愛だから
Ah, because it's 100 percent pure love
BPM... 揺れ動く感情
BPM... shaking emotions.
そっと抱きしめてよ
Please hold me gently.
遠くからじゃなく
Not from afar,
ずっともっと近くで 認め合いたい
but always closer, wanting to acknowledge each other.
溢れる衝動 モテあますだけなら ストップ
If you just have too much overflowing impulse, stop.
Tell me what's wrong with me
何も問題ない振出し
Starting over with no problems.
Right here 意味など全部知りたい
Right here, I want to know all the meanings.
I need you 今すぐ
I need you right now.
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby, I need you, I need you always.
見逃すな 今だ 勝利を願っちゃって
Don't miss it, now is the time, wish for victory.
ハッピークレイジー！ This is Hololive!
Happy Crazy! This is Hololive!
Let's go together!
ある意味普通じゃないさ You know?
In a sense, it's not normal, you know?
鳴り止まない 15 minutes
Doesn't stop ringing, 15 minutes.
目覚めたら 走る 先にほら
When you wake up, run ahead, look.
誰か Just scanning
Someone is just scanning.
A-N-Y-A standby now!
正直飽き飽きなんだよ
Honestly, I'm getting sick of it.
回る 残酷 私には血の味ね
Spinning cruel, to me it's the taste of blood.
分単位 常に挑戦って
Every minute is always a challenge.
招き猫 山と P20
Manekineko mountain and P20.
Good luck 祈る 幸運なんかより
Better than wishing for good luck,
出し切る 実力
I'll give it all, my real power.
Day by day 初出し あらあら
Day by day, first release, oh my.
言ったこと全部 ピンを指した
Everything said hit the mark.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's okay to laugh.
止められない プレーヤーぶっ壊して
Unstoppable, break the player.
Victory to the world, yeah
手を伸ばす感度 上げていくはずよ
Stretching out my hand, the sensitivity should be increasing.
見て、見て、今日の地位 いらっしゃって
Look, look, welcome to today's status.
乱数 並べた 誤算 ステップ
Random numbers lined up, calculation error step.
追いすぎる 外周の上 航路はどこへ？
Over-chasing, above the outer circumference, where is the route?
拾い上げた One kill かっさらう
Picked up a one-kill, snatch it away.
私を強くしてくわ
It makes me stronger.
ポジショニング 高所から 覗かれるのは癪ね
Positioning, being peered at from a high place is irritating.
警戒 1-2-3 死ぬのは嫌で Trip to Trip
Vigilance 1-2-3, I hate dying, trip to trip.
気が付いたら Long treatment
If I notice, a long treatment.
あれれ 隠れて 頂け
Oh? Please hide.
Knight and night fight 奏でる ならば
Knight and night fight, if played,
邪魔は全部キャンセル
all obstacles are canceled.
出してよ 止めないさ これが私の
Let it out, I won't stop, this is my...
チャンピオンになる 知らずにね
Becoming a champion, without knowing.
Victory to the world, set!
共につかみ叩きたいんだ
I want to grab and strike together
吐き出した言葉を
the words spat out.
心地いい 今日の君 染まっちゃって
Feels good, today's you, get stained.
HoloID Chromatic Future! Ayo nyanyi bareng!
HoloID Chromatic Future! Let's sing together!
Ayo nyanyi juga! Ayo mana suaranya!
Sing too! Come on, let me hear your voices!
BPM 走っちゃって
BPM running.
Hey I am 触れないで
Hey I am, don't touch me.
Day by day もがいても まだまだ
Day by day, even if I struggle, not yet.
降り出した シニカル オート取って
Started falling, cynical, take the auto.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's okay to laugh,
みんな いつか チャンピオンを目指すだけ
everyone will eventually just aim for the champion.
Victory to the world, set!
絶対 追い抜くよ あの光で 軌道を
Surely overtaking, with that light, the orbit.
忘れられないほどの 勝利を願っちゃって
Wishing for a victory so great it can't be forgotten.
境地へ行こう Z-I-G-G-Y
Let's go to the state of Z-I-G-G-Y.
(Sigh)
Siapa di sini yang lelah dengan kehidupan?
Who here is tired of life?
Aku, aku!
Me, me!
Kalau capek enaknya gimana nih, HoloHero?
If you're tired, what's a good way to relax, HoloHero?
Dalas saja!
Just deal with it!
Cakep!
Great!
Bukannya sudah biasa
Isn't it already usual
Ditikam oleh kecewa
to be stabbed by disappointment?
(Aduh!)
(Ouch!)
...saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya. Oh oh.
...when the world doesn't go as it should. Oh oh.
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya kau coba lepaskan saja.
Maybe it's time you just try to let go.
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi.
No need to ask why anymore.
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan.
If indeed you don't get the answer.
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui teka-tekinya.
Don't cry, try to get through its puzzle.
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya...
Let it go because in the end...
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira.
You are stronger than you think.
Dah lah saja. Oh dah lah saja.
Just let it be. Oh just let it be.
Jalani saja.
Just live it.
Dah lah saja. Oh dah lah saja.
Just let it be. Oh just let it be.
Jalani saja.
Just live it.
Mau gimana lagi. Walau kadang mati rasa.
What can you do. Even though sometimes you feel numb.
Bahkan hingga tak berdaya.
Even to the point of being helpless.
Dan usahamu terasa sia-sia.
And your efforts feel in vain.
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan.
If indeed you don't get the answer.
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui teka-tekinya.
Don't cry, try to get through its puzzle.
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya...
Let it go because in the end...
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira.
You are stronger than you think.
Lepas semua kendali.
Release all control.
Tancap gas dan berlari.
Step on the gas and run.
Terima dan sudahi.
Accept and end it.
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan.
If indeed you don't get the answer.
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui teka-tekinya.
Don't cry, try to get through its puzzle.
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya...
Let it go because in the end...
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira.
You are stronger than you think.
Dah lah saja. Oh dah lah saja.
Just let it be. Oh just let it be.
Jalani saja.
Just live it.
Dah lah saja. Oh dah lah saja.
Just let it be. Oh just let it be.
Jalani saja.
Just live it.
Halo Comic Frontier!
Hello Comic Frontier!
Halo!
Hello!
Selamat datang di hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary Live Chromatic Future!
Welcome to hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary Live Chromatic Future!
Yay!
Wah, gila gila gila!
Wow, crazy crazy crazy!
Makasih banyak semuanya udah pada datang ke konser 5 tahun kita ya!
Thank you so much everyone for coming to our 5th year concert!
Wah, gak berasa nggak sih udah 5 tahun aja?
Wow, doesn't it feel like it's been 5 years already?
Kalau gitu kita mulai dari perkenalan diri dulu nggak sih?
In that case, shall we start with self-introductions?
Mulai dari aku, aku!
Starting from me, me!
Oke oke oke.
Okay okay okay.
A... Mission! Start!
Teto! Teto!
Aku Vestia Zeta dari hololive Indonesia Gen 3, nice to meet you!
I'm Vestia Zeta from hololive Indonesia Gen 3, nice to meet you!
Yay! Nice to meet you too Zeta!
Oke, next Kaela!
Okay, next Kaela!
Oke oke oke. Kaelog grinding every time, the blacksmith from holoID Gen 3.
Okay okay okay. Kaelog grinding every time, the blacksmith from holoID Gen 3.
I'm Kaela Kovalskia, nice to meet you all!
Yay! Nice to meet you Kaela!
Next, next, next! Kobo Kobo Kobo!
Hi! Bokobokoboko, Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day. Ehehe!
Kobo-kan! Mana suaranya?!
Kobo-kan! Where's your voice?!
Nah, bertiga kami dari hololive Indonesia Gen 3!
So, the three of us are from hololive Indonesia Gen 3!
Halo! Halo!
Hello! Hello!
Wah, nggak nyangka juga deh konser 5th Anniversary hololive ID ini akhirnya ada juga.
Wow, I didn't expect this hololive ID 5th Anniversary concert to finally happen.
Dari lagu pertama saja sudah keren banget guys, kerasa nggak sih?
From the first song it's already so cool guys, do you feel it?
Kasi semangatnya!
Give us some energy!
Iya nggak sih? Iya nggak sih?
Right? Don't you think so?
Sikat!
Let's go!
Parah sih ini ada adrenalin rush kan ya?
This is insane, there's an adrenaline rush, right?
Pengen lari aku rasanya nih!
I feel like running!
Woi woi woi... mau kemana?
Hey hey hey... where are you going?
Stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop.
Nanti keringetan lho, nanti keringetan.
You'll get all sweaty later.
Kak Kaela gimana?
How about you, Kaela?
Aduh, seru banget.
Gosh, it's so much fun.
Aku nggak nyangka sih sampai aku bisa ada di sini ya.
I didn't expect to be able to be here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong konser-nya masih panjang banget.
But by the way, this concert is still long.
Jadi kalian tetap semangat ya sampai akhir!
So stay energized until the end!
Sampai akhir! Semangat semangat semangat!
Until the end! Energy, energy, energy!
Eh tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi,
But since we've been talking about the concert,
emang pada tahu judul konsernya apa?
does everyone know the title of the concert?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah Chromatic Future!
The title of our concert this time is Chromatic Future!
Ada yang tahu nggak artinya apa? Ayo absen!
Does anyone know what it means? Let's check!
Nah ini, Kobo paling tahu.
Well, Kobo knows best.
Yang jelasin yang paling tinggi. Yuk, let's go!
The tallest one should explain. Come on, let's go!
Segitu ya... ya udahlah ya udah ya udah...
Oh, that's how it is... okay then...
Nih ya guys ya buat kalian yang belum tahu,
Listen up, guys, for those who don't know yet,
Chromatic Future itu artinya tuh masa depan yang berwarna-warni.
Chromatic Future means a colorful future.
Jadi karena Hololive Indonesia kan udah 5 tahun nih,
So, since Hololive Indonesia has been around for 5 years,
kita sama-sama dari hari pertama sampai sekarang.
we've been together from day one until now.
Nah, jadi tuh untuk ke depannya kita tuh juga harapannya tuh
So for the future, our hope is that
kita bisa nyiptain waktu dan memori yang berwarna-warni
we can create colorful times and memories
sama seluruh fans dari Hololive Indonesia.
together with all the fans of Hololive Indonesia.
Iya gitu! Betul Kaela Kovalskia! Betul betul betul!
That's it! Correct, Kaela Kovalskia! Correct!
Nah, kalian sekarang udah pada tahu kan
Now, you all know already,
karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
since Kaela just explained it.
Kalau gitu konsernya kan udah mulai nih.
In that case, the concert has already started.
Kalian mau nge-post soal konser ini di medsos?
Do you want to post about this concert on social media?
Jangan lupa hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture ya!
Don't forget the hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture!
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh...
Because we really want to see you...
Pengen lihat semangat kalian!
We want to see your spirit!
Iya, itu! Betul banget, iya nggak?
Yes, that's it! Exactly, right?
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
No typos, no typos!
Asik, share ke semua! Oke?
Cool, share it with everyone! Okay?
Tapi jujur deh kalian tuh pas dibilang
But honestly, when you were told
kita bakal konser lho di Indonesia,
that we would have a concert in Indonesia,
kalian pada kaget nggak sih?
were you guys surprised?
Halo? Didengerin?
Hello? Are you listening?
Betul! Aku setuju juga.
Correct! I agree as well.
Aku merasakan empati terhadap adik saya Zeta.
I feel empathy for my sister Zeta.
Empati... iya iya. Kalau Kaela gimana?
Empathy... yes. How about you, Kaela?
Aku juga waktu itu nggak nyangka banget kayak 'hah, beneran?'
I also really didn't expect it, like 'huh, really?'
'Ini real nih?' gitu kan? Kayak 'loh, bisa gitu akhirnya?'
'Is this real?' right? Like 'how could this happen?'
Mana udah bersembilan di Indonesia pula ya kan?
And with all nine of us in Indonesia too, right?
Keren banget! Keren banget!
So cool! So cool!
Ini kan konser pertama Hololive Indonesia yang bersembilan.
This is the first Hololive Indonesia concert with nine members.
Sebenarnya tuh nggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar
Actually, this is not just the biggest moment
dan terpenting juga untuk fans Hololive Indonesia,
and most important for Hololive Indonesia fans,
tapi seluruh dunia juga pasti bakal nonton nggak sih?
but the whole world will definitely be watching, right?
Iya nggak? Jawab! Iya iya, makasih semuanya.
Right? Answer! Yes, thank you everyone.
Tapi tentu aja ini pencapaiannya nggak bakal cuma sampai di sini.
But of course, this achievement won't just stop here.
Jadi selanjutnya mungkin kita bisa apa ya...
So next, maybe we can...
Dominating the world! Gitu!
Dominate the world! Like that!
We're ready!
Ready ready! Betul banget Kaela, Zeta.
Ready ready! Exactly, Kaela, Zeta.
Selain dari dukungan fans in this opportunity,
Aside from the support of fans in this opportunity,
kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih
we also want to say thank you
untuk semua sponsor yang mendukung terjadinya konser ini.
to all the sponsors who made this concert possible.
Makasih semuanya! Thank you thank you!
Thank you everyone! Thank you thank you!
Eh tapi ngomong-ngomong di konser ini kayaknya ada yang beda.
But by the way, there seems to be something different.
Hmm, Ela kamu sadar nggak?
Hmm, Ela, do you notice?
Soalnya kamu paling peka nggak sih?
Because you're the most sensitive, aren't you?
Wait, iya sadarlah.
Wait, of course I notice.
Kalau Kobo mah nggak bakal sadar.
Kobo wouldn't notice.
Nih nih nih nih. Yang beda tuh kali ini tuh model kita!
This is it. What's different is our models!
Ini model baru nih!
These are new models!
Ooh! Iya iya lucu lucu! Gemas banget!
Ooh! Yeah, so cute! So adorable!
Lucu lucu lucu! Kameranya deketin ke aku!
So cute! Bring the camera closer to me!
Kamera deketin ke aku!
Bring the camera closer to me!
Kak imutan Kobo nih nih nih nih.
Kobo is cuter, look look look.
Oshiri...
My butt...
Kamera deketin Kobo lagi!
Bring the camera close to Kobo again!
Stop stop stop stop stop stop stop!
Mulai mulai mulai! Semua kamera diambil!
It's starting! She's hogging all the cameras!
Oke oke oke, kalau gitu... aduh sampai kehabisan napas.
Okay okay, in that case... gosh, I'm out of breath.
Jangan rebutan di depan konser!
Don't fight in front of the concert!
Iya iya iya!
Yes yes yes!
えっ、やだで。
Eee, okay then...
Kalau... nggak boleh...
If... you can't...
...rebutan Kobo sama Zeta...
...fight over Kobo and Zeta...
...hmmm, ya udah deh kita main aja deh sama penonton.
...hmmm, okay then, let's just play with the audience.
Kobo pengen deh coba kita teriakin penonton,
Kobo wants to try shouting at the audience,
karena kan tadi mereka udah teriakin kita.
because they were shouting at us earlier.
Iya iya iya... maksudnya kita teriakin ini... bareng penonton-tachi.
Yeah, yeah, yeah... I mean, we'll shout this... together with the audience-tachi.
Betul! Teriakin bareng penonton, jangan teriakin penontonnya.
Correct! Shout together with the audience, don't shout at them.
Iya gitu maksudnya.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
Soalnya kan habis ini kita harus nyanyi,
Because after this we have to sing,
jadi kita harus simpen suara dulu nggak sih?
so we should save our voices first, right?
Betul ya. Gak bakal lama itu ternyata...
Right. It won't be that long...
Tenang aja nggak bakal selama durasi stream Kaela ya guys ya.
Don't worry, it won't be as long as Kaela's stream duration, guys.
Eee, ya udahlah... mau teriak-teriak? Ya udah aku nggak masalah deh, aku ikut.
Eee, alright then... want to shout? I don't mind, I'll join.
Gimana nih semuanya? Udah siap belum?
How about it, everyone? Are you ready?
Siap nih kayaknya. Oke, Kobo dulu ya.
Seems like they're ready. Okay, Kobo first.
Aku mau kita sama-sama teriak 'Baka baka baka!'
I want us to shout 'Baka baka baka!' together.
Oke, siap ya!
Okay, ready?
Satu, dua, tiga...
One, two, three...
BAKA BAKA BAKA!
Suka suka! Giliran Zeta, giliran Zeta.
Suka suka! Zeta's turn, Zeta's turn.
Oke oke oke.
Okay, okay, okay.
Pas aku bilang 'Mission Stasto', kalian bareng-bareng teriak 'Stasto' ya.
When I say 'Mission Stasto', you all shout 'Stasto' together.
Siap?
Ready?
A-A-A... Mission...
STASTO!
Oke, habis ini Kaela.
Okay, next is Kaela.
Oke oke oke... nah apa ya... buat semua penonton sama HoloHeroes juga...
Okay, okay, okay... well... for all the audience and HoloHeroes too...
Kalau misalnya aku bilang 'HoloHeroes', kalian bilang 'Hoo-Hah!' Gampang kan?
If I say 'HoloHeroes', you say 'Hoo-Hah!' Simple, right?
Langsung langsung langsung... oke ya? Siap ya?
Straight away... okay? Ready?
HoloHeroes!
HOO-HAH!
Mantap mantap mantap!
Keren keren keren. Akhirnya Gen 3 kompak juga.
Cool, cool, cool. Finally, Gen 3 is in sync too.
Iya, kompak kelihatannya. Masih pada semangat nih ya.
Yeah, looks in sync. Everyone's still spirited, right?
Soalnya dari lagu pertama kita hari ini aja udah kerasa banget.
Because it was already very apparent from our first song today.
Kalian tuh pada nyangka nggak sih kalau lagu pertama kita tuh bakal '100%'?
Did you guys expect our first song would be '100%'?
Beh, mana ada yang nyangka. Aku aja sendiri nggak nyangka juga.
Psh, who would've thought. Even I didn't expect it.
Langsung dibuka dengan 'Hoshinova Mode' gitu. Keren banget kan?
Starting right off with 'Hoshinova Mode' like that. So cool, right?
Kece banget sih... apalagi tadi Zeta sama Kaela nyanyi '100%'
It was so cool... especially when Zeta and Kaela sang '100%'
...tuh udah kayak real 100% ya.
...it was like real 100%.
Itu tuh bisa nggak sih... nggak sekeren tadi?
Is it even possible... to not be as cool as that?
Aku tuh jadi pengen kayak... 'ugh, ugh' gitu kan kalian?
I just wanted to go... 'ugh, ugh', you know?
Kalian pernah nggak sih nyanyi lagu sekeren tadi? Aura farming ya...
Have you guys ever sung a song as cool as that? Truly aura farming...
Aura farming sesungguhnya. Keren banget emang lagunya Moona.
The ultimate aura farming. Moona's song is indeed very cool.
Emang kan Zeta kan soalnya biasanya lagu-lagu yang stylish, yang jazzy jazzy gitu...
Because Zeta usually sings stylish, jazzy songs...
Jadi tadi pas dinyanyiin tuh ya '100%' rasanya jadi beda banget vibes-nya.
So when she sang '100%', the vibes felt completely different.
Terus Kaela juga tadi ngerap ya... 'ta-da-da-da-da-da-da'... kayak apa tuh?
Then Kaela was rapping too... 'ta-da-da-da-da-da-da'... like what was that?
Ta-da-da-da-da-da-da... iya pokoknya keren banget tadi.
Ta-da-da-da-da-da-da... yeah, it was just so cool.
Keren banget ya tadi... tapi habis ini tuh masih ada lagi... 'New Zombie'.
It was so cool... but after this, there's even more... 'New Zombie'.
Ayo, pada tahu dong ini lagu siapa?
Come on, you guys know whose song this is, right?
Tahu lah, tahu lah... Senpai kita, Senpai kita.
Of course, of course... our Senpai's, our Senpai's.
Tadi tuh itu ya... Holoro performance-nya juga keren banget, kayak lagi di game gitu.
Earlier... the Holoro performance was also so cool, like being in a game.
Betul! Setuju. Terus tadi ada backdancer-nya, men!
Correct! Agreed. And there were backdancers, man!
Keren ya guys, keren nggak?
Cool, right guys? Wasn't it cool?
Keren!
Cool!
Ada apa lagi tuh tadi? Lampu laser, terus ada efek kembang api segara...
What else was there? Laser lights, then firework effects and all...
...terus banyak lah gimmick-gimmick yang wow.
...and many wow gimmicks.
Itu backdancer-nya nanti aku hire semua ya buat solo konser aku.
I'm going to hire all those backdancers for my solo concert later.
Wah, udah ngomong konser solo aja.
Whoa, talking about a solo concert already.
Ini omongan adalah doa ya.
Words are prayers, you know.
Iya... tapi konser yang ini belum selesai... belum belum belum.
Yeah... but this concert isn't over yet... not yet, not yet.
Eh, tapi kalian tahu nggak sih sebelum ini tuh nyanyinya lagu apa?
Eh, but do you guys know what song was sung before this?
Eh, aku mah tahu banget lah. Itu lagu terbaru aku... Dalah.
Eh, I know very well. It's my newest song... Dalah.
Iya, udah... nggak usah dibahas... dalah...
Yeah, fine... no need to discuss it... dalah...
Loh kok gitu? Itu tuh maksudnya judulnya 'Dalah', lagunya judulnya 'Dalah'.
Hey, why like that? I meant the title is 'Dalah', the song title is 'Dalah'.
Oooo... iya iya iya... oalah...
Oooo... right, right, right... oalah...
Dalah... bilang dong... abisnya kan kamu sering 'dalah, dalah' gitu...
'Dalah'... say so... because you often say 'dalah, dalah' like that...
Jadi dikirain emang beneran 'dalah'...
So I thought it was just the usual 'dalah'...
Entar 'dalah dalah' pulang dia... kasihan jangan dalah.
She might just say 'dalah dalah' and go home... poor thing, don't say 'dalah'.
Kalau gitu 'Dalah' tuh maksudnya apa sih?
Then what does 'Dalah' actually mean?
'Dalah' sama kehidupan... hidup tuh berat ya guys ya...
'Dalah' with life... life is hard, you know guys...
Kalau hidup berat ya udah 'dalah' aja, abis itu lanjutkan hidupmu, begitu.
If life is hard, just say 'dalah', then continue with your life, like that.
Iya betul teman-teman... di kehidupan yang dewasa ini ya...
Yeah, that's right friends... in this adult life...
Untung lagunya santai, easy listening,
Luckily the song was chill, easy listening,
jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan, nyapa fans, gitu ya.
so we could walk around and greet the fans, right?
Asik banget ya tadi ya,
It was so fun,
aku juga suka banget tadi di sebagian rap-nya ya.
I really liked the rap part earlier.
Da la da la da la da la...
Itu, itu beda lagu gak sih?
Wait, isn't that a different song?
...da la da la da la da la.
Enggak gitu, Bocil. Gak gitu, Bocil.
Not like that, kiddo. Not like that, kiddo.
Ya, tapi pokoknya asik lah ya kalau nyanyi lagu yang chill, santai-santai kayak gini.
But anyway, it's fun to sing chill, relaxed songs like this.
Iya, santai dong.
Yeah, chill for sure.
Tapi ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu.
But speaking of chill, we actually can't chill just yet.
Heh, santai.
Hey, chill out.
Karena katanya gak boleh santai...
Because you said we can't chill...
Iya, iya, jangan santai-santai. Jangan terlalu santai.
Yeah, yeah, don't chill. Don't be too relaxed.
Karena konser itu masih panjaaaaang.
Because the concert is still loooooooong.
Jadi sebelum itu, kalian ada nggak yang mau kalian sampaikan dulu? Mulai dari ini nih yang enggak bisa diem.
So before that, is there anything you'd like to say? Let's start with this one who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja...
Just three words...
I love you.
Keren, the best. Sangat jelas ya.
Cool, the best. Very clear.
Tetap semangat.
Keep up the spirit.
Tetap semangat menjalani hidup ya.
Keep your spirit up in life.
Udah gitu aja. Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang. Semangat!
That's it. Anyway, it's still a long way to the end. Fighting!
Saranghaeyo!
I love you!
Gomawoyo!
Thank you!
Oke, kalau aku, ya, semangat selalu.
Okay, for me, well, always keep up the spirit.
Semangat santai.
Chill spirit.
Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai!
Chill spirit!
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjut ke... wait wait wait.
Okay then, let's move on to... wait wait wait.
Tunggu dulu. Sebelum selesai-selesai ini nih ya,
Hold on. Before we wrap this up,
kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu nggak sih?
should we shout together with the audience?
Iya dong! Ayo ayo ayo!
Of course! Let's go, let's go!
Oke oke. Jadi kita teriak bareng ya.
Okay, okay. So let's shout together.
Dalam hitungan ketiga, kita sama-sama teriak 'Chromatic Future'. Oke ya?
On the count of three, we'll all shout 'Chromatic Future' together. Okay?
Oke oke, 'Chromatic Future' gitu kan?
Okay okay, 'Chromatic Future' like that, right?
Iya iya kayak gitu.
Yeah, like that.
Oke langsung ya sambil lihat sini sini sini.
Okay, right away, while looking here, here, here.
Aku ya, aku penonton yang ini. Penonton sini nih.
Me, I'm for this audience. This audience right here.
Aku ini deh yang tengah, yang tengah. Halo!
I'll take the middle one then. Hello!
Oke bareng-bareng ya.
Okay, together now.
Satu, dua, tiga...
One, two, three...
Chromatic Future!
Everything was easy
I did it all alone
So effortlessly
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Got all problems solved
Without any setbacks there is nothing uncontrolled
There's no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta soar a little higher
Hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a winged peacock
Kan ku taklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With wind magic I'll invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit
All those who sleep to rise
Melawan dunia
Against the world
We'll never give up
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise up above the pain
We're stronger than that
Walking step by step, trusting my pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go
Just believe me
Let it go
It'll never bring me down just believe me
It'll never bring us down just believe me
Fate may bear cruelties still I'm a royalty
And when the universe works against me I would just
Let it go
If it's spicy just sip something let it go
I've been living carefree
There's no bitter words in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Not letting it show
Things but I'm bigger than my feelings so that will be enough
There is no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta be better than ever
Hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a winged peacock
Kan ku taklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With wind magic I'll invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit melawan dunia
All those who slumber to rise up and face the world
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the fate
We're stronger than them
Walking step by step, trusting by our faith
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Believe me, let it go, they'll never bring me down
Just believe me, let it go, it'll never bring us down
Just believe me, won't let their cruelty steal my royalty
And when the universe works against me, I will just...
Let it go!
One voice is not enough to do this!
One, two, three, let it go!
hololive Indonesia CHROMATIC FUTURE 5th Anniversary LIVE
Merchandise Lineup:
Acrylic Panel, Acrylic Stand, Holographic Button Badge, Lanyard & Ticket Holder, T-shirt
Acrylic Panel
Acrylic Stand
Holographic Button Badge
Lanyard & Ticket Holder
T-shirt