(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-14T01:41:20.440375",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Mom
Jenna Roehrs
Jay
Gemma
Hey, why were you looking at my Raora?
No, I wasn't!
Raora already has me. Love is...
first come, first served.
What are you even talking about?
No, she's mine! Mine! Mine! She's mine, man!
Don't take her! No, it's mine!
Raora's mine now! No, mine! Mine! Mine!
Mine! Mine! Mine!
Jay, what on earth are you playing over here?
The Jealousy Game.
The Jealousy Game?
And shouldn't you play something more appropriate for a five-year-old?
Mom, I'm five, and this is what five-year-olds do,
and I thought this was funny.
Oh, you and daddy are definitely having a conversation about this later.
All righty, it's time for your favorite thing. Justice!
Justice! Justice!
Jay, who do you like so much in...
...justice.
They make loads of trouble.
What?
Justice, Justice, Justice!
How to protect Justice!
Members of Justice are expected to possess strength, sound judgment, and an unwavering sense of justice.
In this training video, you will learn the fundamental skills and exercises required of every Justice member.
Now, join us and say it together... For Justice!
The first training is a body search.
Conducted immediately after securing a subject, even the slightest oversight can lead to serious incidents...
...or the destruction of evidence, making this one of the most critical police procedures.
Can Justice keep their emotions in check under any circumstances...
...and carry out a precise body search to completion?
Oh!
Stop, ma'am! No further, no further! It is...
...policy and I'll be conducting a body search.
Come here, madam.
Yes, body search you here.
If you really insist...
Over here, over here, over here, ma'am.
Do you have any electronics, tablets, laptops, devices?
You want... body search?
Turn around here, ma'am.
Arms up! All right.
Straight arms, there we go, wonderful, wonderful. All right.
What is this?
Oh, you know, it's Totini. See my Totini?
They're always hungry, and they really want some food sometimes.
So I always have an emergency cucumber.
Emergency rations, I see, I see. We can't have that on this person, I'm sorry.
I... I take care of them.
All right, spread your legs, ma'am, over here.
Oh, no, no.
Over here, ma'am, over here, ma'am. Right here.
What are you going to do if I don't do it?
Uh, probably arrest you, put you in jail for many years, and...
Arrest me? Really? You're going to arrest me?
What are you going to do?
Oh... What if I... What if I check on you instead? No one's stopping me.
No, no, it's my job, ma'am. My job! Over here, ma'am.
All right. Stand there. What is this?
Oh, oh! What?
I like cooking. Would you like something? Maybe I can cook something for you?
Ma'am, I'm a professional. No dating on the job.
One day, when we have a little bit of pastime, I'm so good at making pasta.
Pasta... I am a bit hungry.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Stop trying to touch me! Stop trying to touch me!
All right, stand here! Stand here, ma'am! Right here, now!
She's kind of hot when she... Three, two, one, arms out!
All right. Let's see.
And what is this?
Oh, that's uh... that's a... Totini jetpack. Oh, no one should see this. Let's get it out of here.
Ma'am! You just threw that small... little creature!
Don't worry about it.
All right, anyway, what is this?
Oh! You have a lot of food-related items on you, ma'am.
Ma'am, you have a lot of food-related items. Yes, yeah, please, please eat that before you go.
Do you want a little bit, too? No, ma'am, I'm on the job. I'm on the job!
Anyway, ma'am, arms up! Come here, come here, over here.
What are you going to do if I don't do it? Are you going to punish me or something?
Uh, maybe, if you don't come here right now. I'm being... behaved.
Not going to do it. What are you going to do about it?
Going to make you do 10 push-ups outside of this training.
Maybe I can do some squats for you.
What is this? No, no! Not this one!
What... No! I can... I can explain! You know, an artist, standard...
Ah, right! An artist's anatomy book. I can explain!
That's my anatomy book! Ah...
Ma'am, you are way too suspicious! You are under arrest, and also for...
...having Totinis with jetpacks! That is unbelievable!
You are a bad, bad kitty! You are a bad kitty, come here!
All right, you are under arrest! Oh, yes I am.
Yeah, yeah, that was a really good round, right? That was it.
Are we going to jail? Are you going to bring me... That's it for the training. That's it for the training.
That's it for the training, Raora. Maybe we can get closer together?
Raora, no! We are done with the training! We're done! No, we're done with the movie! We need to leave here!
All right then! Officer Cecilia Immergreen. We will be...
...conducting the body search.
Stop right there!
Hands up in the air!
I- I didn't do anything wrong!
Do I have your consent to do a body search?
No, no, no!
Do I have your consent? Do I have your...
I didn't do anything wrong! Okay...
Okay, let us see.
Let us see what you have here.
I didn't do anything! On what charges?!
What is this?
Hey! That's mine! Why did you take that from me?
It's not! We've never met before, why would I take something from you?
No, I can't believe you would... You're a thief! You're under arrest!
I didn't steal it! It was given to me!
Stand still! Hands up in the air!
What's this then?
There's nothing wrong with having that in my pocket!
It's a Gramward buddy! We're friends!
Does it live under humane living conditions?
Yes, it lives in a nice little shoebox and it's really happy there! So that's why you should not arrest me, Officer.
Okay, okay, I believe you.
What's this?
Wait... a Noetomo? Why do you have a Noetomo?
For no reason! I have...
Are they friends?
They're friends! He was on a playdate, obviously. He came to visit the shoebox, so that's why. Am I free to go, Officer?
I'm starting to think that maybe, maybe it's okay. Let me see one more time.
What's this?
Nothing... It's nothing... Oh, oh...
君にダンク
[Manga: Dunking on You]
Can't a girl have some BL in her pocket?
Kimi ni Dunk?
I mean, can't a girl have some hobbies? Can't I read? Am I not allowed to read all of...
Stop making those noises!
What's this?
ツンデレ猫耳彼氏
[Manga: Tsundere Cat-Eared Boyfriend]
Another one?!
This one is a cat boy, and then... Have you heard of that really, really awesome manga where whenever they...
Okay, okay, grab... on the floor! On the floor!
On the floor?!
On the floor! Get down! On the floor! Get down!
Stop making those noises! What's this?
狼オメガは逃げ場はなかった。愛されたい
[Manga: The Wolf Omega Had No Escape. I Want to Be Loved]
What's this one then?
So, this one is the one that I... I really, really like this one. You see these two men right here? One of them is an Omega, another one is an Alpha. It's called the Omegaverse. And then...
...they don't actually turn into wolves here, it's just... it's called pack dynamics, and one of them is really, really dominant, and the other one is really submissive, and then one of them can get pregnant! Do you like... Hello? Are you listening, Officer? Officer? One of them gets pregnant, and it's really, really...
The next training is Apprehension Training.
This is a critical close-quarters task in the field...
...requiring officers to approach and subdue a target swiftly.
However, unexpected behavior on site can sometimes shake one's judgment.
Can Justice successfully and reliably subdue the target?
Gigi and Raora's Apprehension Training! You have three minutes! Begin!
Yeah! You're going down, criminal scum!
No! No! Ah!
Put your arms behind your back!
No, don't do that!
No... Gigi, look at my tail!
Look at my tail! My tail is cute!
Do you like my tail?
I'm unsure who's winning.
Hey, Gigi! Don't fall for that!
You know, it's kind of hard for you.
You are Justice! Show me your badge!
Kill her!
Ah... Oh, no, you have the right to remain silent!
No, no, no! You don't want to hurt me, do you?
You are a criminal, so I'm going to have to touch you. I'm going to have to put you in jail.
But Gigi, why would you put me in jail? Gigi, oh... stop! Ah, stop!
Apprehend her!
Kill her! Kill her! Kill her!
Get down! Down! Down! Down! Down!
Oh, Gigi, why would you... why do you want to touch my tail? Hey!
Show me your tail!
Stop! You are a criminal! You're a criminal! You're a criminal!
Down, Raora! Down!
Don't look, don't look!
Get back down! Get down!
Down! Where are you going?
Oh, no one would touch me, right?
No, I would touch you.
I will touch you. I will hurt you.
Lie down. Lie down.
Lie down. You're a criminal.
You're a criminal, so you have to lie down. You have to do what I say because I'm a police.
I'm a loser.
Wait, I have something here. Hold on.
Oh, my clothes... my...
Aaaaah!
I'm trying! I'm trying!
I'm trying!
Get back on the ground!
Oh, you wanna... you wanna be here next to me?
What do you want from me?
You've got to...
Both of them are down, officer.
Kiss me! Kiss me!
Love me! Kiss me!
I win! Guys, I win! Guys, I win!
Okay, okay, okay, that's enough. That's enough.
I win!
That's enough.
That was apprehension.
Did I win?
Who do you think won, Liz?
Wow! And the winner is...
Wait, this is about apprehension training, there's a winner.
Okay, so apprehension... did you do a good job?
I am still free!
In the end, you apprehended her.
Uh, it was in a very... I got her in a leg lock and everything.
I think she's correct.
You definitely locked her down.
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Girl, stop!
You know, I disqualify. Gigi is the winner!
Yes!
GG, well done. You apprehended the...
Actually, I think you won.
I think I won, too.
You won.
Hey, hey, hey.
Not without my consent!
Okay, okay, okay.
[Suspect: Elizabeth / Officer Cecilia]
Elizabeth and Cecilia, apprehension training!
You have three minutes. Are you ready?
Wait, one second.
Here we go.
Flame on!
Flame on! I'm ready.
Are you guys ready now?
We're ready.
Okay. Three, two, one, start!
Suspect! Suspect, stop right there!
Aha!
I am Evil Elizabeth...
...and I have chewing gum in everyone's hair!
How evil am I?
Hands up in the air!
Hands up!
Hands up! And, oh, yeah, yeah!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh!
Help! Help!
Oh, my god, Liz. You should kill her.
She's so strong.
Oh!
Liz, Liz, I've fallen.
Oh. Come on, up, up.
Come on, up, up, up.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. You did great.
You wanna another go?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
Whoa! Oh, no! I've fallen.
I'm doing it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Did I win, Liz? Did I win?
Are you willingly going to come with me to the police station?
Oh, no, because I'm evil.
I'm going to go burn a village.
Okay. Wait, stop!
Huh?
Look at this!
Oh, my goodness!
I am evil, and she is evil.
She's the most evil!
Oh, my god, is that a signed picture of the evil evil evil Nerissa?
Yes! Sign for you!
Give it. I need it.
If you come with me, I'll give this to you.
Oh, yes! I will. Yes, yes, yes!
Okay, hands behind your back, hands behind your back.
I get the picture, though, right?
Yes, of course. Yes, of course. Here, here you go.
Yes, yes, yes.
You were playing dirty! You just humiliated Liz!
No, I am a smart smart cop, and instead of using violence...
...I used my brain. Justice loses!
Oh, my god.
I don't know what you are on about.
Yeah, yeah, you did really well. I think you did great.
You, uh, you know, used a weapon against your, the suspect...
...to, uh, appre- apple- apple tension, apprehend...
...appre- apprehend them.
And, uh, yeah, so I think you did great.
Um, yeah, great job, Cecilia.
I think Cecilia has done the best out of everyone personally.
Yes! Justice's greatest weakness.
No! No! You weren't supposed to win...
...Justice is caught!
We're never going to get definitely... this!
[How to Protect Justice! Interrogation Training]
The second training is... interrogation!
It's a crucial investigative...
This is... where even the slightest inconsistencies...
...in a statement must be detected...
...to get closer to the truth.
Can Justice remain unaffected by the situation...
...and accurately draw out the information?
Yeah, I'm the best, actually.
I have a gun...
...and I know how to use it, so...
Easy. Don't worry about it, I have my ways.
I've been here for so long...
...it's going to be the easiest case of my life.
No, I don't think so.
Because my heart is too pure...
...and my ass is too fat...
...and I'm not a gaslighter like Cecilia Immergreen.
I'm not very confident, but I'll do my best.
Well, well, well, like the criminal...
...we are about to begin your interrogation!
Wait a minute! I'm not a criminal!
Why me? I haven't done anything.
What exactly have I been accused of?
That... That would be the...
...sus-suspected identity fraud...
...and the unlawful acquisition of personal...
Come on, Gigi!
...of Nerissa Ravencroft!
I don't know anything about that.
I'm innocent! Who is Nerissa Ravencroft?
Have you ever seen Nerissa Ravencroft?
You know who Nerissa Ravencroft is.
No, I've never seen her in my life.
Blue, black long hair... red eyes?
Tell her that we saw her!
If I ever saw such a maiden, I would call her sister.
She sounds like one.
Well...
We have evidence! We have evidence!
We have evidence.
Does the name...
...99x_XD ring a bell to you?
Oh, yes. Because 99x_XD is me.
I knew it!
You are the prime suspect in the stalking incident...
Oh, Nerissa Ravencroft...
We have it on paper right here!
And we have all the chat logs that you put...
...in Nerissa Ravencroft's channel right here!
I don't know, I watch a lot of virtual entertainers.
"Nerissa Ravencroft, I am outside of your house right now."
Tell her!
"Nerissa Ravencroft, I see you from the window."
"Nerissa Ravencroft, take off your shirt."
Whoa, now.
That was also you!
I don't know about that.
We have photos! On the phone!
I don't know about that, I think you're mistaken.
I would never speak that way to a princess.
Tell her that we're never going to give her donuts ever again.
And you will never have donuts ever again!
I would have never... donuts?!
How did you know I like donuts?
No more donuts!
No more donuts.
But... but if you...
...if you just confess...
...we have an in with Nerissa Ravencroft.
Yeah, offer her a good deal, Gigi!
We can give you what you want.
A date!
With Nerissa Ravencroft!
Okay, now you guys switch roles.
Gigi, play the bad cop!
Look, I admit it. I know her.
Answer us right now!
Yeah! Go crazy, go crazy on her!
I'm scared.
Hey, you!
Whoa.
A third woman, it is my lucky day.
Chief Raora!
Oh, Chief Raora!
What do you guys think you're doing, huh?
I was doing what you were saying.
You useless! You can't do...
...anything in this place!
Why did I hire you, huh?
You're so useless!
This person... we have all the evidence...
...and you still didn't manage to...
...to make her tell the truth!
Chief, we're trying our best, okay? We're underpaid, overworked!
You're embarrassing us in front of the criminal.
Well, maybe you should do better than this!
You're not even listening to me, are you?
You never fixed our coffee machine!
And we never get free time off, Raora!
Well, if you work more, maybe you will deserve your coffee machine!
Do you like coffee?
No.
Why, what do you want from me?
I watch info videos!
And you're right! Silence!
You know, one of my favorite virtual entertainers...
...Cecilia Immergreen, she does not like coffee.
Do you remember what did you do in that record?
I, I mean, I make up my own stories...
...in my chat logs.
Well, your own story with Nerissa Ravencroft, by any chance?
Get her, boss! Get her, boss!
Whoa...
Go, boss.
I think, I think you're all suspects...
...and I think you're doing great.
Thank you, thank you, thank thank.
So you do know Nerissa Ravencroft!
I know that her name spelled backwards is "Assiren".
How do you know that?
I know many Nerissas, because I'm very popular with the ladies.
Oh, would you say?
What about the photo collection she has in her room?
We have some things that I want to show you, okay?
This paper right here...
Are these my shackles, please?
No, these are all the photos that we found in your room...
...that you have taken of Nerissa Ravencroft!
These photos... Do you recognize these photos of Nerissa Ravencroft?
Who took them? We found them on your camera.
I think my mother... We were... We were with her in Ravencroft.
It was not your mother!
Oh!
There's a selfie right here!
Oh.
That's you right there!
That's you! It's you, it's you!
So, what do you have to say? Is that you or is that not you?
I think there's an imposter here.
Is that you or is that not you?
Tell her about the evidence that we have! The bra,
which was the wrong size, so it's not hers! It's from Nerissa Ravencroft because it's also signed by her!
We found a bra in your room.
And it's the wrong size.
I checked your breast size when you came in,
and it's not this size.
It is Nerissa Ravencroft's.
And it's also blue! Tell her that it's blue! She never wears blue!
And we know you don't wear blue bras.
I checked.
Are you... I think you guys, I think you guys are obsessed.
Stop it, criminal! I mean...
...we can, we can give you more than the bra from Nerissa Ravencroft.
Help me! I need help!
Take the photos.
Take the photos and we're going to get away.
It's me!
Take the photos...
What are you doing to her?!
What did you offer just now?!
I was doing what you told me to do!
You asked her to be an accomplice to Nerissa Ravencroft?!
I was doing what you were telling me to do!
I'm going to get away.
She was talking about...!
We're trying to get her! Not...
We are not supposed to find a new victim!
You told me to do it!
What are you doing? Why am I even paying you right now?!
All I do is get yelled at!
It's my first day on the force,
and I just really wanted to be a good cop.
And then 99X3XD, I thought, I thought...
...she's so good, we had all the evidence and all. She made me do all this!
I've never seen such a thing.
99X3XD was just so cunning and...
...that was kind of attractive, actually.
Those long hairs and those curves...
I should, I should go find her.
Oh, they're totally useless. They can't do anything.
I, I need to find new, new people for this job.
They don't have the guts for this.
Yeah.
But 99X3XD...
...she said that she likes ladies and stuff.
Maybe she would like me. Maybe she could work with me, who knows?
What is she, anyway?
Heh, didn't see it coming.
They didn't know I was, well...
...they didn't know I was 99X3XD.
But they didn't, they didn't crack me one bit.
Heh.
For I am too good. I am too cunning. I am, uh, too, too powerful, as they say.
Can I get out of this?
The next training is Firearms Training!
What's required is precision and split-second judgment.
A moment's hesitation can greatly impact the outcome.
Can Justice remain unfazed by the situation...
...and deliver highly accurate shots?
Firearms training, let's go!
Let's go!
First...
...let's go over the rules!
A variety of targets will appear one after the other.
Your job is to quickly decide whether to shoot or hold your fire.
If it's a valid target, take it out with your revolver.
But be careful, not every target is meant to be shot.
Out of the ten targets, three are no-shoot targets,
so don't let your guard down!
Okay.
Okay, okay, we've got it.
What do you mean?
I wasn't listening, I was not paying attention.
So we should shoot everything.
No!
Most importantly, shoot your friends!
What?! What?! What the freak?!
All right.
Cecilia, you're up first!
Justice! Just like that! Justice!
Cecilia, are you feeling confident?
Really good. Look at my trigger... Oh, it's not... Oh, yeah, I'm really good.
I'm going to shoot everything, and I'm going to win.
Ready,
...set...
...go!
You start... Oh, there it is!
Woah! Nice! Yay!
Cecilia's crazy!
Oh my god! Is that a gnome?
With magic! And dead!
You killed a gnome!
Fairy mushroom? Magic fairy gnome.
Pizza, pizza! Shoot the pizza! Shoot the pizza!
Pizza's a bad thing?
Is pizza a bad thing?
Wait, we're supposed to shoot the pizza?
Uh oh, uh oh... No, Cecilia!
No, she was just a little girl! No!
Ah! That's a royal guard! No! Cecilia!
Hey, she's a killer. He's texting while driving!
Good, good! We got rid of a criminal.
Yeah, that's a criminal right there.
Hey, that's my pension!
Oh yeah, shoot that! Shoot her pension!
Oh, hello, tiny jet?
Very tiny. Yay! Nice shot!
Cucumber, cucumber, cucumber.
No, Cecilia, no! Yay!
He's stealing cookies!
Yes, he's stealing. I did it!
I shot everything!
Cecilia's final score is...
Seven! Seven? Yay, seven!
Six, seven. Wait, why?
Honestly,
I think the cucumber was a minus, and I thought it was a plus...
...because we want to kill the cucumber so she doesn't have to eat it. I don't like cucumbers, right.
And I think even if I shot the ones that weren't meant to shoot sometimes...
In a crisis situation, you just have to make a decision, even if it's the wrong one.
Exactly, shoot!
All right, let's go. Flame on! Flame on!
Three, two, one, go!
Shoot it, shoot it, shoot it! Nice!
She's a cheerleader! Shoot her, shoot her! Oh my god!
Wait, is that Kronii? No, no!
That's a good girl, that's a nice girl. Yeah.
Shoot it! A headshot! Why did you do that?
Okay.
Another one! Look at her back there, wow! Don't shoot!
Why is she on the ground?
Oh, pension! Pension! Shoot it, shoot it!
We need that for justice!
Target seven! My pizza!
I'm hungry, I'm hungry.
Yes! Eat well! Okay.
Money! Money! Money! Shoot it, shoot it! We need money!
No! Why? We need money!
Oh no, Liz!
Oh, a kitty! Cute! Kill it!
It's so funny though.
Shoot me!
Yay, nice! You are done!
Oh, yes! Okay, what is my score?
Your points are... drumroll...
Nine! No points?
No, nine! Nine points! Woah, okay!
Flame on!
[Gigi]
Yeah! Go Gigi!
Your aim is so bad! Slow down!
How are you feeling today, Gigi? Are you confident?
I'm confident! I'm confident!
Get them!
Three, two, one, go!
That was our resolver!
How could you? That's not real!
Money, money, money!
That's money! That's not real! Yay, money!
Keep shooting! Money, money, money!
You have to kill her!
No, that was just a baby! Kill the baby!
The target! Kill it! Yes!
No, bad box!
Oh, my God!
Did you see? Did you know?
Did you know? No! Gigi, hit it!
I can't, I can't hit it.
Oh, my God.
You're lucky, you're lucky,
you're so lucky right now.
Okay.
Whoa! Kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it!
I can't kill it. I looked into its eyes
and I can't kill it!
I looked right into its eyes and I couldn't do it.
Pizza!
Oh, yeah! Yes!
Nice!
No more pizza. No more diet.
No more pizza, pizza for... Whoa!
He's stealing the real cookies! Kill him, kill him!
He's not a real... That doesn't work!
Oh, he's texting while driving!
Oh my god, we have to put him down!
That was so good!
Okay, I think you are done.
Okay, you've run out, you've run out of bullets now, okay?
Okay, Gigi. Okay, we got it. Don't shoot us.
Oh, no, no, no! Ah! No! No!
Okay.
Whoa! It's time to reveal Gigi's score!
So real, so real!
Okay, the final score for Gigi is...
Do it! Shoot, shoot! Eight!
Eight! She got eight! She got eight!
Yay!
[Title: Raora]
It's your go, Raora Panthera!
It's me!
Yeah, yeah, big cat, are you ready? Or...
Big gun? Me?
Liz! Liz, face the gun... Ah!
It's not real. No, no, don't die!
What do I do again?
You shoot those targets, and you shoot
the ones that are bad. Bad targets, okay?
Bad ones.
How do I know which one is bad?
That's up to you to decide as a member of Justice.
Ready? Ready! Yes!
Ready, set, go!
Get him, get him, get him!
Okay, I got... Ah!
You got to shoot that... Behind there,
Raora. A little to the left.
Raora, you're supposed to shoot this one!
Yeah, it says "shoot me!"
Oh! Oh, god. Texting while driving!
Kill him, kill him, kill him!
Texting while driving, kill him!
Wait, get him, he's... We got him!
That guy is finished. Next one for sure. Liz? Liz?!
I'm right here, Raora, that's an imposter!
Oh my god, you killed her, you killed Liz!
No, don't kill her! Don't kill her!
Kill him, kill him! Okay, I got...
Kill him, kill him! Help!
No! That's bad!
Raora with the God eyes, huh?
He's stealing the cookies!
Yeah, what kind of God eyes are they?
Get him, get him!
He's stealing the cookies!
Hey, but it's not... Yeah. What?
Why didn't you kill the guy with the cookie jar?!
All right. Next. Come on, Raora,
you need to get the next one.
Oh, cute! No, he's, he's evil!
He's stealing fairy mushrooms!
He's, he's got mushrooms.
He does have mushrooms.
Hey, I thought he is bad.
He is bad, she is bad.
Ah! Kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it!
Oh, no!
Hey, we got it. We ate... we ate the cookie.
Wait, what is that?
Oh, bad bug! Bad bug! Yeah!
Get it, get it, get it, get it!
Oh, Gigi, get the...
we need to save the world!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Ah! He's jumping real... Ew!
Oh, it jumps real, real fast.
He's cute, though. Wait, why didn't you shoot?
It's cucumber.
Yay, cucumber for dinner!
Oh, money! Money! Do we want money?
Oh no, we don't want money?
We have the Gigi texting. Okay.
What's wrong with the G-text?
Ah! Yay! That is so cool!
That was great! That was, that was,
that was great, Raora! That was really good.
That was really, that was really good,
kitty-kitty. Really good.
I can, I can do something else,
in... in criminals. Oh, really?
Gigi, do you want to save the score?
Do you want to know how much it was?
I know. Do you want to know? I know.
Hold my hand, I need to tell you.
Your point is... it was four.
Four?! Maybe you...
Four points! You did that on purpose
because there's four of us.
You're so, you're so,
you're so clever, Raora.
Justice! Justice!
And with that,
the training is complete! Huzzah!
Oh, yeah! And the winner is...
the winner is... drumroll...
Elizabeth! Oh, yeah!
イェーイ！
Yay!
敗者！敗者！
And the loser... Loser!
Loser! Loser!
大丈夫だよ、ジジ、君が敗者だから。
It's okay, Gigi. You're definitely the loser.
私はこの「神の目」で、君を勝たせてあげたかっただけだよ。
I just wanted to make you win because I'm the strongest with my God eyes, so...
ジジ、背中に隠してるのは何？
Gigi's also... What's that behind your back?
背中の？何それ？
What's that behind my back? What's that behind your back?
ああ！そんなことできない！
Ah! I can't do that!
撃ってきてる！撃ってきてる！
No, she's shooting! She's shooting!
怒ってる！怒ってる！
She's mad! She's mad!
逃げて！
Run away!
反撃して！
Fight back!
次の訓練は交通取り締まり訓練です。
The next training is Traffic Enforcement Training.
この任務では、違反を正確に評価し、正しく処理することが求められます。
This duty requires accurately assessing the violation and processing it correctly.
しかし現場では、予期せぬ行動が警察官の判断を鈍らせることがあります。
However, in the field, unexpected behavior can sometimes shake an officer's judgment.
ジャスティスはどんな状況でも冷静沈着に、適切な対応をとることができるでしょうか？
Can Justice stay unfazed in any situation and carry out the appropriate response?
やったぞ、みんな！よくやった、手下たち。
We did it, boys! Good job, my goons.
車を止めなさい、今すぐ車を止めなさい！
Pull over the car, pull over the car right now!
うわ、大変だ！
Oh no!
手下、手下！声を出せ、声を出せ！よし、ボス。
My goon, goon! Do the voice, do the voice! Okay, boss.
ボナセーラ！こんにちは、これは一体何事ですか？
Buonasera! Good afternoon, what's all this then?
なんで車を止められたか分かりますか？
You know what? I pulled you over... That was really cool!
まあ、なんてこと！静かに！
Oh my god! Silenzio!
何も知らないふりはやめなさい！一時停止を完全に無視しましたね！
Don't act like you don't know anything! You blew right through the stop sign!
私たち、今本当に急いでいるんです！私の夫が…妊娠しているんです！
We are just really in a hurry right now! My husband... He's pregnant!
運転免許証を見せていただけますか？
Can I see your driver's license, please?
免許証、持ってる？
Do you have... do you have your driver's license?
時間がないんです！彼、本当に妊娠してるんです！
We don't have time! He's really pregnant!
破水したんです！病院に行かないと！
His water just broke! Oh my god! We have to go to the hospital!
今すぐ病院に行かないといけないんです、お願いします！
And we have to go to the hospital right now, please!
嘘をついているように見えます。嘘じゃありません！
I think they're liars. We are not... We're not lying!
ほら、こんなにお腹が大きいんです！妊娠していないと思います。
Look how big he is! I think she's not pregnant, sir.
すみません、夫は本当に妊娠してて、今すごくお腹が大きいんです！
Excuse me, my husband is really pregnant! He's really big right now.
赤ちゃんに触らせて。
Let me feel the baby.
蹴ってる！ほら、感じない？私の息子！
It's kicking! It's kicking! Can you not feel it? My son!
あなたの跡継ぎよ！静かに！
Your heir! Silenzio!
どう思う？あの二人、ちょっと怪しい行動をしてるよね。
What do you think? Those two, those two are acting a little bit suspicious.
マンマ・ミーア！大丈夫？
Mamma mia! Are you alright? Do you think... Could it be?
そう、ほら！まさに私が思っていた通りだわ！
Yes, see! This is exactly what I was thinking!
私の息子！私が妊娠しているから引き止めるのね！
My son! No, no, no, you are stopping us because I am pregnant! Yes! It was the baby!
そこに馬がいた。いいえ、私の赤ちゃんです！
There was a horse there. No, it was my baby! It was our baby!
トランクからひづめの音が聞こえたんだけど。
Recently, I heard a hoof sound coming from the truck. Hey! You can't say that about my baby!
ちょっと見せてもらってもいいかしら？嫌です！
Mind if we take a look? I do mind! I do mind! Wait, wait, wait!
ダメダメダメ！トランクの中を見るわよ。
No, no, no, no! We're just going to take a look in the trunk.
お願い、やめて！あなたは間違いなく有罪よ！
Please! No, please! You are definitely guilty!
お願い、警察官さん！やめてください！
Please, officer! Stop, officer, please!
馬だ、警部！馬よ！
It's a horse, officer! A horse!
馬だ！私の息子よ！
It's a horse! It's my son! It's ours!
ジジ・ムリン、セシリア・イマーグリーン、あなたたちを逮捕するわ。
Gigi Murin, Cecilia Immergreen, you're under arrest.
逮捕なんて嫌だ！失うものが多すぎる！
I can't be under arrest! I have too much to lose!
あなたを正式に逮捕します。ボス！私を置いていかないで！
You are officially arrested. Wait! Boss! Boss! You can't leave me, boss!
またね、敗者さん！バイバイ！
See you later, loser! Bye!
追いかけるわよ！乗って！私、運転できない！
We're going to catch her! Get in! Let's catch her! I can't drive!
私たち二人きりだね、ベイビー。
It's just you and me, baby.
All right, the place is empty.
Got about ten minutes before the guard's next patrol.
So, this is the YAGOO trophy...
the Giga-Mega National Treasure.
I'm gonna make a fortune on this!
This is Justice. Is this an emergency?
Help! Help! Please! Please!
Please, is anybody here right now?
I don't know what to do, please!
Calm down and take a deep breath.
Can you tell me exactly what happened?
Uh, calm down... Calm down.
Leave it to us. Leave it to us.
Justice is on the way right now!
Everyone, we have a case.
The ultimate national treasure has been stolen.
Head to the scene immediately!
The ultimate national treasure?
You mean the YAGOO statue?
Who even wants that? Just let them keep it.
Gigi, that is disrespectful!
It is still the ultimate national treasure.
We're counting on you.
Fine, I'm on it.
Oh, wait, Liz!
The super limited edition sweetie pizza drops in just three minutes!
It's limited quantity, okay?
That means I absolutely have to buy it!
Okay, so only two minutes left now.
Just go already!
No! Oh, mio dio! The portal is loading! No! No!
Cecilia, did you get any information?
Cecilia!
Hold on!
Who the hell changed my keyboard to American?!
But I love your keyboard, Ceci!
This was you?!
You... You absolute garbage can!
When I get to you, I'm going to...
Cecilia, every second counts here.
I know, I know. All right, found a backdoor in the telescope.
Cracking the encrypted protocol via brute force.
Enforcing the security patch overdrive on the mainframe system security data...
In English, please.
Fine. I'm in.
The suspect is a woman dressed entirely in black.
Height looks around 168 centimeters.
She really likes people wearing helmets.
Ah, she's fleeing north. If you move now, you can still catch her.
You all heard her. Let's move out and apprehend the suspect!
For justice!
Raora, what are you doing? You're not even driving! Do you know how to drive a car?
Put your foot on... on the gas pedal!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait! What?
There's a horse in front of us!
There's no freaking horse. What freaking horse?
Oh my god, there's a freaking horse. Oh, the horse is right there. Oh my god.
Is this for real? No way that's a real horse!
Oh, we must get out of here now!
Wait, Gigi! I'm not gonna be able to eat my limited-edition San Martin!
My pizza's gonna get cold!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Horses like cucumbers, right? I think there's a cucumber in the trunk.
What? A cucumber? In the trunk?
Gigi! Why do you have a cucumber in your pockets right now?
Gigi, you know I hate cucumbers!
You know why? What?
Gigi, you know I hate cucumbers! Why do you have cucumbers right now?!
Ew! Get out of here!
You know where I'm gonna put the cucumber? Where?
Get out of here right now! I don't want to see that cucumber! Ew!
What about the horse? What about for the horse? No! What about for the horse?
Oh, you hate me. Don't you freaking hate me? You hate me! So you hate me! So you hate me! Just say it! Tell me!
You know how I feel! Why did you bring cucumbers? You brought cucumbers, and you know that I hate- and I hate cucumbers! I hate the taste, I hate everything about cucumbers!
We talked about that many times! Stop, stop, stop laughing!
Those two are away with the fairies.
Cecilia! Do you have any updates on the suspect's location?
Mmh, almost there...
Cecilia?
A little bit more...
Cecilia...
Cecilia Immergreen!
No! I missed!
Look what you did, Liz! You ruined my perfect score!
I was so close!
Not you too!
Did I fail them as a mother?
My heart breaks as their big sister.
I've done everything in my power to look after those three.
Those three wild, eccentric little sisters...
...and guide them to this very day.
I gave them my all!
Oh, what did I do to deserve such cruelty?
Where did I go wrong?
Where did my guidance stray away from the path?!
You... you guys were still... still there, huh?
We're sorry, ERB.
I promise I will be a good girl.
Big sister! Big sister! Big sister!
It's just allergies. I'm not crying. You're crying.
Thank you! We love you, big sister!
Happy ever after!
Justice just like that! Justice did get them.
Guys, everyone!
It's the thief who stole the ultimate yogurt statue!
We're gonna kill them.
What? Kill them? Kill them?
Hey you! Hold it right there!
Because of you, I missed out on limited-edition San Martin...
...and I didn't even get to eat my delicious pizza!
How are you going to take responsibility for this?!
That sounds like a you problem.
Go eat your pizza now.
Oh, by the way, there's a shop nearby famous for its cucumber pizza.
It's to die for.
Cucumber pizza?!
Ew!
Even I've had it before.
Absolutely exquisite.
Ah, this is... ah... this is such an insult!
Impossible!
It's okay, Raora, relax, relax.
DOOM!
Doom?
Doom?!
Justice Shopping!
And now, it's time to introduce Justice's 2nd anniversary merch!
First, take a look at this: the Premium Acrylic Message Board!
We spoke with someone who actually used it.
Oh? You want to meet...
You want to talk about the premium acrylic message board?
Ah, yeah, yeah, sure! Oui, oui!
Ah, this artwork is so cool! I love it so much!
Ah, using acrylic instead of paper was such a good choice.
And it makes it feel really special.
And the foil-stamped replicated messages?
That's honestly the best part!
I can't stop looking at it.
It just looks that much good, you know? Oui, oui.
Please support Justice and buy their merch. Oui.
Thank you. Merci!
Wow, that's some pretty high praise!
We've still got lots more merch to introduce.
So let's move on to the next item. Here it is...
Embroidered Patch Keychain!
So cute!
The illustrator behind this artwork is none other than Raora Panthera!
And guess what?
We've received a special message directly from her!
Ta-da!
This is Raora Panthera, the artist behind the embroidered keychains! Raor!
You know, I'm, I'm so happy I got the chance to draw for my Justice girls.
Greetings or something from my friends always feel really special.
And, and I hope, I hope you're gonna love them as much as I do! Yes, yes, yes!
And you know, they took all my adorable illustrations and turned them into those cute embroidered keychains.
And you know, since they're, since they're keychains,
you can attach them to your bag and take them with you wherever you go.
Yeah, a little bit of extra cuteness for your everyday life!
So make sure to pick one up, and trust me,
the cuteness is guaranteed!
Yes! Look at that, they're so cute, adorable!
What a wonderful piece of merch!
Anyone would love to have that one in their home, including me!
Oh right, let's move on to the next piece of merch.
Take a look at this.
The Medal-Style Badge!
Cool!
We caught up with Justice's leader, Elizabeth, to get her thoughts.
Hmm? You want to hear about the badge?
Of course!
My sweethearts, my JustiCards.
This badge was designed with the image of law enforcement and authority in mind.
The weighty, prestigious look fits Justice perfectly, don't you think?
I think it looks absolutely fantabidozi! It looks fantastic! Very cool.
Anyone who strives for justice should definitely get their hands on one.
Oh, and it also comes in a beautiful display box, so it's perfect for displaying and admiring as well.
I hope when you guys look at your, your medal, or wear it...
...you will remember how us, Justice, are, oh, so proud of you all, and we all really appreciate you so, so, so much.
So I really hope that comes to mind every time you wear or look at this medal.
Mwah!
And that was a message from Elizabeth!
And now, for the final item we're introducing today.
Here it is...
The Double-Zip Patch Hoodie!
Whoa!
We spoke with a fan who actually got their hands on the merch.
Wait, a Justice show?!
Oh, oh my god, oh my god, I'm so excited!
You want to hear my thoughts on this merch as the biggest Justice fan in the world?
That has nothing to do with Justice, I'm just a random fan passing by!
Of course, ask me anything!
Q: What do you think about this item?
Oh, I absolutely love the design!
The patches inspired by all four members of Justice are so cute and stylish!
And I love how each one of them reflects their personality.
And, and the logo and text on the back give it such a cool, premium look.
It's the kind of hoodie that instantly makes you think...
..."Mmm, yes, this is Justice!"
Q: How is it when you actually wear it?
Oh, it's amazing!
The brushed fleece lining makes it super warm and comfortable.
Not only does it look great, but it's also really practical.
And the fact that it comes in both L and LL sizes is fantastic!
I think a lot of fans will appreciate having different size options.
So make sure to buy the Justice merch, okay?!
Wow, jolly good!
Now that's a passionate fan!
And that's it for Justice Shopping!
Bye!
So, how was it?
It was awesome!
And what did you like the most?
The horse!
Oh, the horse. Yes.
And there's this new... flash!
We interrupt your regularly scheduled programming to bring you this breaking news.
We have just received an exclusive update from Justice, the global guardians of peace.
Rumor has it, a brand new track from the iconic four-piece is about to drop at any second.
I repeat, new music from Justice is imminent.
Do not touch that dial.
We will be right back with the world premiere.
This is Ouro Kronii signing out.
Yeah!
Are you there?
You're a SUPER GIRL!
(Justice, just like that!)
(Justice, get, get that!)
If you're feeling trapped, send out a signal right above!
(Gesundheit!)
We'll find you, set you free then you can sign up for the club!
(Innit!)
Danger, fun, fun, fun!
Soul shine like the sun!
(Minna happiness, minna happiness)
(Everyone's happiness, everyone's happiness)
The frig? I'm big! My strong, strong muscle!
They see me run, it's no miracle!
You are shining...
...SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing...
...LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER, SUPER GIRL!
I'm the SUPER!
(PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA) HEY!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
(PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA) HEY!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun, love it!
(I'M SUPER GIRL)
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit!
(YOU'RE SUPER GIRL)
I'm the SUPER!
(PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA) HEY!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
I always want a pizza, stack those fries up to the sky!
(Ciao ciao)
You lot say whatcha think about us hittin' town tonight?
(Justice!)
Feeling happy time!
No sad, say bye bye!
(Motto maniac, justice just like that!)
(More maniac, justice just like that!)
So stomp, stomp, stomp your feet to this beat!
Cuz we are space, no, no gravity!
You are shining...
...SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing...
...LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER, SUPER GIRL!
I'm the SUPER!
(PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA) HEY!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
(PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA) HEY!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
I know you're feeling so super bad!
You don't have depression, you're just super sad!
We are change the world, that's hope!
If you doubt, hope you explode!
Justice loud, justice proud...
...and we keep telling you!
We are SUPER!
(PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA) HEY!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
(PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA) HEY!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
Justice, we are justice, make the baddies go boom!
(I'M SUPER GIRL)
Come on, come on, baby, rocket ship to the moon!
(YOU'RE SUPER GIRL)
I'm the SUPER!
(PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA) HEY!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL!
And that was Supernova Super Girl, our brand new song!
Yay!
And just like that, our second anniversary stream is coming to an end.
So, what did you all think? We'll start with Raora this time.
Oh, me?
Yeah, you first this time.
Ah, it was really fun! It was amazing, I can't believe it's been already, like, two years!
I know! Right? Yay!
I... thank you so much, you guys, as well for being the best... the best companions ever, you know?
Yeah! Yay!
I'm so grateful to you guys, and thank you to Justice Chat for supporting us since two years now, it's insane. Thank you so much!
Thank you, Justice Chat! Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Hello! Thank you very much, everyone, for...
Oh, sorry! Oh, sorry.
This is Cecilia Immergreen! Cecilia Immergreen!
Thank you very much for being here today, everyone! Thank you for two years. Stage of Justice!
Yeah!
Please keep supporting us and listen to our song!
Yes!
Stream Supernova Super Girl!
Oh, Elizabeth is about to play...
No, I'm shaking!
What do I think? I think the stage is very cool! Look at the stage! Woah!
And look at this amazing team. I can't ask for a better...
We love you, ERB!
I love you all very much!
And Justiciais, we love you all very much too.
Thank you so much for supporting Justice. Thank you so, so, so much.
I love you so much!
So many kisses! We are so spoiled! Okay, Gigi!
Mwah mwah mwah mwah mwah...
Are you eating them? She's eating them! Oh my god!
Thank you, Justiciais, for being with us for two years! Two!
We didn't even know we could... I didn't even know Raora could count up to two!
Really? Really? But we made it to two years!
Yeah!
Thank you for supporting us! Please stream Supernova Super Girl!
Learn the chants! Learn the chants! Every song!
Learn the chants! Learn the chants, for some reason.
For some reason, maybe you should learn the chants!
I wonder if there's a lyric somewhere for you to learn when we go Supernova...
Super Girl!
Or "Minna happiness!" Minna happiness!
Yeah!
We all feel like super girls because of you guys. Thank you so much! Yes!
And don't forget to grab the merch! Purchase! Purchase our merch!
Yes, thank you, thank you.
Thank you all so much for celebrating with us today! Please keep supporting Justice, please, going forward as well!
Now then, let's all say goodbye together with our own chant! Yay!
You ready? I'm ready. All right.
Justice... Just like that!
Justice! Get, get, get, down!
Minna happiness! Minna happiness! Bye-bye!
Stay tuned for the premier of Justice's new MV "SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL" right after this!