(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-12T03:52:08.221854",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Greetings, CC, my favorite rival.
Greetings, Ina, my most destined rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Woo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured...
...on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made...
...post about it with hashtag #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay!
Thank you, AmiAmi, for supporting our rivalry.
And for supporting Serendipity!
Be sure to check out their booth at...
...Anime Expo!
Yay!
Hey pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me...
...all 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round1 USA locations nationwide...
...starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X...
...so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there! Bye-bye!
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention for Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
hololive English 4th Concert: Serendipity
Fan Messages
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention for Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.
Last Writes
AutoFister
BloodRavens
A-D-V-E-N-T
Everyone, let's make some noise!
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Higher, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
Sparking up like wildfire
Never ever, have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Take the chance and with my lighter
Start the fire
Don't burn me out
I know the secret
All of those sad stories wearing me down
Snap out of the system
Break out, give it everything
This is our time
We are here to start
Hello, brand new world
Would you welcome the light?
And free us from the night?
Fire, fire, light the fire
Higher, higher, as you desire
Night, beating hearts
Jump into the stream of light
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump into the end of time
一瞬が永遠を語る
A single moment speaks of eternity
連れ去ってあげる
I'll take you away
Rebellion
I know that I can still be the future of this story
I know that I can be free, the one and the only
They tell me that I'm crazy, I'll never let them stop me
We paved our path
Time to get this party started
Never ever, have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Fire, fire, light the fire
Night, beating hearts
Jump into the stream of light
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump into the end of time
一瞬が永遠を語る
A single moment speaks of eternity
連れ去ってあげる
I'll take you away
Jump into the stream of light
それぞれのステージへ
To our respective stages
Jump into the end of time
きらめきの向こう側
To the other side of the sparkle
連れ去ってあげる
I'll take you away
Rebellion
Time to get this party started
Fire, fire, light the fire
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below, below we go
They think they want it, huh?
They wanna get, get, get some
We take them down, down, down
Running on the borderline
Why? It's no surprise
You ain't gonna win, but you can try
I told you, we're on the run
End of the line, lock up
Listen, listen
Run, hide, and scream out loud
Already locked you out, boom!
The games you always play
Call me, call out, won't hear anything
Aiming to strike right on your heart
Throwing the keys, there's no turning back
Draw, Rover, Order, Judge
And we're higher, higher, rise
And further you drop!
Running on the edge
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Tipping the scales
Can't ever let us go
Show you some of the real, might as well know you'll never know
As we follow through for retribution
Run in the line of my vision
What's wrong, what's right?
Rushing in a fantasy
Born to be deceased
Sure that you will never make it out
Eyes on us now
Do it, do it
Nee-naw, nee-naw, nee-naw, nee-naw
Enemies gonna lose, oh!
Plead your guilty heart!
We are not gonna stop
It's just justice!
Get down, get down, let's go!
Run it like that, run it like that
Get down, get down, down, down, down
Takin' you all below, below, below we go
Show you already know
Don't you know it?
Run in the line of my vision
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night of my beacon
Come take a bite
Never-ending...
Draw, Rover, Order, Judge
We've only just begun
Get us!
We rise!
So high! We rise!
Yeah!
Standing on the edge!
Standing on the unpredictable, typical, you
got nowhere to go
Show you something real
My level now you'll never know, half of us so
below you should know
So let's go!
Just that little more unpredictable, beautiful, just that
Look at, look at
Next level, on the criminal, half of us so
It goes below
준비!
Ready!
다 쓸게 get what I share
I'll sweep them all, get what I share
players, they all complain
why me? No, not again
shout loud, ta-ta-ta, bang!
Ain't got time, so try those dice
Look around, we're satisfied
The broken and bruised, I got something to prove now
Abracadabra let's go, watch them like dice as they fall
끝까지 가보자 girl
Let's go to the end, girl
나는 마음대로 해
I do whatever I want
Double, double, double win
A lonely to ladder we shoot
All right, we hit that high
Snake, snake, snake, oh
Come on now, don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라
Heating up hotly
Muzak all day, all night
So turn it up, can't stop, won't stop reaching
Who said the sky's the limit?
Show them that we're in business
We are the young and vicious
Snake eyes, they never lie
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
지켜, 우릴 이끌어 왔던 Party
Protect the party that has led us
봐야지 끝까지, One Safari
We must see it to the end, One Safari
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me
Go, go, go, Baelz
Acting naughty
다 벗어던져
Throw it all off
머릿속은 싹
Clear your head completely
Shake it off, what goes around
Shut your mouth, we'll come back down
Ready to slide
Ready to scream it
Abracadabra let's go, watch as we're ripping it up
꺾이지 않는 눈빛
An unyielding gaze
들여다봐 what you wanna play
Peer inside, what you wanna play
Freeze up, demons
Believe in the beat and just wait and see
We hit that high
Snake, snake, snake, oh
Come on now, don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라
Heating up hotly
Muzak all day, all night
Let me hear you alright! Let's make it loud!
Go!
We go hard!
이 넓은 세계 전부 내 걸로 만들겠어
I will make this wide world all mine
We go hard!
I want it all
죽지 않아 전부 골라
I won't die, pick them all
맞서 싸워 시작이야
Fight back, it's just the beginning
끝까지 달려가
Run all the way to the end
We'll hit that high
Snake, snake, snake, oh
Come on now, don't be shy
다 같이 전부 모여봐 이렇게
Everyone gather together like this
멈출 수 없어 같이 Dance, Dance, Dance
We can't stop, together Dance, Dance, Dance
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just a new beginning
Look at the clouds, we're spinning
Sometimes it takes a villain
Thank God, the time is nigh
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
Cut you off at the ties
This is the only battlefield that can tell you lies
Ego is enormous, so put the camera down and face it
They went and got complacent
Come and run with me
You say you stand for nothing, no one else can relate
Just know the company we keep is in the business of hate
Runaway... Runaway... I'm closing in...
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest, go
Shoot, shoot, shoot, oh baby, there's a mess
Ricochet, ricochet
You can think about me anytime, anytime
So get your street fight!
This is trench war!
I'll make you mosh, mosh, mosh till you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision, let them wonder...
...what they're missing in the front row!
Clean white line
It's a call to arms, we've become the...
Wanted, wasted, hell-driven, make a decision
Are you looking for permission to riot?
You've got it all wrong, think about...
...your identity crisis, now you're alone!
Wanted, wasted, wanted, wasted, wanted...
Stand for nothing, play the coward...
...stand for someone you'll devour!
Wanted, wasted, wanted, wasted, wanted...
Stand for nothing, play the coward...
...stand for someone you'll devour!
Who's the man to say this?!
Whoa!
斜めのこじつけ この国に決めた
A skewed distortion, I decided on this country
角度調整 角度微調整 Yeah
Adjusting the angle, fine-tuning the angle, yeah
吐き出せボイス 体揺らせ...
Spit out your voice, shake your body...
...Please send the message, special and scarred...
...Forget the rest, can't buy my nature...,s:
...forget the rest, can't buy my nature...
...Chips are stacked with some lovely animals...
...Until they crack, 最上級のサイコ...
...until they crack, I've already sent off...
...パスはもうお見送りよ 集まったの公害...
...the highest-class psychopaths, pollution gathered...
...立ち振る舞い 時間無駄無駄無駄無駄...
...our behavior, time is useless...
...ヤバいじゃん I can tell you're not a friend
...useless, useless, useless, isn't that crazy?
全部燃やせ 口尖らせ 急がせる
Burn it all, pout your lips, make them hurry
誰に成り下がろう 犬にでも成り下がろう
Who shall we degrade ourselves to? Dogs?
身勝手なロンリーロンリー 誰に頼る？ストーリー
Selfish, lonely, lonely, who do you rely on? Story...
相容れないでやる 噛み砕いてやる...
I won't accept you, I'll bite you to pieces...
...見下してやる We're not rivals!
...I'll look down on you, we're not rivals!
We're not equals
We're not rivals
Whoa!
才能の才能の 貼り付けられたサバイバル
Survival with talent upon talent pasted over it
ガンガンやってる I can't take this
Going hard at it, I can't take this
Wait, listen when you're out of ideas
Shut up, shut up, I'm the one who's not impressed
Who's the man to say this?!
世間に取り残されて...
Left behind by the world...
...フラフラ フラフラ フラ Yeah
...wandering, wandering, wandering, yeah
フラフラ 捕らえられないぐらい
Wandering, to the point of being uncatchable
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
Now, would I lie to you?
Let me ignite you
Base instincts take control
Like primal ways of a warrior
Is it glory you're after, like me?
Underestimated everywhere I turn
Taking aim, but it doesn't make a difference at all
I got a million different enemies I cannot recall
You're rocking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall...
...hidden motivation, watch it all burn!
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
Now, would I lie to you?
Let me ignite you
When thunder crashes down...
...when the world caves under my pressure, there'll be no one to save
Where is your pride, your human will to survive?
Was it just empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul...
...now all that remains is delusion and decay
Because of you, I live this way
We're not rivals
We're not equals
Lately, I realized I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know, do you remember, remember...
...how we used to be so carefree?
Oh, hey...
I can feel the rain wash over...
wash over...
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 들리는 내 목소리
Upside down, can you hear my voice?
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I cannot break through
the cage I am in and I don't know how to reach to you
Will we ever get a chance to speak alone?
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, feel the sparks inside and I don't flare up
All my talk, all my secrets spilling over, sweet talk
So when I step up to your side, my heart is beating in double time
And every moment makes me feel alive, it goes like...
I can feel the rain wash over...
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 들리는 내 목소리
Upside down, can you hear my voice?
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I cannot break through
the cage I'm in, and I don't know how to reach to you
Will we ever get a chance to speak alone?
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Will we ever get a chance to speak alone?
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hello, hello!
Hello! Hello, hello, hello!
Hello up there! Hello down there!
Hello, everyone! Hello, みんな!
Hello, everyone! Hello, everyone!
Hey, who are you?
Hi there, darlings! This is Hololive English Advent's devilish diva...
...the one, the only, Nerissa Ravencroft!
And with me...
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue...
...also known as the Scarlet Queen, the Harbinger of Order, Leader...
...of Justice!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you...
Lovely!
That's awesome!
Wow! What a setlist so far!
I know, we're starting off really strong!
We had...
Snake Eyes, Snake Eyes!
And we had Mori...
...rocking it out!
And then Kronii coming in with her new song, so good!
Yeah, such cute dance moves!
And we had Advent and Justice, of course.
Yes, yes. Did you enjoy?
Did you enjoy?
Couldn't hear you! Did you enjoy?
Well, you know what, we didn't have solos yesterday.
No, no. So we must be having them today, right?
So excited!
Oh, yeah! For mine, I want to practice something, okay?
A little chant from Great Exardia. So when I go 'Oggi Oggi Oggi', you go...
...'Oi Oi Oi!'
Are you ready?
Okay, here we go!
Oggi Oggi Oggi!
Perfect! Kanpeki!
Perfect! Perfect!
How about you? Any sneak peeks about your solo?
Mmm, would you guys really like a sneak peek?
Well, uh, I think I have to remind you all...
...no matter how you identify, no matter what you are...
...you in this audience today...
...are my wives!
Can I hear it from my wives?!
What the freak! Everyone here is your wife?!
Including you!
So, if I ask you to sing along, you have to, all right?
You're gonna?
Oh... Well, yeah, that's my hint.
Does it give it away?
Maybe a little.
You know, we're singing, and I was thinking...
...that we'd like to hear you...
I sing too.
You guys know I like harmonies?
Yes!
So we're going to split you into different notes, okay?
So we have...
...you guys over here,
...and all of you at the top.
So we're gonna start off with you guys here.
Yeah.
We want you to hold this note.
Ah...
Perfect! You guys...
Up there! Ah...
Alright, everyone together!
Ah...
Beautiful, beautiful!
Oh my gosh! We have our own choir!
So good!
We've got to do that more often, that was cool!
Yeah!
I like hearing you all sing for us.
Hey, that reminds me of a song, doesn't it? You know, that first note?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Something like... 3, 2, 1...
It's wondrous
Somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me
embracing Serendipity!
Wow, that was great, wasn't it?
Harmonizing, yeah!
It's wonderful harmonizing with you. And I just want to say thank you so much for being my friend.
Oh, I love you!
We're gonna sing together!
We're going to sing together, guys!
I got too excited! I got too excited!
I'm just too happy!
I'm so happy too!
Wee-woo, wee-woo!
Wee-woo, wee-woo! You go, wee-woo, wee-woo!
Oh, I spammed too fast. There we go. Wee!
Anyway...
無料配信は次の曲で最後になります。
The free stream will end with the next song.
ライブの続きはぜひ、配信チケットを買って見てね！
Be sure to buy a stream ticket to watch the rest of the live concert!
The YouTube free sneak peek is only until the next song, which is...
...a duet.
If you want to continue watching, click the link in the description and get your tickets now!
Alright, everybody, after three, we all say 'Serendipity', got it?
Thank you so much! We love you guys so much!
We love you!
Alright, here we go!
Three, two, one...
Serendipity!
Performing Units
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Nerissa Ravencroft
Bloodraven
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, become a legend!
青い風がいま
A blue wind is now
胸のドアを叩いても
knocking on the door to your heart,
私だけをただ見つめて
but you just stare only at me,
微笑んでるあなた
smiling gently.
そっと触れるもの
Something gently touching you,
求めることに夢中で
you're so intent on seeking it out.
運命さえまだ知らない
Still unaware of your own fate,
いたいけな瞳
with those innocent eyes.
だけどいつかは気づくでしょう
But someday, you will surely realize
その背中には
that on your back,
遥か未来 めざすための
to aim for the distant future,
羽根があること
you have wings.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
The thesis of a cruel angel
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
will soon fly out from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
With a surging, hot pathos,
思い出を裏切るなら
if you betray your memories...
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a myth!
ずっと眠ってる
Lying asleep forever...
私の愛のゆりかご
...in the cradle of my love.
あなただけが
You alone...
夢の使者に
...by the messenger of dreams...
呼ばれる朝が来る
...will be summoned as morning comes.
細い首筋を
Upon your slender neck,
月あかりが映してる
the moonlight shines down.
世界中の時を止めて
I want to stop time all over the world
閉じ込めたいけど
and lock you in, but...
もしも二人逢えたことに
If there is a meaning
意味があるなら
to the two of us meeting...
私はそう
...then I am, yes,
自由を知るためのバイブル
your bible for learning what freedom is.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A cruel angel's thesis,
悲しみがそして始まる
sadness will soon begin.
抱きしめた命の形
The shape of the life I embraced,
その夢に目覚めたとき
when you awaken to that dream...
誰よりも光を放つ
...you will shine brighter than anyone else.
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a myth!
人は愛をつむぎながら
While weaving love,
歴史をつくる
people create history.
女神なんてなれないまま
Without ever becoming a goddess,
私は生きる
I continue to live.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A cruel angel's thesis
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
will eventually flutter out from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
With a surging, hot pathos,
思い出を裏切るなら
if you betray your memories,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く
embrace this sky and shine!
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a myth!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.