(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-14T00:01:53.044653",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive English 4th Concert Serendipity
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
hololive English 4th Concert Serendipity
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Greetings, CC, my fated rival.
Greetings, Ina, my distant rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Woo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made...
Post about it with hashtag #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay! Thank you AmiAmi for supporting!
Our rivalry!
And for supporting Serendipity,
be sure to check out their booth at...
Anime Expo!
Yay!
Hey, pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me,
all 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round1 USA locations nationwide...
...starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
[Title: hololive English 4th Concert - Serendipity] The concert will be starting soon.
[Attention For Visitors] Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK.
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales] Light Stick, T-Shirt, Acrylic Keychain, Sticker
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales] Acrylic Stand (15 Types)
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales] Button Badge, Acrylic Panel
[Fan Messages from around the world] hololive English 4th Concert - Serendipity
[Title: hololive English 4th Concert - Serendipity] The concert will be starting soon.
[Attention For Visitors] Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Singing bold, we're back again
continuing this odyssey
We'll start this new refrain
brimming with memories
And when the clouded skies become bright
let's reunite!
What's up, everyone? Welcome to holoEN Serendipity!
Yeah! And we are back!
Let's kick off the show with a Myth Medley!
Ready? Set! Three!
Showtime, baby! I would say
today's breakfast was slightly late
Ripping up the stuff, is it really enough?
Cooking, buff, brewing endlessly, why?
Take it easy, what did we learn?
Set a fire in their hearts, let the PC burn
so, optimistic, focus on a quick fix
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks
Growing stronger than ever and never saying die
And I'm aware it's ironic, but where's the freaking lie?
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers, simple as...
Not losing to you young people!
In our hearts, a myth that's priceless in all!
Spanning new dimensions, we can bring another mystery to light
Blending our ascension, dancing in flight, we ignite!
Join us while we're celebrating
in the myth that we're creating
There's another story waiting
through this world and beyond!
Our distant dreams have brought us here
A strong, unyielding bond
guiding us endlessly, will bring us moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on
and though these winds may scatter us, we'll keep this promise
When the moment's finally right
we'll always find a way to reunite!
One, two, three!
Light up, light up, light up, let's begin, we'll start stage-right and shuffle on in
Are you ready? Seal the show, jumping with joy, let's go!
Posing so cute, then we'll keep on entertaining hand in hand
It's our greatest moment yet, a spectacle you'll never forget
We'll party from dusk to dawn, the show will go on and on
Tell them that we're here to stay, and spread the news from Tokyo to Broadway!
Gleaming spotlight
get-get together, we're boogying all night
Beaming so bright
now we're feeling all right!
Since the day we met, we've fought, going strong
and we'll keep moving right along
So keep on dancing on your feet, nothing can stop us, we're perfect, complete
In harmony, no matter where we go, it's meant to be, don't you know?
We're gonna feel so alive when it's our stage
ready to put on another show!
There's an answer out there somewhere
And the muse has whispered truth or dare
The hands of fate are turning the wheel, but no one's keeping score
Take course and be tenacious
'Cause our future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but we are all in
I'll play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
And we'll turn in the betting ring
And these outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
My own chase
A straight face
I've got to try my luck
Keep spinning, spin!
I'm always spinning, spin!
Whoa yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round, jumping into the surge
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on
Our threads unbroken
Cut life by flax and string, casting us together
At the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I'll spin back round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
And with this black or red
I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance
A daring dance
I spin this thread of fate with my own hands
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoa yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Blazing fire!
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
Tension rising to the top
Won't look back, I'll never stop
Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot
It's your fault, baby
Fever burning up inside
It can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
Come on and come on I wanna confess
Baby oh baby I'm gettin' obsessed
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter
Gonna be wanna be ready for more
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
Blazing fire!
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch
It's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm bearing my soul
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play
A dangerous game
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
Look at me, look at me turnin' to ash
Breakin' me shakin' me makin' me crash
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
Drivin' me drivin' me drivin' me crazy
Tellin' me tellin' me what do you mean
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire love, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire love, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire
Go! Go! Go! Go!
I feel it starting
Blazing fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fueling my delusion
I want you burning for me
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me closer, if you dare
Fire love, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire love, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire
Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen
Autofluters
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Let's go!
One, two, three, go!
Go, Gigi! Go, Cecilia!
Autofluters!
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
Look! In the corner, is that the bathroom?
The lines over there are so long!
Oh, no! My seat is far from there!
Ah! Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
All right, let's be German! Oh!
On this day, you were cursed to cope
And keep it in your memory
Oh, come on, you're supposed to hope
And let our black-green madness run and score!
Take our hand, let's fly away
Break a leg, now challenge today
Quick, before your time is up
Give in and be our playmate!
Hop, step, jump, our dreams away
Love yourself, don't be afraid
Find just one condition
Give in, release all inhibitions!
Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi, wait!
Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci, oh, too fast!
Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci, come on, let's fly!
Come on, LA! We want to hear you shout!
Say something, Ceci!
I don't know what to say!
Oh my god, why won't you say something?!
Okay, look, we're performing!
Oh, come on, can't you get one hope
To lose your heart in reverie
There's no way to divert this troupe
So laugh and run, and madness let's restore!
Take our hand, let's fly away
Make a way now, choose the day
Quick, before your time is up
Give in and be our playmate!
Hop, step, jump, our dreams away
Love yourself, don't be afraid
Live up your ambitions
Come on, let's go on with the show!
Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi, wait!
Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci, oh, too fast!
Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci Ceci, come on, let's fly!
Hold on, we're here, we're in LA right now!
We're in LA right now!
Can you even hear us?!
Are you even listening?!
Wait! Your hands are so cold!
And your hands are warm!
We're holding hands!
We're spinning!
All our fun must come to an end
But at least you found a friend
So let us fly and stay
...or rather,
No, you!
Take a hand, let's fly away
Turn around and let us play
Find just one condition, come on
Join in our secret mission, fly...
...away!
More, more, more, more
Come, let's play!
Hello, hello!
Hello!
Hello, LA! How's tonight's very first...
...AX's greatest tweet: "My butt's too big for this seat!"?
Wow, look at it! It's so big and juicy! How impressive!
Hello, everyone!
It's me, Cecilia Immergreen!
And it's me, Ceres Fauna!
And together we are... Ototosister!
Wow, LA! We wanted to do some LA call and response!
So I'm going to say something, and you cheer if you like it, okay?
Okay?
The beach!
HoloLive in LA!
Sitting in traffic!
Booo! Whatever.
Cece, Fauna, in LA!
Okay, everybody! We are so excited to be here at HoloLive...
...Seren-skibidi!
Seren-skibidi.
Please all stand! It is the Fourth of July weekend!
Please stand up, everyone!
For the flag.
Oh, say can you see...
...by the dawn's early light...
...what so proudly...
Okay, okay, okay, shut up, shut up, shut up. That's enough.
Enough of that. Enough of that chit. Okay.
How about we do a Cece-Fauna chant?
No, no, no, not yet, not yet, not yet!
Not yet! "USA" janai. No, no, no.
Not yet! "USA" is not yet. No, no, no.
Okay, guys, since you're standing, we want you to do our chant of our chorus, plus...
Stomping!
...to the beat!
Okay? So, the left side, we want them to be green...
...and this side...
Green! Orange!
Green! Orange! Do it now!
Quickly!
Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect!
Okay, okay, okay. Stomping...
...and you stomp...
...and then we say Cece, Fauna, Cece, Fauna.
Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Madness!
Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Ototosister!
Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Come, let's play!
Together!
Everyone together really fast now.
So, impress us, okay?
Okay.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Madness!
Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Ototosister!
Cece! Fauna! Cece! Fauna! Come, let's play!
Really impressive, guys! That was really, really good.
Maybe America is awesome!
U-S-A! U-S-A! U-S-A!
Yeah, they freaking love us again.
In America! Well, for those at home...
This is sadly the end of the free section, so please...
Wait! There's one more song actually! One more song after this.
Oh, one more song! Sorry, sorry, sorry.
But there's the ticket for the streaming ticket down below, so please check them out.
In the description. Check out the streaming tickets, okay?
All of us forgot to do this today, okay? And...
無料配信は、次の曲で最後になります。
The free stream will end after the next song.
ライブの続きはぜひ配信チケットを買ってみてね！
Please buy a streaming ticket to watch the rest of the concert!
買って見てね！
Please buy it!
Or you can hate us.
All you freaking haters, okay?
Okay, don't hate us.
Don't be a freaking loser.
Don't hate us for the very last part.
Since this is the very first MC, we want you to be as loud as possible, okay?
Hey! So...
Thank you! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Thank you!
We will become a bowling ball and a bowling pin!
And we need you to chant "Serendipity", right? Okay?
Keep chanting until we leave, okay?
Keep chanting until we're gone!
Don't stop until we're gone!
Don't stop!
Okay. Well, one time together, everyone!
Serendipity!
Wheee!
Boing, boing, boing...
I'll be your exit route
Pound the gavel and sentence me to doom
Even though I'm just doing what you do
Decide which lies become the truth
No, you never really thought about it that far
Judging me when I can see you've got the same scars
That's the price that I pay, it's a deep mark
Come, pick your sacrifice
Nail me to your crucifix
Nothing else can fix this
So I'll take the blame
See yourself...
Free, reflex
And not corrected
One request, it's:
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
Murder, murder...
...murder the martyr
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
Murder, murder...
...murder the martyr
One request, it's...
Hypocrisy
I've seen what you do in private rings
All your friends, yeah they know what you really think
To your glory, the masses keep on singing
Ah...
Point at me in a hurry
Pick a scapegoat for the new controversy
Even when I'm buried, hidden, silent, you'll be wary
Please, dear God, show them mercy
Uh
Nail me to your crucifix
Nothing else can fix this
So I'll take the blame
See yourself...
Free, reflex
And not corrected
One request, it's:
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
Murder, murder...
...murder the martyr
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
Murder, murder...
...murder the martyr
One request, it's...
Break me now
Take me down...
Me down...
One request, it's...
I see
Your sins and they're in
Your soul, consuming and
Ignored decay to your core
I'll never win to you
But within, you'll...
Break, break, break, break
And when I...
You will...
Break, break, break, break...
And in your hands, the hammer pounds the nail in
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
Murder, murder...
...murder the martyr
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
Murder, murder...
...murder the martyr
One request, it's...
Do you love me?
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！