(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D SHOWCASE
Nerissa Ravencroft
8/9 20:00 PDT | 8/10 12:00 JST
I was bored to tears
felt like 10,000 years
every back and forth
cut me like a knife
but then a sight in your eyes
and it took me by surprise
and 10,000 volts
brought my heart to life
and I want you here right now
you know 'cause I'm ready to let go
get me through the night somehow
show me all you know
my lips are a mystery
one kiss and you'll agree
if you're down to get familiarized
then baby say it right
N-E-R-I-S-S-A
'kay?
Play with fire
take me higher
if you want to play the game
yeah you gotta say my name
Play with fire
take me higher
if you want to play the game
yeah you gotta say my name
burning up the floor
you got a vibe I can't ignore
in a sea of embers
dancing way into the night
the best is yet to come
'cause you're not like anyone
looking out for someone
shining so bright
there's a scent that's filling up the air
and you're still unaware
that you're falling fast under my spell
oh baby it isn't fair
'cause when I mix up this illusion
I am anyone and everyone
all logic fades away tonight
you gotta say it right
N-E-R-I-S-S-A
'kay?
Play with fire
take me higher
if you want to play the game
yeah you gotta say my name
Play with fire
take me higher
if you want to play the game
yeah you gotta say my name
Take me
higher
It's a game
Play with fire
Say my name
Take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah you gotta say my name
Take me, take me
Play with fire
Take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah you gotta say my name
Play with fire
Take me higher
If you want to play the game
Yeah you gotta say my name
PLAY WITH FIRE
TAKE ME HIGHER
IF YOU WANT TO PLAY THE GAME
YEAH YOU GOTTA SAY MY NAME
Hi-ya darlings! This is Hololive English Advent's
devilish diva, and today, I'm here hosting a cooking show
in my very own kitchen, "Delicious Demonic Dishes"!
As you can see, it's basically my kitchen, however,
I must tell you this is actually a replica. If you'd like to look
on the other side... Yes, you can see the Jailbirds
hard at work making sure that this show goes on without a hitch.
But, today is also about me!
As you can see, it's my 3D debut! How do I look? How is it?
Am I beautiful? Am I kawaii? Am I...
mecha sexy? (Laughs)
Oh, you could look me up and down, I suppose.
Starting with my lovely shoes... going all the way up
to my skirt... and you might realize something's missing.
Since we're cooking today, I've decided to remove my jacket.
So say goodbye to my wings.
But without further ado, I suppose we ought to get cooking,
right? Get right onto things! So, first,
I suppose I have two lovely guests I'd like you to meet,
if they'd like to come on out!
Keke-riki! Hi!
Congratulations 3D debut!
Thank you so much!
Would you like to give an introduction real quick?
Oh! Oh! You two?
Me? Douzo! Okay!
Me? Go ahead! Okay!
待ったかね！待ったよ、待ったかね！
Wait-a-kane! Wait no more, wait-a-kane!
ホロライブJP、秘密結社holoX、鷹嶺ルイだよー！
Hololive JP, Secret Society holoX, Takane Lui here!
And then!
Hi! Hi everybody! Keke-riki!
I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth!
And you know something? We are...
Birds! Birds! Birds! Birds! Birds! Birds!
HoloTori and HoloTori Intern! Intern!
So, will you like, prove yourself to us today?
Mhm! So, they're going to be cooking,
and I'm going to be cooking! But,
shall we start with the first dish? Yes, I am hungry!
I'm hungry too, Lui-nee!
Lui's going to be making us something called Nikujaga!
Okay! Nikujaga! Japanese traditional food! I love Nikujaga!
It's my first time, so I'm very excited! Shall we get started?
Yeah! お願いします！ Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Yeah! Please! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
All right, let's start make Nikujaga!
All right, let's start making Nikujaga!
Yay! Nikujaga, Nikujaga! Abunai, abunai!
Yay! Nikujaga, Nikujaga! Careful, careful!
I'm hungry, hungry, hungry! Please make Nikujaga!
I will make Nikujaga for Nerissa!
Yay! Oh my god! Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry!
You too, don't worry! You too, you too! Thank you!
Yes, senpai too! Senpai too! All right, here,
what we will need for Nikujaga is here!
Ingredients! Take a look! Wow! Memorizing it down!
This is Lui's personal recipe! My Nikujaga recipe! Okay,
let's start with cutting! Vegetable cutting!
Okay, じゃがいも切ります。
Okay, I'll cut the potatoes.
(SFX: Rapid chopping) Oh! And put them in the pan.
Hoi! Yes! Oh, sugoi!
Hop! Yes! Oh, amazing!
And fry! Yes, stir! Oh, it's already in there!
Oh, sugoi! You made them appear out of nowhere!
Oh, amazing! You made them appear out of nowhere!
And please first fry meat! Meat first! Meat first! Yes, meat first!
And then, change the color, changed color,
and put vegetables. Hai! Okay, so not like we did it
and put vegetables. Yes! Okay, so not like we did it
where we threw the potato in first! Yeah! Cook the meat then add
the vegetables and cook them down. Oh, it looks so good!
Yes! Smells good! And changed the color!
Oh, it's okay! Good! Ready! Already!
So, yeah, put water and...
Nikujaga (Meat and Potato Stew)
Potato: 4, Carrot: 2, Onion: 1, Shirataki noodles: 100g, Pork belly: 300g, Soy sauce: 3 tablespoons, Sugar: 3 tablespoons, Cooking sake: 3 tablespoons, dashi powder: 2 teaspoons, Mirin: 3 tablespoons, Salad oil: As needed
Patiently...
Oh, yeah.
Uh-oh, she's stunned.
Nerissa, beef good.
Hey, throw the water.
Okay.
Hey!
Oh, thank you!
What did you put in there?
Yeah, waritan and...
Ah, there we go.
Waritan.
I just threw everything.
Ah, everything, okay.
Okay, so please wait 10 minutes.
10 minutes?!
Yeah, yeah, then we will cover.
Cover?
Get a lid for it.
It's good!
I question.
I have a question.
はい。
Yes.
Why is it like a lid like inside and not like on the top?
Why is the lid inside and not on the top?
Ah, I see, I see. Um...
日本語でいいですか？
Is Japanese okay?
はいはい。
Yes, yes.
はい。味が染みやすくね、なります。
Yes. It makes the flavor soak in more easily.
Ah, it will be like easier to soak in the flavor?
Ah, it'll make it easier to soak in the flavor?
Yes, yes, yes.
美味しい。
Delicious.
はい、More delicious.
Yes, more delicious.
ワクワク。
I'm excited.
はい。
Yes.
10 minutes wait. Wait, wait.
Wait 10 minutes. Wait, wait.
Eh? I'm waiting patiently.
♪ Dun dun dun... ♪
It takes so long.
I can't wait 10 minutes.
Yeah, I don't want to wait 10 minutes either.
Can we hurry up?
Yeah, can we use some magic maybe?
To speed up the process.
That's some magic?
Is that magic?
Alright.
So, please put love.
So, please add love.
Ah, okay.
Yeah, it's magic.
Okay.
Chu-ki! Chu-ki! Chu-ki Beam!!!
After 10 minutes.
Okay!
Easy.
We'll check. Check.
Yeah, check.
Take off.
Take it off.
Oh, that looks good.
Check soft or hard.
Check if it's soft or hard.
Ah, a little bit...
Hard?
Hard. It's still...
So, if hard, please wait more 10 minutes.
So, if it's hard, please wait another 10 minutes.
Okay.
Alright.
But magic.
Hap!
Okay.
Just a snap of the finger.
Oh yes.
Okay.
Stop.
Yes, okay.
Good.
So, complete!
So, it's complete!
Complete! Finish!
Complete! Finished!
Delicious Demonic Dishes WITH NERISSA RAVENCROFT
Okay!
My Nikujaga, Rui's Nikujaga.
My Nikujaga, Lui's Nikujaga.
I'm so excited.
As you guys can see...
It smells great.
良い匂い。
Good smell.
And it looks good too.
As you guys can see...
This is the real, the real Nikujaga.
It's real.
Mhm.
But, I'm hungry.
Okay.
Me too.
Lui-nee is probably hungry.
Hungry.
Shall we try?
Yes!
召し上がれ。
Enjoy your meal.
いただきます！
Let's eat!
First I go for carrot.
First I'll go for the carrot.
Mmm! Mmm!
Oh, this is actually really good.
美味しいです。
It's delicious.
Eat, rice... It's really good.
We have no rice now but...
We have no rice right now, but...
Today is no rice.
Today, there's no rice.
Without rice is also okay.
It's okay without rice too.
美味しい？
Is it good?
It's like... my impression...
It's like... my impression is...
It makes me think it's a very homey flavor.
Of like, um... it feels like this is
Like, um... it feels like this is
something I would eat as a kid
and want to eat, like want to come home and eat,
you know, after a long day.
美味しい？ Very good.
Is it good? Very good.
So good.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
Mmm, 美味しい。柔らかい。
Mmm, delicious. It's soft.
Please listen.
Yeah.
Mmm!
うまい！うまい！
Delicious! Delicious!
ルイさん。
Lui-san.
ルイ先輩じゃなくて...
Not Lui-senpai...
ルイさん。
Lui-san.
Lui, can you make every day for me?
Lui, can you make this every day for me?
Every day? Nyun.
Every day? No way.
But, easy to cooking.
But, it's easy to cook.
She taught you, so now you can make it yourself.
Okay.
Yes.
But...
Ah, it's so good.
I'm like really hungry.
I want to eat it all.
I give you one.
I'll give you one.
I will cook.
Are you?
Yes.
Okay! 美味しい！
Okay! Delicious!
肉じゃが every day.
Nikujaga every day.
But I want to eat like fried...
Fried...
Eh? Chicken?
Or fish?
Right!
I want to eat.
We do happen to have the Queen of Fried Chicken
with us today.
Mhm.
You have to make your signature dish for us.
But I want to eat more, please!
Let's go, shall we?
Let's go!
Yay!!!
It is time to bring KFP to your kitchen.
It's time to bring KFP to your kitchen.
I'm gonna make the best fried chicken
I've ever made in my whole life.
Yes, I want to try.
I want to eat fried chicken.
Oh.
We're missing... thank you for the beautiful intro.
Yeah, we're missing some livestock.
What are we gonna do?
Oh.
Well, I actually have the perfect thing
right here.
Oh.
Jimmy! Oh my god!
Oh, Jimmy!
Take me instead! Take me instead!
No, sorry Jimmy.
If anyone's qualified to do this, it's me.
As a past KFP.
Oh my god!
Past?
Not anymore?
Well, I mean this used to be my form, right?
I guess so.
So, but now I look like this.
But now I look like this.
So anyway, Jimmy, goodbye!
No, Jimmy!
完璧です。
It's perfect.
Mmm, yum.
あ、かわいそう！
Ah, how pitiful!
Wait, maybe...
I can't even look!
Do you think he's too big?
I think maybe he needs to be a bit smaller, don't you?
Really?
I'll do it! Stop!
I'm getting so small!
Extreme violence!
Stop!
うわ、完璧です。Perfect.
Wow, it's perfect. Perfect.
Thank you, Jimmy, for your contribution.
Gosh, this is so sad.
It's okay. He'd be happy.
Are... Is this going to be enough for all of us?
Oh, there will... Yeah, it's... somehow...
Delicious. We'll use magic.
Alright then, here we have the the batter and the flour.
So I'll I'll do this for you, okay? I'll do my best. 頑張ります！
So I'll I'll do this for you, okay? I'll do my best. I'll do my best!
頑張って！
Good luck!
美味しく作る。I will do my best.
I'll make it delicious. I will do my best.
Oh, let me take it up so you can see clearly.
Mhm, secret spice.
Yeah, it's got secret spices in it.
We're getting deep in there, Tenchou. Ah!
Jimmy looking shiny.
Yeah. Wow!
Okay, and then we go into the flour. The flour.
Oh, it's nice and coated.
As you can see, some spices were mixed onto that too, but they're secret. Secret.
Nice.
Okay, and with that, it's time. We have a 160 degrees Celsius heated up...
...oil thingy. What's it called?
So dangerous.
A deep fryer.
Deep fryer! Yeah, I knew that. That was also a test question.
So... here we go!
Oh, stick it in! And another one!
My wing! My wing! It's so hot!
Oh, so dangerous!
Oh, it's already... oh, it's already finished.
Whoa, that was fast.
Oh my god!
Here, want one?
どうぞ、どうぞ。
Here you go, here you go.
Oh! 熱っ！Oh, どうぞ、どうぞ。
Oh! Hot! Oh, here you go, here you go.
熱っ！熱っ！It's on the floor! Oh, it's on the floor!
Hot! Hot! It's on the floor! Oh, it's on the floor!
Ah! Yay!
Yay! You've got... you've got crazy hands to be able to handle that sort of heat, Phoenix.
I guess so. It doesn't feel like anything at all. Yeah, nothing at all.
Fini!
Finished! Thank you, Jimmy!
Delicious Demonic Dishes with NERISSA RAVENCROFT
And now, finally, the food of dreams for any KFP fan...
...the the proper... or the biggest fear... Kiara Fried Phoenix.
Your final form!
Final form KFP, you're looking at it.
But without further ado, I really want to taste it, don't you?
Yeah.
Okay, wait. 乾杯！乾杯！Cheers, Jimmy!
Okay, wait. Cheers! Cheers! Cheers, Jimmy!
Okay! Cheers!
We're really eating chicken right now.
Mmm!
Mmm! Na, I did a good job.
Mmm! See, I did a good job.
You did!
Wait, there's like a lemony taste in it, I think. Where's the lemon come from?
Did I put lemon in there?
You must have.
Maybe you put zest? It was in the batter already probably.
Mhm. 美味しい。
Mhm. It's delicious.
Shouldn't you know? You're the CEO.
Um... spice is good. I let my my Jimmys work for me.
Mmm! Mhm! Na, this is really really good. Mhm.
Mmm! Mhm! Man, this is really really good. Mhm.
Maybe a little bit... dry?
It's very juicy.
After one bite, yeah... I want to more bite. Yeah.
More bite. More bite. I want to eat. Yeah.
I want some sauce. I want sweet-sour sauce.
Mmm, so delicious.
I understand.
Oh, yeah. It's good party food.
We're having a party. Yeah! Should we do a sleepover too? I would like that.
Yeah, in-your-background party. Good job.
Thank you, thank you. Dankeschon. Dankeschon.
Thank you, thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, Jimmy. Your sacrifice is letting us eat the best food ever.
KFP, you're the best. Thank you for your dedication.
Thank you, Jimmy! Thank you, world! Thank you, KFP!
You know, you guys have both cooked, but I haven't cooked anything yet, actually.
So, I think I have something special. It's not technically my dish.
However, it's using things from HoloLive English...
to make something 美味しいです。美味しいそう。
...to make something delicious. It looks delicious.
So, if you'd like, without further ado, I would like to cook for you, so let's go!
Let's go! Thank you, Rissa cooking! It better be good! Cooking fried!
Delicious Demonic Dishes with NERISSA RAVENCROFT
Here we are, ready to make the last dish of the day. Dessert?
Uh... well, behind us, what we have all of the ingredients. If you'll take a look...
I call this dish: HoloLive Soup. HoloEN Soup. Very good.
Wait, Nerissa... Why, Nerissa?
No, no, no. These were donated by my senpais to me to make a soup with.
I asked senpai, I said, 'I want to make a delicious soup, so what will you give me?' And these...
Eh? Sorry, I important job. Okay, see you, see you, see you!
Eh? Sorry, I have an important job. Okay, see you, see you, see you!
See you! Let's give her a chance, maybe... yeah, we'll try. It could be good. We don't know yet. Go, go, all right.
Yes, I guess I'll get started.
Oh, okay. Right into it.
So, uh, we're going to be making it in this big cauldron.
Ooh! Magical, mystical.
And we're starting out with some chicken salt donated by Bae-senpai.
She gave me that before as a present!
Oh! Oh hey! Hey!
I'm so sorry! You can't do that!
Oh my God, Bijou, take it out!
No, I, you know, I think it's fine. I think it's fine that way.
Oh... Why? Oh, what's next?
Uh, this is donated by Shiori. It's an eggplant...
...and it looks like Yorick, her little mascot guy.
It's so... it's so cute, isn't he?
So yeah, just plop! Right in there.
Oh! Oh, not cutting?
Oh yeah, you know, if we cook it long enough it'll like disintegrate, right?
Alright, alright. So yeah, it doesn't really make sense to cut it up...
...because it's going to cut itself up.
Okay, like what do you have the kitchen for, right? Under a knife, we don't need that. No cutting.
And this one, can you predict who it could be from?
It says... Bijou's feet salt? Feet salt! Feet flakes!
Yeah! No!
So just... oh my god! Oh my god!
I can like smell the salt.
Really? It's okay.
Now we have this... this is from Mumei-senpai.
Don't drop the whole thing! Try to be more careful! Maybe this time...
Okay, ah! Here! Careful, careful, careful!
Oh my God! It's okay! 大丈夫！大丈夫！
Oh my God! It's okay! It's okay! It's okay!
Horrible! Why 大丈夫？ Why 大丈夫？ Why did you start?
Horrible! Why okay? Why okay? Why did you start?
No, not 大丈夫. We still have the sapling!
No, not okay. We still have the sapling!
Still have a sapling, which I'm sure this will absorb all the salt, right?
Our veggies, yes! So good.
But first, I want to cut off this...
Oh! No! It's sad!
Sorry about your haircut.
Ah, hey! Yeah, well, I guess that's fine. Could have cut it a bit more, it's small.
And then we just have a little bit of garnish to put on top.
How about we eat separately? No, no, no, they're donuts!
Donated by Fuwawa and Mococo respectively.
They each gave me one, so let's go ahead and put them in!
Oh no! No! Oh no!
However, it doesn't stop there. Now we have to stir the soup.
So we have to give it a really good stir with all those ingredients.
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
Oh yeah, I think it's... look, it's coming together!
You see the colors? Green!
Yes, the color... it's fine, it's fine. Look, it's not even there yet.
No, that looks like melon soda or something.
Just a little more, huh? Perfect! Much better! Much better!
Yeah, not perfect. 紫スープ。
Yeah, not perfect. Purple soup.
Oh, 紫スープ。 はい。
Oh, purple soup. Yes.
Oh my God. It's perfect. It looks like something from Hololive, right?
And no. Don't you think? I'm sure it's delicious.
I don't want to eat. Yeah, you don't want to eat... Really good 肉じゃが。
I don't want to eat. Yeah, you don't want to eat... Really good meat and potato stew.
Is there more 肉じゃが？ More 肉じゃが？ Can we just finish?
Is there more meat and potato stew? More? Can we just finish?
So let's try! Let's eat! Let's eat! Let's eat!
No, oh my god, oh my god. No, no, no, I don't need... let's eat!
It's fine, you guys have to taste it! No, oh my god!
You don't have to try, get back here! It's... this is... I'm your oshi so you have to!
3D debut anniversary, okay. Okay, okay, happy 3D debut. All right, let's go!
Delicious Demonic Dishes with NERISSA RAVENCROFT
And we're finally ready. Here is the final dish, as we've served it up.
Uh, don't you think it looks delicious?
I don't even want to look.
Why? It looks good! Come on! It's purple, it's got donuts in it...
...it's going to be delicious.
Looks like grape juice... it shouldn't look like that. Oh, no.
No, it's okay, let's try it! Without further ado, abomination!
How's it smell? How's the, uh, good point?
Eh? Smell is okay.
Oh! Smell is okay! See? See? See? Smell is okay!
Come on, don't knock it before you try it.
It's like burning my nostrils. It'll be okay.
いただきます！ Same timing.
Let's eat! Same timing.
No! What did you do to us? Oh my god! I didn't do anything!
She poisoned us! Oh my god! Maybe she wants to take control of Holotori!
No! No, no, no! I... it's not... it's really not that bad!
Ugh, what have you... call you alive? It's not that bad, it's fine!
Give... you're delicious! Yeah, I'll try again, see? Maybe hers tastes different.
Oh my god. Is it the same? Yeah, same.
Yeah, same, same, same. Cannot. No, sorry, Nerissa.
It's hearty and it's filling! Enough, enough. Thank you.
This is not how you can treat your senpais. No!
Congratulations 3D debut, congratulations! Stop! Bye-bye!
See ya!
Why are you guys...?
Bye-bye. Thank you. Bye-bye.
ごちそうさまでした！
Thank you for the meal!
肉じゃが食べよう！肉じゃが肉じゃが！
Let's eat nikujaga! Nikujaga, nikujaga!
Unbelievable.
I can't believe this. Well, of course, Jailbirds...
...I'm sure you don't think such a thing about my cooking, right?
Surely you see it and you thought, "Ah, the brilliant purple color is wonderful!"
So... uh, won't you tell me? Won't you praise me?
Come on, Jailbirds, don't you like it?
Wait, wasn't it delicious?
Ah! What the...! Stop!
No! Ah! No! Stop it! Oh! No!
I guess that's it for my cooking show.
This is probably the pilot episode and the only episode.
So, I guess if you enjoyed it, we won't be back.
So... time to distract you with a song performance!
ワ！
Wa!
Let's go!
LOVEマシーン
LOVE Machine
Lyrics ・ Music: つんく
Lyrics ・ Music: Tsunku
あんたにゃ もったいない
You're too good for them
あたしゃ ほんと ナイスバディ・バディ・バディ
I've got a really nice body, body, body
自分でも 恐い
I'm even scared of myself
タダじゃない じゃない じゃない アハー
I'm not cheap, not cheap, not cheap, aha
奔放な 恋をしたっていいじゃない
It's okay to have a wild love, right?
寂しけりゃ EVERYBODY BODY BODY
If you're lonely, everybody body body
誰にも 分からない
Nobody knows
恋愛って いつ火がつくのかダイナマイト
When will love catch fire? It's dynamite
恋はダイナマイト
Love is dynamite
こんなに 不景気だって
Even in such a recession,
恋はインフレーション
love is inflation
こんなに 優しくされたら
If I'm treated this kindly...
アカルイ
To a bright...
ミライニ
...future
就職希望だわ WOW WOW WOW WOW
I want to be employed there! Wow wow wow wow
日本の未来は
Japan's future is...
WOW WOW WOW WOW
世界がうらやむ
Envied by the world
YEAH YEAH YEAH YEAH
恋をしようじゃないか
Why don't we fall in love?
WOW WOW WOW WOW
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
なんだか 物足りない
Somehow something's missing
どこにいたって
No matter where you are...
愛しててほしいわ
I want you to love me
自分でも 伝えるの
I'll tell you myself
恥ずかしい じゃない じゃない じゃない ナイナイ
It's not embarrassing, not not not, no no
理想の ふたりのダンス
If we dance our ideal dance...
憧れよ EVERYBODY BODY BODY
It's a dream, everybody body body
誰しも 気付いてない
Nobody has noticed
恋愛って 夢の落とし穴ミステリー
Love is a mystery, a pitfall in dreams
恋はミステリー
Love is a mystery
そんなの 不自然だって
Even if it's unnatural,
恋のインサイダー
a love insider
それでも 重宝されちゃあ
Even so, if I'm valued...
シアワセ
Happiness...
クルヒモ
...comes the day
キャンセル待ちだわ WOW WOW WOW WOW
I'm on the waiting list! Wow wow wow wow
あんたの笑顔は
Your smile is...
WOW WOW WOW WOW
世界がうらやむ
Envied by the world
YEAH YEAH YEAH YEAH
夢があるじゃないか
Don't we have dreams?
WOW WOW WOW WOW
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
LOVE LOVE LOVEマシーン
Love love love machine
WOW WOW WOW WOW
LOVE LOVE LOVEステーション
Love love love station
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
LOVE LOVE LOVE マシーン
LOVE LOVE LOVE Machine
Wow Wow Wow Wow
LOVE LOVE LOVE ランドリー
LOVE LOVE LOVE Laundry
Wow Wow Wow Wow
日本の未来は (Wow Wow Wow Wow)
Japan's future is (Wow Wow Wow Wow)
世界がうらやむ (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
The world envies (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
恋もしようじゃないか (Wow Wow Wow Wow)
Let's fall in love, shall we (Wow Wow Wow Wow)
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
モーニング娘。も (Wow Wow Wow Wow)
Morning Musume too (Wow Wow Wow Wow)
あんたもあたしも (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
You and I too (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
みんなも社長さんも (Wow Wow Wow Wow)
Everyone and the company president too
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
LOVEマシーン
LOVE Machine
Oh, hi darlings.
I didn't quite see you there.
It's not that kind of thing though.
Welcome to my studio.
This is where I do all of my recording.
Of course you've heard of it, but this is your first time being here.
But more importantly, my little guy here...
これ、これ、はい
Here, here, yes
Look, it's Shadow.
My baby.
My baby bird.
Isn't he cute?
I know you guys are always begging to see him, so there you go.
And now that we're done cooking,
I've gone ahead and put my jacket back on.
Very nice, right?
It really adds to the appeal.
But today is not only all about me,
I have some wonderful special guests
if you'd like to come on out and introduce yourselves.
Hi daddy! Daddy!
What's up darlings? It's your boy.
Darlings?
I don't know, I'm just trying to match the vibe that you have going here, Neriss. This place is awesome.
Yeah, you like it?
Yeah!
マリンです！
I'm Marine!
カリオペです！
I'm Calliope!
I'm so happy to have these two wonderful ladies here with me today.
Thanks for inviting us.
Congratulations! Congrats!
ありがとうございます。 3D、ありがとう。
Thank you very much. 3D, thank you.
Looks so good. You look lovely.
Yeah?
Well, I'm so excited because we have a song we're going to be performing for all of you.
I know, a trio between Calliope, Marine, and Nerissa. Who would have thunk it?
But the team is not quite ready yet.
So first I thought we could 練習...
So first I thought we could practice...
practice a script that we are performing.
Because you know, we are professional actors. はい。
Because you know, we are professional actors. Yes.
Yeah, this thing.
This thing, that script.
That script for that thing.
Yeah, do you remember what our show is called?
I sure do,
but can you go ahead and I guess recite it for the audience who doesn't know.
It is going to be... um... good question,
yeah... it's on here, you see?
Oh, check it. Can you read?
Yeah, totally. Can you read?
I think, "A Brush with Death: A Pirate's Tale".
So please look forward to it coming out on hololivetv.com.
Totally real site, right?
Eventually. I mean, it'll be out at some point.
But, positions! Oh my god,
let's go everyone. Let's go, let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
Be ready. It's a good one.
Okay, okay. Start!
My Goddess of Love! I have the treasure!
愛の女神様！お宝を持ってきました！
I... I... finished! My present, please!
私……やりました！ごほうび……ください。
A wonderful job finding my lost wares, Captain.
私が失いしものをよくぞ見つけました。
A wonderful job finding my lost wares.
But you must realize this was not the treasure I spoke of.
しかしそれは私の言った『宝物』ではありません。
What!?
え！
Of course not! It never was.
It was always about what you had, not what I lost.
全ッ然違います！私ではなく、あなたが持っていたものとの方なのです！
Of course not! It was always about what you had, not what I lost!
All of these things were stolen from my
idiot siblings thousands of years ago.
この宝は全て、何千年も前に私の姉妹が盗まれたもの！
All of these were stolen from my siblings thousands of years ago!
I planted these here for safe keeping, and they were safe,
at least until the waves took this place.
宝はここに埋めて隠していたのですが、ある日大波が全部さらっていってしまった……。
I planted these here for safe keeping, until the waves took them...
You lost the whole island!?
島ごと全部失くしたってこと？
What!? No!
ち、違います！
W-What!? No!
What I am saying is I knew where it was the whole time! I...
宝のありかははずっと分かっていました！ただ……
I knew where it was the whole time! However...
But... what did she see in you?
こんなやつがよかったんだ？
Did you really like this fellow?
A beautiful young woman like her, with an old hag like you.
あんあ素敵な女性が、こんなババアと……。
A lovely woman like her, with an old hag like you...
Old hag!?
ババア！？
I am young, beautiful!
若くて美人でしょうが！
I'm young and beautiful!
Yeah, and I'm the Goddess of Death.
じゃあ私は死神でも名乗ろうかしら。
Well then, maybe I'll call myself the Reaper.
Look at you, you're creeping slowly towards your grave.
「自称」より言ったもの勝ちですものね？
It's better to say it than to just 'self-proclaim', right?
はあ！？
Hah!?
I'm a sexy captain! Pirate captain! Hmph.
Yes, well. Moving on...
I've brought you here to exact my revenge on you, Captain...
...for the untimely death of your lover.
I know that you were the one to take her life...
...and I will not stand for it! You will suffer by my hands!
はあ！？ちょっと待って...
Hah!? Wait a minute...
You know, this quest was just a distraction. It was meant to keep you from watching over your...
...beautiful and sexy lover. And leave room for me to take your place.
But now your lover is dead, and I am left with a hole in my heart.
You will pay for what you've done here and now!
That's enough of that!
Death? What are you doing here? Don't you usually work the graveyard shift?
Unless you're planning on bringing back my beautiful little bird to me,
you can turn right around and poof yourself back to wherever it is you came from.
Well, maybe you don't know me as well as you pretend to.
Or the pirate captain, as well as you think either.
あっ...！
Ah...!
Look, you can go ahead and smite that human if you like.
I'm not going to try and stop you.
But I really think you might regret doing that.
You would take the side of someone so cruel
that they would take the life of their own lover?
I expected better of you!
Besides, how am I supposed to take their place
and make that beautiful cream puff my wife if this fool here has killed her?
Wait, what? You want the Captain!?
No! Where did you even get that from?
Why would you even think that I would want someone as old and badly dressed as you?
でもでも……
But, but...
No, it has always been that treasure box of wonder.
That twin-tail talent.
That sweet girl who can do no sin,
that you kept back on land!
That is the one I have wanted!
You? No, not at all.
Yeah, but you just called that treasure box of wonder a hag not too minutes ago.
What are you even talking about?
I called this wrinkly old wreck here in front of me a hag, not my beautiful bride-to-be!
Oh man, this is rich. You really have no idea, do you, Nerissa?
Why are you laughing!?
I am not old! I am 17!
Let me see if I can help you here. Maybe all the beauty is being hidden by...
...this!
I am not the pirate captain!
No, she is actually his much more beautiful lover, who you claim to love.
That's right, here is the Marine you thought was lost.
That's not possible! I would have known! Or... I would never have...
I have a lot to say, but my most pressing question is:
How on earth did you not know?
You know, that's fair, because they look nothing alike.
But how was I supposed to know?
How did such a simple mustache make her look so decidedly unattractive?
It's just a mustache!
I'm still cute!
Of course you are, dear. She's just an imbecile.
Wait, why am I still mean?
Let me change that. Um, anyway...
But my dear, her stupidity can't protect you now that you've broken our deal.
A broken deal with Death means that your soul is mine!
This is all your fault, drama queen.
You claim to love Marine, but you had no idea that she was hiding behind a mustache.
Because of your idiocy... her soul is mine now!
Me? How was I supposed to know?
She was never supposed to be on this quest in the first place!
Wait, if she's here, then that must mean the real Pirate Captain is dead.
And that's your domain, Miss Reaper.
If the Captain is gone, it means
you have had some responsibility in all of this.
You could have stopped all of this at any time.
無罪！無罪！
Innocent! Innocent!
Oh, so you want to blame me for all of this? It wasn't me who killed the Captain.
I only protected Marine after she begged for me to help hide her identity from you.
She just wanted to complete your stupid quest in honor of her lover.
Yes, but you shouldn't have agreed to hide her.
I would have known if you hadn't meddled,
and I would have given her my favor without this quest.
魂...?
My soul...?
You're lucky she's here to keep me from hurting you.
I'd like to see you try. Besides, this one wasn't me.
あの...
Umm...
Marine put bananas in his tea.
Eh!?
Deathly allergic to bananas...
So that's how it was...
Didn't see that one coming. Hehehe.
Marine also wanted an adventure,
but he said no, so banana's...
Uh, that's... huh. Wasn't expecting that.
Unfortunately, that means that you, a human, meddled in matters of life and death.
However, after that night you... uh, helped me catch that escaped soul a few weeks back,
I haven't been able to stop thinking about you.
It looks like you've already won the heart of the Grim Reaper, so consider yourself lucky.
Oh, that night?!
Night? Don't you dare!
I will protect this woman from her own crimes even in death.
No one else has to know that she was the one who took the life of her lover.
It can all just be an unfortunate accident.
Banana peels are known to be slippery.
Calliope!!
No!! She'll never be able to escape the Reaper's clutches and I can't allow that to happen.
After all, this is your fault, Mori, for even letting her take this deal in the first place.
But the banana...
Mori's doing. It's her fault. Her fault. Ah!
Come, Marine... If you come with me, I can protect you from even death itself.
She can't get you in the realm of the immortal.
You absolute...!
But...
Shut up.
You'll be known as the goddess who protected the banana bandit!
The others won't be very happy with you.
And you think that matters to me? Why?
Banana...?
They'll blame it on her, of course!
No, the best course of action is for me to take her, to protect her.
Enough talk. Think fast, Nerissa!
Innocent!!
Wait! Just a minute!
Otsu-Karaba-ou!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you everyone!
And, good news girls! It seems like the music team is already for us,
so why don't we head over and show them our super cool song performance.
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Whoa, cool place you got.
Thank you.
荒れ狂う季節の中を 二人きり さらり
Through the wild seasons, just the two of us, so casually.
明けてゆく夕日の中を 今夜も さらり さらり
Through the fading sunset, tonight as well, so casually, so casually.
どれほど打ち果てようと 最後には笑いたい
No matter how beaten down I get, I want to laugh at the end.
何のために戦おうとも 時は愛以外
No matter what I'm fighting for, time is nothing but love.
新しい日々は探さずとも 常にここに
New days are always here, even if I don't look for them.
色々見てきたけれど この瞳は永遠に きらり
I've seen many things, but these eyes will forever shine.
あれほど生きてきたけど 全ては夢みたい
I've lived so long, but everything seems like a dream.
あれもこれも魅力的でも 私は君がいい
Even if this and that are charming, I'd rather have you.
どこにいたの 探してたよ 連れてって 連れてって
Where were you? I was looking for you. Take me away, take me away.
何もかも捨ててゆくよ どこまでも どこまでも
I'll throw everything away. Anywhere, anywhere.
荒れ狂う季節の中を 群衆の中を
Through the wild seasons, through the crowds...
君とならば さらり さらり
If I'm with you, it's so casual, so casual.
新しい日々も捨てたもんじゃないね 全てがきらり
New days aren't so bad either, everything is shining.
失くしてしまったものを 振り返って ほろり
Looking back at the things I've lost, a tear falls.
時には途方に暮れて ただ風に吹かれて ゆらり
Sometimes I'm at a loss, just swaying in the wind.
行き先は聞いたの 行き先は決めたの
I asked for the destination, I decided on the destination.
迷わずに行きたいけど しょうがないよね
I want to go without hesitation, but it can't be helped, right?
何かが分かったようで 何も分かってなくて
It seems like I've understood something, but I haven't understood anything.
だけどそれが分かって 本当に良かった
But knowing that makes me really glad.
新しい日々は探さずとも 常にここに ここに ここに ここに
New days are always here, even if I don't look for them, here, here, here...
...と未来とも
...and the future.
出逢いとも
Meeting with people.
言えば 握手とも
Or a handshake.
ああ 惹かれてたけれど
Ah, I was drawn to it, but
全ては夢みたい
Everything seems like a dream.
あれもこれも
That and this,
魅力的でも
though they are attractive,
私は君がいい
it's you that I want.
どこにいたの 探していたよ
Where were you? I was looking for you.
連れてって 連れてって
Take me away, take me away.
何もかも捨ててくよ
I'll leave everything behind.
どこまでも どこまでも
Anywhere at all, anywhere at all.
荒れ狂う季節の中も
Through the raging seasons,
群衆の中も
and through the crowds,
君となら さらり さらり
with you, smoothly and easily.
新しい日々も 拙い過去も
New days and a clumsy past,
全てが きらり
it all sparkles.
Ah, yeah!
Thank you guys!
Thank you so much for coming out.
That was so fun!
Thank you!
Oh my god!
大好き チュチュチュ！
I love you! Mwah mwah mwah!
Wow, it's getting hot in here. Calli, thank you for coming too!
Yeah, no problem. I'm happy to be here. Congrats on 3D!
Thank you! It made it so special to have you two as guests...
...and to get to sing with you two. That's crazy!
But we still have one more song after this one.
Not all of us, just me, sadly.
We have to say goodbye to these lovely ladies.
But the Jailbird Tech have to set it up...
...so we're going to say goodbye for a few seconds...
...and I'll be right back.
Let's go!
Bye bye!
So, this last song for today is actually going to be...
...the titular track of my new EP, "In My Feelings".
Song is the same name.
I really worked hard on this song. I think it came out great.
So, I hope you guys will enjoy listening to...
...my first live performance of it.
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen.
Can't believe the words that came out of your mouth
Never thought that what we have would go this route
Can see the clock is ticking
But I just can't stop thinking
Every little memory's tormenting me
Counting all of my mistakes
Want to sleep but it won't happen
Waiting for the day to break
I'm wide awake reliving the past and
Still haunted by the ghost of you
Everywhere I look it's like you're always there
Despite the fact that I'm on my own
I'm in my feelings, like rain fall on the ground
They're soaking through the sheets and drenching every single inch of me
I'm in my feelings, it's falling all around
Inside this never-ending downpour there's no escape to oh far
Thinking about the night you left and you lied
That morning I had woken, my heart that froze and broken
Feeling like I could drown in the tears I cried
Sinking down into the blue
Like I'm submerged in water
Chills straight down to the bone
Struggling to breathe just thinking about it
Still haunted by the ghost of you
Everywhere I look it's like you're always there
Despite the fact you left me alone
I'm in my feelings, like rain fall on the ground
They're soaking through the sheets and drenching every single inch of me
I'm in my feelings, it's falling all around
Inside this never-ending downpour there's no escape to oh far
Who you're seeing
What you're doing
Where you're going
I don't want to know
Why you're coming back, I don't...
Don't need you to call me
Don't need you to love me
I don't want your weak explanation
Know that I never met your expectations
Now I just want you out of my head
Want to move along, carry on
Hold my head high, but
I'm in my feelings, feelings
Like raindrops on the ground
They're soaking through the sheets
And drenching every single inch of me
I'm in my feelings, feelings
It's falling all around
But at the end of this downpour
Is a highway waitin' for
I'm in my feelings, feelings
I'm in my feelings, feelings, ooh
At the end of this downpour
Is a rainbow I had prayed for
No way, so way, been clawed.
That wasn't enough, was it, Jailbirds? Please!
Jailbirds, do you know what time it is? Ten...
Encore!
Oh, Jailbird!
You guys wanted one more song?
Ah, I see. Come here, come here! Ah!
Well, I suppose if it's you guys asking,
then how can I resist?
But, you know, I am going to
perform one more song for you.
I think it's going to be super hype.
But before that, I have some
important things to tell you about.
But first, ah, reminiscing already.
Today was so much fun.
I had such a good time cooking with Lulu
and Takanashi Kiara-senpai.
The Nikujaga was so delicious.
Like honestly, of everything,
I think that was the most delicious thing.
And I really did fulfill my title
as the Demon of Soup,
because I made a really weird, mind you, soup.
But it was good!
And then getting to read that really silly script
with Marine and Calli, it was so much fun.
The banana... banana...
Oh my god, Marine is a natural comedian,
obviously, because she's in Hololive.
We're all comedians.
And I've had so much fun performing for you guys.
If you enjoyed that last song, "In My Feelings,"
I hope you did.
I was so happy to finally get to
share that with you guys.
So I hope you've enjoyed everything
that I've given you so far.
But without further ado,
I do have some goods for you,
or a good for you. So let's go ahead
and take a look.
Nerissa Ravencroft
Paper Knife
Ah, here it is!
So this is based off of my tuning fork,
which some of you may know,
some of you may not know, is also
actually a microphone.
But as you can see, this is a paper knife,
or a paper cutter.
Do you have mail that has been,
you know, really annoying you as you try to open it?
You're like, "Ah, I can't get it!"
Well, this will solve that.
Do you have a problem and you just like cutting paper?
This will help you too.
Any of your paper cutting needs, this will help you.
Again, it's pretty much a replica of my weapon.
So if you think that's cool, if you want it,
it also comes in a cool box.
So please do consider picking it up.
My paper knife. Hehe.
So also, as I already mentioned before,
my EP just came out. It's already
been out for a little bit now.
But if you haven't heard it, there's three new songs.
It also includes a fourth, "Say My Name,"
which of course is already a fan favorite.
But if you haven't already, it's
available on streaming services,
it's available on YouTube. Please...
Please go give it a listen.
I worked so hard on it and I'm so proud
of all the songs.
Of course you heard the titular track
"In My Feelings".
I, you know, that one, I poured a lot of myself into.
I think it's just so fantastic.
But there's two other songs that you have
yet to hear today.
So if you haven't already,
please go ahead and check it out.
Again, so proud of it and I'm hoping...
...all of them can get to a million listens
on Spotify.
So please listen to them lots and lots and lots!
But without further ado, you guys did call me
on here for an encore.
So I guess I'll stop shilling and I'll start singing.
So without further ado, please listen to
"Sweetest Scarlet".
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Looking to find the words to tell you
This feeling's brand new, trying to make do
Still I can feel my heart is driving
You've got me lost inside the groove,
wishing you would make a move
Cause I can't even look away
Your eyes are shining, still there's something
that you're hiding
Won't you tell me with the warmth of your lips
How you found me was lonely,
then you filled my heart up wholly
Let me know, let me know, let me know
what keeps you smiling by my side
If above or below me,
baby you're my one and only
Let me show, let me show, let me show you
I can love you through the night, yeah
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Baby, you're on my mind all of the time
Yeah, you plus me, I can get behind
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Truly you got my heart right from the start
You fill me with your love
Standing with you beneath the moonlight,
you dazzle though it's midnight
You shine so bright, what is happening?
Longing to have you through the cold night
Now I'm a victim to your charms,
stop delaying hold me close and warm
We'll melt into each other's arms
Don't need permission, my decision's
already made clear
You could feel it from the moment we kissed
How you found me was lonely,
then you filled my heart up wholly
Let me know, let me know, let me know
what keeps you smiling by my side
If above or below me,
baby you're my one and only
Let me show, let me show, let me show you
I can love you through the night, yeah
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Baby, you're on my mind all of the time
Yeah, you plus me, I can get behind
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Truly you got my heart right from the start
You fill me with your love
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
Truly you got my heart right from the start
You fill me with your love
My sweetest scarlet, my sweetest scarlet
My sweetest scarlet
Jailbirds, thank you so much for coming
to my 3D debut!
Thank you!
I hope I was able to put on a wonderful
performance for you.
Seeing all these flowers, it seems
that was the case.
So thank you so much, I hope you enjoyed
my new music.
I hope you enjoyed my performances.
And seriously, thank you, thank you so much
for coming.
I love you, Jailbirds! Mwah!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye!
Bye-bye-bye-bye! Bye!
Jailbirds!!! Thank you for coming to my 3D debut.
This is a dream come true for me, and I'm so happy
I could share this moment with all of you, and it's
thanks to you that I'm here now ♡ THANK YOU
ありがとう ♡
Thank you ♡
Jailbirds!!! Thank you for coming to my 3D debut.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
This is a dream come true for me, and I'm so happy I could share this moment with all of you,
and it's thanks to you that I'm here now <3 THANK YOU!
3D SHOWCASE