(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
The Broken Promise
For aeons,
light and dark have fought ceaselessly
for dominion over the world.
The Broken Promise
Whispers echo of a dark lord whose insidious
grip on the realm is marked by insatiable...
...lust.
Twisted jealousy,
ravenous greed,
unrelenting vanity,
and possessive manipulation.
A group of adventurers rose to face this threat,
with hidden wishes of secrets and shadows untold.
First, there was Nameless,
quick as an owl in the night.
WANTED: STOLEN STRAWBERRY CAKE
A thrill-seeking thief she was, who hunted in the fringes of society.
Next was Cora, a passionate chronomancer and hostess,
whose connections to this world felt as thin as
the threads of time she manipulated
to build her harem.
Faelin was a guardian of nature
whose sweet, charming exterior
belied her true nature.
Descended from the heavens, Irisa brought...
...tidings of doom.
Her innocent and clumsy demeanor...
...stood in contrast to her perfectionist tendencies.
Lastly,
Hexa, a bard who had yet to find her spotlight.
Dazzling were her performances,
whilst her silent dreams of recognition gnawed at her heart.
On a warm summer night, amidst the flickering candlelight...
...of the Singing Shark Inn,
they found their fates intertwined with that of...
...a malevolent Dark Lord,
whose shadow slowly consumed everything in their path.
Hey Faelyn.
How dost thou cope with death?
The fear thereof, I mean.
Hmm, tending to my plants does help...
...stave off the looming spectre of the void, if but for a spell.
Plants, huh?
Tried that once.
Killed them all.
Guess I'm destined to bring death one way or another.
Perhaps thou art stick to nursing pints rather than plants, Hexa.
Nature's children are precious.
Thy liver is not.
Haha! I'll drink to that!
Comely maiden,
might I follow thee home?
'Twas my mother's wish that I follow my dreams.
A fine distraction, Kora.
Namu is so clever, isn't she?
Thou mistakest me for thine accomplice, Namu.
Canst thou not see I am trying to work my magic here?
Already resorting to time magic to ensnare thy quarry?
'Twas but a turn of phrase.
I hardly need magic to court a maiden fair.
Merely my unending charm.
Hast thou not enough trinkets already?
I take no more than I need to survive.
I promise.
Woohoo!
It would seem at least someone is getting lucky tonight!
Let me see.
What'd you get?
Fie!
Here comes the guard!
That is my cue to vanish.
Namu,
methinks the guard doth not arrive bathed in heavenly light.
Greetings, esteemed patrons!
I seek stouthearted souls to accompany me...
...on a dangerous—
Aah!
How charming.
‘Tis not a journey to be taken lightly.
The darkness grows stronger by the day.
Join me, and thy deepest wish will be granted.
Deepest wish?
Sounds like a ruse to me.
What think you?
Might be,
but what if it's not?
Oi, shiny lady!
We're all ears.
So go on, spin us your tale.
How can we trust thee?
Who art thou, anyway?
I understand your skepticism.
In times like these, we all have our doubts.
My name is IRyssa.
I descended from the celestial realm on a holy quest...
...to end the Dark Lord's reign.
‘Tis foretold that by vanquishing the Dark Lord,
one's heart's desires will be granted.
What dost thou mean by our heart's desire?
Each of you carries within you a longing that drives you.
This quest can make those aspirations a reality.
Have you any proof?
There.
Now dost thou believe me?
Kora, what is wrong?
Thou lookest as though thou hast seen a ghost.
What witchcraft hast thou wrought upon her, foul enchantress?
I only showed her the truth.
Is this...
...the future?
Oh, one moment.
I shall return forthwith.
Indeed, it—
Where'd she go?
Aw, she shan't be gone long.
Watch, she'll return in on—
Though it may beggar belief,
IRyssa speaks the truth.
Our wishes can be granted.
Truly?
We can wish for anything?
Any wish.
Well then!
Wherefore do we tarry?
Let us away!
(諦めない強さなら)
(If it's the strength to not give up)
(明日が見えないのなら)
(If tomorrow cannot be seen)
僕らは 迷ってた 真っ暗 狭い部屋
We were lost in a pitch-black, narrow room
僕らは あがいてた 光 差すほう
We were struggling towards where the light shines
不安や しがらみは 大きく膨らんで
Anxiety and entanglements grew larger
襲いかかる 逃げ場はない 差し伸べる手も
Attacking us, there's no escape, nor a hand reached out
嫌というほどに 繰り返して
Repeating to a sickening degree
それでも まだまだ 与えるのか
Even so, will you still give more?
試練の日々よ
Oh, days of trial
諦めない強さなら それなりに平等だけど
If it's the strength to not give up,
it's somewhat equal
振り絞ったよ 今にもダメになりそう
I've squeezed it all out,
I'm about to break right now
そんなとき ふと見上げた 先駆者たちの言葉には
At such times, in the words of the pioneers
I happened to look up at
同じ香り 感じたんだ
I felt the same scent
僕らは 夢を見た さまざま 思い思い
We dreamed various, individual dreams
僕らは 賭けてみた お互いに全て
We tried betting everything on each other
勝率や現実 ときには振り払って
Shaking off the odds and reality at times
泣けばいい 悔めばいい 途中経過さ
It's okay to cry, it's okay to regret,
it's just a process
夢中で 息荒く 走り続け
Continuing to run breathlessly in a daze
気づけば 無数の 仲間たちに
Realizing that to the countless comrades
支えられながら
While being supported
明日がみえないのなら その方角は間違いさ
If tomorrow cannot be seen, that direction is wrong
一呼吸おいて ゼロからの近道もある
Take a breath,
there's also a shortcut from zero
簡単じゃないことでも 複雑に絡まる前に
Even things that aren't easy,
before they get tangled complexly
どうか一度 見せにおいで
Please come and show me once
出会ったんだ
We met
魅かれたんだ
We were enchanted
それが奇跡
That's a miracle
君にありがとう
Thank you to you
きっと諦めない強さなら それなりに平等だけど
Surely if it's the strength to not give up,
it's somewhat equal
振り絞ったよ 今にもダメになりそう
I've squeezed it all out,
I'm about to break right now
そんなとき ふと見上げた 先駆者たちの言葉には
At such times, in the words of the pioneers
I happened to look up at
頼らない 歌うよ
I won't rely on them, I'll sing
明日が見えないのなら その方角は間違いさ
If tomorrow cannot be seen, that direction is wrong
一呼吸おいて ゼロからの近道もある
Take a breath,
there's also a shortcut from zero
簡単じゃないことでも 複雑に絡まる前に
Even things that aren't easy,
before they get tangled complexly
どうか一度 見せにおいで
Please come and show me once
Quite the jig ye have danced back at the tavern.
Was it to charm people or to scare away crows? I couldn't tell.
A brazen stone to cast when none would countenance you without your magic.
You're both very charming.
But not as lovely as Namu.
Huh?
Lovely you say?
Is the moon not beautiful...
...for tonight.
Although, we ought not linger.
Rumor has it that an evil hag liveth in these parts.
And naught whets her appetite like the flesh of adventurers.
Thou art hiding something, we thinks.
What dost thou not want us to know about these woods?
Tell us more about this hag.
Aye, a frightful yarn doth excite my spirit!
Ugh, can't you all see she speaks false?
Ahem!
Gumi and her friend Darla
were adventurers who gathered fruit in these woods.
Gumi had heard of a trove of berries hidden deep in the forest,
so they ventured in and found a grove untouched by man or beast.
They began picking the berries in pure bliss.
That is, until they heard a loud snapping and crunching sound.
What was that?!
They looked around but saw nothing.
Spooked by the unnatural sound, they decided to leave.
But 'twas too late. They'd lost track of time.
Night had fallen, and darkness shrouded the woods.
They split up and marked their path with berries.
After some time, Gumi heard a scream
followed by a bone-chilling crunch.
Gumi ran down the berry trail with all the haste she could muster.
The berries underfoot began to ooze a strange red substance.
It seeped into the ground, each stain bigger than the last.
Breathless, she came upon a large puddle of red.
And in the center, a pile of teeth.
Frozen in horror, she looked up and beheld a grotesque hag looming over her,
Darla's hair hanging from her mouth.
Before she could react, the hag lunged!
How mean to rob us of any chance of peaceful slumber.
Merely trying to keep you all on your toes.
It's working. I don't think I'll sleep a wink tonight.
Let us abscond from this place.
Starting to feel like we're being watched.
Oh, wise choice.
None of you belong here.
アクロウ
~フクロウが知らせる客が来たと~
FUKUROU
~The Owl Informs That a Guest Has Arrived~
ようこそ 深い森の奥
Welcome to the deep forest
珍しいお客さんね
You're a rare visitor, aren't you?
悪いけど ここから先では
I'm sorry, but from here on out
森でのマナーがあるの
There's a forest etiquette to follow
ほーほー
Hoo hoo
フクロウが知らせる
The owl lets us know
ほーほー
Hoo hoo
客が来たと
That a guest has arrived
ほーほー
Hoo hoo
フクロウが知らせる
The owl lets us know
何かが始まる予感
A feeling that something is beginning
ラーウ ラーウ 何が見たいの
Lau lau, what do you want to see?
ラーウ ラーウ あなた次第
Lau lau, it's up to you
悪いけど ここではあなたは
I'm sorry, but here you are
招かれざる客なの
An uninvited guest
ほーほー
Hoo hoo
フクロウが知らせる
The owl lets us know
ほーほー
Hoo hoo
客が来たと
That a guest has arrived
ほーほー
Hoo hoo
フクロウが知らせる
The owl lets us know
何かが始まる予感
A feeling that something is beginning
ほーほー
Hoo-hoo
ラーウ　ラーウ　何が見たいの
Rau, Rau, what do you want to see?
ラーウ　ラーウ　あなた次第
Rau, Rau, it's up to you.
悪いけど　ここではあなたは
Sorry, but here, you are
招かれざる客なの
an uninvited guest.
ほーほー
Hoo-hoo
フクロウが知らせる
The owl lets us know.
ほーほー
Hoo-hoo
客が来たと
That a guest has come.
ほーほー
Hoo-hoo
フクロウが知らせる
The owl lets us know.
何かが始まる予感
A premonition that something is starting.
(La~)
ほーほー
Hoo-hoo
フクロウが知らせる
The owl lets us know.
ほーほー
Hoo-hoo
客が来たと
That a guest has come.
ほーほー
Hoo-hoo
フクロウが知らせる
The owl lets us know.
何かが始まる予感
A premonition that something is starting.
The forest endears itself to me.
Trees seem to whisper of endless paths and treasures untold.
What secrets dost thou hide?
If I can keep us here longer, I might uncover these secrets.
Mayhaps with a little magic, a subtle persuasion, I could convince them.
It looks like we should be going this way, right?
Mm, thou art mistaken. We can't go that way.
Therein lies the lair of a bear, most fierce.
We must avoid it at all costs.
We can handle a bear.
This is the shortest path. 'Twould remove us from this wood most expediently.
I know these woods well. Give me the map.
No.
Give it to me!
Thy tongue doth drip with deceit.
Why should we trust thee to lead the way?
Perhaps I can lead us out.
The trees tell me of an easy and safe path.
The trees?
Trees have no tongues, Fey-Lynn.
Why don't we just go... that way?
Oh, but they do. Hearken well.
Vahire geleph, liarmí nor
Dor sarmlín, kened ner-el.
Fey-Lynn, what art thou...
Oh.
The forest is so beautiful.
I see it now.
Why are the trees so wiggly all of a sudden?
Whoa!
Avert thine eyes! The fireball is no friend.
Look at me!
I'm dancing with the forest spirits!
Be careful! Thou mightest turn into a tree.
Really? Cool!
What's in here?
More secrets?
Back off!
How dare thou layest thy grabby hands on my belongings!
Dost thou mean to open a thrift shop with all this?
Aught is amiss with the leaves.
They're watching us.
They aren't watching us.
Merely judging thee.
Take that!
Mechanical infiltrators?
Back, you fiends!
The hag!
Not my teas!
There's no hag.
The spell hath worked perfectly.
The spell has worked perfectly.
Look at the chaos I've created.
'Tis almost too easy.
It's almost too easy.
Alas, I had no choice.
They wanted to leave so soon.
Why would they want to miss out on the magic this forest holds?
Ah, do I manipulate them too much?
Nay, they will thank me for showing them the wonders of the forest.
The forest, however, is not nearly as magical as my beloved Namu.
She knows these woods so well.
I wonder why.
Every time she speaks, I can't help but be drawn to her.
I may have cast a spell on her...
...but 'tis she that hath enchanted me.
...but it is she who has enchanted me.
Follow me.
檻の中 あたしの愛猫
Inside the cage, my beloved cat
愛猫
Lyrics, Music: biz, ZERA
Aineko
お帰りなさい 君にニャオ
Welcome home, a 'meow' to you
悪い子ね 汚れたお身体で
Bad child, with such a dirty body
行きはよいで 帰りは怖い
The way there is fine, the way back is scary
愛を知らない 飽き猫さん
A fickle cat who knows no love
間抜けな愛嬌とかそりゃ結構
Stupidly charming, that's quite enough
睨めっこ ほらバレバレで もう一躁
Staring contest, look, it's obvious, one more stir
なんで？ お仕置きだ 自己嫌悪
Why? It's punishment, self-loathing
君はあたしだけの愛猫だよ？
You are my beloved cat, only mine?
ダンダン好キニナル 好キニナル ネェ 愛シテ
Gradually falling in love, falling in love, hey, love me
可愛いね 首輪つけてニャオ
So cute, put on the collar, meow
大切に 愛でてあげるニャオ
I'll cherish and adore you, meow
檻の中の子猫ちゃん
The kitten inside the cage
愛のダンスを さあ 踊りましょ
Let's dance the dance of love
喉鳴らし 擦り寄って ほらどうぞ？
Purring, rubbing against me, go ahead?
睨めっこ あら 甘えん坊さんね
Staring contest, oh, what a spoiled child
そっぽを向いても そりゃ結構
Turning away, that's fine too
君はあたしだけの愛猫なの
You are my beloved cat, only mine
ダンダン好キニナル 好キニナル ネェ 愛シテ
Gradually falling in love, falling in love, hey, love me
逃げられやしないの おバカね
You can't escape, you silly
無償の愛が欲しいの 愛して
I want unconditional love, love me
餌が欲しいね だって君は愛猫さん
You want food, right? Because you're my beloved cat
Finally!
We are out of those godforsaken woods.
Where is my bag?
I can't find it.
Thou must have mislaid it when we got lost.
Thou tookest it! Disown it not!
Don't play innocent.
Thy worthless baubles?
To what end?
I spied Fauna with the bag in the forest.
She probably took it.
Surely thou thinkest not that I would take...
...something of thine, Namu?
Nay, thou art right.
It would seem I need to replenish our funds again.
The bank must be missing my patronage right now.
I shan't keep them waiting.
I shall see if I can make some coin...
...performing at the local pub.
I need some peace and quiet.
Then I suppose I shall buy some herbs.
Look at her.
So perfect, so effortless.
Why, heaven, can I not be this perfect?
This beacon of grace doth mock my every stumble and fall.
This beacon of grace mocks my every stumble and fall.
What curse is it that I am condemned to live in this clumsy husk?
They laugh at my awkwardness...
...but I despise it with every fiber of my being.
'Tis a blight, a stain upon my soul.
My ambitions can never reach their full potential in this state.
How can I ever be taken seriously when I can't control my limbs?
I am a mockery, a joke to be pitied and scorned.
Oh, to possess such grace.
I'd trade my soul for it.
Are there any devils I can trade my soul with to be as perfect as her?
Would that it were so easy.
Oh my God
愛のネタバレ「別れ」っぽいな
Love's spoiler, feels like a "breakup"
人生のネタバレ「死ぬ」っぽいな
Life's spoiler, feels like "death"
なにそれ意味深でかっこいいじゃん…
What's that? It's so meaningful and cool...
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんだ　失敬
Dancing with a glossary of similar words, excuse me
神っぽいな
God-ish
Lyrics, Music: ピノキオピー
Lyrics, Music: PinocchioP
もういいぜ　もういいぜ　それもいいぜ　もういいぜ　逆に
Enough, enough, that's enough, enough, on the contrary
興奮してきたなあ
I'm getting excited
おっきいね　おっきいね　夢　おっきいね　おっきいね
It's big, it's big, the dream is big, it's big
景気いいけど　品性はTHE END
It's booming, but dignity is THE END
うええい　うええい
Yay, yay
" Gott ist tot "
God is dead
神っぽいな　それ　卑怯　神っぽいな　それ
That's god-ish, unfair, that's god-ish
アイウォンチュー　ウォンチュー　IQが下がっていく感じ
I want you, want you, the feeling of IQ dropping
邪心っぽいな　それ　畢慶　邪心っぽいな　それ
That's wicked-ish, ultimately, that's wicked-ish
"My God"
アイヘイチュー　ヘイチュー　害虫はどっち
I hate you, hate you, which one is the pest?
その髪型　その目　その口元　その香水　その服　そのメイク
That hairstyle, those eyes, that mouth, that perfume, those clothes, that makeup
アレっぽいな　それ　卑怯　アレっぽいな　それ～
That's like that, unfair, that's like that~
その名言　その意見　その批評　そのカリスマ　そのギャグ　そのセンス
That quote, that opinion, that criticism, that charisma, that gag, that sense
神っぽいな　それ　卑怯　ぽいな　ぽいな　ぽい　憧れちゃう！
That's god-ish, unfair, -ish, -ish, -ish, I'm admiring it!
メタ思考する本質は悪意？　人を小馬鹿にしたような作為
Is the essence of meta-thinking malice? A maneuver as if to belittle people
無為に生き延びるのは難しい　権力に飲まれて揺らぐ灯
Surviving in vain is difficult, a light flickering being swallowed by power
神を否定し神に成り代わり　玉座で豹変する小物達
Denying God and becoming God, small fry who undergo a sudden change on the throne
批判に見せかけ自戒の祈り
A prayer of self-reflection disguised as criticism
Do you know?
何言ってんの？それ　ウザい　何言ってんの？それ
What are you saying? That's annoying, what are you saying?
意味がよくわかんないし　眠っちゃうよ　マジ
I don't really get the meaning, and I'll fall asleep, seriously
飽きっぽいんだ　オーケー　みんな　飽きっぽいんだ　オーケー
I'm fickle, okay, everyone is fickle, okay
踊れるやつ　ちょうだい　ちょうだい　ビーム
Give me someone who can dance, give me, give me, beam
キッショいね　キッショいね　それ　キッショいね　キッショいね　逆に
It's gross, it's gross, that's gross, it's gross, on the contrary
逆にファンになってきたじゃん
I've become a fan, haven't I?
ちっちゃいね　ちっちゃいね　器　ちっちゃいね　ちっちゃいね
It's small, it's small, the vessel is small, it's small
天才ゆえ孤独ですね　かっけぇ…　かっけぇ…
Lonely because you're a genius, cool... cool...
"Gott ist tot"
God is dead
神っぽいな　それ　卑怯　神っぽいな　それ
That's god-ish, unfair, that's god-ish
"My God"
超健康　健康　言い張って　くたばっていく感じ
Insisting on super health, health, the feeling of kicking the bucket
ヤケっぽいな　それ　畢竟　ヤケっぽいな　それ
That's desperate-ish, ultimately, that's desperate-ish
もう哀愁　哀愁　エピゴーネンのヒール
Already sorrow, sorrow, the heel of an epigone
そのタイトル　その絵　そのストーリー　その音楽　その歌　そのメロディ
That title, that picture, that story, that music, that song, that melody
アレっぽいな　それ　卑怯　アレっぽいな　それ
That's like that, unfair, that's like that
その名言　その意見　その批評　そのカリスマ　そのギャグ　そのセンス
That quote, that opinion, that criticism, that charisma, that gag, that sense
神っぽいな　それ　卑怯　ぽいな　ぽいな　ぽい　憧れちゃうわ！
That's god-ish, unfair, -ish, -ish, -ish, I'm admiring it!
愛のネタバレ「別れ」っぽいな
Love's spoiler, feels like a "breakup"
人生のネタバレ「死ぬ」っぽいな
Life's spoiler, feels like "death"
すべて理解してしまった
I've understood everything
無邪気に踊っていたかった　人生
I wanted to dance innocently, life
(Humming)
Thine angelic humming speaks of a great darkness in you.
Thou oughtst sing more to expel the demons within.
Demons? I have not any demons,
but I thank thee for the compliment.
Or thou anew?
I'm married to the church, I'm afraid.
We're about to begin rehearsal.
Take up that hymnal and join us.
I don't think
a fine flock of beauties the choir be.
Maybe I could give it a chance.
Gah!
What songs are you singing?
Turn to page 165,
and thou shalt see the lyrics there.
Uh... hi?
Hey.
Nice to meet you.
Aren't you cute?
Are you ready, everyone?
Let us begin.
Hey!
Uh... hi?
Why don't we get out of here?
What dost thou say?
But we haven't even started rehearsal yet.
What dost thou mean?
Hey!
Uh... hi?
I fell in love the moment I laid eyes upon thee.
Have we met before?
Hey!
Uh... hi?
Good day.
I'm Cora.
What is thy name?
I'm Diana.
Well met.
Hast thou newly joined the choir?
Nay, but...
I would much like if thou joined my...
I mean, I mean... life, life!
Thou art an amusing one.
I should like to become better acquainted with thee.
Are you ready, everyone?
Let us begin.
「さあ、踊ろうか」
Let's dance, shall we?
ヴェノマニア公の狂気
Lyrics, Music: mothy
The Madness of Duke Venomania
今日もまた美しい淑女が
Today again, a beautiful lady
僕の元 訪れる
comes to visit me
微笑みを浮かべる貴女は
You, with a smile on your face,
新しい妻となる
will become my new wife
禁断の悪魔との契約
A forbidden contract with a demon,
手にいれたこの力
this power I have gained
僕を見た全ての女は
Every woman who sees me
魅了され 堕ちていく
is enchanted and falls
女性を魅了する力を手に入れた
I gained the power to enchant women
男は一人住む屋敷の地下室に
The man, alone in the basement of his mansion,
気に入った女を次々と連れ込み
brought in the women he liked one after another
ハーレムを作り上げた
and built a harem
毒を秘めたリビドーの味
The taste of a libido hiding poison
突き刺した刃の快楽
The pleasure of a blade thrust in
血と汗は混じり合い やがて
Blood and sweat mingle, and soon
紫の滴へと変わる
turn into purple droplets
服を脱ぎ捨て抱き合えば
If we cast off our clothes and embrace,
現実へはもう二度と戻れない
we can never return to reality again
燃やされた昔の肖像画
The burned portrait from long ago
捨て去った過去の僕
My past self that I threw away
誰しもがあざけり笑った
Everyone mocked and laughed
あの顔は忘れたい
I want to forget that face
傍らの可愛い娘を
The cute girl by my side,
抱き寄せてキスをする
I draw her close and kiss her
彼女はそう かつて僕のこと
She is, yes, the one who once
馬鹿にした幼馴染
mocked me, my childhood friend
ある日を境にして国中の女が
Starting from a certain day, women across the country
いつしか次々と行方をくらませた
one after another, began to disappear
あるものは女房 あるものは娘を
Some their wives, some their daughters
失い途方に暮れた
lost them and were at a loss
闇に染まるリビドーの色
The color of a libido stained in darkness
とどまらぬ無限の情欲
The unstoppable, infinite lust
幻想は全てを呑み込み
The fantasy swallows everything
僕はもう人ではなくなる
and I am no longer human
神に逆らい堕落する
Defying God and falling into depravity,
これが僕の望んでた狂気のnight
this is the night of madness I desired
今日もまた美しい淑女が
Today, once again, beautiful ladies
僕の元　訪れる
come to visit me.
さあおいで僕の胸の中
Come here, into my arms.
踊ろうよこのハーレムで
Let's dance in this harem.
近づいた貴方を抱きしめ
The moment I hugged you
微笑んだその瞬間
as you drew near and I smiled...
突然の鋭い痛みと
A sudden, sharp pain,
血に染まる僕の胸
and my chest is stained with blood.
消えた恋人を探してた若者
A youth searching for a lost lover
居場所を突き止めた悪魔の住む屋敷
tracked down the demon's mansion.
若者は女装して悪魔に近づいた
The youth approached the demon disguised as a woman,
懐の刀を悪魔に突き刺した
and plunged a dagger into it.
毒を秘めた刀が刺さり
The poisoned blade struck,
僕はその場に倒れ込んだ
and I collapsed on the spot.
血と汗は混じり合いやがて
Blood and sweat mingled, eventually
紫の滴へと変わっていく
turning into purple drops.
術の解けた女たちは全て
All the women, freed from the spell,
我に返り屋敷から逃げ出した
came to their senses and fled the mansion.
僕のこと一瞬だけ見て
Looked at me for just a moment...
最後に屋敷から出たのは
The last one to leave the mansion was...
あの幼馴染 待ってよ
That childhood friend. Wait...
まだ君に好きだと言ってない
I haven't told you I love you yet.
Ha...
Why have I thought that I allowed myself to be walked into this quest?
To suffer the odious hijinks of these bumbling fools.
The crude, unsightly and boorish lot they are.
Me thinks they could scarce walk a straight line, much less perform.
Or God forbid, dance.
Ha...
Their company doth abase me, who should be foremost among my peers.
Humble bard I may be, but the world shall soon know of my eminence.
And fawn and adore me as they should.
I may yet be unknown.
But soon, once this silly quest is over and I have my wish...
Townfolk will swoon over my ballads.
Royalty will beg me to grace their parties.
And the name of Hexa shall ring o'er hill and valley as the greatest performer this realm hath ever known.
And then... And then...
The stage is open! For any who might wish to perform!
Is there none who dare take the stage? What of you, Miss?
I see thee tapping thy feet for the songs. Dost thou dance?
Oh, me? Wha... I don't know.
Oh, please give us a song, Miss!
It won't make us think I sing.
Well, thou art dressed like a singer!
So a singer's garbs doth a singer make?
Very well. I'll do it!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen!
Are you ready for the greatest performance of your lives?
Ah, ah...
La-la-la-la-la...
Once in a faraway, faraway world was a collar that coiled like a snake
I want someone please - I need someone please
Oh, I listened close as it howled in ache
Please don't be angry and please don't abandon me.
Don't leave me here on my own (kay?)
It wrapped itself tightly, daily and nightly - only with praise would it loosen it's hold
I placed in the top of my class~
there's no one left for me to surpass
Don't I look cute in this dress?
I really, really...
Must confess - it's tightening 'round my neck!
Give me your love, all of your love,
give me your love - all you can conjure up
till you go mad with ecstasy
All of the hurt, all of the ache - help me escape! Take it, oh take it away!!!
All of the hurt, all of the ache -
help me escape!
Take it, oh take it away!!!
Is there no end to this pain?
Ah...
Grow as you may
but the necklace will stay just as small as the day it was found
It's so suffocating, the endless placating -
no one is, no one is ever enough!
Won't lose to anyone, always ranked number one,
aren't I a beautiful child?
(Hey,)
I'm better than her -
I'm better than him,
oh everyone, come round and gawk at perfection!
Meeting you right after school,
I'm finally confessing to you
Ain't it too good to be true?
Ah-ah!
A girl, like me, in love with you -
who's miserable, vulgar, and crude!
Give me your love, all of your love, give me your love -
You can have everything
If I have you, I can have you -
shoulder my load, now yours to behold
Still not enough, you're not enough -
never enough.
Still I won't loosen my hold
Truly, I'm so sorry.
Give me your love, all of your love, give me your love -
all you can conjure up
Give me your love, all of your love -
till you go mad with ecstasy
I know it hurts -
(it) only gets worse -
God how it hurts -
Soon you'll be craving the pain
This is my happiness now!
I know not how you fared, but I was successful in my venture.
More trinkets for thy thrift shop?
Uh, nay, 'twas coin we needed, was it not?
I merely took out a small loan from the bank. They shan't mind.
I acquired some healing potions.
Luckily, it was a simple matter to trade for some of these jewels I found in the woods.
Thou liar! 'Twas thou who took my bag!
Thou misapprehendest me!
I merely found these lying on the floor of the forest.
Perhaps there was a bag.
Confess about stealing my stuff!
Doth every bag that happens to fall in the wood belong to thee?
IRyS is always acting selfishly.
She's the newest, so 'twas probably her.
Thou darest to accuse me!
If thou wert truly innocent, would the thief not more likely be Hakos?
She is simple and craven, and acted half-mad back there in the forest.
Me? Why art thou accusing me?
It could be none but Ouro with a strange obsession with Namu.
Thy words ring true.
Can I just have the bag thou foundest in the forest?
Nay, 'tis mine!
I knew 'twas folly to undertake this quest with you all!
Fie on you! Fie on you all!
Most of all on thee, that wanton and witless womanizer.
I saw thy pathetic attempts at charming innocent choir girls.
Better to apply thy sorcery upon thyself, that thou might vanish to the betterment of the world.
Me? My romantic diversions serve no concern to thee,
thou uncouth mud-cake field rat.
Dost thou and thy companions of flesh...
...and trees.
Have you all forgotten about our quest?
Why art thou in such rush to go?
Didst thou steal it?
Certainly not.
I only want us to continue our quest and not linger on this useless bickering.
You two have been fighting or sticking to each other this whole time.
Make up your mind already!
Do you like each other?
We like each other.
Do we not, Namu?
If 'twas thou who stole my bag, then no, I don't like thee.
Really?
Look what thou hast done, thou sodden-witted cur!
Thou hast wounded her!
Synchronicity
～第二章 巡る世界のレクイエム～
Lyrics: ひとしずくP　Music: ひとしずくP x Yama△
Synchronicity
~Chapter 2: Requiem of the Cycling World~
Lyrics: Hitoshizuku-P Music: Hitoshizuku-P x Yama△
時の揺りかごで
In time's cradle
冷たい夢を見る
I see a cold dream
君が歌ってくれた
You sang for me
愛しい　愛しい　子守唄
A lovely, lovely lullaby
君が望んだのは？
What you desired was...?
―終わらぬ世界―
...an endless world?
俺が望むのは
What I desire is...
―世界の終わり...？―
...the world's end...?
選ばれし声は
The chosen voices are...
迷い、憂い、微笑み、労わり歌う
wandering, grieving, smiling, caring, and singing.
悲しみを　苦しみを　喜びに　笑顔に変えて
Changing sadness and suffering into joy and smiles,
報われずに　君は朽ちていくの？
Will you decay without being rewarded?
―ただ、祈る―
I just pray...
救いたい、ただ君だけを
I want to save only you,
守りたい、この世界を
I want to protect this world.
想いは　変わらない
My feelings will not change.
巡り巡る世界に　やすらぎと祝福を―
May there be peace and blessings for this cycle of worlds.
命を　この手で全て、終わらせたい
I want to end all life with my own hands.
ああ　届かない
Ah, it doesn't reach.
―伝わらないよ―
...It's not being conveyed.
願いは虚しさだけを残して
My wishes only leave emptiness behind.
何故？　全て奪われ
Why? Everything was taken away...
―未来を照らして―
...light up the future.
痛み、苦しみ、背負わされても...
Even if I am burdened with pain and suffering...
―永遠に続くレクイエム―
...an eternally continuing requiem.
抗えない運命を
In the face of an unavoidable fate,
―光を、運命を―
...the light, the fate.
全て今、解き放つ
I release it all now,
―闇を　解き放つ―
...release the darkness.
君が望んだのは？
What you desired was...?
―あなたの未来―
...your future.
俺が望んだのは...何故？
What I desired was... why?
―戻らぬあの日...？―
...those days that won't return...?
追い続けたのは　優しい笑顔
What I kept chasing was your gentle smile.
それだけなのに
It was only that,
―終わらない歌声を―
...an unending singing voice.
絶望を、希望に変えて
Changing despair into hope,
叫び続けて
Keep screaming,
―滅びる運命なら―
...if it's a fate to perish.
せめて今、弔いの
At least now, for a funeral...
―ただ、祈る―
I just pray...
果てしなく　遠く遠く―
Endlessly far, far away.
歌よ　響け
Let my song resound!
巡り巡る世界に　やすらぎと祝福を
May there be peace and blessings for this cycle of worlds.
光を、運命を、闇を、解き放って
Release the light, the fate, and the darkness.
終わらない絶望を
Endless despair...
―歌声を、希望に変えて―
...changing the singing voice into hope.
報われずに　君は朽ちていくの？
Will you decay without being rewarded?
―叫び続けて　ただ祈る―
...keep screaming and just pray.
せめて今、弔いの
At least now, for a funeral...
果てしなく、遠く遠く―
Endlessly far, far away.
歌よ　響け
Let my song resound!
君が望んだのは？
What you desired was...?
俺が望んだのは...
What I desired was...
残された声は　嘆き　君を想いながら
The remaining voices, grieving while thinking of you.
独り、君のために歌う
I sing alone for you.
命を　この手で全て、眠らせたら
If I put all life to sleep with these hands,
―巡り巡る世界に　やすらぎと祝福を―
...then may there be peace and blessings for this cycle of worlds.
ああ、朽ちていく　運命は終わり
Ah, decaying. Fate is over.
この身は　君とならどこまででも...
With you, I can go anywhere...
はじまる声　全て叶えて
The beginning voice, grant everything.
―未来を照らして―
...light up the future.
滅び、散りゆく　この身とともに
Along with this body that will perish and scatter,
―永遠に続くレクイエム―
...an eternally continuing requiem.
抗えない運命を
In the face of an unavoidable fate,
―光を、運命を―
...the light, the fate.
すべて今、解き放ち
I release it all now,
―闇を解き放ち―
...release the darkness.
光の底に、眠れ
Sleep in the depth of the light.
Where is the Dark Lord?
Dark Lord, reveal thyself!
We are here to defeat thee!
Huh? How queer.
The silence... it's...
...as if this room was empty...
...from the very beginning.
Might it be?
Our Promise (Remix ver.)
Lyrics: noire
Music, Arrangement: Jeremy Robson
The quest began at the cusp of dawn
Blank map in hand eager to be drawn
Cascading secrets
Holding onto wishes untold
With every stride, a new tale bound to unfold
In realms never seen
In planes beyond belief
Smiles beamed and gleamed radiantly
Wonders hidden with each turn
Always together
In harmony, all perils can be weathered
A melody chases the laughter of five
Through days like forests deep and wide
When paths diverge
We meet again where dreams converge
Hear our hearts collide
Fears out of sight
Stars ever bright
Our promise ignites
Hours slip by with familiar song
Twilight's glow, the shadow's gone
Exchanging secrets
Knowing the power they behold
With every change, an old tale passed to be told
In trails never walked
In lands beyond one's thought
Lessons taught in destinies sought
Echoes of the world unknown
Searching for treasures
In harmony, our souls steadily tremor
A melody chases the laughter of five
Through nights like sand burying time
When paths diverge
We meet here where our dreams surge
Hear our hearts collide
Fears out of sight
Stars ever bright
Our promise ignites
The Broken Promise