(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
[Text: supported by Pocky / ACL]
Ayunda Risu
Kureiji Ollie
Vestia Zeta
Moona Hoshinova
Anya Melfissa
Kaela Kovalskia
Airani Iofifteen
Pavolia Reine
Kobo Kanaeru
TERIMA KASIH!
[Text: THANK YOU!]
BERKAT KALIAN, KAMI BISA BERSINAR
[Text: THANKS TO YOU ALL, WE CAN SHINE]
TERIMA KASIH UDAH BIKIN STAGE INI
& HIDUP KAMI LEBIH BERWARNA!
[Text: THANK YOU FOR MAKING THIS STAGE
& OUR LIVES MORE COLORFUL!]
Terima Kasih!!
[Text: Thank You!!]
TERIMA KASIH BANYAK!!!!!
[Text: THANK YOU SO MUCH!!!!!]
Terima Kasih!! Kalian Semua Keren BGT!!
[Text: Thank You!! You All Are Super Cool!!]
Terima Kasih!!
[Text: Thank You!!]
Makasih ya! :)
[Text: Thanks! :)]
terima kasih
[Text: thank you]
Ayo mulai!!
[Text: Let's begin!!]
CHROMATIC! FUTURE
[Title: CHROMATIC! FUTURE]
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も
My body and soul...
奪い去る衝動
...the impulse that snatches them away...
加速してく
...continues to accelerate...
鼓動が
...the heartbeat.
この手で make you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine.
君に届けたい
I want to reach you
Id:entity
ステージに一歩を 踏み出した
I took a step onto the stage
おはよう！ こんばんは！
Good morning! Good evening!
と世界に叫んでみよう
Let's shout it out to the world
本日のライブでは
In today's live,
どれの自分を見せるの？
which "me" will I show?
前からそう悩んで
I've been worrying about it for a while,
好きな自分になれない
I can't become the "me" I like
そしてある日誰かに言われた
And then one day, the painful words
痛い言葉なんてに迷っていた
someone said to me left me lost
いつも映る笑顔失わないように
So as not to lose my ever-present smile,
これ以上は期待を裏切らないと決めた
I decided not to let expectations down anymore
溢れている雑音の中
Within the overflowing noise,
この声響けるか？
can this voice resonate?
心に宿る声を聞いてみよう
Let's listen to the voice dwelling in my heart
これはずっと見せたい自分だった
This was the "me" I always wanted to show
集まった声たちがひとつになる
The gathered voices become one
id:entity
日々が過ぎてやっと
The days pass and I finally
スポットライトに立てるけれど
stand in the spotlight, but...
Saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya
When the world doesn't go as it should
(Oh oh...)
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya
Maybe it's time
Kau coba lepaskan saja
You just try to let go
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
No need to ask why anymore
Jika memang…
If indeed...
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi
Don't cry
Coba lalui teka-tekinya
Try to go through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Let it go
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Dahlah saja
Oh dahlah saja
Just dahlah
Oh just dahlah
Jalani saja
Just live it
Dahlah saja
Oh dahlah saja
Just dahlah
Oh just dahlah
Jalani saja
Just live it
Mau gimana lagi
What else can I do?
Walau kadang mati rasa
Even though sometimes numb
Bahkan hingga tak berdaya
Even until helpless
Dan usahamu terasa sia sia
And your effort feels useless
Jika memang…
If indeed...
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi
Don't cry
Coba lalui teka-tekinya
Try to go through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Let it go
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Lepas semua kendali
Release all control
Tancap gas dan berlari
Step on the gas and run
Terima dan sudahi
Accept and end it
Jika memang…
If indeed...
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi
Don't cry
Coba lalui teka-tekinya
Try to go through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Let it go
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Dahlah saja
Oh dahlah saja
Just dahlah
Oh just dahlah
Jalani saja
Just live it
Dahlah saja
Oh dahlah saja
Just dahlah
Oh just dahlah
Jalani saja
Just live it
Maa ii ka
Whatever
Comic Frontier！こんばんは！
Comic Frontier! Good evening!
こんばんは！
Good evening!
ようこそ･･･
Welcome to...
『hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future』へ！
hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future!
やばいやばい
Oh my god, oh my god!
5周年のライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming to our 5th anniversary concert!
まさかもう5周年とはわ！
I can't believe it's already been 5 years!
じゃあ自己紹介から始めましょうか？まずはゼータから！
Shall we start with self-introductions? Let's start with Zeta!
はいはいはい
Yes, yes, yes!
よし･･･あっ後ろか
Alright... Oh, from the back.
アアア！ミッションスタート！
Aaa! Mission start!
スタート！
Start!
ホロライブインドネシア3期生のベスティア・ゼータです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Vestia Zeta from hololive Indonesia Gen 3! Nice to meet you!
よろしくゼータ！はいはいはい
Nice to meet you, Zeta! Yes, yes, yes...
よし次はカエラ！
Alright, next is Kaela!
はいはい！カエロ！毎日鍛冶をやってるホロライブインドネシア3期生の鍛冶屋。
Yes, yes! Kaelo! The blacksmith from hololive Indonesia Gen 3 who grinds every day.
カエラ・コヴァルスキアです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Kaela Kovalskia! Nice to meet you all!
よろしくカエラ！
Nice to meet you, Kaela!
次はこぼだ！こぼ！
Next is Kobo! Kobo!
やっほー！ぼこぼこーこぼ・かなえる、アットユアサービス！
Yao! Bokobokobo Kobo Kanaeru, at your service!
君の日々を照らす太陽になりましょ！えへ！
Let me be the sun that shines on your days! Ehe!
Kobokers声上げて！
Kobokers, let me hear you!
3人で･･･ホロライブインドネシア3期生、holoh3roでーす！
The three of us are... hololive Indonesia Gen 3, holoh3ro!
やあ ついにホロライブID5周年ライブができるとはわ
Wow, I can't believe we're finally having a hololive ID 5th anniversary concert.
一曲目からもうめっちゃカッコいいよね！その熱き、感じてるわ！わ！
The first song was already so cool! I can feel the heat!
Satu lagu dari awal udah keren banget kan?
From the very first song, it's already so cool!
Parah sih... iya kan?
That was insane, right?
Adrenalin banget...
The adrenaline is really pumping...
pengen lari aku rasanya nih!
I feel like I want to start running!
Woi woi woi... mau ke mana?
Hey, hey, hey! Where are you going?
Iya iya stop stop stop!
Whoa, whoa, stop, stop, stop!
Nanti keringetan loh, nanti keringetan!
You're gonna get all sweaty!
Kalau Kaela gimana?
How about you, Kaela?
Aduh seru banget... aku enggak nyangka sih
sampai aku bisa ada di sini ya.
Man, it's so much fun... I never thought
I'd actually be standing here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong konser ini masih panjang
banget... jadi kalian tetap semangat ya sampai akhir!
By the way, this concert is still far from over...
so stay hyped until the very end!
Semangat semangat semangat!
Let's give it our all! Give it our all!
Eh tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi...
emang pada tahu judul konsernya apa?
Hey, we've been talking about the concert...
but does everyone know the title of the concert?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah... Chromatic Future!
The title of our concert this time is...
Chromatic Future!
Ada yang tahu enggak artinya apa? Ayo absen!
Does anyone know what it means? Raise your hands!
Nah ini, Kobo paling tahu!
Now this... Kobo definitely knows!
Iya... yang jelasin yang paling tinggi!
Right... the tallest person should explain it!
Iya, yang jelasin yang paling tinggi! Let's go!
Yeah, the tallest person explains! Let's go!
Gitu ya... ya udahlah...
Oh, that's how it's gonna be? Fine...
Nih ya guys buat kalian yang belum tahu...
Chromatic Future itu artinya masa depan yang berwarna-warni.
Alright guys, for those who don't know...
Chromatic Future means a colorful future.
Jadi karena hololive Indonesia kan udah 5 tahun nih...
Since hololive Indonesia is now reaching
its 5th anniversary...
Kita sama-sama dari hari satu sampai sekarang...
We've all been walking together
from day one until today!
Nah jadi itu untuk ke depannya kita tuh juga harapannya
kita bisa nyiptain waktu dan memori yang berwarna-warni...
So for the future, our hope is that we can continue
to create colorful times and memories...
Sama seluruh fans dari hololive Indonesia!
Together with all the fans of hololive Indonesia!
Betul! Kaela Kovalskia! Catat tuh!
Exactly! Kaela Kovalskia! Take note of that!
Iya iya iya...
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Nah kalian sekarang udah pada tahu kan...
karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
Well, now you all know, right?
Since Kaela just explained it.
Kalau gitu konsernya kan udah mulai nih...
kalian mau nge-post soal konser ini di medsos
jangan lupa hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture ya!
Since the concert has already started, if you post
on social media, don't forget the hashtag
#holoIDChromaticFuture!
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh...
Because we really want to see your...
apa sih... pengen lihat semangat kalian!
how do I put it... we want to see your passion!
Iya itu betul banget! Ya enggak?
Yeah, that's exactly right! Right?
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
Don't make any typos! Don't make any typos!
Asyik! Share ke semua, oke?
Awesome! Share it with everyone, okay?
Jadi... tapi jujur deh kalian tuh pas dibilang
kita bakal konser loh di Indonesia...
kalian pada kaget enggak sih?
But honestly... when you were told that we'd be having
a concert in Indonesia... were you guys surprised?
Halo? Ada yang dengerin?
Hello? Is anyone listening?
Betul!
Right!
Aku setuju juga... aku merasakan empati
terhadap ini adik saya Zeta.
I agree too... I feel a sense of empathy
towards my little sister Zeta.
Empati iya iya...
Empathy, yeah, yeah...
Kalau Kaela gimana, Kaela Kovalskia?
How about you, Kaela Kovalskia?
Aku juga waktu itu enggak nyangka banget
kayak 'Hah? Beneran? Nih riil nih?' gitu kan.
I also couldn't believe it at the time, I was like
'Huh? Seriously? Is this for real?'
Kayak... loh bisa gitu akhirnya mana udah bersembilan
di Indonesia pula ya kan... keren banget!
I mean... finally all nine of us can perform in
Indonesia together... it's so cool!
Keren banget! Iya!
It's so cool! Yeah!
Ini kan konser pertama hololive Indonesia
yang bersembilan.
Yes, this is the very first concert
with all nine members of hololive Indonesia.
Sebenarnya tuh enggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar
dan terpenting juga untuk fans hololive Indonesia
tapi seluruh dunia juga pasti bakalan nonton enggak sih?
Actually, this is a huge moment for hololive
Indonesia fans, but surely the whole world
will be watching too, right?
Iya enggak?
Right?
Jawab!
Answer me!
Iya iya makasih makasih semuanya!
Yes, yes! Thank you, thank you everyone!
Tapi tentu aja ini pencapaiannya enggak bakal
cuma sampai di sini aja kan?
But of course, this achievement
won't just stop here, right?
Jadi next-nya mungkin kita bisa apa ya...
dominating the world gitu! We are ready!
So next, maybe we can...
dominate the world! We are ready!
Ready ready ready ready!
Betul banget Kaela, Zeta! Selain dari dukungan fans,
kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih untuk semua
sponsor yang mendukung terjadinya konser ini!
Exactly, Kaela and Zeta! Besides the support from fans,
we also want to thank all the sponsors
who made this concert possible!
Makasih! Makasih makasih makasih semuanya!
Thank you thank you thank you!
Thank you! Thank you, thank you everyone!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Eh tapi ngomong-ngomong di konser ini kayaknya
ada yang beda enggak sih? Hmm... Ela kamu nyadar enggak?
Soalnya kamu paling peka enggak sih?
By the way, doesn't something feel different?
Hmm... Ela, did you notice?
Since you're the most observant, right?
Sadarlah... kalau Kobo mah enggak bakalan sadar.
Nih nih nih nih...
Of course I did... Kobo probably wouldn't notice.
Look at this, look at this...
Yang beda tuh kali ini tuh model kita!
Ini model baru nih!
What's different this time is our models!
These are new models!
Gemes banget! Lucu lucu!
So cute! So cute!
Kameranya dekatin ke aku! Nih nih nih...
kalian mau lihat keimutan Kobo nih nih nih...
Bring the camera closer to me! Look, look...
you want to see Kobo's cuteness, look at this!
Ini nih... o-shiri!
Look at this... my butt!
Eh... oh eh eh eh...
Whoa... whoa, whoa, whoa...
Woi woi woi... ini kamera diambil Kobo semua
enggak sih? Ini ke aku! Aku juga! Aku juga!
Jangan Kobo doang!
Hey, hey... Kobo's taking all the camera time,
isn't she? Point it at me! Me too! Me too!
Not just Kobo!
Satu, dua, tiga... udah selesai!
Kameranya balik ke Kobo lagi!
One, two, three... and done!
Camera back to Kobo again!
Stop stop stop stop stop! Mulai mulai mulai...
semua kamera diambil!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop! There she goes again...
taking all the camera time!
Oke oke oke... kalau gitu...
Okay, okay, okay... well then...
Aduh aduh aduh... sampai kehabisan napas.
Jangan berebutan di depan konser!
Man, I'm out of breath.
Don't fight over the camera during the concert!
Iya... iya iya iya...
Okay... yeah, yeah, yeah...
Iya loh... Zeta kalau marah takut loh!
Right... Zeta is scary when she's angry!
Iya deh, kalau Zeta udah ngomong...
Alright, if Zeta has spoken...
Takut ih!
It's scary!
Iya, iya, ya udah deh.
Yes, yes, alright then.
Kalau nggak boleh rebutan kamera sama Zeta...
If I'm not allowed to hog the camera from Zeta...
Hmm... shouganai.
Hmm... it can't be helped.
Kita main aja deh sama Penonton-chan!
Let's just play with the fans!
Kobo pengen deh coba kita teriakin penonton...
I want us to try shouting at the audience...
...karena kan tadi mereka sudah teriakin kita!
...because they were shouting for us earlier!
Maksudnya kita teriakan interaksi kita bareng Penonton-chan-tachi!
I mean, let's do our call-and-response with the fans!
Betul!
Exactly!
Teriaknya bareng penonton, jangan teriakin penontonnya!
Shout with the audience, don't just shout at them!
Iya, gitu maksudnya!
Yeah, that's what I meant!
Soalnya kan habis ini kita harus nyanyi, jadi kita harus simpen suara dulu nggak sih?
Because we have to sing after this, so we should save our voices, right?
Betul ya, nggak bakal selama itu ternyata, tenang aja...
That's right, it won't take that long, don't worry...
...nggak bakal selama durasi stream Kaela gitu ya guys ya!
...it won't be as long as Kaela's streams, okay guys!
Ya udah lah, mau teriak-teriak ya udah, aku nggak masalah dah, aku ngikut.
Whatever, if you want to shout, fine, I don't mind, I'll join in.
Aku ngikut!
I'm in!
Gimana nih semuanya, udah siap belum?
How about it everyone, are you ready?
Siap nggak?!
Are you ready?!
Siap nih kayaknya! Oke, Kobo dulu ya!
Seems like they're ready! Okay, Kobo first!
Aku mau kita sama-sama teriak...
I want us to all shout together...
BOKOBOKOBO!
Oke, siap ya?
Okay, ready?
Satu, dua, tiga!
One, two, three!
BOKOBOKOBO!
Suka, suka! Giliran Zeta, giliran Zeta!
Nice, nice! Zeta's turn, Zeta's turn!
Oke, oke, oke, oke.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Pas aku bilang "Mission Statto", kalian bareng-bareng teriak "Start!", ya?
When I say "Mission Statto", you all shout "Start!" together, okay?
Siap? A-a-a... Mission...
Ready? A-a-a... Mission...
START!
Oke, habis ini Kaela!
Okay, next is Kaela!
Oke, oke, oke, oke, nah...
Okay, okay, okay, okay, well...
...buat semua penonton sama Holoh3ro juga...
...to all the audience and Holoh3ro too...
...kalau misalkan aku bilang "Holoh3ro!", kalian bilang "HU-HA!", gampang kan?
...if I say "Holoh3ro!", you say "HU-HA!", easy right?
Langsung, langsung, langsung!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Oke ya, siap ya? Holoh3ro!
Okay, ready? Holoh3ro!
HU-HA!
Mantap, mantap, mantap!
Awesome, awesome, awesome!
Keren, keren, keren! Akhirnya Gen 3 kompak juga.
Great, great, great! Finally, Gen 3 is in sync.
Iya, kompak.
Yeah, in sync.
Kelihatannya masih pada semangat nih ya!
Seems like everyone is still full of energy!
Soalnya dari lagu pertama kita hari ini aja udah kerasa banget.
Because even from our first song today, we could really feel it.
Kalian tuh pada nyangka nggak sih kalau lagu pertama kita tuh bakal 100%?
Did you guys expect that our first song would be 100%?
Beh, mana ada yang nyangka. Aku aja sendiri nggak nyangka juga.
Who would've expected it? I didn't even expect it myself.
Langsung dibuka dengan Hoshinova Mode gitu, keren banget kan?
Opening right away with Hoshinova Mode, it was so cool, right?
Keren banget sih! Apalagi tadi Zeta sama nyanyi...
It was really cool! Especially when Zeta sang...
Zeta sama Kaela nyanyi "100%" tuh udah kayak real "100%" ya!
When Zeta and Kaela sang "100%", it was like the real "100%"!
Itu tuh bisa nggak sih... Nggak sekeren tadi, aku tuh jadi ingin kayak...
Is it even possible... It was so cool that it made me want to go like...
Uh, uh! Gitu kan? Kalian pernah nggak sih nyanyi lagu sekeren tadi?
Uh, uh! You know? Have you ever sung a song as cool as that?
Aura farming? Aura farming...
Aura farming sesungguhnya! Keren banget emang lagunya Moona.
Real aura farming! Moona's song really is amazing.
Emang kan Zeta kan soalnya biasanya lagu-lagu yang stylish, yang jazzy-jazzy gitu.
Yeah, because Zeta usually does stylish, jazzy songs.
Jadi tadi pas dinyanyiin tuh ya, "100%", rasanya jadi beda banget vibes-nya.
So when she sang "100%", the vibes felt completely different.
Terus Kaela juga tadi ngerap ya...
And then Kaela was rapping earlier too...
Ta-da-da-da-da-da... Iya, pokoknya keren banget!
Ta-da-da-da-da-da... Yeah, anyway, it was so cool!
Keren banget ya tadi!
It was really cool earlier!
Tapi habis ini tuh masih ada lagi... "NEW zomBIE!" tadi.
But after this, there's even more... That was "NEW zomBIE!".
Ayo, pada tahu dong ini lagu siapa?
Come on, you all know whose song this is, right?
Taulah, taulah, senpai kita, senpai kita.
Of course, of course, it's our senior's song.
Tadi tuh itu ya, Holoro tuh perform-nya juga keren banget, kayak lagi di game gitu.
Earlier, Holoro's performance was also really cool, like being in a game.
Betul, setuju! Terus tadi ada backdancer-nya, men!
True, I agree! And there were back-dancers, man!
Keren ya guys! Keren nggak?!
It was cool, right guys?! Wasn't it cool?!
Terus ada apa lagi tuh tadi? Lampu laser, terus ada efek kembang api segala...
And what else was there? Laser lights, and then fireworks effects and all...
...banyak lah ya gimik-gimik yang "wow".
...there were so many "wow" gimmicks.
Itu backdancer nanti aku hire semua ya buat solo konser aku.
I'm going to hire all those back-dancers for my solo concert.
Wah, udah ngomong konser solo aja.
Whoa, talking about a solo concert already.
Ngomongan adalah doa ya. Tapi konser yang ini belum selesai.
Words are prayers, you know. But this concert isn't over yet.
Belum, belum, belum!
Not yet, not yet, not yet!
Eh, tapi... kalian tahu nggak sih sebelum ini tuh nyanyinya lagu apa?
Eh, but... do you guys know what song was sung before this?
Eh, aku mah tahu banget lah! Itu lagu terbaru aku... "Dahlah".
Eh, I definitely know! That's my newest song... "Dahlah".
Iya, dahlah, nggak usah dibahas.
Yeah, forget it, let's not talk about it.
Lho, kok gitu? Itu tuh maksudnya judulnya "Dahlah", lagunya judulnya "Dahlah"!
Hey, why like that? I mean the title is "Dahlah", the song's title is "Dahlah"!
Oh...
Oh, "Dahlah"! Bilang dong!
Oh, "Dahlah"! You should've said so!
Habisnya kamu kan sering "dahlah, dahlah" gitu, jadi kirain emang beneran "dahlah".
Because you say "dahlah, dahlah" so often, I thought you really meant it.
Entar dahlah-dahlah pulang dia.
Otherwise, she might just say "dahlah" and go home.
Kalau gitu "Dahlah" tuh maksudnya apa sih?
In that case, what does "Dahlah" actually mean?
"Dahlah" sama kehidupan. Hidup tuh berat ya guys ya...
"Dahlah" towards life. Life is tough, you know guys...
...kalau hidup berat ya udah "dahlah" aja, habis itu lanjutkan hidupmu!
...if life is tough, just say "dahlah", and then move on with your life!
Iya betul teman-teman, di kehidupan yang dewasa ini ya.
That's right everyone, in this adult life of ours.
Untungnya lagunya santai, easy listening, jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan nyapa fans, gitu ya?
Fortunately, the song is chill and easy listening, so we can walk around and greet the fans, right?
Asyik banget ya tadi ya? Aku juga suka banget tadi dance bagian reff-nya ya?
It was so much fun! I also really liked the dance during the chorus!
Dala dala dala da...
Itu... itu beda lagu gak?
Wait... is that a different song?
Gak gitu deh... kayaknya...
I don't think it was like that... probably...
Ya tapi pokoknya asyik lah ya kalau nyanyi lagu chill santai-santai kayak gini.
Anyway, it's fun to sing chill, relaxing songs like this.
Iya santai dong. Tapi...
Yeah, it's relaxing. But...
...ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu. Hei, santai!
...speaking of relaxing, we actually can't relax just yet. Hey, chill!
Karena kayaknya katanya gak boleh santai...
Because apparently we're not allowed to relax...
Iya! Iya! Rileks!
Yeah! Yeah! Relax!
Iya iya iya, jangan santai-santai. Jangan terlalu santai.
Yeah, yeah, don't get too relaxed. Don't be too chill.
Karena konsernya tuh masih panjang!
Because the concert is still long!
Jadi sebelum itu, kalian ada gak yang mau kalian sampaiin dulu?
So before that, is there anything you guys want to say first?
Mulai dari ini nih, yang gak bisa diem.
Let's start with this one, who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja. I love you.
Just three words. I love you.
Keren! The best! Sangat jelas ya.
Cool! The best! Very clear.
Tetap semangat, tetap semangat menjalani hidup ya. Udah gitu aja.
Stay spirited, keep the spirit in living your life. That's all.
Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang. Semangat!
Anyway, it's still a long way to the end. Keep it up!
Saranghaeyo! Gomawoyo!
I love you! Thank you!
Oke kalau aku... ya, semangat selalu!
Okay, as for me... yeah, always stay spirited!
Semangat santai! Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
Chill spirit! Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai ya?
A chill spirit, huh?
Semangat santai!
Chill spirit!
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjutkan...
Okay then, let's continue...
Wait wait wait, tunggu dulu!
Wait, wait, wait, hold on!
Sebelum selesai-selesai ini nih ya, kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu gak sih?
Before we wrap this up, why don't we shout together with the audience?
Iya dong! Ayo! Ayo ayo ayo!
Of course! Let's go! Come on!
Oke oke. Jadi kita teriak bareng ya, dalam hitungan tiga.
Okay, okay. So we'll shout together on the count of three.
Kita sama-sama teriak Chromatic Future. Oke ya?
We'll all shout "Chromatic Future" together. Okay?
Oke oke, Chromatic Future! Gitu kan ya?
Okay, okay, Chromatic Future! Like that, right?
Iya iya kayak gitu, kayak gitu.
Yeah, yeah, just like that.
Oke langsung ya, sambil lihat sini sini sini... sambil lihat...
Okay, let's do it, while looking here, here, here...
Aku ya, aku, aku yang penonton ini nih...
Me, me, I'll take this audience...
Iya iya, kalau gitu yang ini center ya...
Okay, then this one will be the center...
Yapoo~
Oke bareng-bareng ya. Satu, dua, tiga!
Okay, together now. One, two, three!
CHROMATIC FUTURE!
Everything was easy
I did it all alone
So effortlessly
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Got all problems solved
Without any setbacks
There is nothing uncontrolled
There is no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know, I gotta soar a little higher
Hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a winged peacock
Kan ku taklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan ku ajak
With the magic of wind I will invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit
All those who slumber to rise up
Melawan dunia
Against the world
We'll never give up
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
With hunger and love
Walking step by step
Trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go, just believe me
It will never bring me down
Just believe me, let it go
It will never bring us down
If it's spicy, just sip something
Let it go
I've been living carefree
There's no bitter wars in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Not letting it show
Things but I'm bigger than my feelings, so that will be enough
There is no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know, I gotta be better than ever
Hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a winged peacock
Kan ku taklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan ku ajak
With the magic of wind I will invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit
All those who slumber to rise up
...melawan dunia
...rise and fight the world.
We'll never give up
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than that
Walking step by step trusting my own faith
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Believe me
Let it go
They'll never bring me down
Just believe me
Let it go
It'll never bring us down
Just believe me
Won't let their cruelty steal my royalty
And when the universe works against me,
I will just let it go
Let it go
Well, I've got to do this!
One, two, three, let it go!
hololive Indonesia
CHROMATIC FUTURE
5th Anniversary LIVE
[Title: hololive Indonesia CHROMATIC FUTURE 5th Anniversary LIVE]