(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Ugh...
Oh, 皆さん...
Oh, everyone...
Oh, I don't feel so good.
Ugh...
Look, I'm gonna collapse from thickness.
Like I just went through a freaking portal or something crazy just happened.
At least I can see chat. Howdy.
No, no, I'm okay. Don't you worry about me.
I'm fine.
There's a... there's a lot of Dead Beats here today.
Maybe Dead Beats, KFP members, Takodachis...
...that's a lot of... ugh... people.
Let me catch my breath for a minute here.
Hold on.
That was some crazy traveling that I just did.
I think I went through like a wormhole or something.
It's not my fault that my eyes are done...
...No, hey, wait a minute!
Hey,
don't you start saying sh-
You start saying stuff like that, I swear to God I'll beat you within an inch of your life.
It's fine.
We're supposed to celebrate my fifth anniversary.
I'm five!
Can you guys believe I'm five?
Hold on, I probably should adjust the camera a little bit.
You can't see me, hang on.
Oh, you know what? I think I can take control of it if I click...
...there we go!
Oh.
Hey there!
What's up?
Ah... what do you... what do you think?
Do you like it?
Do you like this new outfit I found myself in?
Oh, "You look cute" Thank you!
Um, a lot of the girls told me I look like a robber...
...which, now that I've said it, you guys, you know, might be able to see it.
But, you know, there are various things that I can do and change with this...
...so...
So, "Beautiful" Oh, thank you!
"You look amazing" Thank you very much.
"Nice outfit" they say. I'm glad that you like it.
There's... there's many things that I can do...
...um, but I feel like I should...
You know, a good magician never shows all of their tricks like right away.
You know?
So, I figure, we have lots of time to celebrate...
...what is essentially five years of all of us being together, right?
So, I feel like I should be a little happier about that, right?
Thankfully, I can do something about that.
Yay! Five years, five years!
But you know, as you guys know, your Mori has like...
...little bit of a resting B-word face.
So I kind of... kind of have to force myself to smile a little bit.
That's okay, I can do that.
I can totally do that.
Hee!
Oh, wait, ah, sorry, I grabbed you.
I didn't mean to grab you.
What if I...
Peace.
Bero.
Tehe-pero-pero.
Hold on, I can do more than that though.
That's not... I'm not a one-trick pony or anything.
Aargh!
This is my favorite face...
...ever!
Is this... this is how I look all the time off-stream when you don't see me.
It's like I... I click "Stream Owari" and then my eyes just immediately shrink...
...to look like this. Just so you know.
This is... this is my usual, this is my normal, my nature.
So shocked.
Uh, "Shock" is one word for it. Uh, deadbeats and ghostcats see this...
...every day. You're right.
You're right, Deadbeat, this is... this is the Mommy that they're used to.
And then this is just my current... my constant state of being.
You guys don't mind, right?
Resting B-word face.
No problem, no problem.
Hi.
No, you guys are... you guys are... I'm just tired, but I'm happy.
I'm happy but I'm tired. This is normal, this is usual.
Nope, it's all good.
But but some day, um, we have plans to get like some really good...
...very decent face tracking. So look forward to that.
Um, oh by the way, just really quick before... before we get too in-deep into this...
Um, I have an announcement. There's a special goodie available to you guys.
You guys like goodies? I like goodies. You guys like goodies?
Um, we have...
We have a very special item for those of you that use VRChat.
It is a penlight for this specific event that you'll be able to claim.
There's going to be a link in the description, they're updating it as we speak.
Um, and also there will be a link on Twitter... X... Twitter for you guys to grab it.
It's very special, it's got the logo from this specific event.
And I... I wanted to put it out there, thankfully with the help... um, of the AEV...
...and... and VRChat... to do something really special for you guys.
This is a claimable item just to celebrate this... this big event...
...together with you guys.
I hope you guys will enjoy it and use it in VRChat...
...and have lots of fun with your friends if we ever do something like...
...future concerts in VRChat. I'm always really open to like...
...figuring out new tech and stuff like that... together with, you know...
...the other members and all these really amazing, technically powerful folks...
...and figure out like what more cool creative stuff we can do together...
...in terms of like lives and whatnot.
DUE TO A THANATOLOGICAL INCIDENT THE ELEVATOR IS OUT OF SERVICE
...for this amazing world that we're gonna go explore.
Oh man, it's nostalgic.
It's nostalgic.
Um, I want to do more fun stuff like this.
That's what I've realized after working so hard on this project for so long.
So, um... so yeah!
Thanks for, for being a part of it though, you guys.
I feel like I can get even wackier. Hold on.
Expressions, face expressions. Hold on.
Delay!
Wow!
This isn't a me you get to see very often.
Hehe. Aaaaah!
Then there's also... constant sleepiness.
Is this... this too is Seyun's guy?
My beloved.
Now I look like her. Um, we should move along.
I know that we should move along.
First I want to give a really huge thank you to...
...two folks who made this outfit possible.
Thank you so much to...
the designer of this outfit, Nanoless.
You guys know Nanoless?
Nanoless is so amazing and just has the most beautiful designs ever, outfit designs...
...and I had wanted to work with Nano for the longest time.
So I'm so glad that I got this outfit fully designed by Nanoless.
Hopefully we might get, we might get like a reference image at some point.
But thank you so much to Nano for creating this outfit. I love it so dearly.
I want to use it in music videos.
Um, so please look forward to that in the future.
And I also want to give a big ups to Yuly as well...
...who designed the model for this outfit, did all the 3D modeling for it.
So Nanoless did the design and Yuly did the actual 3D modeling.
And neither of those are easy tasks at all.
So thank you for going out of your way to make time for...
...just a little five-year-old Reaper like me.
I say five, I'm actually NO years old, but you get the point.
It's been five years together, right?
But yay! Yuly's so, so GOATed. Nano's so GOATed.
Thank you so much! And of course, this world...
...we're gonna get a little bit more into the creation of this world as well, I think.
But before we do that, we gotta kind of...
I want to kind of explore a little bit.
You know, there's stuff to look at around here, you guys. Hold on.
Did you guys see... hey, hang on a second.
There are a bunch of signs around here.
My Reaper looking extra cute. Thank you!
Your Reaper is trying to figure out where the heck we are...
...but there are some clues here and there that we can look at, right?
DUE TO A THANATOLOGICAL INCIDENT THE ELEVATOR IS OUT OF SERVICE
So let's take a look at this.
WHETHER YOU ARE ALIVE OR DEAD, PLEASE SEEK OUT YOUR LOCAL PSYCHOPOMP
Oh... I can read!
Due to a thanatological incident, the elevator is out of service.
Whether you are alive or dead, please seek out your local psychopomp.
I know a couple psychopomps. None of them are in Holo...
...but maybe someday we'll get a psychopomp.
I feel like we'd be really good friends and get along.
I don't know, five years I've been here, we haven't had a psychopomp...
...but who knows, in the next five we could maybe welcome one.
That would be cool.
Ame's elevator. See, that's what I'm thinking.
I remember this elevator even just from the shape of it, right?
DO NOT ANNOY THE ELEVATOR ATTENDANT, AME
Do not annoy the elevator attendant, Ame.
Yeah, no, this is, this is definitely, this is 100% Ame's elevator, I think.
What happened to it?
MAXIMUM CAPACITY 12 PEOPLE 50 IF SMOL
Do you guys know what the heck happened to this place?
Maximum capacity: 12 people. 50 if smol.
Do you guys remember when we had less than 12 people?
Because I do. I remember when we had less than 12 people.
Look at that. Then not everybody would have been able to fit into the elevator.
You know, what about...
...Advent and Justice, right? They wouldn't be able to fit.
Um, I mean if they could, if they were smol.
But the elevator would need to be renovated so that we could all fit.
Ame, Ame elevator... back then.
Smol, long times. Yes, time has flown by so fast, says Chat.
DO NOT FALL INTO TIME VORTEX
Hmm... time flies when you're having fun, right guys?
We don't know what will happen, but it doesn't look good
Let's see. Do not fall into the time vortex.
STRONG QUANTUM FLUCTUATIONS
We don't know what will happen, but it doesn't look good.
Keep yourself observed at all times to avoid disappearing
Okay, gonna heed those wise words.
Strong quantum fluctuations.
Keep yourself observed at all times to avoid disappearing.
Heh? What the heck?
I don't want to disappear, I have stuff to do.
Speaking of stuff to do, maybe we should move right along...
...because there are some really cool spots around here and I think I see...
DO NOT FALL INTO TIME VORTEX
Get this, Dead Beats.
A resort.
Will Mori Calliope be going there?
Probably, probably... yes!
I will for the sake of...
for the sake of this journey.
I'll go to the resort.
You guys want to come with?
Oh, I don't want to go alone.
So, my Dead Beats got to come with me, okay?
You guys got to come with me.
Is that all right?
You guys cool with that?
I could kind of use a rest.
It would be nice.
We got some fun surprises today.
So please look forward to them.
But, I guess we'll try and make our way out of here then, shall we?
Hmm...
Let's do it.
We need to observe you to prevent a disappearance.
You make a good point, skeletons.
You make a good point.
Well, let's go ahead and head on over then, shall we?
What does this say?
HUB...
Oh, I can't... Sorry, chat's kind of in my way.
That's all right.
I want you guys here.
I want you guys here, so...
it's no problem.
HUB AREA, it says.
Okay.
Observing, they're observing right now. Okay.
Mone-chans, do you hear that? They're observing.
Also, Mone-chans are here today working as hard as possible...
with cameras and such.
Thank you, Mone-chans.
All right, well I guess off we go.
To the resort! Oh gosh.
I don't like going to resorts because, Dead Beats...
I feel like I'm going to give in to my base, you know, human instincts...
instead of my Reaper side, which says "work, work, work."
My human side says it's time for a vacation.
So let's...
Let's just go.
Let's just go and see what happens, you know?
Making my way uptown.
Whoa!
I really need to fix my posture.
No, it's fine! Don't...
My posture's not the best.
I'm just... also, I can walk on water, by the way...
in case... in case you didn't know.
You guys like my Naruto run?
It's just my current state of being and movement.
You're back!
Oh wait, did you guys see the design on my back? The skull?
That's my logo.
That's my logo. I really want to release this jacket someday.
Wouldn't that be cool?
This would be a pretty cool jacket to release as merch.
I feel like I release too many clothing items, though.
We really don't need that many.
Well, anyway, I guess we better...
better get out of here.
Uh, what am I looking at?
Oh gosh, I don't want to show you guys what the clothes can do yet.
Uh, we'll get to that later, shall we?
Okay.
Let us be on our way, up the stairs.
I'll try... my posture's great.
I never would bend my back while I walk.
That's not something that Mori Calliope would ever do.
Whoa!
You guys see this?
This is a full-on, this is a full-blown resort.
What's... oh.
Hold on a second.
Hey, what's this little switch here? It's got a camera.
Okay, can I activate it, I wonder?
Oh.
Whoa! Check it!
You guys get a sweeping view.
Nice perspective.
Anything wrong with your spine?
No, it needs relaxation, which is why we've come here...
to this resort.
It looks like I could run around it as like a Dark Souls map.
Not everything is Dark Souls, I just... you know.
There's a bar!
Wait, hold on, I just barely missed...
Hang on, I have to fix my knee.
There's a bar!
Dead Beats!
Hold on, we're in trouble now.
Hang on, let's get to the center here.
Whoa!
I don't look very enthused, but I am excited.
Booze? No, wait a minute, Dead Beats.
Wait, it's not time yet.
It's not time, we have to... "Bar Mori"?
Do you guys remember Bar Mori?
Because I remember Bar Mori.
Oh, that was so fun.
I loved Bar Mori.
We should... we should have had more adventures there...
but that's on me.
That's on me, I got too busy with other stuff.
My knee's been feeling tired these days.
All about my knee.
There we go.
Anyway.
Fancy, classic.
This is not VR Chat, this is a vlog on Cali's vacation.
Wait, no, you've got it all wrong!
I'm working hard, I promise.
Look at the way that the water reflects off of me, though.
Isn't it pretty neat?
Hold on, can I do peace?
Peace!
I'm doing a pose, I'm doing a pose...
Hope you guys get lots of screenshots.
And remember to use #5YearsOfMori...
to share your favorite screenshots.
Okay? #5YearsOfMori.
You can also share your favorite memories...
um, or, you know, fan art too if you want.
Like whatever... whatever you want to use.
#5YearsOfMori to celebrate five years...
of the Grim Reaper invading your personal space.
And by personal, I mean like your home.
You know, because when you watch me, I'm there...
in your home.
Well, I guess we should look around maybe a little bit more.
Hmm...
Cool, whoa, what's this?
I dare not.
I dare not lay down.
We don't have time for that.
We don't have time.
Let's let's get moving around a little bit
'cause we got stuff to do.
Hang on a sec. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
YAGOO?
Hey, there's a bar over there, though.
There's a— there's a bar.
Before we get to YAGOO...
...can we just— can we hit the bar really quick?
Hang on.
No, this is— this is big.
This is big, big news.
All right. Dead Beats.
Welcome to Bar Mori.
Oh, you guys are back here.
I wonder if I can move— Let me get a martini.
Wait.
Hang on, I'm pulling you over here. I'm pulling my
chat in front of my face so that I can I can see them.
Okay. Pop, float, and we're—
Okay. There we go.
Now I can see you perfectly!
Now I can— I can take your order.
What would you guys like?
Can I get some whiskey?
Yes! I actually— I saved some just
for this special occasion, so...
...let me go grab it. Right here.
Yes. Welcome to Bar Mori. Here it is.
Hold— hold to gra— oh, this one. Hold to grab.
Oh, this! Okay, I got it.
No, I— AAAHHH! Wait, I dropped it.
Okay. Hold on, hold on, hold on. No, okay.
I'm not very good at this.
I— maybe I really do need a vacation.
Wait, no. Okay. Hang on.
The melon soda! See, that's a— that's a good choice.
All right. Here's— Got any glasses here?
We don't... um...
Well, all right, all right, chat. This is for you.
Fetch!
It landed perfectly upright!
It landed perfectly. You know what? This reminds
me I used to tell you guys about my— my old job.
I used to have a tough old job
that I did back in the day...
...and I served somebody like a drink that
didn't have enough like vodka or tequila in it...
...and they threw it in my face.
I remember telling you guys about that.
Well, I've been through a lot,
and I'm ready to unleash my rage!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Something happened.
Okay. Sorry, I had a blackout right there for
a second. All right, is this Amaretto?
Can I juggle it?
Yeah, I can!
Oh man, she's too good. Oh, she's too skilled.
Oh god, I dropped it. Okay, it's 'cause I got cocky.
It happens all the time for me. Uh, hang on, I got it.
No problem.
"So talented," they say. Big ups!
What do you mean? No, no E— There's no E-sports.
Stop! 違うよ！
Stop! No way!
It's coming out of your paycheck.
You know what I think about that?
I may have thrown it too far. Oh, there it goes!
Hey, this is way— this is better than I thought.
Whoa, this is— this is actually very
stress-relieving, believe it or not.
Bleh! Yeah, sometimes you just feel like you gotta...
I was supposed to be serving the Dead Beats.
Is this the thanks that they get...
...after five years of being loyal support—
supporters of the Grimm Reaper?
You know what? Yeah, it is!
It's messed up. I have other goodies. I have other
I have other goodies for you guys, I promise.
Yes, yes it is. It's so worth it. That—
you guys are too kind to me.
The Dead Beats are the kindest, what the heck.
Waffle house, watch out, watch out, watch out!
There's no...
...forget your street fights. This a trench war.
Hang on, can I pick up the— WHOA!
Oh my— I can pick up everything!
They freaking killed it with this.
Who is they? I will tell you shortly.
But anyway, we— we could play with—
I could throw bottles at you guys all day...
...but we do have to move right along
'cause we got a schedule to keep.
Schedule to keep!
All right. Let's go check out what
the heck happened over here.
Um... what am I looking at?
That's a... that's real special
right over there. The YAGOO.
Let me see if I can pull you guys up before me
again. Get in front of my face.
But yeah, so you can see... hang on. I gotcha.
Now don't be afraid. Don't be afraid, my small lambs.
This man will not hurt you. He's just...
he just has really expensive shorts.
#5YearsOfMori
That's a— that's my boss, by the way.
This is Michelangelo's YAGOO.
Golden swim trunks. Actually, uh 24-karat gold
swim trunks on my boss.
Good for him, good for him. Thank you for
thank you for the the resort resources.
Hey, is that Justice?
JUSTICE
Cool! We also have paintings of my
cute kohai as well here. Very nice.
And then the architecture—
WHOA! Okay. We're not that ancient.
MYTH
Yo, who made this?
Who made this Myth?
I don't know, what do you guys think?
Ancient myth?
Oh man, this is where my membership money goes.
That Dead Beats right, it sure is. Right right here.
to a grand carving such as this.
Myth.
Yes, the oldest and most decrepit and most ancient.
After that we moved into the promise age.
I promise, cute!
I love that this one is different in that it looks
like it could be a kindergarten's drawing,
but it's clearly not, like they made it with intent.
So it's not really what it is but...
Anyway.
Let's go Promise!
And then we also have, oh we can't forget them,
Advent right here.
There's Advent.
Look at all my cute kohai.
Solidified in history.
What a place of beautiful art.
There's a lot of artisticness that went into this,
a lot of artistry.
Oh man, we gotta give thanks though to whoever
put all of this together, right?
Shall we go take a quick look?
Here we go.
This map was created by SeafoamBoy,
map design and concept, art and modelling.
And then, Mmaellon,
programming and camera systems.
Wow, why are we looking at this plaque like
they're dead or something? Did they die?
I don't think that they died or anything
like that.
They did so well though.
I mean, Seafoam's vision here is just so amazing.
I can see there's so much nostalgia and love
for the five years that
HoloEN has been together like this.
I just think it's such a cool concept and I'm so
excited to share all of this with you guys.
It's so so cool.
Probably one of the coolest things I've ever done
in those five years is get a place like this.
Get to visit a place like this, right?
And then of course we can't forget Mmaellon who has
helped so much with the programming
and the camera systems.
I mean the camera systems is my favorite part
of this whole thing.
Like normally you can't do all this crazy stuff
with cameras.
But I'm so, so, so grateful.
Ah, thank you so much to you guys for the help
and all the programming too.
Man, my brain is... you guys know how my brain is.
It's not capable of handling things that programmer
brain can handle.
So I really, I really appreciate it.
And I'm so excited!
I don't look like I'm excited, but I'm excited
to get to the rest of it.
So yay!
We know. Hey, hold on a second.
Well, that's okay, I invited that conversation.
But there's something I want to... there's
something that's been bugging me.
Dead Beats, while we've been here...
It's that I feel like I did something here already.
I feel like I have a memory of being here at
a different time.
And I'm not just talking about the fact that it
reminds me of the original Myth lobby in many ways.
But oh wow, I really did just drop drinks
everywhere, huh? Okay.
That's kind of messed up. I really shouldn't
have done that, that was very rude of me.
I feel as though I've sung a song here
before with friends.
And I want... I'm thinking I might end up
remembering that.
I think I've sung a couple of songs here.
And so I think I want to flash back to those
if I can.
I feel like if I channel like my innermost
mind, my inner brain,
then I can have like a That's So Raven moment
where like you gaze into the future,
but instead it's the past.
The end will be a breeze... sorry sorry.
Anyway, so let's...
let's do that everybody, let's...
Let's go!
Flashback!
FLASH BANG
Produced by PES / Arranged by PES / MATZ
Lyrics by PES / Mori Calliope
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Come on. Check us.
On and on it goes on and on you gotta let me go
but I'm already gone.
On and on it goes on and on you gotta let me go.
でしょ？
Right?
くらえ、慣れろこれが始まり
Take it, get used to it, this is the start
パーティーや集まれ人生は早々
Party time, gather 'round, life is fleeting
明日、名残に俺だ
Tomorrow, I'm the remnant
クソ遊びだ 醒ますデザインさ 早々
It's a shitty game, a design that awakens, quickly
死期、危機、欲し
Time of death, crisis, desire
命の、管理
Management of life
迷える私と、養子
Lost me and the child
あら あら あら あら
Oh my, oh my
本当は ずっともう oh oh
The truth is, for a long time now
楽しいフリして eh eh
Pretending to have fun
消えた私を oh oh
The me that vanished
君が見つけて
You found me
ね、ほら
Look, see?
ふらふらするでしょ
You're feeling dizzy, right?
くらくらするでしょ
Your head is spinning, right?
ほろほろ溶けそう
Feeling like I'm melting away
そうでしょ
Right?
FLASH BANG
くら、くら、狂いそう
Dizzy, dizzy, like I'm going crazy
そろ、そろ、壊れそう　So the show
Slowly, slowly, like I'm breaking. So the show.
Flashback
Hey! Hey!
Come on!
Break it down!
Flashback
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Come on everybody! Woo!
Flashback
Yeah yeah, Verse 2.
まどろむ Underground
Slumbering Underground
弾みついた開放感
A bouncy sense of liberation
剥がれたペルソナ
A peeled-off persona
Holly night, break it down
Holy night, break it down
だんだん　崩れてく感覚
Gradually, my senses crumble
詰まるのは息をするように簡単
Getting stuck is as easy as breathing
狂っていく　私　時は待ってなし
Going crazy, me, time doesn't wait
涙は枯らし　あらあら
Tears are dried up, oh my
山なんか転生した
Like I've been reincarnated into the afterlife
みたいな異世界感　まとって違う人みたいだ
Clad in an other-worldly feel, like I'm a different person
そりゃ今日もお美しであっともっとアンダ
Well, today you're beautiful too, and more...
You choose me
あの頃の君はもう幻のように吸い込まれそう
The you of those days is like a phantom now, about to be sucked away
それが Flashback　滑り出すんだ目が回るんだ
That is the flashback. It starts sliding, my head is spinning.
ぐるぐるぐるぐる
Round and round and round and round
本当はきっともう
The truth is, surely already
戻れないよね
We can't go back, can we?
ちらつく心
A flickering heart
君を探して
Searching for you
よ、ほら　ふらふらするでしょ
Yo, look, you're getting dizzy, aren't you?
くらくらするでしょ
Dizzy, dizzy, aren't you?
ほらほら、解きそう　そうでしょ
Look, look, it's about to come undone, isn't it?
Flashback
ギラギラ酔いましょう
Let's get dazzled and drunk
さあさあ踊りましょう
Come on, come on, let's dance
真っ白に目眩むほどほら焼き付けてよ
Look, sear it in until it's dazzlingly white
Flashback
Woo-hoo! Nice job, CHAD-KAS!
Buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz!
Well done. You guys got some moves.
Oh my god.
What's she doing?
Are you good?
I was thinking you could use a little rest.
I think you could... What is she doing?
Hey, hey. It's okay.
IRyS, I think...
I think you guys need to go relax.
You guys need to go... All right, great.
Have some fun at the resort, you know there's a cool bar.
Resort time!
I'll see ya!
Bye, you two!
Oh god, I have a feeling it's about to get real wild back there.
Maybe we should do another song though, in the meantime, huh?
Bye, guys! They're gone.
They'll have fun. Don't worry about them.
Let's... let's do another song, shall we?
Let's go!
Kamoflauge
My Kamoflauge
What you gonna do, shit, take a walk?
Like I had a choice
Like a see-saw, just say so
Hush my boy
Never pick a figure
And disappearing, ice, na-na-na
Secret sinners, oh you rang
Can't fool me like tick-tick-bang
Come alive, there you go
眩日な逃避行
A dazzling escape
どこまでも匿名希望
Wishing for anonymity forever
Excuse to see some proof it's me
Puh-puh-pa don't react, eyes right here
Whoa-oh-oh, so crazy what you want
Predicting all my flaws
But all you see is my Kamoflauge
Whoa-oh-oh, hey baby why so sharp
Your Mona Lisa tough
Still nothing you search can show my heart
My Kamoflauge
My Kamoflauge, what you gonna do shit, take a walk
Come alive, got to shift with the scene and the vibe
And I'm just shuffling with the moment
Don't let it stop, no chance, this who you got to be
Come alive, where you go
鏡合わせの向こう
Beyond the mirror alignment
すり抜ける　この包囲網
Slipping through this dragnet
Excuse to see some proof it's me
Puh-puh-pa don't react, eyes right here
Whoa-oh-oh, so crazy what you want
Predicting all my flaws
But all you see is my Kamoflauge
Whoa-oh-oh, hey baby why so sharp
Your Mona Lisa tough
Still nothing you search can show my heart
My camouflage
What you gonna do, shit, take a walk
Hey, why so sharp?
Shit, take a walk
My camouflage
Doing something new, shit, can't you knock?
Can't fight no more
Hideaway, hideaway
What is this dark side I'm heading for?
It is something
So crazy what you want
Predicting all my font
But all you see is my camouflage
What happen-ah? Hey deadbeat, why so sharp?
Your Mona Lisa touch, doing something new, shit, can't you knock?
So crazy what you want
Predicting all my font, but all you see is my camouflage
What happen-ah? Hey deadbeat, why so sharp?
Your Mona Lisa touch, doing something new, shit, can't you knock?
My camouflage
What you gonna do, shit, can't you knock?
Guess I gotta use this camouflage.
Bau bau bau bau bau bau bau!
Hi!
Oh geez! Thank you guys for dancing with me today!
Wow, and you guys sound so good too!
Oh! I'm being hugged!
I'm being hugged! Oh my gosh!
Wait, go enjoy the resort, you guys. Have fun!
Get some rest. Bye-bye!
There's doggy treats over there... maybe.
Go find 'em. Go find 'em.
They're gonna go look for the treats.
(sigh) Maybe... maybe I should relax here for a little bit.
No! We have more songs to do, Dead Beats.
No rest for the wicked.
So, while my friends are enjoying the resort,
I'm gonna go do some more work.
Just for a little bit, though. We can go back later, right?
Yeah. That's what I'm gonna go do.
Well, let's get out of here.
No, no, we can come back later.
We can come back later. I'm out.
I'm outskies. I'm out.
Yeah, don't... don't worry about... about those guys.
Hey, listen, in fairness, don't worry about the Xbox mic either.
I did that to them on purpose.
It was not them, it was me.
I cursed their mics with Xbox mic syndrome because...
(chokes) Choking on my own spit.
Because... because... their voices are too cute and they needed to be nerfed.
That's all that it was.
But no, it's not... it's not their fault. I assure you it was all me.
How dare you! That's fine. I will take... I will take your insults.
I will take all of them.
Also, if my friends, if my friends ever need me to come in for a song
and like, tank all the bad words, let me know. I'll do it.
I went through... I went through a period in the past five years
where I was like... Here, we can walk and talk.
We can walk and talk. I went through a period of time
within the past five years being like, 'You know what?'
'Maybe I should calm down with the curse words.'
But... but it's just because, you know, I'm getting to be an old woman, right?
As you can see, I'm walking like a decrepit, crotchety old lady...
...with my shoulders all the way down.
But honestly, if it's for a song, who cares, right?
It's just... just for F-word.
Yeah, speed walking. Good old curse words.
We stay family-friendly here, but to be honest... to be honest,
I've... I've heard children use fouler language than I've ever used in my life.
So, you know what? It is what it is.
It is what it is. It looks like I'm rapidly roller skating.
Maybe that's what I'm doing. Maybe there are skates
on the bottom of these shoes and you guys don't even know.
Anyway, um, I look like less of a robber, don't you think?
Without the beanie?
I look a little bit less like I'm gonna break into your home...
...which is, I don't know, a plus or minus depending upon how you view it.
But I can take my headphones off too. See? There, they're gone.
They're gone. I don't really know. I mean, it kind of covers my jewelry
so it's kind of nice that you can see the finer details, right?
So I've got like a little skull lapel. Check it.
Lapel... lapel? It's maybe just a pin. I don't know.
But I'm really into chokers these days and spikes and stuff like that.
So, yeah. Law-abiding Reaper. Oh, but of course, but of course.
Definitely. Looking respect-... oh, of course, yeah.
Looking... checking respect... Yeah, only with respect.
With respect. What do you guys think?
Do you like the inside of my jacket too?
It's got kind of like a checker pattern. Anyway, we're supposed to be moving.
Wait along, but I'm kind of taking my time around here as well.
We do have many more memories to... re-familiarize ourselves with though.
Let me... let me grab you.
Oh, don't worry. You won't feel it and it won't hurt.
Okay, I've grabbed you successfully.
Let me... hold on. Swirl eyes? What do those look like?
Hang on. Oh, I'm still on desktop. Okay.
Swirl eyes...
She's a little quirky and crazy.
But it makes me like her more, I guess. I don't know.
You're still here after five years? You've certainly got some taste.
All right, let's go ahead and move.
I love the architecture in this place.
Lots of respect to the underworldian culture here.
With our... our underworldian maidens.
I don't know who this lady is. Could this be the real Calliope?
Could it be...
...the real Muse Calliope? It could be.
If it isn't, then that's now my headcanon, but...
...but I probably should change my... my eyes to not be so swirly. Sorry about that.
I'm just being extra quirky today.
Lore, hmmm? I'm telling you, I think that it's the original Calliope.
We're going to move with respect, right behind her.
And I wanted to say I saw this before, but I didn't want to get too ahead of myself.
Check this out guys. Where are we?
What is this place? You can see the sky and the fragments.
But then beyond, there's like a swirling deserted city.
And then I see that there's like... I'm really interested in the Hell Temple that's over here.
Do you guys see that Hell Temple? I think we should go there next.
It reminds me of something that I've seen before on multiple levels, right?
I think that you guys might be able to draw the links between the places that we're visiting today...
...and also some VR shenanigans that we've gotten down to in the past, right?
But... but for now, it looks cool. Yay!
Design is wild, right? Isn't it awesome?
And we're going home, onto the next stage indeed, AD-LIB indeed.
Like from AD-LIB and JIGOKU 6. AD-LIB and JIGOKU 6 was... was my concert, right?
But JIGOKU 6 is my EP. Maybe it's not the best idea to use the same...
...the same word in my concert/shows, because people might get confused.
Anyway, we're going over the bridge to check out what the heck this place is.
I love lanterns! The aesthetic is pretty much on point for what I enjoy, but...
...uh... Hold on. I'm getting that... weird feeling again, like I've been here before.
Uh... hang on a second. Hey, hey, hey, hold up. You see that? It's one of those... one of those camera signs.
What if we touch it? Hold on a sec. Let me see that camera. Camera right here.
Uh... this should give us a sweeping view. Okay, check it out. Oh, whoa!
Okay, now I'm feeling ultra nostalgic.
Heh? I feel like this isn't the first time that I entered this place though. Like I've seen it before.
Uh... I think I feel a memory coming on you guys. A memory singing a song with someone here.
Well, if that's the case, then let's... let's check it out!
Oh, this place is pretty cool too! Heh? Cool stuff everywhere.
Especially... well, this is awesome! It's got lanterns!
What the heck? Didn't I dance in front of that fire during JIGOKU 6?
Hey, is that the pirate from the Future Island stage that was in the JIGOKU 6 concert?
It has to be! This place is awesome! This is so cool! What the heck?
Heh? I wonder... are there any friends around here too? What friends are here, I wonder?
Oh... oh... oh... Are you okay?
Oh, she's climbing up those stairs.
I know there's a lot of stairs. Jimodori? Are you okay?
I know it was a lot of stairs. She's really wheezing.
Oh god. Are you okay, little one?
I'm alive...
This place is flames!
Hey there!
Hi! You might not know this, but I can see a lot of things from down here.
I... I know you can. I... I figured as much.
Whoa, hey. Don't look too long though. Don't look too... Whoa there, whoa. She's a little close.
You've got such a big head here. I didn't expect to see you like this.
Oh my lord. Uh... wait, you're not mad at me?
No, no, no, I have no problem with it, it's just...
That... really... what is it... the ahoge... it really sticks out.
Oh my god! Ouch! Ouch!
Why are you beating on me? Hey! Oi, oi, omae!
Why are you beating on me? Hey! Hey, hey, you!
It's a show! Move over! Quick! Quick!
Stop! Stop it! Why are you so crazy?
I know the answer. I know the answer.
What's the answer?
I love you so much though.
And I love you, Mori-chama. I can't wait to...
Oh god...
...do so many things with you.
I want to do some things with you too,
but one of those things is... thing.
One... thing on this stage in front of this fire.
Name two!
Um... dance on this stage in front of this fire.
Okay, what's the third one though?
Um... be beside you.
Does it start with kissing me?
Um, maybe later... we can... not in front of the people.
It depends on where, too. You may kiss my hand if you want.
(Mwah!)
Okay, yeah, that's...
Perfect, perfect. Alright, that's great.
Shall we sing a little... a little song?
Oh god, I'm flustered now.
Alright, let's sing a dang song together.
How about it?
Alright, play music!
Check one two. Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
虚像のCarousel feat. Reol
Phantom Carousel feat. Reol
Mori-shi! Jijimura! Let's go!
Let's go! Woo!
Are you listening?
One, two, one by one to play the toy
soldiers of a corporation
Showdown なら One on one
If it's a showdown, it's one on one
アタシだろうに　至れり尽くせりそりゃ当然
It's obviously me, getting the royal treatment is only natural
さあ　やってやりましょう
Now, let's do this
Are you entertained? Now let the karma rain down
I can play the hero if it means I'll be the last clown
Living in the twisted diorama that is industry
Failing in the streets, making it for those of us...
今夜も変身　君様様々
Transforming again tonight, thanks to you, my dear
一緒にアタシに夢見てよフリーキー
Dream of me together, freaky
妄想並列　ロールプレイ　這い這う
Parallel delusions, roleplay, crawling around
君とだから全部　Let's dig in!
Because it's with you, let's dig in to it all!
Mirror, Mirror Tell me again
ひび割れた姿で愛でたのはストローク・ラック
What I adored in my cracked form was stroke luck
Louder, Mirror Just say that I'm enough
優劣さえ　一抜けで勝ち逃げで鳥越
Even superiority/inferiority, I'm first to quit, a clean getaway to the birds
Yeah yeah, are you ready? Go!
Hate to be the one to break the fairy tale apart
But the cash inside the mechanism's what they label smart
Drop dead, nobody cries. Step now and fall behind.
Every idol beauty's got a beast inside of mind
ハイ、注目！　表紙のマガジン
Hey, look here! The magazine cover
Things you said but didn't mean,
it's reading like a ransom letter
Full of stains we'll never clean or wash away
滑稽ですね、如何せん、そんなもんじゃない人生
It's laughable, isn't it? After all, life isn't just that
豪奢的　義務、ここら辺が　義務
Luxurious duties, around here are the duties
無像無相　小さく　知恵の　正味分
Formless and shapeless, a small portion of wisdom
ボコボコでは　なくなった　角角や　自慢を
The bumpy bits are gone, the sharp edges and my pride
いつも　アンタに　捧げたかった　多角
I always wanted to offer you my many facets
逆にもっとショーインしたの　No way, 好きです
On the contrary, I've shown more, no way, I love you
時を流せん　欲したの　No way, 来なよ
Time won't flow, I wanted it, no way, come here
Proudly in a culture, caught up in the couture
慣れ慣れ　誰かの　享楽も　望み
Getting familiar, someone else's pleasure is also desired
Watch us! SOS! 私たちは誰？
Watch us! SOS! Who are we?
光が射す影
A shadow where light shines
Mirror, Mirror Loud and Enough
死神だって　神に乗って
Even the Reaper rides on God
ようこそ　極彩の　理想郷
Welcome to the richly colored utopia
奪う destiny 逃れよう
Let's escape the destiny that snatches away
You lie, so well, Mirror, Mirror
本当の　私は　Where is?
Where is the real me?
走馬灯から現世　お疲れ様
From the revolving lantern to this world, good job
あたしら　ダラダラ　仕事しない　リバート
We're just lounging around, not working, Revert
ノリノリ　君は　ロールプレイ　這い這う
In high spirits, you're roleplaying, crawling around
喜ばせてぜんぶ　買ってく　プライド
Make me happy and I'll buy up all your pride
何回でも　あたしがいれば　OK
As many times as it takes, if I'm here, it's OK
メンテ肯定した　ちょっとの　魂
A bit of soul that affirmed the maintenance
捧げたよ　close な　画角　五角形
I offered it, a close frame, a pentagon
My check! 地獄から　新登場　インの　アイドル
My check! A new appearance from Hell, the Inn idol
愛を背負った　ビトン錠
Vitron pill carrying love
Keep it up! 選り好み　腰に添え
Keep it up! Picky choosing, hand on hip
呑み込む　魅惑　ご馳走様
Swallowing the allure, thanks for the feast
Canvas to follow the irrelevant
You only gotta celebrate,
you only gotta get out of your shell a bit
If you ever make it better,
hope that you can take it with you
Always good as naked, it's a live-in or first to break!
I don't care anymore!
Yeah! Yeah! Jijimurins doing some stuff!
I'm freaking out!
What's she doing?
I'm freaking out! I'm freaking out!
Hey! Yeah! Whoo! Mori Calliope!
It's just business Mirror, Mirror Tell me again
ひび割れた姿で愛でたのはストローク・ラック
What I adored in my cracked form was stroke luck
Louder, Mirror Just say that I'm enough
優劣さえ　一抜けで勝ち逃げで鳥越
Even superiority/inferiority, I'm first to quit, a clean getaway to the birds
It's a paradise
捧げた手を出して果てまで愛を込めて愛想
Reach out the hand you offered, with love to the end, courtesy
鳴らせ　レコード　廻るは　カルーセル
Sound the record, the carousel is turning
Oh my god, it's a mad, mad world!
It's a paradise
水鏡　対極を
Water mirror, the opposite pole,
本当の　ものさし　なんてもう
a real ruler is no more
吐く嘘なら　バットエンドなら　代えよ
If it's lies you spit, if it's a bad end, let's change it
本当の...
The real...
I remember when Gigi was freaking it, do you guys?
She was freaking it.
I think it's super cute that I feel...
...I get the feel that only she has chosen to be in that form.
Only Gigi... only Gigi wanted to be so,
...so small and rotund and cute.
Anyway, I guess we should look around a little bit. She does that all the time.
I see some Grims in here know what's up, or any...
Gigi, Gigi's so special.
Oh, I love her, I love her very much.
She's always so nice and fun to hang out with.
I was so glad that I could, I could sing on a stage like this with her.
Speaking of this stage, should we look around a little bit? Here, follow me.
What's this? This seems like a really cool view over here.
I love that the lanterns have like this Myth... Myth logo on them. Check it.
Do you guys see? Look, and they glow in like red and yellow.
And you can see so many different areas just from here.
Heh, Myth forever, right guys?
See that place over there, that... is that... is that Atlantis? I want to go to Atlantis.
Wait, we can't... we can't get ahead of ourselves though. There are a lot of different places to look at, but...
Oh man, I guess we can, we can look at a little bit more of this area.
Uh, let's see.
As I mentioned before in the memory, that, that pirate...
...is that the pirate from the...
...from the Future Island performance from Jigoku 6? The concert?
I think it is. Look at that big guy.
And it says... I think that's the kanji for "king" on his... Oh gosh, there's fire in my eyes.
We don't want to fall down there,
...but if we did fall down there, something cool might happen. Maybe there's a secret underneath that fire.
I want to discover the secrets. But there will be time to look at secrets later, I think.
Uh, getting really... getting really hot, Dead Beats.
Ugh, I don't feel so good.
But the heat is reminding me of something.
The heat is reminding me that... I think that... this wasn't the only performance that I did here.
I think there was another one, with two... with two other people.
If I stand here, I might be able to... remember.
All right. I think I do.
Okay. Check it out!
There’s only hell or Mo', it’s all the same
Flawless and cautious, oh what a heckin' shame
清楚の depth, you’re just a shame
The depth of "Seiso", you’re just a shame
Mori!
Shit! I’m a walking disaster,
Then I’ve got the last girl.
You say stop, I go faster,
Talkin’ slaughter and laughter. Boom boom bap!
あとどれまま見せて？
How much more of that will you show me?
あっという間に lipstick
Lipstick on in the blink of an eye
I can hear you wanna blow up this シカトは無し
I can hear you wanna blow up this, no turning a blind eye
I'ma hit it like a light switch, pow!
I'm such a cosmic pain, they walk into Tommy Shop,
Ain't no hero, サバイバルできのう
Ain't no hero, couldn't survive yesterday
Hey, got devils in my brain, come make 'em shut up next,
Say a prayer, now this is what I'm sayin'.
Forget sports, this is war, what you waiting for?
Good Lord, Mori's bored, welcome to the killin’ floor.
Got no will to rot,
Don't look at me like I'm dumb.
Do my swear, life ain't fair, I don't care, the end is nigh.
The end is nigh.
The end is nigh, uh, didn't get the memo yet, end is nigh.
Boys line up single file, gonna end the world in style,
Gals armageddon stuff, I gotta kill 'em all cause end is nigh.
There’s only hell or Mo', it’s all the same,
Flawless and cautious, oh what a...
下剋上、見事。
Succession from below, magnificent.
死の独り子。
The only child of death.
She on a new world order's throne, does that make you see?
Prepare for the apocalypse, they hit my guts a rhythm hits,
Don't take the bait, stick to the script, then brim like a fool when the numbers dip.
What now? Make 'em shut down,
Yeah Shinigami gang in a rough town,
Break new ground, black and blue sound,
またまたブチかまし next round.
Giving it my all once again in the next round.
悪知の my mind, don't want you to die, prices a little bit of ego.
With my cunning mind, I don't want you to die, prices a little bit of ego.
The cynics want a seat in these rows, emperors got hella new clothes.
Forget sports, this is war, what you waiting for?
Good Lord, Mori's bored, welcome to the killin’ floor.
Love ain't fair, but hold up what's this?
Naturally that means death is justice.
Let me liberate you, step back I hate you, we gonna make it go bam bam bam bam bam!
The end is nigh.
The end is nigh...
Single file, when having the worst of times
Get onto my level and start the fight
Gotta come on, gotta end this night!
Rat-tat-tat-ta-da!
So end it all...
...end this night!
End this night!
Something's gotta give
Gonna burn that retching live
Get onto my level and step the light
Let it pass by, end this night!
Woo! Yeah, yeah!
All right! Big up Raora and IRyS!
Come on!
Rat-tat-tat, end this night!
We Are Currently Experiencing Technical Difficulties. Please Hold!
Uh oh, where am I?
Hang on! Hang on guys!
Where are my Dead Beats? Where are...
I think I found them. Hang on.
Uh... my Dead Beats! Oh gosh...
I feel like I have to go pick up my special camera.
My special camera, I left it...
I left it at the... the other... the other place.
Yeah, that performance was a little too hot, you guys.
Uh, I think it destroyed...
it destroyed the computer, it destroyed VRC, it destroyed everything.
That's how hot of a performance that was.
Hold on, let's... I bet we can cut through here
really quick to get my camera.
(Grunts) Hang on.
Well, you guys know how it's been the past five years.
There's always a little surprise guest...
...some scuff.
I... I like to believe that EN has moved on
from all of that, but occasionally it will creep back up on me.
That's okay, no problem.
I'm gonna grab my camera.
Okay, here we go.
Oof! Quite the workout.
But I got it.
Hello!
As you can see, I'm, uh...
What if we just...
I think I've got the power to teleport.
Oh! Okay.
Whew! I'm gonna get the camera.
What'd you guys think of the Hell Temple?
I figured maybe we could move right along, though.
Um, there's some secrets around the Hell Temple...
...that I think we'll leave for a little bit later.
But for now, I wanted to say,
do you guys see that hand over here?
What is this?!
This is some end-of-the-world stuff.
Look at that.
Do you see that hand?
It's just, what's the hand doing there?
What if I were to stand on the hand
and do some poses?
Maybe we can get some poses of me
standing on the hand.
This is like some, some Evangelion stuff.
You know, it's just me and my skeleton
at the end of the world, standing on a hand.
What the hand doin'? What the hand doin'?
Let me pull my deadbeats closer to me.
Hang on a second.
Uh, okay, pull, I'm pulling you closer.
I'm reeling you in like you're a fish on a hook.
Giant skelly!
Yeah, let's grab some screenshots if you want.
This is Mori Calliope posing on a hand.
Wait, I should do something super whimsical.
What if I did a pose with like,
no eyeballs or something?
Hang on.
'Cause that could be fun. No eyes!
What she doin'?
What she doin' on the hand?
What she doin' on—did you know I could
stretch my leg this far—
Oh god, I'm gonna fall!
No, it's no problem.
I'm just being super whimsical.
I'm being super whimsical.
Do a backflip! I can't. I can't.
The tracking is just too, too good over here.
It's too good.
It's not possible. I'm too busy
doing real body tracking.
Anyway, you guys want to...
let me get my eyes back.
Ugh, it's been a crazy day, huh?
Well, let's, let's go ahead and check out the city...
...because there's some stuff here
that I wanted to look at, so.
Not just the hand, but check this out.
What is this little arena over here?
With all this de-brass?
Actually, the word is debris.
Maybe we can get a better look.
Hang on, would you guys like a better look
at this place?
'Cause I would like a better look at this place.
So what if we... Oh!
Hey guys, I found one of those camera thingies.
Uh, if I press this button,
we might be able to get...
Ooh! Check it!
It's a dilap-dilapidated...
...dilap-titated city.
Is that big Papa Deadbeat?
Could that be THE Papa Reaper up there?
Was Adventure held here? You would think, right?
See, that's the kind of vibe
that I'm getting from this place.
This dilapidated city.
And that's a deadbeat being chained by his neck.
Maybe we could save him. I feel bad.
That's actually my house.
Oh god, I'm sorry, deadbeat.
I didn't mean to show your house like
that in front of everybody.
Oh, I'm sorry. Wait, that was an accident.
But look, people really could live here.
Would I choose to live...
maybe I should build my house here.
'Cause I'm looking into building a house,
right deadbeats?
I mentioned that. Maybe I should
build my house here.
Oh! You guys want to see something cool, actually?
There's something that I haven't shown you
I can do with this outfit.
You're really close. I'm really close to you. Hi.
Check this out. Hold on, I'm changing. Don't look.
Okay, here we go.
No jacket!
No jacket Mori Calliope!
Check it out!
My hands doing funny things.
Did you know that I have 50 extra
tendons in my hands?
Peace sign. Let me do a peace.
Peace! Handy-cam.
Gasp! Shoulder exposed. No way.
It looks pretty cool though.
Perfect for summertime, right?
Although I get the feeling if I put on the beanie...
...I would definitely look like a robber in that case.
What can you do?
Nothing much, but summer just ended,
did it really?
I don't feel like it's ended.
I feel like we still got a ways to go.
But back to the relevant subject here.
Back to the relevant subject.
We're in this dilapidated city.
Isn't this cool?
I'd love to just rest my legs,
but I feel like another memory's coming on.
You know? Another "I've been here before
and sang some songs with some friends."
So, would you guys like to see that?
Maybe we can both have a brain blast together.
Channel your third eye.
Channel the inner part of your brain
to remember things that you forgot.
That's something that I could really...
...actually do more often.
It'd be very helpful for me.
But anyway,
um,
let's go ahead and run the memory!
Cult Following
All Composed by WARGASM (UK)
Producer: Charlie Russell
Lyrics by: Mori Calliope / WARGASM(UK)
Cut your water ties.
This ain't the only battlefield I can advertise.
Ego isn't armor,
so put the camera down and face it.
They want to get complacent.
Come and lung with air,
you say you stand for nothing no-one else can relate.
Just know the company you keep
is in the business of hate.
Are you afraid?
I'm close to getting paid.
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest.
Going shoot shoot shoot, oh baby did you mesh?
Ricochet,
ricochet,
you can think about me any time, of any day.
Forget your street fights,
this trench war.
I'll make you mosh mosh mosh till you hit the floor.
Getting thirsty for collision,
let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row.
Lock and load.
Now here we go!
This ain't a lifeline,
it's a call to arms.
Become the risen, the unforgiven.
Make a decision if you're looking for
permission to write,
you got it wrong.
Say goodbye to your identity,
click flash, now you belong.
Situation is fluid at all,
took out my writers' paint and markers
and I ruined the wall.
It's not that complicated,
I could choose to run but I crawl,
just let the ankles of the skeptics
who I wish and we fall.
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest.
Going shoot shoot shoot, oh baby did you mesh?
Ricochet,
ricochet,
you can think about me any time, of any day.
Forget your street fights,
this trench war.
I'll make you mosh mosh mosh till you hit the floor.
Getting thirsty for collision,
let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row.
Lock and load,
now here we go!
This ain't a lifeline,
it's a call to arms.
Become the risen, the unforgiven.
Make a decision if you're looking for
permission to write,
you got it wrong.
Say goodbye to your identity,
click flash, now you belong.
Fighting all our battles now the kind too well,
they go ready set rage and they follow us to hell.
Finger on the trigger about to cock it and line,
got a lyric in the chamber
but I'm aiming my own gun.
Forget your street fights,
this trench war.
I'll make you mosh mosh mosh till you hit the floor.
Getting thirsty for collision,
let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row.
Lock and load,
now here we go!
This ain't a lifeline,
it's a call to arms.
Become the risen, the unforgiven.
Make a decision if you're looking for
permission to write,
you got it wrong.
Say goodbye to your identity,
click flash, now you belong.
Ever onward.
Lock and load.
Stepping up to play the coward,
step by someone you've devoured,
it's a sick, twisted mess,
created existence.
Ever onward.
Lock and load.
Stepping up to play the coward,
step by someone you've devoured,
it's a sick, twisted mess,
created existence.
Ever onward...
Errors creeping through the core.
Protocols failing.
System collapse in 3, 2, 1.
La la la...
OVER//RIDE
Lyrics/Composition/Piano: Mizuki Kamada
Bass: Shinichirou Iwakiri / Drums: Genta Shirakawa
はずれたノイズの無い側で
On the side where there's no stray noise
Just to face another delete
模良も正義も立たない Of course
Of course, neither virtue nor justice stands
洒落たらぬ Rewind, what is mine?
An unstylish rewind, what is mine?
最深蝕む Parasite
Parasite eroding the deepest part
Just watch the dance 絹抜ける
Just watch the dance, slipping through silk
Echo 伝播 Glitching mind
Echo propagating, glitching mind
Mirror mirror mirror
何度終わっても
No matter how many times it ends
何度壊されても
No matter how many times it's broken
それでもまだ
Even so, still
戦え 抗え 進め
Fight, resist, move forward
根性を宿して
With guts in your soul
OVER//RIDE, OVER//RIDE ゼロの光放つへと
OVER//RIDE, OVER//RIDE, towards emitting zero light
この狂った世界で
In this crazy world
証明を叫ぶ
Shout out the proof
No rewind, no reset その先に
No rewind, no reset, beyond that
咲く花が
The blooming flowers...
狂っちゃいない 選んだ道だ
I go, I ride, I'll go bright.
I'm not crazy, it's the path I chose
I go, I rise, overbright
We fall, we rise, we override.
Feeling extra erratic,
can't expect nothing but bad
Lost inside nightmares,
set the fear, strip it big
Unleash emotions make us stares,
in the end going nowhere
Drowning, what's the truth?
Rise and break the chain!
懺悔的行いのファイアウォール
A firewall of penitential actions
Just one more step go go go Gloria low
Cry out, break down those broken dream
Rewire rewire rewire
Never let you never up ああ でも
Never let you never up... Ah, but...
何度閉ざされても
この手でまた
No matter how many times it's closed off
With these hands again
つなげ えがけ
終焉の扉へ
I'll connect it, I'll draw it
To the door of the end
Override Override 灰の中から
Override Override, from the ashes
光を掴め
Seize the light
ただ 無慈悲な夜に
Just in the merciless night
真実をかざせ
Hold up the truth
No Rewind, No Reset 選ばれぬ道に
No Rewind, No Reset, on the path not taken
咲く花よ
The flowers bloom
狂っちゃいない 選んだ道だ
I'm not crazy, it's the path I chose
I go, I ride,
I'll go bright.
We fall, we rise, we override.
嗚呼 貸し出した世界で
Ah, in the world I lent out
これだけが響いた
Only this resonated
孤独を焼き尽くせ
Burn away all loneliness
限界を蹴り飛ばせ
Kick away the limits
宿命をねじ伏せろ
Overpower fate
Zero out despair now!
Override Override 天の子の声に
Override Override, to the voice of the child of heaven
響く声を上げろ
Raise a resonating voice
この痛みを抱いて
Embracing this pain
最果てへ向かえ
Head for the furthest ends
No Rewind, No Reset カオスの先に
No Rewind, No Reset, beyond the chaos
咲く花がある
There is a flower blooming
狂っちゃいない 選んだ道だ
I'm not crazy, it's the path I chose
I go, I ride,
I'll go bright.
We fall, we rise, we override.
She died!
Do you guys remember when Nerissa Ravencroft died?
Cause I do!
Uh, these have been really fun, these memories.
I've really enjoyed looking through them with you guys.
I saw somebody in chat said "Help, is she on desktop?"
No, she's in the world with us!
But you know, a desktop is very helpful for folks who cannot...
...who cannot be present in the exact place...
...or do not have to have full body capabilities at the moment.
But you know, I think despite all the technical...
...technical walls that we've had, you know...
...bringing this nostalgic trip down memory lane to life...
...everything... everything has been so interesting and fun the whole time and...
...and I'm just so happy to be able to spend that with you guys here...
...to show you guys this amazing creation.
Look at that deadbeat! Look at me and the dead- deadbeat. Don't be shy, come back.
There's a deadbeat.
There's the deadbeat!
That's a deadbeat.
That's a deadbeat for you.
Mori Callia-peak. I like that.
Can we start using th- You can if you want.
I- I won't say it, but... if you want to.
Makes me happy, it makes me happy that you enjoy...
What if I jump? I'm jumping.
Seeing if that makes a difference in anything.
Like if the camera can really handle the... the full capacity of my jumps.
Anyway, we're kind of... we don't have all the time in the world, but you know we...
...if we want to look at secrets...
If we want to look at the secrets, we probably gotta get moving a little bit.
But there's one... there's one special secret that I want to look at...
...before we move on to the Faded Atlantis that I'm really excited about checking out.
Do you guys want to go?
If you don't know where it is, you may have noticed...
...if you look yonder, if you look way over there...
...you can see that there's a black square in the... in the cliffside.
Way over there in the cliffside of the Plaza.
So I was thinking maybe we could go there.
There's a little secret over here.
Perhaps it leads to another memory?
I don't know, I'm kind of nervous. I feel like...
...what if this... well what if... what if we're not able to get back?
The ominous square in the wall...
Typically if you see a—hidden walls, visions
of hidden walls. Maybe I should roll through.
Like Dark Souls.
Waka-kon-waka water.
Anyway, anyway.
Shall we go inside?
Whoa!
Hey!
I know this place.
Do you guys know this place?
Do you guys remember?
Oh man, it's been a really long time, huh?
I know it, some of you were around
for for this, but...
Remember when we had one of our... aw.
And see the banner? Happy
HoloMyth 2 year anniversary!
Blast from the past, right? All the memories.
Remember when we all sang and danced
in an interesting way on this stage?
And I remember we had so many
things to announce back then.
And we did it in 360 too!
So like people could—could use their phone
and like sit in the center
and like rotate it around.
And they could look at their oshi the whole time.
I wonder how many Dead Beats
were looking mostly at Mori?
You don't have to though, because there are so many
wonderful people to enjoy and support, but...
...but if you did look at me lots, I'd be really happy.
I want to do something like
that again sometime, actually.
Kind of walking around this old place
and thinking that to myself, you know, like...
...it'd be really cool to do something like that again.
And then we can't forget the backstage, right?
You guys were allowed backstage...
...which is very special,
don't you think? Hold on.
Whoa!
Remember we had you guys sit—
we had you guys sit right there on this stool.
In this exact spot. Haha.
Back in the day.
It's all kind of dark and dimly lit now.
Since it was so—so long ago.
Somehow it still feels like home, you know?
I'd really love—I'd love for you guys
to be able to visit this spot, too.
But maybe you'll be able to.
Well, we'll talk about that a little bit later, but...
...I guess we better get out of here.
We got an Atlantis to look at.
So, let's get—let's get moving, I guess.
As much as I would love to sit here
and just reminisce about everything
that's happened, right?
I think maybe we should go ahead and get moving.
Heh.
Before I get too sentimental.
Let's go!
I'm happy you're with us, Calli.
I'm happy I'm here.
Thank you for making it fun to be here.
Well, well it's a happy occasion, right?
We should be—we should be
happy and excited for the future.
So let's—let's go! We're going, we're going.
But a moment of quiet reflection
is fun too, don't you think?
I think so. Oh, the way to Atlantis is kind of far,
so I hope you guys can keep up with me.
Get running, Dead Beats! We're running, we're running.
Woo! Woo!
All this training I've been doing
and I still feel like I'm not
in enough shape to be doing this.
But we're going, we're going.
Atlantis time! Atlantis time!
Let's go, let's go, let's go! Ikuzo!
Oh, here we are. Tada!
Okay.
This is another one of those... ooh.
Wait, check this out. Whoa!
That's Atlantis! Atlantis finally! At last,
we get to see it.
I feel like this is based off of
a room of a good friend of mine.
Mmm.
Do you guys remember Gura's Atlantis room?
It was based off of her.
Kind of makes me think about that.
Eh but what the heck is Council—is that Council Rys?
It might be Council Rys. I'm not totally sure, but...
...before we jump in there...
...I'm getting the feeling
that I've entered this place before.
Well, shall we go ahead and take a look at another
musical couple—couple of musical memories before
we get too deep into exploring, shall we?
All right, Dead Beats. Play—run the memor—
I'm having a brain blast! If
you could gaze into the past—
Next, here it goes.
Let's do it then.
Wait... is this supposed to be Atlantis?
Man, so many memories.
I remember Atlantis. I remember all the places...
...that we had in the original, the original VRC Myth map.
This brings back a lot of memories.
There's something kind of different though, right?
There's something kind of different about this place.
Like, um... who, who are those people over there?
I think I know these people.
Familiar faces all around me...
...familiar faces.
I want to sing a song with someone here though.
Who would I sing with here, I wonder?
Wait, I am up here!
Wait a minute, what? Is that... is that Biboo?
I'm up here!
Wait, I see a rock. There's a rock way up there.
I'm coming down! I'm coming down!
Yeah, come on! Yeah, no problem.
There's a lot of stairs. There's a lot of...
Oh, okay. I guess she doesn't care about the stairs.
Ah! Oh God, ah!
Dang, you freaking came in like a wrecking ball there.
Hi Biboo.
Hi! Hi!
You're so small.
Nice outfit!
Thank you! My brand new, my brand new digs.
What do you think? My new gear.
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoa there! Don't get too close there, skipper.
Hold on a second.
No, no, no, no.
You're like not the first person to do this today, I think.
You look so good! Look at you! You look so nice!
Thank you! I appreciate...
You look... we look like we're in the same band or something like that.
What the heck? Look at her, she's voguing.
Oh my god, I can vogue too.
Eh-heh! Eh-heh! Eh-heh! Eh-heh!
No, I'm not as good as she is.
But you know what? I think we should sing a song together.
Do you want to sing a song?
Yeah! Let's sing a song together!
We should sing... we should sing something really intense.
We should sing like, like a hard rock song if you want.
Like camping?
Uh... no. No camping. No camping.
You said it because 'in tents'... like camping?
Biboo... Biboo... Stop.
You're reminding me of Ina right now with the puns.
Oh my god. I should smack you, but I won't. I won't.
I'll be serious!
Yeah, just a little. It doesn't have to be too serious.
Just serious enough, right?
Alright! Let's run it then! Play music!
Done made us say this!
Overkill
Composed & Arranged by Yuki Tsujimura / MEG(MEGMETAL)
Lyrics by Mori Calliope / Yuki Tsujimura
どの子が数寄？
Which one do you fancy?
この子に決めて
Decide on this one
各個、調整
Individual adjustment
覚悟、微調整
Resolve, fine-tuning
I can turn the point kind of place any bets
Decide who is fragile and discard the rest
Gambler by nature, chips start to stack
Raising lovely animals until they crack
祭脳、災能
Festival brain, disaster ability
繁殖寄生体
Breeding parasite
You're indirect and done made us say this
Workout, breakdown, toss 'em when you've had enough
Yo choice, each choice I can tell you're not impressed
右向け右、左向け左
Turn right, turn left
Leave the defective, unworthy of investment
I can turn the point kind of hot mess worthless dog
寄って集まって射る者よ
Those who swarm and shoot
Gambler by nature, chips start to stack
Raising lovely animals until they crack
Beautiful dreams evade notice heart
Close your eyes and dial sys back
祭脳、災能
Festival brain, disaster ability
外れろゴミ共
Get lost, you trash
Done made us have no regret to be this
More way, starving、時間の無駄、無駄、無駄
More way, starving, a waste of time, time, time
Yo choice, each choice I can tell you're not impressed
あっちもこっちもこじらせたサイコ
Psychos everywhere, out of hand
お道化になりそう、どうにでもなりそう
I might become a clown, anything could happen
舞台外ならのみののみ、トラベルパラダイス オールフォーミー
Outside the stage, only just, travel paradise all for me
I also night gallery、横からでも登って見下してやろわ
I also night gallery, climbing from the side, I'll look down on you
目を開けて　先取りのハレ
Open your eyes, anticipating the celebration
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
ハッとして　駆け出す花開くわ
Taken aback, I start running, flowers bloom
Wanted, Wasted
All Produced by Takuya Yamanaka (THE ORAL CIGARETTES)
Lyrics by Takuya Yamanaka (THE ORAL CIGARETTES) / Yuki Tsujimura / Mori Calliope
I guess I’ll take the lead, no turning back
Point to take a look at deep inside
The cheat to exploit in your eyes,
my guards, my size, my dice, my drama
Cross it out!
Wanted, wasted, sorry to face it
we can’t stop falling down
Tell me I'm worthless, show you I'm nervous
One man's treasure's another man's surface
愛されたいのに愛せない　夢を見てるのは何故？
I want to be loved but I can't love, why am I dreaming?
変えたい現実　無惨なクソ　荒んで　ハミになる
The reality I want to change is miserable crap,
growing desolate, I'm becoming a misfit
やってやって　やってそのまま気づいちゃって
既得権益　奪い合うエンディング
Do it, do it, just like that realize it
The ending where vested interests are fought over
縁から逃げ出さないアンドロ
Android that won't run away from connections
援助はそれまでだ貸し借りに仕上げて頂戴
Support ends there, please finish it
with lending and borrowing
明快アンダーテイカー　仰天影喰らえ
Clear undertaker, eat the amazing shadow
Ah, ah, ah, ah, 響けメーデー　メーデー
Ah, ah, ah, ah, resound Mayday, Mayday
タンタンタンタン　鳴らす
聞こえないふりして逃げられると思ってんの？ クソ
Tap, tap, tap, tap, making a sound.
Do you think you can escape by pretending not to hear? Sh*t.
愛されたいのに愛せない　夢を見てるのは何故？
I want to be loved but I can't love, why am I dreaming?
変えたい現実　無惨なクソ　荒んで　ハミになる
The reality I want to change is miserable crap,
growing desolate, I'm becoming a misfit
Oh my god, oh my god... Oh my god, oh my god...
気づいちゃった
I've realized
魂！
Soul!
愛されたいのに愛せない　夢を見てるのは何故？
I want to be loved but I can't love, why am I dreaming?
変えたい現実　無惨なクソ　荒んで　ハミになる
The reality I want to change is miserable crap,
growing desolate, I'm becoming a misfit
足りない　足りない　足りない　足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough
足りない　足りない　足りない　足りない！
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough!
Yeah, yeah, dead beats, I know you saw that...
You saw Staff-san flying around with the mute button.
Can you guess which, which memory song we, we sung first?
But in all seriousness, I want to give a huge shout-out to all the staff
that worked really, really hard on all of this.
Because honestly, this entire production—hold on, I'm working, I got this.
Honestly, this entire production, the whole team, like in studio,
has been like five people.
And then everybody working on it behind the scenes is like three or so.
Compare that to like the 30 plus people
that work on the really high quality productions...
...that they do for birthdays and stuff like that,
you know, your one, the one that you get to do every year.
I was gonna say one free one,
but you only really get to do one, right?
Which is why I'm so glad that we did this together,
and I'm so grateful that it turned out the way that it did.
But, but hold on a sec, look. I want you to look...
Oh god, my jacket! Jacket!
Look at everyone, it's CouncilRyS!
This is a bit of a smaller, a smaller little performance area
compared to the others, but look at that Gura trident!
Although I will say, lady in the back,
is that supposed to be Gura? 'Cause there are some differences.
I'm sure that you all can...
Not now, not now baby.
Not now. But you never know.
I don't really know if that's something that she cared very much about, but...
Catching strays, catching strays.
Nah, but... I look really angry. Hold on, why do I... There we go.
Oh man. I hope that... I hope that my friends who...
...are no longer active with us anymore are living their best lives out there...
...and doing amazing cool stuff wherever they are.
You know?
That's what I want more than anything.
That would make me happy.
A lot of those faces around us here too. I really appreciate them.
I'm glad I got to get to know them.
And I'll keep watching 'em in my own way. In my heart.
Stop getting sentimental! It's getting later into the stream so it's happening.
We gotta move along though. We gotta move along because there's something that I really...
...I really think I need to show you. There's something really cool.
Follow... follow me!
Off we go! We're moving, we're... we're moving on up! We're going, we're going out of here.
There's... Oh, but really quick. I wanted to mention something. And I think that this might be a good place for me to announce this.
There's... uh, something... there's a little secret something-something below this area.
It's related to Mori. It's related to Mori but...
...there's a little... a little secret for Dead Beats to check out underneath this stage.
How... how would you be able to check it out though if we didn't see it today?
Well, that's because the plan is to release this world in the next few days...
...to you guys! So that you can hang out here with your friends...
...and explore around and just chill together.
And it'll be so fun! I hope that you guys will have a good time with it...
...and explore and find little secrets... um, like what we found or what we're finding today.
So make sure that you get a chance to and we'll make sure that you guys know where to access it and find it.
So that'll be really fun!
Um, let's go, let's go. Still things I want to show you.
Oh man, how far... Oh! You know what?
This is the place over here that... that I was most interested in running towards.
Come on, come on, come on! Let's go, let's go!
We're moving, we're shmoving! Here we go!
Guys! Did any of you guys see this in the distance? The...
...the desert.
The desert!
The nerd run? Hey, don't say... that's not true! It's a very cool run.
It's a very cool run I'm doing right now. No, no, no.
My walking on the water, that's totally...
No, Chat, don't worry. It's just...
Geez... No, I'm not... I'm not J-man. No, Chat, wrong, wrong, wrong.
Chigau yo. 'Ame Desert?' question mark, question mark, question mark. Yes.
Yeah.
It looks kind of gray right now.
But here, let's take a look.
That's an Ame Desert.
That's the Ame Desert over there. And that big clock...
Do you guys think... you think there maybe something behind the clock?
Cause I want to go find out.
I want to see how far I can... I can dive into this place. But I get the feeling we might find something nice.
Really quick. Hold on a sec.
Oh, I'm excited, I'm excited! What are we going to find?
A bus stop? Question mark. There is a bus stop in the middle of the desert. We built one together in Minecraft... I knew it!
It's a dimensional door!
Guys, look!
I found a dimensional door! Though I kind of had a feeling it would be here...
...and I may have gotten told by the powers that be that there was something back here.
But shall we go take a look together?
Let me take off this beanie, I'm sick of looking like a robber. It's very cute though.
I mean, I... the idea was mine to have the beanie on... Let's go into space together.
What? No, no, no. Whoa! We're in space!
Is it okay for me to be walking on this floor? I'm not gonna die, right?
Hey!
Is this the original bus stop?
This is the original desert bus stop! It feels like... and everything is in the same...
...kind of lower poly style.
Another bus stop? Bus stop.
And then in here...
...something familiar?
Whoa! HoloMyth... one year.
Smol EN.
In a timeline.
This I didn't...
This is the original place.
We've got the Ina room.
I feel like I shouldn't be allowed to be here, but I want to sit down for like a cup of tea.
The original!
Look at that little Takodachi being so good.
And all Ina's paintings for all of us.
Memories.
Crying Yagoo statue, look at him, look at him cry.
We'll go in there in a second.
Then there's my old room! You guys remember my old room?
And the moon stage! Wow, from the Hell Temple, it's like the same...
...the same style and everything. Remember when I did a small concert here?
The Mori Cave.
Wow, it was so fun chilling out here with you guys.
I know it's kind of older now and a little worn down, but...
...I miss this old chill spot.
I wonder if we've got all of them here, oh my goodness.
We have time to check out all of them?
What's time looking like? We're gonna have to move on pretty soon,
but I don't want to! I want to keep looking.
Look, KFP Square!
Oh man, do you guys remember all the fun like Easter themed stuffs...
...or like spring themed stuff that used to happen? Was there an egg hunt?
I'm pretty sure there was a VRChat egg hunt once that we did in this kind of place.
And all the little games that we did as well.
Kiara did so much fun VRChat stuff too.
If I remember correct, memory serves, and I think it does.
Oh, memory serves correctly.
I feel kind of out of place here being in full color, but...
I feel old, dads, says chat.
Oh, it's not that long ago, it's only half a decade. Let's go...
...to...
What we got here?
Oh, I guess that, yeah, there was the Ame desert and then Gumba's room.
Which we already, we already checked out Atlantis, but look...
...you can kind of see everything's kind of older and worn out here.
And the pillars too are kind of broken, but I remember it.
I remember what this place used to look like.
And it was so fun getting to explore all the different rooms too.
Oh, I can hear Right On Time right now.
It's really nostalgic.
Well, I hope that you guys get a chance to enjoy this world.
Cuz there was so much love put into it by Seafoam, thank you so much.
And thank you so much to Malin as well for working so hard on this. I love it!
I want to do my own exploring later. And then we can't forget...
You guys, here we are, the original Open Bar!
It's the bar!
Our old bar where we hung out and just chatted the days away.
All the silly stupid jokes.
In our small forms.
Everything's kind of decrepit now, but...
...the beginning, right? All the memories.
Movie nights.
We had a lot of fun watchalongs, didn't we?
The elevator, auditorium...
Remember... oh my gosh, wait, hold on.
Happy HoloMyth First Anniversary!
Yeah, four years ago.
Hi Mom!
Hey Deadbeats! Look at how much I've grown.
We've all grown, haven't we?
Everybody was crying cuz we couldn't meet each other.
And then we did!
Man, half a decade, huh?
We should... we should get out of here before I get too emo.
Let's...
funny walk, funny run, ah ha ha!
So silly. We got barely any time left, but...
...I'm sure it'll be okay.
One last thing I wanted to show you is this place.
It's the ship!
Sunfish ship.
You guys remember this place too? Remember our small adventures together?
Oh man, and we looked out here and we saw Sana was so big.
Yeah, and then, and then of course our captain was driving here.
Cool adventures.
The sunfish.
Maybe I should take this baby on a joyride.
I'm sure Ame wouldn't mind.
I'm thinking about it though,
especially after coming back here.
Well, I think we should quick teleport
back to the desert, guys,
since we don't have much time left.
I have teleport abilities though.
All I have to do is summon my persona.
Okay, here we go.
But I hope you guys get a chance to check
this place out in more detail, you know?
That would make me really happy.
Ah, we're back!
Because I feel like after all that we've
looked at so far
and all the memories that we've experienced,
there's a special song that I want to sing here.
But I have the feeling I already sang it.
Well then, shall we remember?
Let's go!
Last Days
Lyrics: Mori Calliope Track: benlussboy
Melody Composition: cocobunny
Castle made of thorns
Moon that rose and crimson
Groped for something more, all I got is distance
Driving ruthless, feels like the end of a light
Runnin' through the night, all of us our curses
Stuck here unalive, floatin' on the surface
Still in shallow, probably left to rot, I'm sinkin'
So close to giving up, giving out, giving in
Could I still live again, live again, live again?
But what's the point in fighting
when nothing lasts at all?
On your last day, standing here alone with you
I found my vision was untrue
Now I can wake up again
Don't tell me it's over
It must be, is it gonna be just me left behind?
Me and my mind
Forever wasting time
Back then there was nothing left to lose
Back then every night was wine and blues
That's when every pen I tried to use
Ended up leaking the weakness and bled through
All in past tense, mistaken, faking like I never
Was taken, waking up every night pacing
Walk down deep in my soul is what I really
want to shout now
Out of control but I still hold it inside
And now there's no way to hide,
you want to know if I'm fine
Well, at least nobody's dying
So close to giving up, giving out, giving in
Could I still live again, live again, live again?
But what's the point in fighting
when nothing lasts at all?
On your last day, standing here alone with you
I found my vision was untrue
Now I can wake up again
Don't tell me it's over
It must be, is it gonna be just me left behind?
Me and my mind
Forever wasting time
Every now and then reality creeps in
Every now and then I glimpse of the deep end
You live once still, so when I'm not around
Remember me, remember what we found
On our last day
Standing here alone 'cause nothing lasts forever
Wake up, wake up yeah,
no I can't wake up, wake up yeah
No, it's not over, it can't be
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Is this goodbye?
On my last day
Doesn't matter where or when I swear I'll find us
Some things...
'Cause I know some things just can't come true
But I want to see you again sometime
That song in my heart keeps me alive
Hey there Dead Beats.
Hey there. It's me.
It's okay to be sad.
It's okay to miss the people
who changed our lives if they aren't here anymore.
I think... it's okay.
But as long as we have memories, right?
Um... then I think maybe...
just maybe, it'll be okay
even if we never truly move on.
Well, I'm happy that we have memories, right?
And to never, never forget all the stuff
that we did together.
Cuz we did some really amazing stuff,
don't you guys think?
I think we did.
And I don't want to forget any of that,
cuz like I said, I don't really have any plans
to get going anytime soon.
But I guess the way that I feel about it is...
I'd like to keep remembering all those people
and things that we did fondly,
regardless of anything.
Even through the years,
and though they may pass by,
and even when the wounds aren't fresh anymore...
I still... I still want to remember.
I know it's hard to... it's hard to move forward
sometimes when the things that we love
and care about are still behind us, right?
And stuck in the past.
But I'm gonna be here to make you smile
no matter what right now,
'cause there's still stuff I want to do, you know?
And yeah, that's a good point,
that good memories,
they should make you sad because...
because that means they were truly good.
We did a lot of really good stuff,
you guys think?
Well, I'm glad that I sang that here with Ina.
I'm really glad.
But there's still some people
that I haven't sung with,
so let's head to the final area, shall we?
What if I just, bam, teleported myself there
and used my crazy powers of...
Oh, my waist is broken.
That's okay. No, it's fine. All good, all good.
I probably just need to T-pose real quick.
Hang on, watch this. Watch my sick T-pose.
Hang on. I'm already good at this.
I've become a pro at VRChat
in just this short time.
There we go. Fixed. All right.
Time to summon my persona
and head to the final area!
Oh! Oh, we're here. We're here.
Oh, where'd my camera go? I lost it!
Is it hiding somewhere? Is it behind me?
Oh, I found it. There you are.
Found you!
Um, this is one of my favorite areas, I think.
You guys! You guys, look!
What is this? Green fields?
Oh! There's one of those camera thingies.
Hang on, okay. Uh, check this out.
Whoa! It's too beautiful!
Can you guys imagine hanging out
with your friends here?
Wouldn't that be so awesome?
I'm running up that hill.
I'm running up the hill.
Oh my gosh! Hey! Wait a minute! What's this?
Was Ina painting something here?
I didn't know about that. Heh.
I mean, it is a really nice scenery
to paint, I suppose.
So I guess it makes sense. I'd want to paint here. Hehe.
So expansive. Oh, sorry. Hang on...
That's okay, it doesn't matter.
So surreal and tranquil.
I guess this is a good place to tell
you guys the news
about a special thing that gets released
for anniversary, especially.
Do you guys know what it is?
Are we going to run the clip?
I think we're going to run the clip.
All right, guys, we have merchandise!
So I created a little commercial
before we get to singing here.
Run it, Sapsan!
Heh! Minna-san! It's been five long years
together, but we've done it!
We made it to year five together!
And while the future's looking pretty
crazy and eventful,
let's take a little time to celebrate
the story thus far, shall we?
And what better way to do that than
with every Holo's bread and butter,
the bane of every Dead Beat's wallet's existence,
that's right, ev-erbode, it's time for
premium goods, goods, goods, goods!
Yeah, premium goods time. Now you guys,
you guys know what time it is. You get
ready for it every year, right?
And you guys know how I like to release merch
that's more on the fashionable side than practical,
but I think there are a few things that
you guys are going to love here.
And remember, if you grab it quick and manage
to cop the premium limited set,
you'll get a hand-signed postcard from me!
Horray! Happy!
But like always, supplies are extremely...
...extremely limited, so don't miss out, okay?
Okay!
First, we got a poster. Duh.
I mean, you guys expect posters by now, I think.
You guys are used to posters for me and as every
good Dead Beat knows,
Mori Calliope is a poster fan and Mori Calliope
fans are fans of posters.
I see your rooms. I know.
Not like in a creepy way or anything.
But this one's a bit smaller than the usual huge
posters that I always do for these merch drops,
but...
...it's to help with the shipping costs this year.
Uh, I don't know, we'll see. Crossing my fingers,
but no guarantees.
Throw it into your cart, see what happens, I guess.
I went for an Underworld live show concert poster
as a concept here...
...and my very own Yuki-same Mama created
something fun and energetic for the occasion.
So, let's reminisce on the amazing shows that
we've gotten to experience together...
...with this big-size poster! Yeah, yeah.
Next up, oh man, this one is big!
One of my favorite apparel artists, Crisalys,
has graced this humble black t-shirt
with a high-quality and subtle design of your Mori,
dressed in grimoire attire, playing her bass,
probably a little badly, in an antique shop.
It's the type of shirt where you probably get,
you know, compliments from fellow quirky folks,
but the average bystander, like, wouldn't look
twice at you kind of deal.
I don't know, again, I can't guarantee
exactly what's going to happen.
Anyway, you might find Dead Beats out
in the wild too, so that's fun.
It's just the kind of shirt that subtly expresses
your love for Mori Calliope
without being too, you know, in your face, right?
And the design is so, so, so good!
I own like five shirts by Crisalys,
now I'm about to own six.
Anyway, don't miss out.
Next up, it's a Grimoire plushie!
Take her everywhere with you.
That's what seems to be all the rage
these days, right?
And if you give her a squeak, she says something.
Uh, I don't know what yet, but maybe we'll
all be a little surprised.
She's got such a cute and huggable design,
I'm sure she'll make fast friends with
your other plushies.
Especially... ugh, that weird cat.
You know, maybe you can dress her up and put her
in a plastic purse for a day out.
Just... just have fun. I don't know. Be whimsical,
whatever you want to do.
Finally, it's a concert and live show staple:
a casual wristband!
Show your support for your Mori in your everyday
life or at a local show,
even if, you know, I'm not the one playing.
Something easy to slip on and fun to rock out with.
I want to see all of you guys wearing them
at my future shows, okay?
And there's a voice pack too!
Mori Takes a Break?
Heh, what kind of title is that?
It sounds like some fan fiction to me,
but give it a listen, I guess.
Japanese and English voice available.
日本語もあります。
Japanese is also available.
Grab the full set and you will get a foil
duplicated stamp on a special postcard.
Be really fast and get your hands on that
limited edition set,
and you might just get your hands on a
hand-written autograph from Mori Calliope.
Actually, it's not that you might, you will.
You will get a hand-written autograph from
Mori Calliope...
...if you're fast enough.
We always do gold though, so how about I sign it
with an extra special pink pen?
I don't know, I'll have to see if they let me.
Look forward to it!
And again, these are limited to a certain amount.
So, if you want to grab a real autograph from
your Mori, do not miss out on this chance.
The sales period will run for about a month, so
get your premium goods ASAP, okay?
It's like a full-on concert hall over here
between poster, t-shirt,
squeezable mini Mori, and wristband.
Get ready for lots more shows together,
Dead Beats!
And thanks for the unforgettable five years!
Whoa!
I wonder how much further can we go together?
I want to see!
Hello!
Thank you so much everybody.
I hope that you guys enjoy the goods. Please look
forward to receiving them.
They're very cool. I'm super excited with how
they turned out.
So make sure that you don't miss it.
I think the shop will open in about six minutes.
You'll be able to pre-order your merch and get
the limited if you're quick.
You gotta be quick because they do have
a limited number.
But yeah, please enjoy and thank you always for
supporting me so much.
There will be a members-only encore after this
featuring a few more songs...
...and just getting to chat with my members,
which I'm excited about.
Um, so please look forward to that.
And there's a new song coming out!
I should look a little happier about that.
There's a new song coming out!
And I haven't really given any hints about
what kind of song it is.
People are like, "Oh, it's gonna be so emotional,
this looks like an emotional song."
But knowing what the song is makes me
laugh really hard,
because it's actually a lot simpler than you think.
But something about my early music is that,
man, I was so honest, you know?
And so I wanted to write a song that not just
me, myself, I as a person could relate to,
but anyone... anyone who has an oshi could
but anyone... anyone who has a favorite could
relate to.
And so I hope that you will enjoy it because it
feels like an older Mori song...
...while also being a newer Mori song.
It's hard to explain, but I guess you'll just have
to watch it and see.
MV is really cute, so we'll watch that premiere
together too,
so don't go anywhere after the credits.
Uh, please look forward to it.
New song, new song. Stream it lots!
Let's watch it live.
And um, share it around. I don't know, if you want, if you like it.
Um, but I still have one last song memory to replay in my mind here in this beautiful area.
So shall we run it? The last song of today.
Thank you so much, Dead Beats.
Catch you on the flip side. There might be an after-credits scene.
Let's go!
Scuffed Up Age
Lyrics by Mori Calliope / Camellia
Music by Camellia
Ha-ah-ah... La-la-la...
Lost in thoughts, a frosted frame of mind,
Honest to God, it's just not our time.
Promises flawed by cosmic design,
コレクティブで手を取り合いたい
I want to hold hands in the collective,
でもな、無駄なあがきさせない
But hey, I won't let it be a futile struggle.
Coming of age, the stage doesn't light up,
Just right away they told us it might have.
夢はもう、諦めます
I'm already giving up on my dreams.
The cynical mind says why'd you try?
Why not give up and play the bad guy?
わかってるさ
I know.
運命が波立てながら
While fate is making waves,
あなたの元へするのなら
If I'm heading towards you,
崩れ落ちそうな体
This body that feels like it's collapsing,
抱きしめるから
I will hold you close.
We choose to know
The struggles of this scuffed up age,
We're living in go-sani
たくさんの
Many...
経験を糧と
...experiences as nourishment,
この夜明け
At this dawn,
口ずさむわ
I'll hum a tune.
Like not your days,
それでも
Even so,
あなたを救っていたいから
Because I want to keep saving you.
Can't find a reason to stay,
Some busted world led us astray,
Once just was left to decay,
We choose to go on anyway.
Lost in thoughts of an always changing face,
Allies and friends hiding more than one space,
Not really surprising, why are you compromising?
The sun is rising, a new horizon,
With friendships acting like lies and the knives in your back,
so what are you prioritizing?
You aren't sick of crying?
See, I don't buy it,
But here we are hanging on, fighting strong as spiders.
儚いじゃないわ しきれない
It's not fleeting, I can't finish it,
もう目ぇ閉じてしまいたい
I want to just close my eyes already,
暗いの世界
In this dark world.
The cynical mind says why'd you try?
Why not give up and play the bad guy?
わかってるさ
I know.
埃まみれの街で
In this dust-covered town,
あなたの溜息の影
The shadow of your sigh,
私の傘をないで
Don't take away my umbrella,
抱きしめたいから
Because I want to hold you close.
We choose to know
The struggles of this scuffed up age,
We're giving in go-sani
汚れだって
Even if it's dirty,
It really hurts to grow,
Believing in a world of fate is overrated,
までも
Even...
あなたを美しく謳うから
...so, I will sing of you beautifully.
Must be something surreal,
And in this dream we can heal,
This busted world built up real,
Someone remember the way it feels,
Like night the city feels dead but like...
The lights and sights and sounds are treasures.
こんな世界に
In a world like this,
抗って歩く
I'll keep walking and resisting,
力なんてさ
The strength for that...
私にはないけど
...is something I don't have, but...
Face up, this world can kill the inspired,
Why don't we turn this scuffed up page?
We're writing in
こんな世界じゃ
In a world like this,
Believe in the logic we know,
Kono yoake is rarely fair,
Decide your fate, it's your life,
あなたを美しく謳うから
Because I will sing of you beautifully.
Tomorrow's a brand new day,
Like all those optimists say,
But the truth is rather ruthless, it might be rain,
The question is will you bear the pain?
What's your reason to stay?
This shining world led us astray,
Won't leave it all to decay,
I choose to love it anyway.
Ahhh... Ohhh...
We chose to know...
...the structure of the scuffed...
...bit we live in...
...so don't give in...
What are you still doing here?
The show's over.
Go watch the music video!
Thank you Yoolies and Naneless for the 3D!
Bye!
Thank you all for 5 incredibly strong, wonderful, whimsical
at times painful but so, so special years as Your Mori.
There are so many more views I want to see,
but for now just know how thankful I am
that I get to be your pink woman. Always.
We laughed! We cried! We cringed.
—And we'll do it again, dammit!!
Mori Calliope - Happy 5 years.
Here's to more.