(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
SPECIAL COLLAB
We're ready to greet the world
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand new start
Let's go live, bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully meeting heart to heart
Connect the World
Waking from a dream, stepped into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue
How will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
Like in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars
Radiant and warm, cosmic energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life
Surely we've gotta take that chance
We're running non-stop straight to the top, that's right!
We're ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase creating a new place where we can shine
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand new stage
Let's go live, bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we'll turn the page
Breaking through the doubt we know
Figure out a way to clear each towering trial
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile
We'll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing no matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars, let's go!
I want to chase a wish unwaveringly
Playing out this grand story
Share the future stars we can see
Making them reality
Take my hand and reach for the sky
All we need are glittering dreams
A heart and soul, all fulfilled
In the world we build
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways
Discovering highways to everywhere
Step by step
Gathering stories that we can share
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation
The shining sensation, a dream unfurled
Let's make friends
Picking a moment of history
Joyfully
Follow me
We'll connect the world
You'll hear our song
Ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues
We'll carry on, starting now
Setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world
Yay!
Guys!
You good? You good?
Yeah, very great. Okay.
We're all in 3D together!
Yay!
All right, let's introduce each of these beautiful ladies.
Hi-RyS! It's IRyS from Hololive English.
I'm your friendly neighborhood Nephilim representing hope.
Yay!
Konfauna! It is Ceres Fauna,
your gaming Kirin and idol in 3D for you today.
Konfauna!
Konfauna! Yay!
Kronichiwa!
It's Ouro Kronii from Hololive English,
and we are here to have some awesome time.
Swag.
Swag!
Oh, hi.
I'm Nanashi Mumei, and I'm mooming in 3D. Hello!
Mooming! Hello! Yay!
What's up? It's Hakos Baelz reppin' Chaos
from Holo EN Council.
A-yo, your rat idol, I'm here. Yeah!
Nice! She's shaking those ears!
Yay! We're finally in 3D together!
We just finished singing our first song together.
It was "Connect the World,"
Hololive English's idol song,
and I'm so happy I was able to sing
with all of you guys today in 3D.
That was just our first song.
We still have a lot in store for you.
Stuff you would never expect.
Oh? Could it be? 何?
Oh? Could it be? What?
How are you liking it so far?
It's pretty good. It's great. Yeah.
You guys like it? I love it personally.
Yeah, we love it. It's great. Love!
Even if you dislike,
be sure to smash that like button!
Smash! Smash it! Smash it!
But don't just smash that like button.
Be sure to talk about what you think
using the hashtag #CouncilRyS3D
because we want to hear your thoughts, man.
Yeah! Use the hashtag! Use the hashtag! Use it!
The hashtag might be #CouncilRyS3D...
...but that might not matter too much anymore.
What? Oh?
Because IRyS here with these lovely, lovely...
...lovely Council ladies...
Oh, yes. My ladies. IRyS-lady.
Hurry up!
...the five of us will be forming a new official unit
called...
Hololive English -Promise-!
We promise you an amazing time!
Yay!
So in celebration of our newly formed official unit,
HoloPromise, today we're going to promise
to sing many songs, play many games,
and celebrate being together in 3D.
You guys ready?
Yay!
You guys look so ready. I'm hyped!
Well, we're gonna go get ready
and start off with the first game.
So everybody, exit stage right!
Now Loading...
Yee-haw! Welcome everyone to the Promise Games!
Promise Games
Now, well, you know, since IRyS has joined us
to create Promise,
we present to you with the Promise Games.
We're gonna figure out who's really on top.
Number one!
I promise you, I'll be first. Number one.
I promise you, she'll be first.
I'm gonna be the top.
I promise you, not bottom.
Someone will be first,
someone will be bottom.
We're gonna battle through different games today,
and whoever has the most points at the end
will be the champion of said Promise Games.
Everyone okay?
Yeah! Okay!
So, if we're okay, I would actually like to
explain the very first game that we're gonna play today.
Alrighty!
The first game will be...
everyone knows this game...
Red light, Green light!
Now, look behind you everyone.
Actually no, look in front of you.
Look, look, look what's in front of us right now.
Oh my god! Look at this beautiful obstacles course!
Yes! This isn't just your regular Red Light, Green Light.
Whoever can avoid the obstacles and touch the goal
will earn one point!
Okay, and if you're caught by the Oni,
you'll have to stay on the course and crawl for the rest of the round.
And you don't just crawl, you can...
you can babubu babu and... sabotage!
Sabotage! Oh!
Alrighty, so let's go through the details of the course.
First is the Balance Beam.
Pass this obstacle by crossing over without falling.
Yes, the usual.
Balance Beam Course
Oh gosh, flashbacks...
And then after that, there is the bar, the limbo bar.
You pass this obstacle by crossing under the bar limbo style.
Bar Course
Flexibility! Let's go!
I'm stiff like a stick.
And last! After the limbo, we have the tires.
Tire Course
You pass this obstacle by jumping across using the tires with one leg.
You hop, hop. Okay? Yeah, hop.
Okay, and we have a special guest today to play the part of the Oni.
Let's introduce her, here she is!
Hello!
A-chan!
You're so soft! Why are you so cushy?
I'm so squishy!
I lost my power because of overtime.
Overtime! Oh no! She can't be superhuman anymore.
Anyway, congratulations on your 3D! Yay!
And thank you for inviting me back.
But today, I'm a strict, scary Oni.
Oh no! We're in trouble. Yeah, looks very scary.
You look very soft. I want to use you as my couch.
I want to sit.
No, no sit! Sit on... I'm only flat. Don't push me!
Well, we have this very cute Oni here today. Yeah, cute.
Yes, so is everyone ready to play?
Okay! Let's get...
...Red Light, Green Light started!
We decided on the order beforehand with rock paper scissors, so...
I won!
Yes, we won, I won! She won!
Alright, we play! Are we ready?
Let's go! We play, we play.
Ready, set, go!
Green light!
Red light!
IRyS out!
Okay...
Green light!
Red light!
무궁화 꽃이 피었습니다
Red light, green light, 1, 2, 3.
I'm out!
(Screaming and baby noises)
Babu! Babies! Babu!
Babu! Babus! Mumei!
Oh, you were so, so weird!
Weak!
I'm not weak!
Red light.
Green light.
Wait, wait!
So many babies out there.
Babu, babu, babu!
Mama Mumei! Green light!
Red light.
Green light.
Babu, babu. Oh!
I'm going slow.
Oh, she's listening.
She's... okay, she's listening.
Red light!
I win! I win!
Alrighty, since we all didn't make it, we're doing one more.
Doing one more! One more!
Wanna switch order this time?
It's so easy for you.
Go same order? Same order?
Okay. Alright, right, right.
Okay, are you ready?
Ready! Let's go!
Green light.
Red light.
Mmm... nothing.
Green light.
Red light.
Mommy! Mommy! I'm out!
Green light.
Red light. Ah, I win!
Dammit! Okay, okay. Green light.
Goo goo ga ga.
Red light! Babu!
Oh, almost!
Goo goo!
Green light.
Red light! I'm watching you!
I'm watching you!
Baby! You're almost... almost...
Mama! Mommy!
Red light!
Green light! Green light!
Red light! Ah! You're out!
Bae! Dammit!
Dammit! Ah, nice game, nice game.
So amazing, you guys were doing great!
It was just a light tap. Okay, sure.
Alrighty, as the game is over, congrats Bae for winning! Yay!
Congratulations! We, a lot of us crawled a lot today.
Yeah.
But it's still too early to tell who's gonna win the Promise Games.
We still have a lot more.
Alrighty, thank you so much A-chan for being our seeker!
Thank you A-chan! No! Stay away!
She's touching me! Touching me! Touching me!
Alright, see you in the next game! Bye!
Now Loading...
Oh! What? We made it to the next game arena!
Yay!
And I'm here to introduce the next game,
which will be the Meteo Smash Challenge!
Smash! Smash! Smash!
But we're not the ones who will be smashing.
We're smashing?
No, no. We're in great peril today.
But it'll be easier to show you than to tell.
So everyone please, please spread out to your designated areas.
Spread out! Okay.
Spreading out. Spreading out.
And from the heavens appears... oh!
Another square meteorite!
That's a meteor!
Is everyone alive in there?
I'm alive! Hello!
Still 3D! Still 3D, not flattened.
I'm not pancake.
As long as you make it through one of these holes
in the meteorite, you will survive.
Anyone who avoids the meteorites all the way through earns a point!
However, the game becomes more difficult as time
goes on because there'll be fewer and fewer holes.
The game goes until there's only one person left.
We might have time to play a few rounds.
And no sharing! No sharing your holes!
So if anybody's...
If push comes to shove, we shove.
We shove.
Shove. Okay, gotcha.
Alright, everybody understand?
Yeah! I understand!
Alright! Let's start!
Ready!
Everybody ready?
I'm in! Right? I'm in! I'm in!
I think we all survived!
Oh my hair!
Okay, next one!
Hi! How many times is the meteor
going to land on us?
And then... it's a viciously square meteorite.
We're alive.
All natural.
Goodbye! Goodbye! I'm sorry!
Oh no, it was so fast!
I'm down! I'm sorry!
Oh god, blood on my hands!
You just had to stand there with IRyS.
Everyone safe? Everyone safe?
Nice, nice, nice!
Who do you think's gonna win?
I don't know.
I just want to survive.
True.
Left! Top! Right! Left! Top! Right!
Oopsy! Oopsy!
I'm dead. Pancake, pancake. I'm a pancake.
Want some maple syrup on you?
I see you, Kronii.
I see you too.
Wait, you're alive?
Wait, I'm alive?
I'm alive!
You're alive!
Not anymore, I guess.
She's dead. She did, she did.
Oh my goodness. We've got two people left.
I'm ready! Let's go!
Final! Probably final.
Oh wait... oh! Oh! Easy!
Fauna hasn't moved!
Fauna wins by doing absolutely nothing!
We'll see about that!
Competition's...
There's still enough space!
I'm gonna push! I'm gonna push!
She made it! She made it!
I made it!
Oh no! Oh no!
She didn't make it!
Wait, meteor was too fast!
I was pushed!
Looks like we have a winner!
Kronii! Kronii! Kronii!
I think we can do one more game.
One more game! Let's do that.
I need my revenge.
Can we... are we revived? Can we come in?
Yeah! We're revived!
We live! We live! We live!
Hey! Yay!
Wait, do we live?
I live!
We live!
Alright, one more game.
If Kronii gets a point, she's on the board for Kronii.
I'm sorry! I'm so quick!
I wasn't expecting that!
I'm sorry! Sorry!
Everybody's survived!
We shifted so fast!
Tried to push me! You tried to push me!
You tried to push me! You tried to push me!
No! No! No! Don't push me nature! Ha!
Oh, at least I'm not the first one.
Here comes next. Nice.
Wait, did we make it?
I made it! Nice, nice!
Oh nice, nice, nice.
That was a nice break.
I feel like pushing again.
Let's not.
Well, looks like someone's gonna get pushed!
Shove! Shove!
Wait, ah!
I'm out! I'm out!
I'm surprised I won that push.
It's because I tripped.
Nice!
I'm ready.
Oh!
Wait, is it done?
It's done. Nice.
I'm good, I'm good.
Oh, this is why Mumei—
Target selection.
I made a grave mistake.
Oh, hello.
You should've gone for me.
It's IRyS versus Baelz.
Oh, this is easy.
Bae is scary.
Oh, IRyS is super far.
I'm so lost.
Okay, okay.
Oh, easy. I don't have to move honestly.
Why did you move?
It's strategy. Strategy, strategy, strategy.
Oh!
Oh, okay. Okay, okay.
We good? We good? We good?
Alright, what next?
Oh!
Sabotage!
I'm ready. I'm ready for some sabotage.
Sabotage, I'm ready for some—
I am not hearing you.
I hear nothing.
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Did she make it? Did she make it?
Not yet!
Bro...
Kronii, you're strong.
Thank you, everyone, for pushing me from behind.
I'd like to let everyone come in again.
Come here, come here.
My goodness.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The voices, the voices were just so tempting.
This was a huge game for Kronii.
She's now in the lead with triple point!
Triple point!
Oh, wow.
Baelz is behind with one point.
And with that, I believe we're ready for our next game.
Next game! Next game!
Next game, let's go!
Okay, so the next game is Avoid The Void Challenge!
Avoid the void! Avoid the void!
Yeah, well, hopefully avoid the void.
I think you might already know if you take a look at the stage.
Oh!
This looks... is this really okay?
It's fine, don't worry about it.
Nah, nah, nah, just your imagination.
So, for each step, you have to pick either
the left or the right asteroid.
And if you pick the wrong one, you'll fall down—
Into the void.
Yeah, it's gonna be pretty hard.
Into the goal without falling, so you can try again until you make it.
Wait, we don't die?
Yeah, we don't die.
We don't die.
Darn it!
Darn it?
What do you mean, darn it?
Darn it! I wanted the risk, you know?
It's fine, IRyS, next time.
But this is the promise theme, next game.
Promise, we promise. Promise, promise.
So the person with most points goes first, which is me.
And the rest of you guys are gonna go after me.
I go next?
Highest points to lowest.
I go third because I'm confident.
You go third because you lost rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors! I'm confident!
And then after that, me, me!
I got second place!
And I won the rock-paper-scissors because I'm just lucky like that
and I go last, yeah.
Let's see how lucky you are when you fall.
And you have the most advantage because of that.
Luck's on me!
Well, I guess, I guess I gotta start.
Yeah! You're starting! Let's go!
Okay, let's jump right into it.
Okay! Jump right in! Later!
Jump, but think about it, think about it a little, you know?
No, don't think about it.
Go through your instinct.
I feel very good. I think...
I think it's the left one.
Yep!
(Screaming)
Never mind.
Never mind!
That was a shame.
Wait, does that mean... okay.
It's your turn.
Okay, my turn, my turn.
Bae is up.
Hey, you're back!
Hi!
Yeah, yeah, I...
Oh, why are you back?
Yeah, why...
What are you doing here?
Is that how it is? You don't want me to be back?
No!
We like you!
Of course we want you back!
All right.
All righty, ladies.
Okay.
First...
Uh-huh.
Okay.
And this...
(Exhale)
Oh, is she safe?
Am I safe?
Safe!
Oh, safe!
Nice!
Who's next after her?
She's doing pretty good, she's...
Then you should probably start.
Should start already.
All right, good.
Mind games, mind games.
They wouldn't do another diagonal...
Boom!
Mind games, mind games.
Mind games.
Safe!
Safe! Oh!
Okay, okay.
Wait, why are you following me?!
How does this work?
Wait, how does this work?
We don't go one at a time.
Boom!
Whoa!
Oh, wow!
Oh, she's lucky!
She's lucky!
So fast!
I don't mind.
All right. Give us some of this luck.
Safe! Oh!
Next!
Lead the way!
Okay!
Lead the way, Rat!
That's a lot of pressure!
Okay.
Guide us, guide us.
You're the leader.
Let's go.
You see the mathematical meme that's...
...going through my head right now?
(Laughter)
Boom!
(Screaming)
No...!
I know where to go.
I know what I must do.
Okay.
Fauna.
Think about it.
Oh, boy.
Sure, she...
Okay.
I really have to think hard about this next one.
Think harder.
You don't need to think about it.
You don't need to think about it, just jump in front!
That's in front.
Okay.
So slip...
Oh no, wait.
Now I know how it feels.
Now you...
Now you think about it.
One of them!
We're waiting!
Wait...
(Screaming)
Oh no!
Oh no, no, no, no!
Oh, am I next?
Okay, I have to...
I have to think about it.
Think about it.
I have to think if I should jump or not.
Got to think...
Before you jump.
No, just go!
Just go!
Think before you jump.
I'm waiting.
All right.
I go.
It-tse-tse-tse.
Okay.
All right!
Looking good.
It's good.
It-tse-tse-tse. Okay.
That way?
Oh.
Okay, what...
It-tse-tse-tse!
I hate this. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Me too.
I'm gonna...
I don't mean to brag, but...
I want to survive as long as possible until the last minute.
I'm gonna...
It-tse-tse-tse-tse-tse!
Ah!
She safe?
Huh?
Safe!
Oh!
Safe! Okay.
Okay, I'm safe too.
Nice!
Look, Mumei!
I'm right behind you.
Okay, now what could it be?
Could it be...
I would expect to go here.
Are you gonna jump there?
But perhaps that's what they think I'm thinking.
It might be a third time's a charm on this side.
It might be, it might be that.
But are you...
You want me to fall!
No, no, no!
I don't want you to fall until we get to the end.
Make sure you get to the end.
Okay, so what do you want me to do, IRyS?
Okay.
I think...
Third time's a charm.
Okay.
Safe!
Oh!
Yes!
I knew it!
Nice, nice!
I knew it too!
Okay.
Now this work.
This is work.
It would be really interesting if it was the fourth one, right?
Right?
Yeah.
But would it be?
Let's test that theory.
I don't know...
My Nephilim senses are tingling and saying it's...
I think I'd be...
I don't think it's jump across.
I think I...
I just have to go here. Okay.
I just...
Oh!
Safe!
Okay!
I'm not so sure about my chances anymore.
I'm like this close to falling in the back.
If I make a mistake...
Okay, I think it's about time...
...you start falling.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
That's mean!
I don't have a good feeling...
...about this baby!
Okay.
About time!
Which is it gonna be?
I don't know.
Am I gonna regret this?
Whoa!
Safe!
Okay!
All right.
Let's see.
You got a 50/50 chance of being right.
50/50 chance of being...
And if you fall, you fall.
I get an automatic win.
Mumei.
Pick the right one.
No.
The right one.
Don't pressure.
Pressure!
Pick the right one.
What, the right one?
Go with your instinct.
The right one or the wrong one?
I...
It-tse-tse-tse-tse-tse!
Whoa!
Oh!
Oh, she made it!
She made it!
All right.
Okay, well we know the way.
We know the way we're going.
Everyone get back!
Everybody!
Tse!
Mumei, I love you!
I make good choices!
Damn it!
You are so good.
Thank you, thank you.
The Mumei instinct is real. It's the killer instinct.
It's the killer instinct. It really is.
She got the sixth sense.
Seventh sense?
You just have to have no fear whatsoever.
No fear at all.
Wait, what? Wait, what?
How many senses do you have?
Um, probably like 30.
Oh wow, 30 senses. Yeah, that's a lot.
That's good sense.
Okay, well, since Mumei is the winner for this game,
Mumei gets one point.
So right now, the points in total...
IRyS has no points.
Ah! You didn't have to say that!
You didn't have to say that!
I still have two points.
Mumei has one point. Bae has one point.
Wait, am I really the only one
that doesn't have any points?
No, no. Fauna also...
Fauna doesn't have a point yet.
Wait, we're together.
Together in last place! It's okay.
It's okay because there's still one more game.
So this could change everything.
It could change everything.
Game changer!
We don't know. We don't know really.
No idea.
Well, yeah, well... onto the last game!
Are you guys ready?
All right everybody, it is time for our last game.
Last game! Last game!
Oh, so much fun!
But I still have zero points.
Well this is your chance! This is your chance!
What chance? There's a chance?
Your chance is with...
Tug of War!
Tug of War
Oh no! Tug of War! Oh dear!
Shut up, shut up!
I'm amazing at Tug of War.
You've never seen it before.
Let me explain the rules here. Okay.
When it's your turn, you have the chance
to challenge somebody. One member to play against.
When it's your turn, you have the right to challenge one member to play against.
Whoever loses the tug of war will fall into space.
Whoever loses the tug of war will fall into space. - If the person you challenge wins, they keep their points. - If you win, you get all the points from the person who loses.
Into the void. The void comes back.
The void makes its return.
And whoever wins will get all of the points
from the person who lost again.
What? What? All of them?
All of the points?
Wait, hold on a second.
What was the point of all the other games then?
That's point-less!
Aren't you glad?
Anyways, let's figure out who goes first.
How are we going to figure that out?
Maybe we should do
the weakest person has to choose.
IRyS! IRyS!
Oi, oi! You said that way too fast!
IRyS! Well she's right next to you.
She looks pretty weak.
Excuse me? I may stay at home...
...but I actually have hidden muscles
all over my arm.
Really? Show us. Please show us.
I'll show you guys. Okay, who's the winner
so far? Who's in the lead?
Kronii! Kronii!
Nah, nah. Come here. Come here.
Don't touch me! Come here! Let's go.
Hai! Hai! You stay there.
Noodle-RyS will show you guys.
You called yourself noodle?
No, I'm Udon-RyS! Because Udon is much
stronger than regular noodle. Oh, I see.
If you make fun of me and you lose, you're going to
be so mad. Ooh! The battle's begun.
You guys ready? Ready! Yeah!
Ready, set, go!
This is what you get! The underdog!
So IRyS wins!
Yay!
I got that muscle right here.
Okay, who wants to go next?
Who wants to challenge the winner?
I'm feeling pretty confident.
I think I can take you on, IRyS.
You have the guts, I applaud you for that...
But you-you-you-you-you-you-you-you!
You're like a lettuce!
You're like a salad!
You're like a piece of salad!
Oh, them's fighting words.
This is some trash talking.
Are you two ready?
I'm ready.
Any final words?
Prepare to die, IRyS.
Prepare for me to rip your salad out.
Ready, ready, ready...
Ready, set...
Go!
Bye, IRyS.
Well, nice.
So Fauna has put IRyS into her place
as the weakest.
Shut up!
One of the weakest, I guess.
Alright, I think...
I want to go up against Fauna.
You're going against Fauna?
Civilization versus Nature.
Oh, that's good.
Who will win?
Okay, let's go.
Battles of ready, time.
You can say it.
All right.
Are you ready?
My stance...
Battles stance.
Do you have any trash talk—I mean,
pre-game talk?
Fauna, your leaves look like they're wilting.
Hey! Let's go!
Why is everyone talking about my leaves today?
I'm gonna develop a complex.
Your face is nice.
Oh, your face is pretty nice, too.
Okay, that's getting too nice. All right, no.
Ready...
Set...
Go!
In the end, Nature prevails.
Oh my goodness. I guess so.
It all comes back to Nature.
All right. Anyone who hasn't gone?
Okay, I guess I will challenge...
I'm here to defend my salad today.
You got anything to say about your salad?
Words about my salad too.
Your salad's on the line.
Salad!
You're going down!
Salads suck!
Are you two ready?
More like "sad-lad".
All right.
Ready...
Set...
Go!
Wow, some wilted salad right there.
Wilted salad.
It was soggy. It went bad.
It rotten.
So, even though... has anyone been
keeping count of points?
But whoever wins, you have the most points...
you have everybody's points now.
Yeah, I have all your souls.
All right, so Kronii didn't get to choose.
IRyS chose her, but now it's Kronii's choice.
Your chance, who is it?
Kronii, your only option... you have no choice.
Your only option is Bae, if you want to win.
Unless you don't want to win, then you
can choose...
Okay.
Is this fair, though?
Because she's like... I guess you're the
weakest now.
I want to choose you! I want a rematch!
It makes no sense.
I want a rematch!
Bae's gonna win.
You have to try to get your points.
If you beat her, technically that means
I'm the strongest still.
All right, Kronii, it's showtime.
Oh my god, are you okay?
Kronii, I always... I really liked you.
I still really like you, and maybe you can...
Does it make you weak at the knees?
Oh, looking at you, I'm like weak at the knees, Bae.
But the only person who can put me
at my knees is Kronii, not you. I'm sorry.
God damn it, I tried.
You guys ready?
All right, final...
Ready, set...
Go!
Oh!
Oh, where did that come from, Kronii?
Kronii!
Wow!
Okay, maybe Kronii is not the weakest.
Maybe she is the strongest.
Okay, Kronii had something to prove, and she proved it.
Okay, okay, everybody calm down, calm down.
Okay, okay, okay.
That concludes the game, it's time to go to the next stage.
Oh yeah, the next stage?
The final stage!
Oh, the final stage.
To find the results! Results!
Of who won every single game!
Yeah! Let's go! Yay!
NowLoading..
And it is time to announce the final score!
Yeah!
We have reached the end of the Promise games.
Already?
I know, it's such a shame. Aw man.
But to help announce the results, we're going to bring back A-chan!
A-chan! Yay!
I'm here!
So cute! A-chan!
Feed me, feed me. Feed me, feed me, feed me.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, the championship of the very first Promise games is...
Wait, can we have a drumroll?
[Drumroll] Okay...
Kronii! You are the winner!
Oh! Ouro Kronii!
I did not see that coming.
I did not see that coming either.
She is totally unexpected!
Oh my goodness! This is a surprise.
Wait, it's a surprise? Okay, this is crazy.
Okay, as the championship, Kronii will be awarded a special trophy.
A trophy?
Special trophy? Oh, I want a trophy.
Excuse me? I would've tried harder if I knew there was a trophy.
I thought the results were for laughs and fun.
I know.
Okay, here it is.
Where? Where?
Oh! Oh! Oh my god!
Who's that? Who's up there?
Where is it? I want one too.
Yes please, I'm waiting! Oh!
No, no, no, only Kronii. Thank you, thank you, Kronii.
Wait, yeah, how does it look? What kind of trophy is it?
Kronii has won this special Yagoo trophy!
It's okay, you can keep it, fam. Whoa!
Wait, is he shirtless?
Shirtless? He is shirtless!
He's been hitting the gym!
Yeah, he is built! He's a buff boy!
He looks good! Damn! Very nice!
How cute it is, right?
Now let's have a word from the champion.
Speech! Speech! Speech! Speech! Speech!
Okay, well...
First of all, I would like to thank me, myself, and I.
And, um...
It's just not a surprise, but I would like to thank that as a surprise for many of you.
Though it isn't...
Though it isn't for me, honestly. But, you know...
Yeah, yeah, get on with it, get on with it.
Okay, okay. It's an honor.
It's an honor, I am very happy to have another trophy added to my collection.
My never-ending collection. Thank you so much.
I mean, I guess we should...
おめでとう！おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congratulations! Congratulations! Congratulations!
ありがとう。Heh heh heh.
Thank you. Heh heh heh.
Yeah, thank you for very nice, tender, shinjy voice.
Okay, anyway, what are you girls gonna do after this?
After this?
There's more? You thought this was it? No! What?
We're gonna do a live show!
Yay! Let's go!
You guys ready? Get hyped, there's a lot more to come.
We're gonna go get ready for the show now. We gotta go switch stages.
So, everybody... off stage right!
We'll see you guys in a bit! Bye-bye! Bye!
Wait, A-chan? I'm... I'm alone. Oh...
Oh, I'm alone. I feel sad.
Ah, enjoy watching the live.
Ah... かわいい。
Ah... So cute.
ANGELUS -アンジェラス-
ANGELUS
Lyrics: BOUNCEBACK Composition: BULGE
誰かのために流す涙
Tears shed for someone else
祈りのように頬に伝う
Run down your cheeks like a prayer
それを弱さと隠さないで
Don't hide that and call it weakness
優しさと受け入れて
Accept it as kindness
呼吸さえも忘れさせる
The sky I found in your eyes
瞳の中に見つけた空
Makes me even forget to breathe
太陽だけが輝いてる
Only the sun is shining
何を探し続ける
What do you keep searching for?
鏡を見つめ誓ったあの日
That day you gazed into the mirror and made a vow
あなたにはきっと見えていた
You surely must have seen it
自分の背中にも翼が
That you too have wings...
あると
...on your back
あなたが変わり世界が変わる
You change, and the world changes
夢に届け愛の炎
Reach for your dreams, flame of love
ゆらゆら蜃気楼を越えて
Beyond the swaying mirage
空には光大地に水は
Light in the sky, water on the earth
その心に強さを
Strength in that heart
未来へ辿り着く
Reaching for the future
アンジェラス
Angelus
望みがもし叶うのなら
If my wishes were to come true
風になること選ぶでしょう
I'd probably choose to become the wind
迷いを捨てたあなたの羽根
Your wings that cast aside all doubt
私の風を掴む
Catch my wind
高鳴る胸と恐れる気持ち
A throbbing chest and feelings of fear
痛みが混ざり合う過去を
A past where pain is mixed together
振り切れたらそこに原色の
If I can break free, then there will be...
虹
...a primary-colored rainbow
一秒ごとに世界を変える
Change the world with every passing second
刻み出した鼓動
The heartbeat that's started to tick away
ジリジリ燃え上がる願い
A desire that slowly burns up
海より深い見果てぬ夢を
An endless dream deeper than the sea
追い求める強さが
The strength to pursue it
闇を照らして行く
Will go on to light up the darkness
アンジェラス
Angelus
走り続けるなら
If you keep on running
飛び立てるはず
You should be able to take flight
あなたが変わり世界が変わる
You change, and the world changes
夢に届け愛の炎
Reach for your dreams, flame of love
ゆらゆら蜃気楼を越えて
Beyond the swaying mirage
空には光大地に水は
Light in the sky, water on the earth
その心に強さを
Strength in that heart
未来へ辿り着く
Reaching for the future
アンジェラス
Angelus
情熱の欠片を
A fragment of passion...
手にして
...in your hands
ANGELUS -アンジェラス-
ANGELUS
Angelus!
リンリンリン！おはよう Wake up!
Rin rin rin! Good morning, wake up!
ドキドキモーニング
Doki Doki Morning
ド・キ・ド・キ☆モーニング
Lyrics: ナカメタル  Composition: のりぞー / 村カワ基成
Doki Doki ☆ Morning
Lyrics: Nakametal  Composition: Norizo / Motsunari Murakawa
パッツンパッツン前髪パッツン
Bangs cut straight across
Cutie style
真っ白一直線、アイ！出して
A straight white line, GO! DASH!
超やばい！
Super crazy!
今日の立地、アート、キャッチ、ソッチ、ドッチ、ウェイ、ジャッジ、ウォッチ
Today's location, art, catch, that way, which way, way, judge, watch
いま何時？
What time is it now?
チョピリ ホカホカ チョピリ バーバー
A little warm, a little...
Bye bye star
今日の立地、アート、キャッチ、ソッチ、ドッチ、ウィー、ジャッジ、ウォッチ
Today's location, art, catch, that way, which way, we, judge, watch
超やばい！
Super crazy!
今日のリッチ、アート、キャッチ、ソッチ、ドッチ、ウィー、ジャッジ、ウォッチ
Today's rich, art, catch, that way, which way, we, judge, watch
いま何時？
What time is it now?
知らないふりは キライ キライ
I hate pretending not to know
知らない世界 行きたい 行きたい
I want to go to an unknown world
幼児系 乞食系 期待 期待
Childish style? Beggar style? Expectations!
レパ 背伸びしたい したい
Repa, I want to stand on my tiptoes
よね？
Right?
リンリンリン！おはよう Wake up!
Rin rin rin! Good morning, wake up!
お願い ちょまって ちょまって
Please wait a bit, wait a bit!
リンリンリン！焦らず Hurry up!
Rin rin rin! Don't rush, hurry up!
バタバタモーニング
Hectic morning
リンリンリン！Our watch make up!
Rin rin rin! Our watch make up!
お願い ちょまって ちょまって
Please wait a bit, wait a bit!
リンリンリン！戸締まり忘れて
Rin rin rin! Forgot to lock up
ドキドキモーニング
Doki Doki Morning
知らないふりは キライ キライ
I hate pretending not to know
知らない世界 行きたい 行きたい
I want to go to an unknown world
幼児系 乞食系 期待 期待
Childish style? Beggar style? Expectations!
レパ 背伸びしたい したい
Repa, I want to stand on my tiptoes
よね？
Right?
リンリンリン！おはよう Wake up!
Rin rin rin! Good morning, wake up!
お願い ちょまって ちょまって
Please wait a bit, wait a bit!
リンリンリン！焦らず Hurry up!
Rin rin rin! Don't rush, hurry up!
バタバタモーニング
Hectic morning
リンリンリン！Our watch make up!
Rin rin rin! Our watch make up!
お願い ちょまって ちょまって
Please wait a bit, wait a bit!
リンリンリン！戸締まり忘れて
Rin rin rin! Forgot to lock up
ドキドキモーニング
Doki Doki Morning
(Scream)
リンリンリン！おはよう Wake up!
Rin rin rin! Good morning, wake up!
お願い ちょまって ちょまって
Please wait a bit, wait a bit!
リンリンリン！焦らず Hurry up!
Rin rin rin! Don't rush, hurry up!
バタバタモーニング
Hectic morning
リンリンリン！Our watch make up!
Rin rin rin! Our watch make up!
お願い ちょまって ちょまって
Please wait a bit, wait a bit!
リンリンリン！戸締まり忘れて
Rin rin rin! Forgot to lock up
ドキドキモーニング
Doki Doki Morning
リンリンリン！おはよう Wake up!
Rin rin rin! Good morning, wake up!
リンリンリン！Our watch make up!
Rin rin rin! Our watch make up!
リンリンリン！おはよう Wake up!
Rin rin rin! Good morning, wake up!
ドキドキモーニング
Doki Doki Morning
We did it!
Back-to-back songs!
IRyS and I, we performed Angelus!
What did you guys think?
So sexy!
So seductive! So loud!
Oh, I'm gonna melt!
And we sang Doki Doki Morning! What did you three think?
And you guys sang Doki Doki Morning! What did you three think?
That was... My goodness...
That was just so hot, yeah!
The hair flips! The gowns!
I want more! Man...
I really hope everyone enjoyed the songs as well!
But, it is time for...
SHILLIN' MERCH!
Let's take a look at all the merch that was revealed during everyone's individual showcases!
Next, okay starting with...
Fauna!
I'm up first!
Yay!
Sap-Ring Smartphone Ring
Size: Approx. H30xW30mm
Material: Zinc Alloy, Iron
I have to show off for you the Sap-Ring Smartphone Ring,
an object which I personally have found very useful.
Stick it on the back of your phone, any phone,
and use it to stand up your phone, watch YouTube,
watch Hololive wherever you are.
Wherever you go, you'll have a stand.
And it's in the cute shape of a sapling!
Yay! Nice! Perfect! Perfect!
Next is me! What's up? Yeah,
Warden's Capely Embrace Blanket
Size: Approx. H70xW100cm
Material: Polyester
so have you ever wanted me to hug you?
Well, I will never do that.
But, you can imagine yourself being hugged
by getting yourself Warden's Capely Embrace.
Look! Looks like my cape.
It's gonna be great.
Go get it. Get it! Yeah! Woo!
Who's next? Me! Me, me, me, me!
Oh, hi!
I have here my silicone lantern.
Mumei's Lantern
Size: Approx. H240xW105xD105mm
Material: Lamp/ Silicone, Zinc Alloy LED Light/ ABS Resin
You can be matchy-matchy with me, we can be twinsies!
And it can light up the darkness in your life,
or it can light up whatever is lurking in the shadows. Yeah!
Woo! Get it! Get it! Beb-beb-beb-beb!
Gee, ever feel like you have nothing in your wardrobe
because all your t-shirts suck? Don't worry, I got you:
Street Rat T-Shirt
One-size-fits-all
Material: Cotton, Polyester
the Street Rat T-Shirt! We have the same logo,
we can match! We can match!
And it goes with the snapback and all your other merch,
like your bag and stuff. Ayy! Yeah! Get it!
Ayo! Yeah! Yeah! And that's not it!
Because we have... the usual!
The usual you never expected though even though it's the usual:
3D Acrylic Stand
Size: Body/ Approx. H202-287mm x W95-258mm
Material: Acrylic
the 3D Acrylic Stand! Woah!
As promised, the 3D poses!
They're much bigger than the usual acrylic stands,
and they look really nice together.
So you better get the whole set. It's gonna look amazing. Yeah!
Speaking of HoloPromise... yeah!
Did everyone enjoy Promise's first collab stream? Yeah!
That was fun. I was so happy to be here with you girls,
with HoloPromise! With HoloPromise!
We promise you many more fun times to come.
Yes! That's a promise! Indeed.
A great future right ahead. Good for us! Cheers to that!
That means guys... I'm afraid running out of time.
Nooo! Ohhh!
Looks like we have to go, guys. Nooo!
If only we had just one more fun... well,
hold on. Are you asking what I think you're asking?
Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
All right, I guess we have time for one more song!
Yay! All right, let's go!
GO!!!
Lyrics: KOHSHI Composition: TAKE
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming for the heights
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, regardless of how we look
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, just as we believe
Oli oli oli oh-! Just go my way!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放すのさ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) Let it loose like a bullet liner!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) 突き進むのさ Get the fire!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) Push forward and get the fire!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放すのさ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) Let it loose like a bullet liner!
Right here, Right now (Bang!)
迷い道の途中 人の地図を広げてどこへ行く?
In the middle of a lost path, where are you going with someone else's map?
極彩色のカラスがそれを奪い取って破り捨てた
A richly colored crow snatched it away and tore it up
さぁ 心の目を開いて しかと今を見極めろ
Now, open your mind's eye and see the present clearly
失うものなんてないさ 不安を纏い
There's nothing to lose, even clad in anxiety
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming for the heights
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, regardless of how we look
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, just as we believe
Oli oli oli oh-! Just go my way!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放すのさ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) Let it loose like a bullet liner!
Right here, Right now (Bang!)
後先考えず
Without a second thought,
忍び寄る影が
creeping shadows
いつも僕らを惑わせる
always lead us astray.
勇敢に行こう 大きな風が
Let's go bravely, a great wind
希望へ繋がる時を歩める
We can walk through a time connected to hope
眼差しをすれば一刀で己の明日切り開け
With a single glance, carve out your own tomorrow
Yeah! 誇張なんてどこにもないさ そうだろう？
Yeah! There's no exaggeration anywhere, right?
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming for the heights
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, regardless of appearances
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, just as you believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here, Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ飛ばすのさ Like a juggernaut
I'm gonna blast it away like a juggernaut
Right here, Right now (Burn!)
ぶったき潰すのさ Fire
I'm gonna smash it down, Fire
Right here, Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ飛ばすのさ Like a juggernaut
I'm gonna blast it away like a juggernaut
Right here, Right now (Burn!)
ぶったき潰すのさ Fire!
I'm gonna smash it down, Fire!
We are Fighting Dreamers この仲間達と
We are Fighting Dreamers, with these friends
Fighting Dreamers 全てを巻き込み
Fighting Dreamers, involving everything
Fighting Dreamers 志高く
Fighting Dreamers, with high aspirations
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! We are Fighting Dreamers!
さあ高みを目指して Fighting Dreamers
Now, aiming for the heights, Fighting Dreamers
なりふり構わず Fighting Dreamers
Regardless of appearances, Fighting Dreamers
信じるがままに Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just as you believe, Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just go my way!
Don't forget your first impulsive go my way!
Let's keep your adventure first impulsive go my way!
Don't forget your first impulsive... yeah!
Let's keep your adventure first impulsive...
Go Right here, Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ飛ばすのさ Like a juggernaut
I'm gonna blast it away like a juggernaut
Right here, Right now (Burn!)
ぶったき潰すのさ Fire
I'm gonna smash it down, Fire
Right here, Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ飛ばすのさ Like a juggernaut
I'm gonna blast it away like a juggernaut
Right here, Right now (Burn!)
ぶったき潰すのさ Fire! Yeah!
I'm gonna smash it down, Fire! Yeah!
Promise -hololive English-
Thank you for the good times!
Thank you for all the support!
THANK YOU EVERYONE!
Thank you for everything! Best Fauna
Thanks for watching
SPECIAL COLLAB