(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Kobo Baby Party! #Kobo3rdAnniversary
Cerah sekali hari ini.
It's so bright today.
Yah, langit yang sangat biru.
Yeah, a very blue sky.
Langit biru, membara hati.
Blue sky, burning heart.
Putih awan, setulus cintaku pun bersemi.
White clouds, as sincere as my love blooming.
Ini kurang kece nih.
This is not cool enough.
Hah, bentar.
Hah, wait.
Kita baca chat dulu ya guys, kita absen dulu ya.
Let's read the chat first guys, let's do a roll call.
Bo intro bo intro... eh, saya bukan Kobo ya.
Bo intro bo intro... eh, I'm not Kobo.
Panggil aku Ceboo.
Call me Ceboo.
Ya sama-sama bo sih.
Well, both are "bo".
Tapi di sini saya bukan Kobo ya, tapi...
But here I'm not Kobo, but...
oke, intro dulu ya guys.
okay, intro first guys.
Bocebocebo, Cebokan Nairu siap menghujani hatimu
Bocebocebo, Cebokan Nairu is ready to rain on your heart
dengan petir cintaku.
with my lightning of love.
Anjis. Oke, mari kita lihat live chat lagi.
Damn. Okay, let's look at the live chat again.
Kak itu ada gitar di belakang, coba mainin dong.
Kak, there's a guitar behind you, try playing it.
mendengar Kak Cebo bernyanyi.
hear Kak Cebo sing.
Wiya, ada gitar ya? Oh.
Wiya, there's a guitar? Oh.
There's guitar here. Sodesune.
There's a guitar here. That's right.
Tapi gimana ya, aku gak pandai nyanyi guys.
But how, I'm not good at singing guys.
suara Kakak ganteng banget pasti bagus kalau nyanyi.
your voice is so handsome, it must be good if you sing.
Aduh, iya iya. Ya udahlah shoganai wa.
Gosh, okay okay. Well then, it can't be helped.
Tapi satu lagu aja ya, okay only one song okay.
But just one song, okay only one song okay.
Maaf ya guys kalau sedikit gimana gitu,
Sorry guys if it's a bit like that,
soalnya aku emang gak pandai nyanyi.
because I'm really not good at singing.
Ya udah, let's go.
Well then, let's go.
星みたいに隠れて
Hiding like a star,
終わらないピントで
with an endless focus...
HELP!!
天使はもうこの部屋にはいない
The angel is no longer in this room.
顔も知らない人達と
With people whose faces I don't know,
目が合う今日この頃
our eyes meet these days.
何かを指針にして
Using something as a guide,
動き始める歯車
the gears start to move.
私の耳を劈くような音
A sound that seems to pierce my ears,
いらない物ねだり
begging for things I don't need.
夜が明ける頃 誰かの寝言が
Around the time dawn breaks, someone's sleep-talking...
終わる心が なんて密かだ
A heart that ends, how secret it is.
このままじゃ生きられない
I can't live like this,
何にも満たされない
nothing fills me.
流れた間の数が増えていくから
Because the number of flowing moments is increasing
たまにあるラッキーザマに合わない
I don't fit in with the occasional lucky states
名前も知らない人と目が合う今日この頃
These days, making eye contact with strangers
何かを指針にして振るい
Shaking with something as my guide
夢見る時間に限りがあること期待してたら
If I was hoping that dreaming time was limited
励まされていくそこは私じゃなきゃいけない
I'm encouraged; it has to be me there
理由はどこになんて失敗作
Asking where the reason is... what a failure
踊り場を歩いていたいたけ
I just wanted to be walking on the landing
身を私かじゃ終われない
I can't end it if it's just me
臆病も魔が差しちゃう
Even cowardice is tempted by evil
独りよがりなだけの優しさ
A kindness that's just self-satisfied
目を逸らしちゃう頃
Around the time I look away
Bagaikan cinta berlayar hampa tanpa nyawa
Like love sailing empty without a soul
Mengutuk punya pilihan
Cursing having a choice
踊り場を歩いていたいたけ
I just wanted to be walking on the landing
身を私かじゃ終われない
I can't end it if it's just me
ほらね
See?
面倒なんです。全部大正解
It's a bother. Everything is perfectly correct
でも狂うも好き放題
But going crazy as much as I want
私は叶えるの
I will make it come true (Kanaeru)
私じゃいられない
I can't stay as myself
今だけを見つめていたい
I want to gaze only at 'now'
そう今だけを零さないように
Yes, so that I don't spill this moment
Keren banget gak sih?
Wasn't that really cool?
Suara Kobo eh Jebo maksudnya
Kobo's voice— wait, Jebo's I mean
Aku keren, suara keren ya gak?
I'm cool, voice is cool, right?
udah disemangatin sih
I've been encouraged, after all
緊張する。でもや
I'm nervous. But you know,
発された。 Natori さんに励まされて、私ももっとカッコよくなりたい
Natori-san encouraged me, so I want to become even cooler
うりゃ！
Hya!
Lah? Tapi bentar...
Huh? But wait a sec...
Kok mendung gini?
Why is it getting cloudy?
Kalau hujan gini kan gak jadi keren
If it rains like this, it won't be cool anymore
Ni timing hujannya gak bisa di-delay?
Can't the timing of this rain be delayed?
Ngapain payung lagi... kasa...
What's with an umbrella now... umbrella...
Kasa pake gitar apa gak ya? Jangan ya.
Should I use the guitar as an umbrella? No, better not.
あ、仕方がない
Ah, it can't be helped
Aku pasti bisa
I can definitely do it
見て！この伝捨魔のパワー！
Look! The power of this Densha-ma!
え？コボ？コボ kenapa anjir?!
Eh? Kobo? What happened to Kobo, damn?!
Bangun bangun bangun! Hello? Help!
Wake up wake up wake up! Hello? Help!
Pokobo! Pokobo come on! Eh? Bangun bangun!
Pokobo! Pokobo come on! Eh? Wake up wake up!
Gugu gaga
Eh? Gugu gaga?
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
No! We can't do this again! I'm here for your anniversary, not to raise you from a baby up again!
hoho! usu usu~ munya munya~
Eh? Now what is she saying now?
Eh? Now what is she saying?
usu~ munya munya~
Oh, there's subtitle below. Wonderful.
Oh, there's a subtitle below. Wonderful.
Blue kid has been suspended by the sky, the sky angyyy!!!
the blue kid has been suspended by the sky,
the sky anggyy!!!
The blue kid has been suspended by the sky,
the sky is angry!!!
おしょしょ！
Oshosho!
Oh, why would the sky be angry
about my sweet child?
She had treat the sky roughly!!
She had treated the sky roughly!!
おしょしょしゅ、おしょしゅ。
Oshoshoshu, oshoshu.
Hmph, I believe there's a misunderstanding here.
Please, bring her back to normal, I beg you!
hoho~ In order to bring her back to normal,
is to train her, to be an idol!!!!!! Good luck~
Eh? Eh? I-Idol?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, okay.
Kobo-bo, come on, let's just go inside first,
okay? And we'll talk about it.
んぐぐあぐあ...
Ngugu agwa...
Can you stand up and walk normally?
I know you can.
Gonna try, try. Here, here, here.
You've done this before, many years ago.
All right, there you go!
あー！
Aaah!
Oh no! Are you okay?
Okay, okay. You know what? If you 頑張る
Okay, okay. You know what? If you work hard
and do your best to walk on your own,
then I will make your favorite food at home.
Ah...
Kusogaki, not again.
You little brat, not again.
And here we are back!
Wait, Biboo?
Attention! Attention! I-I-Attention, please!
Time for your first lesson, because
apparently we're here with a lot of kids,
but I think I would like some
introductions first, okay? So we have some order.
Let's begin with... hmm, you?
Tell me your name.
あ-い-び-び... よっぴ！
A-I-B-B... Yoppi!
Ha! Yoppi-yoppi!
Your name is Yoppi? Yoppi? Okay.
Very good, Biboo! Okay.
I go next to you. Who are you? Hmm?
Introduction!
び-び-わ-わ... べいぶ！
B-B-W-W... Beibu!
Okay, good job! Beibu! Thank you!
Who are you, cutie-patootie? Hmm?
んまま、んまま、んまま、ふわぁー！
Mm-mama, mm-mama, mm-mama, Fuwaaa!
Okay, okay! And now...
Because I seem to not be able to recognize
my own child today, who are you?
こ-ぼ-ば！
Ko-bo-ba!
Okay, I guess it was Kobo after all.
Good job everybody! Well done!
You did so well!
Kobo, do you remember who I am?
ママ！ママ！ママ！ママ！
Mama! Mama! Mama! Mama!
Yes, Mama! But also known as Takanashi Kiara
from Hololive English Myth!
And today I seem to be the babysitter
of this group.
But, but, but, ちょっと待って。
But, but, but, wait a minute.
Why are these babies here anyway?
What's going on?
hoho! usu usu~ munyamunya~
I thought I made only Kobo into a baby
it seems that all the girls on this island
have become babies!
Kiara, I asked you to babysit!
キアラ、子守り頼んだよ〜
Did you understand?
わかった！ わかった！
Understood! Understood!
Okay! Doesn't matter. Everybody, I think we should play a game, yeah?
Okay! No problem. I have an idea. We're gonna draw something over there.
I'm gonna draw something, and you all will guess what it is!
ばば？
Baba?
Yeah! And if you get it right, you'll get a big cake! How about that?
Are you ready?
Yes! Babu!
Okay! We'll start with round one!
While I draw, you will behave! いい子にしてね〜
While I draw, you will behave! Be good babies, okay?
座って！ ここに、座って、座って、座って！
Sit down! Sit here, sit, sit, sit!
It's finished! Everybody, please take a look! 見て見て！
It's finished! Everybody, please take a look! Look, look!
What is this? What is this thing?
これは、何でしょう？
What is this, I wonder?
にゃ？ ねこ？ 猫？ Cat! Cat!
Nya? Neko? Cat! Cat! Cat!
Maybe! Potential answer. もしかしたら、そうかもしれないけど...
Maybe! Potential answer. It might be that, but...
What does Yopi-chan think that this is?
What does Yopi-chan think this is?
かば？ かば！
Hippo? Hippo!
こぼ！ こぼ！ こぼ！
Kobo! Kobo! Kobo!
I don't think so... But we will see! We will see!
Biboo-chan! What do you think that is over there?
うんち！
Poop!
え？ Is my drawing that bad? そんなにひどい？
What? Is my drawing that bad? Is it that bad?
Abugo-bo! Not unchi, what is this? Tell me!
Abugo-bo! It's not poop, what is this? Tell me!
いん... いんご... いんご... いぬ！
Do... Do... Do... Dog!
いぬ？ りんご？ りんご？
Dog? Apple? Apple?
Yes! いぬ！ 正解！
Yes! Dog! Correct!
Okay! Round two! Start time!
Please behave, okay? シー... スタート！
Please behave, okay? Shh... Start!
じゃじゃ！ Look at this!
Ta-da! Look at this!
Let's think, what could it be?
Yopi-chan! What do you think that that is?
Yopi-chan! What do you think that is?
ドリアン！ ドリアン... ドリアン！
Durian! Durian... Durian!
ルナちゃん！ ルナちゃん、見て見て！ バブ、これ何？
Luna-chan! Luna-chan, look, look! Baby, what is this?
くさい！ くさい！ くさい！
Stinky! Stinky! Stinky!
So also durian? Maybe, maybe, could be!
What do you think people, what is that over there? Think, think, think!
Banana!
You know banana is yellow.
Please save me, what is this?
あー、えー
Aa, ee...
あーあー
Aa aa!
アンニン、アンニン
An-ning, an-ning!
ああー！アンニン！アンニン！アンニン！
Aaa! An-ning! An-ning! An-ning!
アンニン？
An-ning?
アンニン
An-ning.
オッケー！アンニン！アンニン！
Okay! An-ning! An-ning!
アンニン！オカカ！オカカ！
An-ning! Okaka! Okaka!
ストップ！ストップ！ワンモア！
Stop! Stop! One more!
落ち着いて！もう一周！ラストよ、いい？スタート！
Calm down! One more round! Last round, okay? Start!
ウグガガ…あーあー
Gugu gaga... aa aa...
できた！できた！見て！ジャジャーン！
Finished! Finished! Look! Tada!
お！これは何？
Oh! What is this?
そんなに難しくないでしょ？分かるわよね？
It's not that difficult, right? You know it.
今回は…まずはコボに聞いてみようかな！
This time... let's ask Kobo first!
オカカ？オカカ？オカカ？
Okaka? Okaka? Okaka?
アヤムママ？オカカ？オカカ？
Ayamu-mama? Okaka? Okaka?
オカカ！オカカ！オカカ！
Okaka! Okaka! Okaka!
多分ね…みんなにも聞いてみるわね！
Probably... I'll ask the others too, okay?
アバワワ？オカカ？オカカ？
Aba-wawa? Okaka? Okaka?
アバワワ！アバワワ！アバワワ！
Aba-wawa! Aba-wawa! Aba-wawa!
アヤムママ？ワワ？
Ayamu-mama? Wawa?
あー…オヨヨ…トマト？トマト？
Aa... oyoyo... Tomato? Tomato?
トマ、トマ、トマ、トマト！
Toma, toma, toma, Tomato!
トマト！トマト？トマト！
Tomato! Tomato? Tomato!
ベイビー・セシス、あなたはどう思う？
Baby Cecis, what do you think?
あー…アヤムママ…
Aa... Ayamu-mama...
トマト！トマト！トマト！トマト！
Tomato! Tomato! Tomato! Tomato!
コボちゃん正解！オカカが正解よ！
Kobo-chan was right! Okaka was the answer!
いい子ね、いい子ね！
Be good, be good!
もう、この子たちったら本当に面白いわね！
Goodness, these children are so funny!
よし、みんなでもっと仲良くしましょう？
Alright kids, how about we get along better?
お歌を歌って！歌いたい？
By singing a song! Do you want to sing?
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yea! Yea!
ググ・コボ、あなたもよ。もういじめないから大丈夫。
You too, Gugu-Kobo. They won't bully you anymore.
さあ、一緒に楽しみましょう！
Come back up. Let's have fun together!
お歌の時間よ！イェーイ！
Singing time! Yea!
チッチッチッ チモチモチモ チモシーきもちウレシーってマジ
Chi-chi-chi Chimochimochimo, Timothy's feeling so happy for real
チッチッチッ チモチモチモ チモシーってまじタノシーきもち
Chi-chi-chi Chimochimochimo, Timothy's having such a fun time for real
雨降って地固まる…ケド「幸運な場合」って条件がナイ？
Rain makes the ground firm... but is 'good luck' a missing condition?
晴れもっといいことがアル！それ強運の範囲って状況 the nice
Sunny, more good things will happen! That's the range of great luck, situation: the nice
チッチッチッ チモチモチモ ピンチがきてチモシーがいて
Chi-chi-chi Chimochimochimo, if a pinch comes, Timothy is here
チッチッチッ もちろんダまじ待ってろって任せてSay！チモシー
Chi-chi-chi, of course, wait for me for real, leave it to me, Say! Timothy
四葉のクローバー採ればそれは葉っぱ？Yes, Happy
If you pick a four-leaf clover, is that just a leaf? Yes, Happy!
チモシー頼もしいらしい あと優しいって話！メルシー
Timothy seems reliable, and I heard he's kind too! Merci!
あっちこっちタチマチ変わる運気予報はふむふむでモフモフ…
Here and there, the fortune forecast changes instantly, hmm-hmm and fluffy-fluffy...
ニッチもサッチもいかないダラケ！
It's a mess where nothing goes right!
チッチッチモチモ...
Chi-chi-chi mochi-mochi...
ち ち ち もち もち
Chi chi chi mochi mochi
知 の 地 もし
Wisdom of the earth, perhaps
ち ち ち もち もち
Chi chi chi mochi mochi
きみ の きもち
Your feelings
マ ミ ム メ ミ モ
Ma mi mu me mi mo
雨 の ち 晴れ て
After the rain, it clears up
なんか ちょっと ファンシー
It feels a little bit fancy
ち ち ち モチ モチ モチ モチ 飼育 も 嬉しい で マウス
Chi chi chi mochi... I'm happy to raise you!
ち ち ち モチ モチ モチ モチ 楽しい 気持ち
Chi chi chi mochi... Such a fun feeling
雨 だけ だ ツイてない です こんがらがら 来なさい 病まい
Only rain? How unlucky. Come on, tangled-up illness
晴れ た から ポイ り みたい だ し 偶然 の ラッキー たまん じゃ ない
Since it cleared up, it's like a dream. Accidental luck is great
ち ち ち モチ モチ ピンチ が 来 て チモチ が い て
Chi chi chi mochi... A pinch comes, and Chimoshi is there
ち ち モチベーション 上げ 見 てる 目 も 持っ てる だけ
Raising motivation, I'm just watching with these eyes
みんな ドラマ オンライン な 毒 さ 飲も たぶん
Everyone's like an online drama, let's drink the poison, maybe
ちもし は 後輩 だし 不遇 だし いい 感じ
Chimoshi is a junior and unfortunate, but it feels right
ちもし！
Chimoshi!
あち こち 毎日 あれる 運気 予報 は
Every day, here and there, the stormy fortune forecast
混ぜ 混ぜ と フム フム
Mix it up, hmmm hmmm
何とか 蟹とか し て あげ ましょう
Let's do something about it
ち ち ち もち もち
Chi chi chi mochi mochi
道 の 地 もし
The road's ground, perhaps
ち ち ち もち もち
Chi chi chi mochi mochi
罪 な きもち
A sinful feeling
マ ミ ム メ ミ モ
Ma mi mu me mi mo
みんな の ラブ キャッチ
Catching everyone's love
盾 アイドル だし
Since I'm a shield idol
カムカム 潤う ち ちゃん 恋 も 雲 も 美声
Come, come, moisturizing Chi-chan, love and clouds and a beautiful voice
ミコエ タバ ウサギ だ けど
A bundle of rabbits, but...
一肌 脱い じゃい ましょう
Let's give it our all!
つい て おいで よ
Follow me!
Okay, everyone!
Who wants the cake, hmm?
Mama! Mama!
Cake! Cake!
ち ち ち もち もち
Chi chi chi mochi mochi
知 の 地 もし
Wisdom of the earth, perhaps
ち ち ち もち もち
Chi chi chi mochi mochi
きみ の きもち
Your feelings
マ ミ ム メ ミ モ
Ma mi mu me mi mo
雨 の ち 晴れ て
After the rain, it clears up
なんか ちょっと ファンシー
It feels a little bit fancy
ち ち ち もち もち
Chi chi chi mochi mochi
道 の 地 もし
The road's ground, perhaps
ち ち ち もち もち
Chi chi chi mochi mochi
罪 な きもち
A sinful feeling
マ ミ ム メ ミ モ
Ma mi mu me mi mo
みんな の ラブ キャッチ
Catching everyone's love
盾 ボク は ちもし
I am the shield Chimoshi
Yay!
Good job everybody!
No! We can't eat some cake!
Cake! Cake! Cake!
Stinky.
Kobo-chan! So stinky!
I want to take a shower!
Shower! Shower!
Better!
Cake! Cake!
Habis bermain, keringat bercucuran
After playing, sweat is dripping
Rambut jadi lepek, juga berminyak
Hair becomes limp and oily too
Tapi ku lelah, ku ingin tidur saja
But I'm tired, I just want to sleep
Memang mencuci muka tidak cukupkah?
Isn't washing my face enough?
Bau badan tak tertahankan
Body odor is unbearable
Mami Papi pun kewalahan
Mom and Dad are overwhelmed too
Di tengah mereka ku harus pergi mandi secepatnya
Between them, I must go shower as soon as possible
Washa washa washa, washa rambutku
Wash wash wash, wash my hair
Washa washa washa, washa tubuhku
Wash wash wash, wash my body
Washa-washa-wah
'ku gosok badanku
I scrub my body
Shiki-shiki-shi, 'ku sikat gigi
Shiki-shiki-shi, I brush my teeth
Sekarang sudah wangi
Now I'm fragrant
Shoko-shoko-shok
keringkan rambutku
I dry my hair
Shoko-shoko-shok
keringkan badanku
I dry my body
Pakai seragam yang lengkap
Wear a complete uniform
bersiap 'tuk sekolah
getting ready for school
Sampai jumpa mami papi
Goodbye Mommy, Daddy
Selamat pagi, tapi masih dikasur
Good morning, but still in bed
Tangan dan kakiku
My hands and feet
malas bergerak
are lazy to move
Mata mengantuk
Eyes are sleepy
ku ingin tidur saja
I just want to sleep
Memangnya yang nggak bisa, bentar lagi kah?
Is it really not possible, just a bit longer?
Perut sakit
My stomach hurts
ku kelaparan
I'm starving
Mami papi, aku kewalahan
Mommy, Daddy, I'm overwhelmed
Katanya mereka, ku harus pergi mandi dulu, maka...
They said, I have to go take a bath first, so...
Washa-washa-wah
'ku cuci rambutku
I wash my hair
Washa-washa-wah
'ku gosok badanku
I scrub my body
Shiki-shiki-shi, 'ku sikat gigi
Shiki-shiki-shi, I brush my teeth
Sekarang sudah wangi
Now I'm fragrant
Shoko-shoko-shok
keringkan rambutku
I dry my hair
Shoko-shoko-shok
keringkan badanku
I dry my body
Pakai seragam yang lengkap
Wear a complete uniform
bersiap 'tuk sekolah
getting ready for school
Sampai jumpa mami papi
Goodbye Mommy, Daddy
Mimpi
A dream
indah
beautiful
menjadi
becomes
nyata
reality
Untuk anak yang patuh aturan
For a child who obeys the rules
Kelap
Twinkling
kelip
twinkling
bintang di langit
stars in the sky
Semua hal bisa 'kulakukan jika sudah mandi
All things can I do if I have taken a bath
Jika aku rajin mandi, aku bisa menjadi putri yang sesungguhnya
If I'm diligent in bathing, I can become a true princess
Washa-washa-wah
'ku cuci rambutku
I wash my hair
Washa-washa-wah
'ku gosok badanku
I scrub my body
Shiki-shiki-shi, 'ku sikat gigi
Shiki-shiki-shi, I brush my teeth
Sekarang sudah wangi
Now I'm fragrant
Na-na-na, na-na-na, na-na-na
Rapi dan wangi kalau sudah mandi
Neat and fragrant if I've taken a bath
Menjaga kebersihan bersama
Maintain cleanliness together
Cintai dirimu
Love yourself
Ayo mandi!
Let's take a bath!
Wangi! Sudah! Wangi!
Fragrant! Done! Fragrant!
Cintai dirimu ya!
Love yourself, okay!
Ahhh...
Gugu gaga!
Babu babu!
Gugu gaga?
Tada!
Gugu gaga, washa washa washa, emm emm emm
Eto, gugu gaga, washa washa washa, emm emm emm
Um, gugu gaga, washa washa washa, emm emm emm
Gugu gaga, gugu gaga, emm emm emm, gugu gaga
Emm emm emm, washa, washa!
Gugu gaga, gugu gaga, gugu gaga, emm emm emm
Ciiieee!
Gugu gaga!
Agagugo, gigugo, agugo!
Gugugaga, gugo!
Gugu, syo syo syo!
Gugu, gugu, gugu!
Euuugh...
Hmm-hmm-hmm
Hey, Kobo!
I've been waiting for you here!
Congrats on your third anniversary!
Gugu gaga!
Huh?
Wait, why 'gugu gaga'?
Babu babu!
Babu babu?
Gugo!
Okay, okay...
I get it, you've been cursed.
Well, I'm actually familiar with curses, okay?
So, what's up?
Babu babu!
A... gugo!
うー！あうー！うー！ぶーじゅー！ぶーじゅー！ぶーじゅー！ぶー！
Ugh! Auu! Ugh! Boojoo! Boojoo! Boojoo! Boo!
Okay, okay. I see. You're in training so that you can be an idol, so that you can talk normally.
あうー！あうあうー！あー！
Auu! Au auu! Ah!
Naruhodo. Okay. So you can still dance and like, sing just fine but no talking?
I see. Okay. So you can still dance and like, sing just fine but no talking?
あー！うごっ！
Ah! Ugoh!
Oh, okay. Well, maybe you need to perform with Dada.
だ…だ…だ…だ…だ…
Da... da... da... da... da...
Oh, okay, okay. Say: Dada.
だ…だ…だ…ダダー！
Da... da... da... Dada!
Jesus Christ... Okay! All right, all right. You know what? Let's just... let's take it slow, okay? Let's take it slow.
あー！ぐーぐーがーがー！あー！
Ah! Gugu gaga! Ah!
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ みんな食べるよ
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Everyone eat up!
ツル・ツル・テカ・テカ 明日も晴れるかな
Tsuru Tsuru Teka Teka, I wonder if it will be sunny tomorrow
ダバデュア ダバジャバ 忘れ物するなよ
Daba-dua daba-jaba, don't forget anything!
ダバデュア ダバジャバ デュア 大きくなったら
Daba-dua daba-jaba-dua, when I grow up...
お空に声が届くかな？
will my voice reach the sky?
いつまでも一緒だよ
We'll be together forever.
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ みんな食べるよ
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Everyone eat up!
ツル・ツル・テカ・テカ 明日も晴れるかな
Tsuru Tsuru Teka Teka, I wonder if it will be sunny tomorrow
悲しくて 泣いていた
I was so sad that I was crying
ひとり歩く帰り道
on the way home, walking all alone.
こんな時 ほんわかな
At times like this, I want to see...
みんなに会いたいな
everyone who's so warm and kind.
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ おまじないだよ
Maru Maru Mori Mori! It's a magic spell!
ツル・ツル・テカ・テカ にっこり笑顔
Tsuru Tsuru Teka Teka, a beaming smile!
いちにのさんしで ごましおさん
One, two, three, four, black sesame salt!
たくさんだと おいしいね
It's delicious if there's a lot of it!
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ ぷかぷかお風呂
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Floating in the bath!
ツル・ツル・ピカ・ピカ ゴシゴシブラシ
Tsuru Tsuru Pika Pika, scrubbing with a brush!
皆さん今晩は また明日
Good evening, everyone! See you tomorrow.
朝ご飯は何でしょうね
I wonder what's for breakfast?
ダバデュア ダバジャバ...
Daba-dua daba-jaba...
大人になっても 虹色の
Even when we grow up,
夢を描こうね
let's keep drawing our rainbow dreams.
指切りして 照れりんこ
Make a pinky promise, feeling a bit shy!
お星様 綺麗だね
The stars are so beautiful, aren't they?
手をつないで 願い事
Hold hands and make a wish!
たとえ遠くに いても
Even if we're far apart,
心はひとつだよ
our hearts are as one.
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ 幸せ元気
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Happy and energetic!
テクテク トコトコ 前に進むよ
Step by step, we'll keep moving forward.
いちにのさんしで ホームラン
One, two, three, four, home run!
愛がいっぱい ランドセル
A school backpack full of love!
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ 大きくなるよ
Maru Maru Mori Mori! We're growing big!
ドキドキ ワクワク ドアを開けるよ
With excitement, we'll open the door!
皆さんしっかり また明日
Stay strong, everyone! See you tomorrow.
もっと素敵な日になる
It's going to be an even more wonderful day.
ダダー！アンジン！
Dada! Anjing!
Oh yeah, you like Anjing too? That's nice.
大好きだよ
I love you so much!
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ さあ歌いましょう
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Now let's sing!
ツル・ツル・テカ・テカ にっこり笑顔
Tsuru Tsuru Teka Teka, a beaming smile!
いちにのさんしで ごましおさん
One, two, three, four, black sesame salt!
たくさんだと おいしいね
It's delicious if there's a lot of it!
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ ぷかぷかお風呂
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Floating in the bath!
ツル・ツル・ピカ・ピカ ゴシゴシブラシ
Tsuru Tsuru Pika Pika, scrubbing with a brush!
皆さん今晩は また明日
Good evening, everyone! See you tomorrow.
朝ご飯は何でしょうね
I wonder what's for breakfast?
いつもいつも ありがとう
Always, always, thank you.
よくできました
Good job!
Uh, so... so how was that? How is it now?
あー！ぐーぐーがーがー！あー！あー！あー！あー！もう！ばぶばぶー！
Ah! Gugu gaga! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Jeez! Babu babu!
Still baby, huh? This is weird. Man, the curse should be lifted because you did really, really...
Well, you're very like...
...アイドルみたい、可愛い、可愛いこぼ、でしょ？
...idol-like, a cute, cute Kobo, right?
Mori Calliope needs a little bit of work though.
And what is wrong? I need to talk to that curse.
I will visit whoever did this to you now,
and I will ボコボコ their ass.
and I'll beat the crap out of them.
So keep yapping while I... I'm gonna get out of here.
My work here's done. 頑張れ、頑張れ！
My work here's done. Good luck! Good luck!
Bye bye!
ググガガ
Gugu gaga
ググガガ　ググガガ
Gugu gaga, gugu gaga
ブブブババ
Bu bu bu ba ba
アブバブ
A bu ba bu
ギュッ！ギュッ！ ギュッギュッギュッ！
Gyu! Gyu! Gyu Gyu Gyu!
ギュッギュッギュッのギュッ！
Gyu Gyu Gyu no Gyu!
ギュッ！ギュッ！ ギュッギュッギュッ！
Gyu! Gyu! Gyu Gyu Gyu!
ギュッギュッギュッのギュッ！
Gyu Gyu Gyu no Gyu!
サンサンとおひさま 笑顔日曜日
The sun is shining on a smiling Sunday
おでかけしましょ
Let's go out
はぐれないように
So we don't get separated
しっかり仲良くね 手をつないで
Let's be sure to get along, holding hands
ずっとずっとずっと 一緒にいようね
Let's be together forever and ever
明日も明後日も
Tomorrow and the day after,
大人になっても
Even when we grow up,
大好きだよ
I love you
夢いっぱい ギュッギュッギュッ
Full of dreams, Gyu Gyu Gyu
みんなでおにぎりを もぐもぐハッピー
Munching on rice balls together, happy
幸せを ギュッギュッギュッ
Happiness, Gyu Gyu Gyu
愛情たっぷりでもぐもぐ
Munching with plenty of love
ニコニコほらね 心が踊る
Smiling, look, my heart is dancing
ステキな日曜日
A wonderful Sunday
ギュッギュッギュのギュッ！
Gyu Gyu Gyu no Gyu!
ザーザーと 雨が降ってる 日曜日
Pitter-patter, rain is falling on Sunday
でも平気だよ
But it's okay,
傘さして
using an umbrella
長靴はいて 出かけよう
Wearing rain boots, let's go out
おしゃれをして
Dressing up in style
ちょっぴり ちょっぴり 寂しいときでも
Even when I'm a little, little bit lonely
水たまり跳んで 君と遊んだら
If I jump over puddles and play with you
忘れちゃうよ
I'll forget all about it
ハートいっぱい ギュッギュッギュッ
Full of hearts, Gyu Gyu Gyu
明日もまた会おう 約束ハッピーグッデイ
Let's meet again tomorrow, promise, Happy Good Day
思い出を ギュッギュッギュッ
Memories, Gyu Gyu Gyu
心のポケットに ウキウキしましょ
In the pocket of my heart, let's be excited
雨がやんだら 虹が見えたよ
When the rain stopped, I saw a rainbow
ステキな日曜日
A wonderful Sunday
ギュッギュッギュのギュッ！
Gyu Gyu Gyu no Gyu!
同じ気持ち ひとつ増えたら
If we share one more feeling
笑顔もひとつ 増えるから
One more smile will grow too
つかまえようよ たくさん集めよう
Let's catch them and gather many
宝物を
Treasures
ね！
Right!
夢いっぱい ギュッギュッギュッ
Full of dreams, Gyu Gyu Gyu
みんなでおにぎりを もぐもぐハッピー
Munching on rice balls together, happy
幸せを ギュッギュッギュッ
Happiness, Gyu Gyu Gyu
愛情たっぷりでもぐもぐ
Munching with plenty of love
ニコニコほらね 心が弾む
Smiling, look, my heart is bouncing
ステキな日曜日
A wonderful Sunday
グッデイ！
Good day!
ギュッ！ギュッ！ ギュッギュッギュッ！
Gyu! Gyu! Gyu Gyu Gyu!
ギュッギュッギュのギュッ！
Gyu Gyu Gyu no Gyu!
はずむココロ！
A heart that bounces!
飛ぶようなテンション！
Tension that makes me feel like flying!
さあ Connect しよ！
Now, let's connect!
ツナガルコネクト
Lyrics: Ayaka Miyake Music: DECO*27
Tsunagaru Connect
I'm me... No more hiding now...
Change me... So I'm trying now...
あれ？ 今こう思っていて
Wait, I was thinking this just now...
あ、そうじゃなくて
Ah, no, that's not it...
ええと あの
Um, well...
願わないや、なんて
I don't wish for it, or something...
だけどどうするんだっけ？
But what was I supposed to do?
システマティックにググるオーロラ
Systematically googling the aurora
コンパス Z 効かないし
Compass Z isn't working
ムブス カスタマイズ 足りないなにか
Moves, customization, something's missing
インストール 出来たらな
If only I could install it
案外不完全で
Unexpectedly imperfect
世界はなんだって
Whatever the world is
本音不確実で
Honest feelings are uncertain
答えは僕達だ
The answer is us
迷路なんてないよね
There are no mazes, right?
まずは始めてみようかな
Maybe I'll try starting for now
違う姿 違う形
Different appearance, different shape
なのにどうして同じ気持ち
Yet why do we feel the same?
つないであげてる時間が
The time we're spending connected
溶け合う温もりありがとう
Thank you for the warmth that melts into one
思い切り伝えたいな
I want to tell you with all my heart
カラフル笑顔心地いいな
Colorful smiles feel so good
つながっていくみんなと
Connecting with everyone
ここが私の好きな場所
This is my favorite place
はずむココロ！
A heart that bounces!
飛ぶようなテンション！
Tension that makes me feel like flying!
今 connect しよ！
Now, let's connect!
I'm me... No more hiding now...
Change me... So I'm trying now...
一生懸命頑張ってみたって
Even if I try my absolute hardest
変われないって諦めて
Giving up, saying I can't change
トライしてみるって前段
The preliminary step of trying
断念して
Giving it up
提案も白紙修正
The proposal corrected to a blank slate
パッとままに 思い通りにいかなくて
Doesn't go as planned right away
ポッキリ折れてた心
My heart was snapped in two
もう一度踊らせていきたいな
I want to make it dance once more
案外不完全で
Unexpectedly imperfect
日々とにかく一生
Every day, for a lifetime
もう重ならないんだ
They won't overlap again
明日は私達だ
Tomorrow belongs to us
そう遠く届かなくても
Even if it doesn't reach far
一歩踏み出してみようかな
Maybe I'll try taking a step
違う色と 違う夢で
With different colors and different dreams
包み 未来を描こう 素敵
Wrapped up, let's paint the future, it's wonderful
見えない糸感じてる
I'm feeling the invisible thread
温かい優しさありがとう
Thank you for the warm kindness
思い切り歌いたいな
I want to sing with all my heart
ハピフル笑顔届けたいな
I want to deliver happy, full smiles
出会っていくオリジナルに
To the originals I encounter
みんなと大切な場所
A precious place with everyone
一人じゃないよ
You're not alone
チャンス待っていた
I was waiting for the chance
みんなと一緒に一歩
One step together with everyone
前に進めること
Being able to move forward
見つけていくから
Because I'll find it
違う姿 違う形
Different appearance, different shape
なのに本当同じ気持ち
Yet truly the same feeling
つないであげてる時間が
The time we're spending connected
溶け合う温もりありがとう
Thank you for the warmth that melts into one
思い切り伝えたいな
I want to tell you with all my heart
カラフル笑顔心地いいな
Colorful smiles feel so good
つながっていくみんなと
Connecting with everyone
ここが私の好きな場所
This is my favorite place
はずむココロ！
A heart that bounces!
飛ぶようなテンション！
Tension that makes me feel like flying!
さあ connect しよ！
Now, let's connect!
I'm me... No more hiding now...
Change me... So I'm trying now...
あ、痛い 痛たた...
Ah, it hurts... Ouch ouch...
え？ 痛い！ お！
Eh? It hurts! Oh!
I can speak! Whoa!
And my dress too!
Congrats, you have now gotten back your power!
おめでとう！ これでまた力を取り戻したね！
Congratulations! You've gotten back your power!
へえー？
Hee?
Whoa! I've gotten back my power now!
And my... my dress...
My... my fuku is changed!
My... my dress has changed!
Why do I have mic though?
Why do I have a mic though?
Ah, but anyways, thank you!
Thank you, Tellos!
Now I can talk normal!
Now I can talk normally!
やったー！
I did it!
You're such a good friend!
でもなんで？
But why?
Kenapa baru sekarang digantinya?
Why was it only changed now?
Ini buat apa mic-nya?
What is this mic for?
Hah?
Huh?
うん！今日もいい日になるといいね！ 3周年おめでとう！
I hope you have a great day, Happy 3rd Anniversary!
Okay...
Sekarang waktunya...
Now it's time for...
CILUS!!!
Apaan tuh Kobo?
What's that, Kobo?
Ya, jadi Cilus ini maksudnya...
Yeah, so Cilus means...
Merch kali ini adalah...
This time's merch is...
Tadaaa!
Boneka Cilus!
Cilus Plushie!
チルスぬいぐるみだよ！
It's the Cilus plushie!
かわいいでしょ？
It's cute, right?
安い！ハハハハ。
It's cheap! Hahahaha.
これ安い。
This is cheap.
絶対買ってね。
Make sure you buy it.
かわいいからね。
Because it's cute.
Jadi kalian harus punya Cilus...
So you guys must have Cilus...
...sebagai teman tidur kalian.
...as your sleeping companion.
Teman mandi kalian.
Your bathing companion.
Teman motoran kalian.
Your motorcycling companion.
Bisa menjadi teman kalian yang gak punya teman. Hahaha.
It can even be a friend for those of you who have no friends. Hahaha.
Anyways,
Tolong dibeli karena...
Please buy it because...
...bisa habis. Iya.
...it might sell out. Yes.
Jadi jangan sampai kehabisan. Karena...
So don't let it run out. Because...
Nggak apa-apa, harus aja beli pokoknya.
It's fine, you just have to buy it anyway.
Okay!
Kalo gitu...
In that case...
Udah nih, kita jual Cilus udah.
That's it, we're done selling Cilus.
Promo Cilus udah nih.
The Cilus promo is done.
Jual plushie Cilus.
Selling Cilus plushies.
Oke.
Okay.
Selanjutnya apa? Udah selesai kita.
What's next? We're finished.
Kita udah di penghujung acara, guys.
We're at the end of the show, guys.
Yaudah deh kalo gitu...
Alright then...
See you next time ya.
See you next time.
Kobo mau ngucapin makasih...
Kobo wants to say thank you...
...udah ngikutin perjalanan Kobo...
...for following Kobo's journey...
...perjalanan gugu gaga ini.
...this gugu gaga journey.
見てくれてありがとう。見てくれてありがとう。
Thank you for watching. Thank you for watching.
Thank you for accompanying me in this baby gugu gaga journey.
じゃ！
Well!
おつこぼ！
Otsu-Kobo!
See you next time! Bye-bye!
Eh?
Halo?
Hello?
Eh?
Ini... di mana ya?
Where... is this?
Arsi?
Arsy?
Arsy Widianto?
Iya, halo.
Yes, hello.
Hah?
Kita udah kenal?
Do we know each other?
Eh, Kobo Pawang Hujan, 8 tahun...
Eh, Kobo the Rain Shaman, 8 years old...
...sudah punya pengalaman 3 tahun.
...already has 3 years of experience.
Ini pengalaman ke-3 tahun...
This 3rd year experience...
...penggemar ringan Arsy Widianto.
...a casual fan of Arsy Widianto.
Selamat, Happy 3rd Anniversary ya, Kobo.
Congratulations, Happy 3rd Anniversary, Kobo.
Diucapin ama ayang, eh ama Kak Arsi!
Congratulated by my love, I mean, Arsy!
Tapi btw bukannya Kak Arsy sibuk ya orangnya?
But btw, isn't Arsy a busy person?
Kok bisa tiba-tiba di sini?
How can you suddenly be here?
Gak tahu... tadi aja tiba-tiba...
I don't know... just now suddenly...
...kayak aku ditarik dibawa terbang sama awan gitu aja.
...it felt like I was pulled and flown away by a cloud, just like that.
Hah? Sama awan?
Hah? By a cloud?
Iya.
Yes.
Eh?
Btw...
Ya?
Yes?
Aku tuh sebenarnya udah kenal kamu, Bo.
I actually already know you, Bo.
Hah?
えっ？ Arsy Widiantoくん？
Eh? Arsy Widianto-kun?
Aku cuma pura-pura lupa aja.
I'm just pretending to forget.
Hah?
Jangan-jangan kamu beneran lupa ya, Bo?
Could it be that you've really forgotten, Bo?
えー... あたし...
Uh... I...
Banyak yang harus terjadi hari ini.
A lot has happened today.
Kepalaku sedikit sakit.
My head hurts a little bit.
It's okay Kobo, gak apa-apa.
It's okay Kobo, it's fine.
Tapi kenapa ya perasaan ini familiar?
But why does this feeling feel familiar?
Seakan kita sudah saling kenal satu sama lain sebelumnya.
As if we've already known each other before.
Seberat itu trauma kamu, Bo?
Is your trauma that heavy, Bo?
Maaf Arsi.
Sorry, Arsy.
Sebenarnya aku ingin dekatmu
Actually, I want to be close to you
Namun ku sadari ku tak bisa
But I realize that I can't
Tak boleh ku disini
I shouldn't be here
Bahaya ku makin cinta
It's dangerous, I'm falling more in love
Ku tak ingin jauh
I don't want to be far
Tak ingin berpisah
I don't want to separate
Mengapa semua selalu indah
Why is everything always beautiful
Saat dengan mu
When I'm with you
Sayang untuk di akhiri
It's a pity to end it
Andai kau bisa mengerti
If only you could understand
Betapa beratnya aku
How heavy it is for me
Harus aku tetap tersenyum
I have to keep smiling
Padahal hatiku terluka
Even though my heart is hurt
Adakah hati cinta ini
Is there any heart of this love
Bila ku tak jadi denganmu
If I don't end up with you
Jika memang
If it really
memang ku harus pergi
if indeed I must go
Yakinlah hatiku kamu
Be sure that my heart is yours
Bukankah semesta
Isn't it the universe
yang pertemukan kita
that brought us together?
Haruskah kusampaikan
Should I tell
pada bintang
the stars?
Mengapa bukan kamu
Why is it not you
yang memiliki aku
who possesses me?
Andai engkau bisa mengerti
If only you could understand
betapa beratnya aku
how heavy it is for me
Harus aku tetap tersenyum
I must keep smiling
padahal hatiku terluka
even though my heart is wounded
Adakah hati cinta ini
Is there still a heart for this love
bila ku tak jadi denganmu
if I don't end up with you?
Jika memang ku harus pergi
If indeed I must go
Yakinlah hatiku kamu
Be sure that my heart is yours
Mengapa cinta pertemukan
Why did love bring us together
Bila akhirnya dipisahkan
if in the end we are separated?
Dan mengapa ku jatuh cinta
And why did I fall in love
Pada cinta yang
With a love
tak jatuh padaku
that doesn't fall for me?
Arsy
Kobo
Harus aku tetap tersenyum
I must keep smiling
padahal hatiku terluka
even though my heart is wounded
Adakah hati cinta ini
Is there still a heart for this love
bila ku tak jadi denganmu
if I don't end up with you?
Jika memang ku harus pergi
If indeed I must go
Yakinlah hatiku kamu
Be sure that my heart is yours
Kamu...
You...
Yakinlah cinta
Be sure of this love
untukmu
for you
Anjay, amnesia sebentar
Wow, amnesia for a moment,
kita jadi pemain film.
we became movie actors.
Bisa, bisa nih kayaknya nih.
It could work. This suits us.
Pasti akan ada sih per... per...
There will definitely be some... some...
Wow! Wow! Apakah?
Wow! Wow! Is it?
Aoyama Tadashi akan tergantikan oleh Yamakun?
Will Aoyama Tadashi be replaced by Yamakun?
Anyway, makasih advice-nya.
Anyway, thanks for the advice.
Banyak banget pelajaran yang bisa diambil dari stream ini.
There are so many lessons to be learned from this stream.
Terima kasih ya, Bang Arsy Widianto-kun.
Thank you, Bang Arsy Widianto-kun.
Aku juga berterima kasih banget. Aku happy banget.
I'm also very grateful. I'm so happy.
Jadi, aku lanjut ya.
So, I'll be going now.
Ni nggak nggak ilfeel kan diundang ama anime ya?
You're not turned off by being invited by an anime, right?
Enggak lah.
No way.
Enggak ya?
Really?
Ya kalau buat kamu mah apa sih yang enggak.
For you, I'd do anything.
Udahlah, tenang aja.
Don't worry about it.
Eh ayo kita kita kayak... Coba coba di-pet-pet bisa nggak kita?
Hey, let's... Can you try to give me head pats?
Kok kayaknya pendek banget sih aku?
Why do I look so short?
Kayaknya aku nggak sependek ini deh harusnya. Ha? Ha?
I shouldn't be this short. Huh? Huh?
Ha? Ha? Ha? Buset, sombongnya! Parah banget.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Geez, how arrogant! That's too much.
Eh kita kita fist bump fist bump fist bump.
Hey, let's do a fist bump.
Oke, fist bump.
Okay, fist bump.
High five! High five!
Ya udah deh.
Alright then.
Oke, baiklah. Terima kasih banyak sekali lagi, Kobo. Makasih banget.
Okay, then. Thank you so much once again, Kobo. Thanks a lot.
Jangan ke mana-mana, ikut ini nggak? Makan-makan dulu kita.
Don't go yet, want to join? Let's go eat first.
Boleh. Mau ke mana? Mau makan apa? Ayo.
Sure. Where to? What do you want to eat? Let's go.
Ih buset, sok soft-spoken gini buset guys! Aaa!
Geez, he's acting all soft-spoken! Aaa!
Ayo ayo, ya udah nanti di belakang ya.
Come on, okay, let's meet backstage then.
Ya udah, oke.
Alright, okay.
Ya udah, aku lanjut ya.
Okay, I'll head out.
Istirahat dulu ya?
Taking a break?
Iya. Kamu jangan capek-capek juga ya.
Yeah. You don't overwork yourself either.
Oke, iya iya. Makasih. Dah.
Okay, yeah, thanks. Bye.
Arigato. Dah dah.
Thanks. Bye bye.
Mata ne. Dah.
See you. Bye.
Eh iya Cirus-ga dah. Iya dianterin sana.
Oh right, bye Cirus. Yes, take him there.
もう終わりましたかな？
Is it already over?
Hee, yattai!
Yay, I did it!
Iya, yukkuri shitai.
Yeah, I want to take it slow.
Jadi gimana surprise-nya? Kalian suka nggak?
So, how was the surprise? Did you guys like it?
Eh! Cirus!
Cirus, ini dia yang akan kita obrol nanti guys!
Cirus, this is what we'll talk about later, guys!
Kawaii, kamu nanti bakal dijual banyak ya Cirus ya?
So cute, you'll be sold a lot, right Cirus?
You will be... You will be sold...
by many many customers, so...
please be a good Cirus. Hehe.
Kalau gitu kita beneran closing-nya!
Then, let's really do the closing!
Semoga kalian seneng sama surprise itu,
I hope you liked that surprise,
performance tadi, eh!
and the performance just now!
Bokoboko, Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day. Ehe!
Bye bye semuanya! Terima kasih! Bye bye!
Bye bye everyone! Thank you! Bye bye!
Chape.
I'm tired.
Chape!
Tired!
もう終わりだ！
It's finally over!
Say Dada.
Dada!
星みたいに隠れて、合わないピント
Hiding like a star, focus is lost
天使は、もうこの部屋にはいない
The angel is no longer in this room
顔も知らない人と目が合う、今日この頃
Meeting eyes with strangers, these days
何かを指針にして、動き始める歯車
Guided by something, the gears start moving
私の耳を劈くような音
The sound that pierces my ears
ないものねだりで夜が...
Wanting what I don't have, the night...
明け始めてく、不透明なまま
begins to break, remaining opaque.
手探りで進む、一歩、一歩
Fumbling forward, step by step,
その先に何があるか、今はわからなくても
even if I don't know what lies ahead yet.
信じていたい、私の歌声を
I want to believe in my own singing voice.
誰かに届くまで、歌い続けるから
I'll keep singing until it reaches someone.