(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Nerissa...
When was the last time we saw her?
She hasn't left her room in two weeks.
She doesn't love us anymore!
Fear not, my friends.
Is that Jailboss?
Tonight, we infiltrate her bedroom.
Follow me.
I know a secret passage.
Nerissa!
Oh no!
You dare enter my room?
With that—
Don't mess with a girl's sleepover!
生まれ変わった
A reborn...
赤い花
...red flower.
誰のために咲くのか
For whom does it bloom?
ゆらゆら
Swaying, swaying...
答えのないまま
...without an answer.
運命は脆く
Fate is fragile,
愚かな結末
a foolish ending.
磔にされた
Crucified,
心は泣いてる
my heart is weeping.
予定調和を
Knowing the pre-established harmony,
知るこの雫が
this teardrop...
貴方には見えていないのでしょう
...is invisible to you, isn't it?
なら
If so,
此処まで
this is the end.
悲しい声に 言葉に
Driven away by sad voices,
追いやられて
by words...
俯いたまま 微笑む
Smiling while looking down,
赤い花
the red flower.
深く根を張る 痛みが
If this deep-rooted pain
贖罪なら
is my atonement...
分かり合えない
We can never understand each other.
ずっとこのまま
It will remain like this forever.
変わらない運命
Unchanging destiny,
周囲は不条理
surrounded by absurdity.
剥き出しにされた
Exposed,
感覚の違い
the difference in our senses.
ありふれた刃を
Brandishing a common blade,
振りかざす
you swing it down.
貴方には見えていないのでしょう
You probably cannot see it, can you?
もう
Anymore...
消えない
...it won't disappear.
傷
This wound.
風が吹く夜に
In the wind-blown night,
散ってしまう花の色を
the color of the scattering flower...
貴方は知ることもきっと
...you will surely never even know,
ないのでしょう
will you?
底の底まで
Falling to the very bottom,
堕ちたら
if I fall...
黒い景色
...into a black scenery.
俯いたまま 泣いていた
Crying while looking down,
赤い花
the red flower.
朽ちていく心の中
Inside this rotting heart,
未だ抗ってる
still struggling...
ありのまま
...wanting to live
生きていたいと
just as I am.
悲しい声に 言葉に
Driven away by sad voices,
追いやられて
by words...
俯いたまま 散りゆく
Scattering while looking down,
運命でも
even if that is my fate.
深く根を張る 痛みが
Even if this deep-rooted pain
消えなくても
does not disappear...
藻掻き続ける
I will keep struggling,
何度だって
again and again.
淡い想いに
To these faint feelings,
手を伸ばして
I reach out my hand.
My love, where are you?
Hello? Are you over here?
Oh, there you are!
My darling!
Oh, you look so cute laying on my bed like that.
Isn't he just adorable?
I just want to squeeze him!
But, I'll leave him be for the time being.
Jailbirds,
I have to welcome you...
to my room, as this is a very, very special day.
Do you know?
Do you remember?
That today is my... birthday?
In case you don't know me,
let me quick introduce myself.
Hiya darlings!
This is Hololive English Advent's Devilish Diva,
the one, the only,
Nerissa Ravencroft!
And I'm so happy to have you in here for my room...
debut.
Being able to celebrate with you guys is so amazing.
But, I thought it would be more fun
if I had some friends with me.
So, I've invited some very special people today.
Would you guys please come on in?
Yay!
What's up you puppies?
Leave him alone!
Bau bau!
Advent... Assemble!
And we're here today...
to celebrate Nerissa!
Yay!
Happy birthday!
Thank you all for coming.
We're here for your cat.
You're here for me, right?
We're here for your bed.
Ah, yes. What do you guys think, by the way?
It smells like you.
I'm glad.
I want to show off some details...
I know you guys have been here before,
but this is the Jailbirds' first ever time
seeing my room.
So, let me go ahead and point out
some of the details.
First, because everyone's so interested in it,
I want to highlight the bed area.
In this area we have a lot of my personal plushies,
Cat!
and my cat.
He does have another cat bed,
but he likes to sleep there.
It's also... it's very Princess-y, right?
Just like me, right?
Babygirl coded.
I also have a beautiful painting right above my bed.
And I see something else there. Is that a Jailbird?
No, no way.
That's not a Jailbird, right?
Who knows?
Then, behind me,
over behind Fuwamoco,
there is this beautiful vanity area.
It's my kind of... It makes me feel
even more Princess-y.
You can see there's a bust of my head...
Wow, you got a bust made of yourself?
It's important.
I also have a Renaissance painting.
Scattered throughout the room too,
you might notice them,
I have little Advent references.
There's a Pero hiding.
Somewhere over here.
Up there,
I have a Novalite.
And then over here,
over by the vanity area, there's a little Geo. So...
Lots of little Advent references
all around for you to enjoy.
Yeah, that's it. That's awesome, right? That's it.
Alright, time to leave.
Well, thanks for having us.
Thanks so much, we're leaving now.
You're leaving? What the? You're not leaving!
Oh, I saw your cat.
I mean, okay, so are you going to have us
do anything then while we're here?
Yes! Well, I've prepared
a very special game today, actually.
I think you guys are going to have a lot of fun.
So... It's something a little out of the ordinary.
I'll protect you.
Today, you must treat me like your princesses.
Oh? Well, like your princess, actually.
Like a princess? Like a princess?
No, I'm your princess! And you are my princes.
So, it's going to be a Blind Date.
You have to make my heart flutter a lot.
And make me feel amazing on my birthday.
I guess it sounds like fun then.
I'm the... I'm the one being rizz-ed in this game.
I'm excited to see your unexpected sides.
So... I need to prep everything in my room.
So I need you all to... Get over there.
No, no, no, just over there.
In the corner.
I'm going to set up everything, okay?
Wait, what if I go around you?
I'm setting up!
Are we supposed to get dizzy like this?
I'm gonna pull everything, okay?
Are we supposed to look?
Just spin! Just spin!
Just don't worry, it's just...
the furniture's a little heavy.
Let's spin around.
I have everything all ready!
Okay!
What do you guys think?
Whoa! A chair!
What is this?
It's a set!
It kind of doesn't match the room's theme though.
I'm gonna put on a blindfold too.
What?
Why?
Don't worry, don't worry, don't worry.
With Piyans on this projector...
Piyans?
You guys can relax, okay? Relax.
And come close to me, you're so far away!
So, on this projector here, there's going to be prompts with various questions.
And situations will appear.
So you all have to answer them one by one.
Your voices are gonna be altered with a voice changer.
Oh!
Why?
Is it gonna be cute?
Yeah!
But I'm not gonna be able to know who's talking.
So based on that...
I won't have any preconceptions about anyone.
Because it'll just be based on your rizz alone.
So feel free to be extra romantic, okay?
What's that, Shiori?
Don't worry about it.
We'll do our best to be romantic then, huh?
Yeah!
Let's start!
The name of the game is Cellmate's in Love!
Cellmate's in Love!
Cellmate's in Love
The questions for everyone will be displayed on the projector screen.
So please read them carefully.
But... I must put my blindfold on now.
Okay.
So I guess she won't know who's answering...
So the person should move quietly.
So she doesn't know the order.
Yeah.
And plus we have a voice changer.
Okay, well, we should probably line up now, huh?
Okay.
Who wants to go first?
I don't know.
I think you should go first.
Okay.
Wait, can you answer in this order then?
Yeah!
Okay.
No!
You read the first question!
First Date!
It's been over two years since Rissa and I became friends...
But... I think it's time to take our relationship beyond friendship!
Wow.
I'm scared I might ruin what we have...
But... I also really want to tell her how I feel!
So...
Everyone, gather your courage...
And finally decide to ask Rissa out on a date!
What would you say to her?
And where would you like to go for your first date?
Try to ask her smoothly!
That was a lot.
Okay, so it's not just a hypothetical situation, right?
It's a long point, isn't it?
We all have to figure out how to ask her out.
And ask how we are now, right?
Well, are you ready then?
Okay.
Bye!
I'm right here!
Okay.
Yo Rissa.
You know...
I've been thinking...
You're really important to me.
And...
I'd like to go out somewhere special together.
And I...
When we have some time.
Just the two of us.
You know?
So...
I was thinking...
Maybe...
We could go to that cafe that you said you liked a few months ago.
Oh, your favorite, right?
Uh, we could go there.
We could have a nice evening and then maybe...
You know, once our tummies are all full.
Then we can go on a bit of a stroll.
Enjoy, you know, the city lights...
Maybe the water...
Would you like that?
I would like that!
That sounds so sweet!
Well...
Then...
It's a date.
Okay.
Let's do it.
So romantic.
Okay.
I did my best.
You did great!
Okay.
Good job, good job.
I'll go.
I'll just go.
Okay. Do your best, Biboo!
I'll go.
Show her what you're made of.
Can we lower the mic a little bit for me?
I don't think you need that.
No, your love is tall enough.
Wait, uh...
This is kind of mean, isn't it?
Deal with it.
That's fine.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Hey.
Nerissa.
You and me.
Movies.
Tonight.
Come or don't.
But if you don't...
You're gonna miss out on so much, baby.
You know we're gonna do at the movies?
We're gonna pick the scariest movie ever.
I'm... I'm gonna cry...
I'm gonna cringe at the jumpscares...
I'm gonna be so beaming scared,
you're gonna have to comfort me.
And then you're gonna have to put your arm around my shoulder
and be like, "It's okay, sweetie."
"You'll be fine."
And then I'm gonna... I'm gonna nuzzle myself into your chest...
Yeah, while you comfort me.
And we're gonna bond over fear.
And it's gonna be the most amazing thing ever.
Oh my gosh, that sounds uh...
Whoa... I'm kind of interested.
Sounds like a booty call.
But I'm a little scared too.
I feel like I'm gonna have to be the one comforting you...
I don't know how I feel about that.
That's the point.
Yeah, that's the point.
Well, that's a good... Okay, let's move on to the next person then.
Good job.
Yeah, nice try.
Next person. Who's next?
Whoa, are you ready to go?
After that, you have to show off.
Get going. Go on.
I'm waiting.
Rissa...
Well, you know...
We've been close for a little while now...
It's gone by really fast, right?
But we've never really been able to hang out, just the two of us.
You know? Rissa?
I think I'd really like it if it was just you and myself.
That's what I was thinking.
Maybe we could go... I get...
A massage together?
And then, afterwards...
Once we feel so much more relaxed and free...
We could go to a cafe...
A cafe that's very special to me.
Because I know you're a little indecisive too.
And then, we could just chat.
And... more.
More?
That sounds so fun too!
You guys are really speaking to my heart here with these cafes...
And dates and stuff.
I like it a lot.
I think we have one more contestant, so Bachelorette number four...
Will you please take the stage?
Make it romantic!
*Stomps angrily on the ground*
I wanna go on a date with you!
My lady... *tips fedora*
*Pulls out 10 million dollars in cash*
*Waves it under your nose*
This is all for you.
And you know what? Not only that...
But I have 10 million roses in the ground right here!
Wait, do we all... don't die?
Just like my love for you.
That's how it's supposed to be.
You are as beautiful as the moon.
So bright, so elegant, so in the night sky.
I love seeing you at night, ma'am.
Sorry, what are we doing for this date?
Oh sorry! I forgot about the date!
Go on a date with me though!
Okay, you've convinced me.
I think all of you have successfully managed to rizz me on a date.
So there's our first question.
Yay! Come on back!
Let me get my cash again.
I can't tell who my favorite is yet.
I think we're going to need some more questions for me to be able to pick.
More? Alright.
There's more?!
Alright, well let's move on to the next question then.
Alright... We successfully asked Nerissa out,
and she happily said yes!
Yay!
Since it's our first date,
we want to make her feel special and happy, right?
Of course!
Well, what kind of surprise do we have in store for our first date?
A surprise?
Yeah, I love surprises.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now the question is... are we gonna continue the story of our first date?
Yeah?
Maybe... let's do that.
Me?
Okay.
Okay, blindfold back on.
Again! Yay!
Alright, I'm ready to be rizzed.
Alright, well we're ready to rizz you.
Let's go in order of rizz then.
Okay, the twins.
Here I go!
She's so brave.
So then, during our date...
While we're walking along the water at night with all the city lights around us...
Suddenly...
You lose sight of me.
Huh?
You feel a bit panicked...
and then suddenly, you see a bunch of mascot characters.
Huh?
And they're doing a little bit of a dance. Just un-uh, ah-uh, ah-uh!
And then, all of a sudden, one of them goes...
Bwah!
And out comes me!
Ah!
A bit of a surprise!
And ah, I have roses.
And I say, you're the character of my life.
For you!
So cute!
Yes!
That's so romantic, Bachelor Number One?
Thank you! Romance, yeah!
Okay!
Good.
Thank you!
Yeah!
Nice!
All right.
Next up is...
Let's go!
Go on my little rizz champion.
Okay, I got this. Yeah. Steal the mic... okay, well whatever.
So...
How Nerissa hears it...
All right Nerissa. After our date, you know, um, you have to take me home...
because I spilled my drink all over myself from being scared 'cause you were comforting me, right?
Uh, so afterwards, I take you home to my place.
And you know what we're gonna do? We open the door...
and there's trash everywhere.
And that is my surprise because I know everything about you and I know that you love cleaning.
So, surprise! My room is dirty and you have to clean it.
And you love that so much. And that's so romantic for you. Like, "Yeah woman, clean my house."
And... and I let you. I let you clean my house.
And you... you feel so strong about that.
You know, I do love to clean. Especially for my friends.
However, I think if I was on a romantic date, uh, it would not be at the top of my list.
But... but in... in the trash there's like treasures for you that I put in the trash, like flowers.
Oh!
There's like... there's flowers...
You have to dig for it.
I think I would be turned... I think I would be turned off by that.
I feel like when I found them I might be like, "Oh, that's cute", but I might be a little...
You did your best. So let's move on to the next one, how about that?
No one understands me! My type of romance!
It's okay!
Okay, who's next?
Did you like it?
Good job.
Thank you.
I'm gonna do my best!
Well, you know...
here at this cafe...
I guess you're really excited for the cakes that we ordered, right?
And...
Well...
I wanted to surprise you.
And I know there's one thing that you love very much.
So...
How Nerissa hears it...
Nerissa...
Look me in the eyes.
You see this here?
This is my smartphone.
Bam!
Down on the table.
Today...
I'm giving you all my attention.
Because you're my princess.
Um, today...
It's just you and me.
Whoa...
The rest of the world disappears when we're together for you?
That's such a good surprise.
I love it so far, Bachelor Number Three!
All right, let's hear the last bachelor, shall we?
That was a good one.
Yeah.
Good job.
Yeah I'm sad. I'm sad.
My lady.
As we walk on the moon where our date takes place in...
I reconstructed it from the ground up.
There is an amusement park in your honor, in your name.
Nerissa Ravenland!
And there are Jailbirds.
As far as the eye can see.
And you... each one serves you to the utmost ability they have.
You can even step on them. That is my surprise.
An entire army just for you. A fat flocks.
Oh my gosh, that is kind of romantic.
Yeah. But they're moon jailbirds.
They're moon jailbirds? It's like a whole different species.
Are they like, white colored too then?
Yes, they're also maybe fatter.
Oh!
Yeah. Fat on my love for you.
What?
You feed them with your love?
That's how they survive.
Well, thank you Bachelor Number Four.
No problem.
That was awesome.
These are all awesome dates.
Wow, even mine?
Oooh...
Well, it was a good attempt.
Good job! Yeah! Everyone did so good! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Let's move on to the next question, shall we?
Ah, all right!
Question Number Three!
The surprise was a huge success!
Heart-stirring line
Even on this special date...
you feel frustrated that the 'just friends' vibe has not gone away yet.
Now you want Nerissa to see you more than a friend!
And you wanna...
You want her to think of you as a... more of like a romantic interest!
So it's time to make your move!
How are you gonna do it?
Say something to win her heart!
Please do win my heart, Advent.
Please.
Don't look!
Is that possible?
I'll put my blindfold back on,
and you guys can come up with...
everything you want to say.
Think, think!
Time to think!
Well, thinking time's over!
Bachelor Number One,
would you please approach the mic?
Say some what?
Say something to make her more than friends!
Oh, I see, I see.
It's my time!
Bachelor Number One!
Go Bill!
Let's go!
Yeah.
Um...
I'm Bill.
Bill?
Nerissa...
You know...
we spent a lot of time together.
And...
I think...
I know you pretty well.
I would hope that...
you would think the same of me.
But...
I feel like...
you know...
I'd like to take things...
a step further.
You know...
we're not...
just friends...
anymore, right?
So...
Can I...
Can I hold your hand?
Please?
Princess?
You can... you can hold my hand.
If you want to.
I'll...
I'll hold your hand.
That's enough!
Thank you!
That's so sweet!
Hand holding?
That's such a big advancement of our relationship.
But I'd still like to hear...
Bachelor Number Two.
Good luck.
You got this.
Trash!
Trust.
Trash.
You're trash.
Don't be trash.
Just do a story.
Go William!
I'm William.
Alright, baby...
I'm coming over here...
What?
Whoa!
Wait!
Is this...?
You hear me in your ear, right?
Yeah.
Smell me right now.
She smells like trash!
I smell good! I smell good!
That's the pheromones, baby.
That means you're attracted to me.
The pheromones!
If you think I smell good too,
that means you like me so much.
You're so attracted to me.
So I think we should take our relationship to the next level.
What do you say?
You're too close!
Is that a yes?
Baby...
Yes or no?
I kind of... I enjoy that aggressiveness a little bit I think.
Yeah.
Oh!
Good, good!
It's, it's...
Your hands looked deadly.
Maybe just a little forceful, maybe just a little sudden.
'Cause in your dirty... in your dirty room...
with all your dirty trash...
and your dirty flowers underneath the trash...
I don't know, like I feel like it might be a little bit disgusting.
When it's just you and me baby,
in the moment you will forget about everything.
I see.
Well let's move on to Bachelor Number Three.
You can do this.
You can do it.
What's her name?
Go Matilda!
Matilda?
Matilda!
Why was I Bill?
Why not?
Nerissa...
We had some very nice times together.
Just you and me.
And...
Well...
You know we're genmates but...
to me...
we're a lot more than that.
You know...
Every time...
I sent you...
one of those pictures...
that... maybe showed a bit too...
That was just me and you.
There was a reason behind that.
And...
well...
today I'd like you to know that.
So...
um... I'm waiting for your answer, okay?
Cute!
It's so innocent too!
Thank you, Bachelor Number Three!
Good job!
Alright, we have just one bachelor left.
Bachelor Number Four,
will you take the mic?
Nerissa, my dearest...
I like you more than a friend.
Even... I don't know how you feel about me...
And regardless of who you choose...
Whatever makes you happy...
I will honor it.
And I will hope that you will always be happy with that person.
Whether it is the beautiful Matilda...
The other people I've named and forgot I named...
You're just so wonderful...
And your smile is precious.
*Tips fedora*
Walk away with my 10 million dollars of cash depending on how you answer!
Oh my gosh!
So sweet!
That was so earnest too, wait.
I wasn't expecting that from you, Bachelor Number 4, Steve.
No one ever expects that with a person with 10 million dollars.
No.
Well how sweet.
You guys all did so good!
I feel my heart racing for sure!
So, which one made your heart skip a beat the most, huh?
Well, the honest answer of who made my heart...
STOP...
...would be Bachelor Number 2.
I take that as a win.
That's pretty good!
But I don't... it's difficult to say.
It's difficult!
Again, it's still hard to pick.
I think we have to ask a few more questions before I can settle on one of you.
One more!?
Yes, two more questions.
So, shall we read off the next one?
Okay! Let's go to the fourth question then!
Okay.
The sweet days you longed for...
With Nerissa...
It's been two years since you finally confessed your love.
Two years!
And...
Embraced something truly special between the two of you.
Everything seemed perfect.
Like a dream you never wanted to end!
But...
A tiny mistake on your part...
Sparked a huge fight between the two of you!
With all your heart...
Apologize for the wrong you've done...
And strive together to overcome this trial that threatens your love!
Okay...
Got it.
So we've been dating for two years...
And you guys have upset me.
Crisis!
So, won't you please apologize and make it all better?
I'll put my blindfold back on.
So make things right between us, okay, you four?
Two years...
Two years is pretty serious.
Alright, Bachelor Number 1, it's your turn.
Okay.
Here I go!
Nerissa...
I'm sorry...
I know I hurt you, very deeply...
With all my...
Well, it wasn't meant to be like this...
But ultimately, it turned out this way.
My...
Indecisiveness...
Lack of action...
I know...
That you, the love of my life...
I should have done it.
I should have... already proposed to you!
Already have made you...
Long before, but...
I'm sorry for hurting you this way.
For hurting you at your core...
In your heart, so deeply.
Could you ever...
Forgive me?
What a cutie!
Still Bachelor Number 1.
You managed to be so earnest and sweet!
You're really reaching to my heart.
Let's move on to Bachelor Number 2 and see what sort of answer they're going to give.
Good job champ.
Good job champ!
Yeah!
Hey Nerissa.
I know I was gaming with the boys...
And then you walked in...
And you wanted attention.
And I was like...
"Five minutes!"
"I can't pause the game!"
"It's an online game Nerissa!"
But...
And then you went away crying...
But after the gaming session...
I was like "hmm..."
"Maybe I did do something wrong..."
"Maybe I should have..."
"Maybe I should have invited her to play a game with me."
So...
I'm gonna do something...
That I've never done ever once in my life.
I've never done this before.
Apologize!
I've never apologized to anyone ever!
And I'm gonna apologize to you now...
So listen.
I want to be your Player Two.
I'll play with you instead of the boys.
Come here babygirl.
Yeah.
That's... I think that's good, Bachelor Number Two.
Let's move on to Bachelor Number Three.
Does she love that?
Thank you.
Alright, Bachelor Number Three to the mic, please.
Hey.
I know...
Things have been a little weird recently, huh?
But...
I wanted to say something.
Nerissa...
I'm sorry.
I know...
You know...
Maybe I was acting a little childish.
I kept on saying things...
Like... you're stinky.
And then...
You know...
Maybe you took that personally, but...
It's just... I was teasing you...
Because I love you!
I love you Nerissa Ravencroft!
And I'm sorry.
And I just wanted to say...
Is that...
You're stinky.
But...
I love it.
I love your stink!
That's enough.
Let's move to the last bachelor, Bachelor Number Four.
That was pretty good.
What the heck?
What a beautiful stench.
Okay.
Last one.
Hey Nerissa.
It's me, one of the boys.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry that...
The other person and I were gaming instead of giving you attention.
Hello?
We were just having so much fun playing games together.
I should have been focused on you.
I'm crying right now.
I'm just so sorry.
I'm so sorry as one of the boys.
This is your feet and apology.
Th-Thank you?
I guess in your universe I have two boyfriends?
I'm dating both you and Bachelor Number Two.
I forgive you for that too by the way.
I forgive you.
Oh, very understanding lovers.
It's understandable, we were gaming too hard.
It was so good.
It was pretty hot.
That's a good game right here.
Well, I think I'm getting closer to my answer.
Of what one of these lovely bachelors I'm going to pick.
But I think we're going to maybe need one... one more question?
One more?
Okay.
Wow, let's move on to the final question.
And after this one, Nerissa makes her decision...
About who she chooses, so Nerissa...
Ah?
Please answer carefully, okay?
Choose from the heart, okay?
I will, from the heart.
From the heart!
Yeah, in fact, Nerissa why don't you read the final question...
So you can finally see.
Oh, okay.
Question Number Five: My Eternity.
Oh!
This is your moment, Bachelors.
Make the ultimate marriage proposal to me.
Huh?
I've never made a marriage proposal before.
Marriage proposal?
Now is the time.
So let me put my blindfold back on.
And I'm looking forward to seeing your answers, or hearing them.
Two years and she still can't see us.
Um...
You know... ah...
The marriage proposal, should we really be going to the mic?
Oh.
Ah.
I guess you guys can do whatever you'd like.
Bachelor Number One, will you approach?
Slowly.
Thinking.
Bachelor Number One, do not love me or something?
Where are you?
It's such a special day.
We've been out to dinner at my favorite restaurant.
Are you standing me up on such a special day?
Um...
Nerissa Ravencroft... yes?
What's so funny?
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Just like that?
Please?
I mean, we've been dating for two years!
What do you mean?
We're getting married!
Bachelor Number 2!
Oh.
Just let that go, bro.
Yeah...
Boom.
I toss something on the ground. Pick it up.
I know you're blindfolded, pick it up anyway.
Pick it up.
What?
Go.
Oh my god!
What is going on?
It was a ring!
I put a ring on your finger!
We're engaged!
It looks like plastic!
We're engaged now!
That's the wrong hand!
I will marry you!
Get out of here!
We're married!
Get out!
That was so scary.
I'm so scared.
Gotta go comfort her now.
Yeah, please, no more harassment, Bachelors.
Let's move on to Bachelor Number 2...
Wait, Bachelor Number 3.
Bachelor Number 3, please.
Many seasons have passed...
...since we met.
Many memories.
Hard times.
Beautiful times.
Many tears we shed together while we watched the sun rise.
I'd like to spend many more sunrises...
...and sunsets together.
Will you be my... everything?
Yes.
Aw, that is so sweet!
Bachelor Number 3, you're so sweet!
I don't feel like I should clap.
All right.
You don't have to.
We have one more contestant. Bachelor Number 4.
Would you please... approach?
What?
What's going on?
My bro.
Yes?
You are like the bro-est of my life.
Eh- what the heck is going on?
Thanks.
We've been gaming for like two years, bro.
Yeah bro, we have been.
I know.
Wow.
I love playing shooting games with you.
Hello?
You are my number two.
Or my number one even.
I'll be your number two, bro.
Hello?
Wow.
Yeah.
I just love you so much, my bro.
Whoa, thanks, bro.
Yeah.
Will you marry me?
What?!
Well, I think I'm disqualified.
Yeah.
Bachelor Number 4...
Get out of here!
Oh my god.
And with that, the questions are through.
Oh.
She can come to the wedding though.
We've had some awesome... maybe if you can call it that...
...love stories born.
Some good, some bad.
From one to four, whose story did you like the most?
Please reveal the number, Number One!
Who is the most romantic?
I'm gonna go backwards actually.
Drum roll!
I think it's obvious which bachelor did NOT steal my heart today.
Oh...
That way, huh?
Okay, drum roll...
Bachelor Number 2, step forward.
You are disqualified!
Get out of here!
Bachelor Number 4, step forward.
Oh.
You are disqualified!
Get out of here!
Somehow I feel like I knew it was you two.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Come on, wifey.
This is the hard part now.
I'm between Bachelor Number 1 and Bachelor Number 3.
Who stole my heart the most?
Was it the earnest Bachelor Number 1...
...or the very sweet Bachelor Number 3 who seemed to know me best?
Ah, I can't decide.
But if I had to pick between this impossible decision...
I'd have to pick... Bachelor Number 3!
What does this mean?!
It's okay!
You can join us here.
It's okay! We're married!
You are the bride!
No!
But I must say, knowing that each of you thought so deeply...
...about a life with me...
...except some of you maybe.
It makes me feel so special on my special day.
So thank you for warming my heart.
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday, I guess.
Rissa...
You're so fluffy.
I love you.
Bau bau...
Bau bau forever.
Bau bau.
Ah... What a wonderful birthday this is.
I've even found a wonderful partner.
It feels like this next year of my life is going to be so amazing.
I know, right baby? Hehehe.
Hey! The blind date's over.
Snap back to reality. Let's play Twister!
Oh! Yeah!
Ah, I got Twister ready so we can all play together.
Looking at it, it might be a bit tricky for all five of us to play at once though.
Yeah, I think you might be right.
What should we do then?
Umm... Well, how about to make it fun,
we can play one at a time.
You know what? Actually,
I've just thought of a special rule for today.
Let's call the game...
Posing Twister!
Posing Twister! Whoa!
As the name suggests,
the rule is to strike poses while playing Twister.
For example, if the instruction says
'Right hand on red, and cat pose',
you place your right hand on red and do the cat pose.
Once all four limbs are in position,
you can move just one limb to strike the specific pose.
The time limit will be one minute.
And if you can keep your balance for the full minute,
you can clear the challenge.
But, if you lose your balance at any point,
the game is over.
Quick question!
Yes?
Can the audience mess with the player?
Huh? Yeah, why not?
So, who wants to go first?
What? Uh... well we were just playing,
so somebody else go first.
Yeah, someone go first. Okay.
I guess I'll go first... okay.
Watch out! Okay! Do your best Mococo-chan!
I'll show you how it's done, okay?
Do your best, yeah!
I'll try my best to distract you.
I'll have fun!
I've never played Twister before.
It's your first time then?
Well, you got one minute. Okay?
Do your best.
You ready? Then let's start!
Go!
First up!
Left foot on green, and wolf pose!
Awoooo!
Okay, next.
Right hand on red, and cat pose!
Wait, isn't that pretty fast for a first timer?
Faster! Faster!
Nya!
Left foot on blue, cow pose!
Cow?
Moo...
Right hand on red, hero pose!
Wait, I thought my right hand is on red?
Right hand on red again?
Hero pose!
Left hand on yellow, happy pose!
Happy! Happy happy!
Now place your left foot on yellow and express anger!
I'm furious!
So much rage!
Right hand on blue...
It feels like I'm gonna split apart!
You did so good!
All right, Mococo! You passed with flying colors!
All right, who's next? Mococo?
Um... well...
Biboo! You're next
because you made fun of me at the beginning.
Okay! I'll do it then!
Because of that, I'm going to be your biggest distraction, okay?
Okay.
How about I tell Biboo what to do then?
All right, let's start!
Right foot on blue,
graceful Queen Pose!
Oh my...
Okay, Miss Elizabeth Roseblood Flame...
Left foot on blue, lion pose!
Now do a lion pose.
Roar! Rawr!
Left hand on red...
Give me a rabbit pose.
Rabbit?
What does a rabbit say?
Figure it out, I'm not a rabbit!
Peko!
Now place your right foot on green...
...and go Bau Bau!
Bau bau!
Bau bau! Bau bau!
Left foot on red...
..."grr" pose!
Now give us your best "grr" pose!
Grrr...
Right hand on blue...
Okay.
Now kawaii! Go kawaii!
Haa? Kawaii desho?
Huh? I'm cute right?
Kawaii kara yurushite.
Forgive me because I'm cute.
Good enough for me.
Did I win?
You didn't lose your balance...
...but I didn't think that was a very cute poser at the end. What about you guys?
No...
Wasn't good enough.
But, you did your best, so good job!
Yay!
Alright, you pick who's next Biboo.
Ah... okay Shiori, you go next.
Okay, tell me what to do.
Alright, boss me around.
Okay Shiori... are you ready?
Yeah, I guess so.
Let's start!
Left foot on yellow...
...baby pose!
Left foot... put it on yellow.
Yellow, got it.
And now you're gonna show us baby Shiori.
Waaah!
Okay, now...
Again!
Left foot on yellow...
...horse pose!
Horse pose?
Neigh!
Okay, next is...
Right hand on blue...
Got it.
...coolest prince pose.
Will you marry me then? There.
Kyaa!
Okay... uh let's stop this. Right foot...
...on yellow...
Okay.
...and... witch pose!
This is my broom somewhere here.
Okay there's a broom here.
Okay... now your...
...left hand...
...on red.
Okay.
And do a bear pose.
I am already in bear pose.
Grrr!
Okay, you're gonna take your right hand...
...and put it onto yellow.
Okay.
And you're gonna do a butterfly pose.
I am wiggling like butterfly.
I am flying!
Good job!
Good job Shiori!
Wow you did so good Shiori!
Wow you guys are all too good at this.
I don't know...
...you'll do great.
Well, Fuwawa, I think you're up.
Okay...
I don't know if I'm gonna be as good as everybody else.
You got this.
Okay Fuwawa go on.
Your best now.
Bau bau!
Okay, let's start!
Right foot on green...
...hula dance move!
Right foot on green?
Yeah right.
Hula~
Whoa~
Okay okay.
Left foot on yellow...
...dolphin pose!
Oh no do they need water?
There's no water!
Dolphin sounds!
Okay next...
Right hand on red, fighting pose.
Right hand on red...
Good luck.
Good luck with that.
Oh no...
You can do it! You can do it!
Fight! Fight!
You can do it!
You got it!
I can't put my foot all... ah, your foot! Your foot!
Okay okay next.
Right foot on yellow, puppy pose!
That's her default.
You can't take your hands off!
Where do you lean?
Huh?
Right foot... right foot...
Bau bau!
Well that's gonna have to do.
Yay!
Winner!
Alright Nerissa, it's your turn now.
Okay, I'm ready to...
You got this.
...I'm ready to blow you all out of the water.
What?
I don't think you can.
No, I don't actually.
Alright, show us your flexibility. Are you ready?
I'm ready!
Let's start!
First up, left foot on green...
...sexy pose!
Left foot on green, sexy pose!
Right foot on yellow, even sexier!
Left hand on blue, wet cat Rissa pose!
Right foot on green, sea lion pose!
Right hand on blue, do one push-up!
Left hand on red, octopus pose!
Left foot on blue, pirate pose!
How do you like my posing everyone?
Beautiful!
Can we all do a sexy pose together?
Sexy pose everyone. One, two, three!
One more?
One, two, three!
What should we do next then?
Actually, I was thinking maybe we could do Karaoke together?
Karaoke!
And now, please enjoy.
Dark Breath
Da-da-la-da-la-da Dark Breath
Number one, one, one
You want it more, want it more.
Hey.
You will love it now, love it.
崩れ落ちてく
Crumbling down
支配は始まった
Domination has begun
今更賭けたって No
Even if you bet now, No
自覚ないはずよ
You shouldn't be aware
そして...
And then...
捕まえてみたよ
I tried to catch you
影形もない My heart
Not a trace left of My heart
I'm so crazy, crazy love.
半信半疑な素振りは No No
Skeptical behavior is a No No
心に従って
Follow your heart
挑戦心見せてよ 今こそ
Show me your challenging spirit, right now
Baby don't let me down.
Dark Breath...
革命的存在 I was born
Revolutionary existence, I was born
いつだって渋滞感情
Always congested emotions
吹き飛ばして
Blow it away
浅はかな言葉
Shallow words
並べたって
Even if you line them up
何もないことくらい
That there's nothing there
Baby I know.
笑い話でしょ
It's a funny story, right?
漂う香り
Drifting scent
知りながら堕ちてゆく
Falling while knowing
潜む姿
Lurking figure
Baby baby smile.
心侵食される前に
Before my heart is eroded
その手を預けて
Entrust that hand to me
目覚めさせるの Your ending
I'll wake you up, Your ending
I'll never let you down.
So real... 誰もが羨む桃源郷へと Change
So real... Change into the utopia everyone envies.
It's crazy crazy love
偏在の情報と手段は来た
The ubiquitous information and means have arrived.
万歳に渡すね
I'll hand it over with a cheers.
誰にも気づかれないけど
No one will notice, though.
デリレルわ
I'm going delirious.
Love pump pump pump pump
Gotta be kidding me 癖になるでしょ？
Gotta be kidding me, it'll become a habit, right?
Love pump pump pump pump
尚も救われてないのよ
I'm still not saved, you know.
Oh no...
Ya stop the ransack generation
普通じゃない速度
Unusual speed.
It's accelerated, accelerator on more
済ませて
Get it over with.
Love pump pump pump pump
Wawa!
No, it's uh...
Are you ready?
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん？
How about Paipai Mask?
未来 恋の果て 残されたデルタ
A Delta left behind at the end of future love.
出処不明の金の山
A mountain of money from unknown sources.
あいつの気配がするものは
Everything that reminds me of him...
未練ばかりで食えやしない
...is just lingering regret, inedible.
あたしゃ生きながら化けて出る
I appear as a ghost while still alive.
鏡の前で早変わり
A quick-change in front of the mirror.
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん
How about Paipai Mask?
今宵もひと暴れ
Going wild again tonight.
踊れ踊れ踊れ
Dance, dance, dance!
乱れ髪 弾む胸
Disheveled hair, bouncing chest.
運命の罠に酔いしれて
Drunk on the trap of fate.
Shines Spark!
Shines Spark! ララ 皆
Shines Spark! La la everyone!
Pai pa pai pa pa pa pa pai
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
Paipai Mask is a millionaire.
Pai pa pai pa pa pa pa pai
黄金の塔 舞い上がれ
Golden tower, soar high!
ほらほら踊るんや
Come on, come on, dance!
万歳バンザイ恋者は
Banzai, banzai, the lover...
刹那を生きろよ
...lives for the moment.
瞬間 Flashback する
Instant Flashback.
浮世忘れて捨てる Dancing High
Forget the fleeting world, discard it, Dancing High.
Pa ya pa ya
Discotheque Queen
Ah, パイパイ仮面
Ah, Paipai Mask.
Pai... pai...
Pai... pai... pai...
Wawa?
Huh?
Singing a song together, what do we both have in common?
Uhh...
Come on, you say it.
Okay...
Pai!
悪い奴だとは 知りつつも
Knowing full well he's a bad guy...
恋は盲目 止めどなく
...love is blind and endless.
愛のために魂も青くした
I even turned my soul blue for love.
あたしは頓馬な道化師さ
I'm such a clumsy clown.
虫カゴの蝶は 飛ばなけりゃ
If the butterfly in the cage doesn't fly...
虫ケラのままで終わっちまう
...it'll end up just being a worm.
パイパイ仮面が解き放つ
Paipai Mask unleashes it.
今宵も羽ばたくよ
Taking flight tonight as well.
喰らえ喰らえ喰らえ
Take this, take this, take this!
ゲテモノよ クセモノよ
You bizarre thing, you villain.
運命やそなた やってられん
Fate and you, I can't deal with it!
Shines Spark!
Shines Spark! ララ 皆
Shines Spark! La la everyone!
Pai pa pai pa pa pa pa pai
パイパイ仮面はBorn to Born
Paipai Mask is Born to Born.
Pai pa pai pa pa pa pa pai
視線の先はスキャンダル
Ahead of the gaze lies a scandal.
Don't don't 揺らせよ
Don't don't, shake it!
Rush hour に Vibration
Vibration in the rush hour.
さぁ行け 嘘まみれよ
Go on, you liar.
泡沫 Bubble motion
Ephemeral Bubble motion.
一瞬で Zone に入る Dancing High
Entering the Zone in an instant, Dancing High.
Pa ya pa ya
Discotheque Queen
Ah, パイパイ仮面
Ah, Paipai Mask.
今日もあいつはどこかの国で
He's in some country again today...
どんな悪さしてるやら
...up to who knows what kind of mischief.
あたしはいつでも
I'm always...
あんたの身元...
...your identity...
Bye, bye-bye, ba-ba-bye-bye-bye
Bye bye 仮面大富豪
Bye bye, Masked Millionaire.
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Let the golden butterfly soar.
踊れや踊れや 己よ
Dance, dance, you yourself!
万歳万歳 恋者は
Hurrah, hurrah, for the lover...
刹那を生きろよ
Live in the moment!
瞬間 クライマックス
A momentary climax.
浮世忘れて更ける
Forget the fleeting world and indulge.
Dancing high, pai-ya-pai-ya
Discotheque Queen
Ah, bye bye 仮面
Ah, bye bye mask.
Discotheque Queen
Ah, bye bye 仮面
Ah, bye bye mask.
ぐるぐる@まわる@まわルーナ
Guru Guru @ Mawaru @ Mawaluna
まわるまわるまわルーナ
Spinning, spinning, Mawaluna.
まわるまわるまわルーナ・ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, Mawaluna-Luna.
まわるまわるまわルーナ
Spinning, spinning, Mawaluna.
まわるまわる地球もぐるぐる
Spinning, spinning, even the Earth goes round and round.
瞬く間に街中が
In the blink of an eye, the whole town...
まわるまわる頭クラクラ
...is spinning, spinning, my head is dizzy.
幕が上がり祭りの始まり
The curtain rises, the festival begins.
まわれまわれ眉をしかめたら
Spin, spin! If you frown...
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわっても
Even if we spin round and round...
もっともっと
More, more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわっても
Even if we spin round and round...
もっともっと
More, more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわっても
Even if we spin round and round...
もっともっと
More, more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわって
Spinning round and round...
まわルーナ!
Mawaluna!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる笑っても
Even if we laugh round and round...
もっともっと
More, more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる踊って
Dancing round and round...
みんな
Everyone!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる踊って
Dancing round and round...
もっともっと
More, more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわって
Spinning round and round...
もっともっと
More, more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわりすぎたら
Round and round... if we spin too much...
世界の暗闇が
The darkness of the world...
みんな包む
...will wrap around everyone.
LOVE LOVE 大好き守るから
LOVE LOVE, I love you, I'll protect you.
くるくる地球はまわり始め
Round and round, the Earth starts to spin.
一億年
For one hundred million years.
いつまでもこのまま まわる
It will spin like this forever.
みんなに幸せを
Bringing happiness to everyone.
まわりつづく まわルーナ
Keep spinning, Mawaluna.
ますます社会がぐるぐるま...
Society is spinning more and more...
あれ?
Huh?
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわって もっともっと
Spinning round and round, more and more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるわらって もっともっと
Laughing round and round, more and more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるおどって もっともっと
Dancing round and round, more and more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるさわって もっともっと
Touching round and round, more and more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるわらって
Laughing round and round...
まわるーな!
Mawaluna!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわって もっともっと
Spinning round and round, more and more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわって
Spinning round and round...
ずっとずっと
Forever, forever!
まわルーナ
Mawaluna!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわってもっと
Spinning round and round, more!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるまわって... なぁ
Spinning round and round... hey.
ぐるぐるまわる まわるーな
Spinning round, Mawaluna.
ぽぽぽぽ...
Po po po po...
ぽぽぽぽ... ぽ!
Po po po po... Po!
ぽぽぽぽ...
Po po po po...
ぽっぴぽー ぽっぴぽー
Popipo, Popipo
ぽっぴぽー ぽっぴぽっぴぽっぴぽー
Popipo, Popipopipopipo...
ぽっぴぽー ぽっぴぽー
Popipo, Popipo
ぽっぴぽー！
Popipo!
ぽっぴぽー
Popipo
ぽー！
Po!
Mayday, mayday
ねぇ 声は届いてる？
Hey, is my voice reaching you?
心がきっと痛いみたい
It seems my heart surely aches.
Baby なんて魅力的
Baby, how charming.
見せるテクニックは
The technique you show...
すぐにクラクラ
...makes me dizzy instantly.
Mayday それじゃ物足りない
Mayday, that's not enough.
次にもっともっと欲張るスタイル
Next, a style that gets greedier and greedier.
Hey Hey もっと散らしてよ
Hey, Hey, scatter it more.
あなたの心に入ってたいの
I want to get inside your heart.
Ah 蜜 アマイ ワナ
Ah, honey, a sweet trap.
Ah ハマってあげようか
Ah, shall I fall for it?
Ah 自在にコントロールして
Ah, control me freely.
Ah ハズむメロディー
Ah, a bouncing melody.
フラフラって 酔ったフリの宵
Swaying, pretending to be drunk this evening.
そこまで フラフラって 酔っちゃうわ
I'll get drunk swaying that much.
麻痺の感触 絶対 負けじゃない
Numb sensation, it's absolutely not a defeat.
Fake like じゃない 罠
It's not a 'Fake like', it's a trap.
でも君のMindじゃ絶対
But in your Mind, it's absolute.
Help me だって
Saying 'Help me'.
Mayday 舵が取れないの
Mayday, I can't steer.
気持ちがモヤっと晴れないし
My feelings are hazy and won't clear up.
Baby なんかじゃいられない
I can't just be a 'Baby'.
まだまだ機能 願望BOX
Still more functions, desire BOX.
染めもチョメチョメ絶対
Dyeing too, censored, absolutely.
あるわけないじゃない
There's no way that exists.
Can not believe
愛なんてただの勘違い
Love is just a misunderstanding.
Don't like でも今のまま
Don't like, but as it is now...
大人ぶっている
...pretending to be an adult.
この感じ
This feeling.
だってもう 溶け出すような
Because already, like melting...
体温に身 任せれば
...if I surrender my body to the heat.
Don't care 私じゃないみたい
Don't care, it's like it's not me.
Ah No text me
イヤイヤ
No, no...
でも漏れちゃうくらいに
...but enough to leak out.
I want 埋もれてたいな
I want, I want to be buried in it.
でも私がNOは絶対
But my 'NO' is absolute.
Let's taste it
ねぇ どうして
Hey, why?
愛は悪戯するんだろう
I wonder why love plays tricks.
ねぇ いつかは
Hey, someday...
叶えたいのも消えるの
...will even the wish to come true disappear?
後悔は案外簡単に
Regret comes unexpectedly easily...
否定して壊れちゃうけど
...denying and breaking it, but...
いつかだけの心は
...a heart for 'someday'...
気が付くの手を伸ばしちゃって
...realizing it, reaching out a hand.
その先欲しい
I want what's beyond.
Tada...
Just...
痛い
It hurts.
此処に居たいの Cry
I want to stay here, cry.
落ち着きましょう
Let's calm down.
その手で触れてよ
Touch me with those hands.
ほら 泣いて
Look, crying.
グラグラって酔っちゃいそうな Mind
A mind that feels like it's wobbling and getting drunk.
愛刺さる罠
A trap where love pierces.
モガモガって寄っちゃったのは Ah
Struggling and drawing closer, ah...
このせいで
Because of this.
Help me
Rescue me
Save me
Mayday
どうしても溶け出す様な体温に
By the body heat that seems to melt no matter what,
身も分別きこそ外れ出したんだ
Even my body and reason have started to come undone.
もう Ask me して
Just ask me already.
Huzzah!
Hey!
Birthday, birthday!
Happy Birthday, Nerissa!
Thank you, Liz!
And, hmm, you better have a freaking wonderful rest of your day...
...because I'm... I'm monitoring you, alright?
You... you got it, Liz.
Thanks for the invite.
For Justice!
Oop. And she's gone.
Goodbye, Liz! I love you!
Good day, Nerissa Ravencroft.
Mother of my child?
Happy Birthday!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
越境にも宅にもなくグーグー
Not crossing borders or staying home, snore snore.
手に持つ少なみいざチューチュー
With little in hand, now kiss kiss.
飯は食わねば (Ah) 寝る寝るねばな
Must eat food (Ah), must sleep sleep.
Time is sleepy...
此処何処迷子で Go Go Go!
Where is this? Lost child, Go Go Go!
Dancing Darling
ジャンジャン新幹線行
Bang bang, bullet train bound.
感傷あり
Sentimental.
人類発祥何処
Where did humanity originate?
いい感じ
Feeling good.
早々商売信仰
Early belief in business.
去る者は猿 Pa Pa Pi Pa Pa!
Those who leave are monkeys, Pa Pa Pi Pa Pa!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
あわ星もはほら
The bubbles and stars, look.
此処此処これだろだら
Here, here, it's this, right?
So one, one, one one one, one!
チキチキ Wa Ha!
Chiki chiki Wa Ha!
問題世界や
Problematic world.
やっぱパパパレ
After all, Pa Pa Pa Pare.
笑ってないで踊れば Ya Ya Ya Oh
Don't just laugh, if you dance, Ya Ya Ya Oh.
反動で泣いた
Cried from the recoil.
酔うわ宛呑まれたど
Getting drunk, swallowed by the destination.
喰らおう蕎麦のせ
Let's eat, topped with soba.
アチャチャチャチャチャ Party!
Achachachachacha Party!
U wa a a i a i
気分は High トントンダン
Feeling High, ton ton dan.
U wa a a i a i
I know my eye ドンドンパン
I know my eye don don pan.
繋がってんだけど録なんだ DNA んだ
We're connected but it's recorded, it's DNA.
連覇でんと思い出去る一言
A single word leaving memories with consecutive victories.
補修いいんだ働いてんだ錬金なんだ
Repairs are fine, I'm working, it's alchemy.
休みなし毎日がいついつ金曜？
No rest, every day, when when is Friday?
Dancing Darling
ジャンジャン等身大進行
Bang bang, life-sized progression.
人類魔性
Humanity's devilish nature.
あるでしょ AI 暴走
There is, right? AI rampage.
Ah もう寂しい
Ah, already lonely.
早々怪我信仰
Early injury belief.
もう指指まで One, Two, Two
Already up to the fingers, One, Two, Two.
Liar, Liar, Dan Dan Sya
I'm die.
Thank you forever.
Oh my god, Oh my wife
ようやく信じて辿り着いた
Finally believed and arrived.
無限螺旋抜け出して
Breaking out of the infinite spiral.
Faraway, Faraway!
Happy Birthday Nerissa!
Hi!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
いつもはほら
Usually, look.
此処此処懲りたろだんな
Here, here, learned your lesson, right master?
So one, one, one one one, one!
チキチキ Wa Ha!
Chiki chiki Wa Ha!
問題世界や
Problematic world.
やっぱパパパレ
After all, Pa Pa Pa Pare.
笑ってないで踊れば Ya Ya Ya Oh
Don't just laugh, if you dance, Ya Ya Ya Oh.
反動で泣いた
Cried from the recoil.
酔うわ宛呑まれたど
Getting drunk, swallowed by the destination.
喰らおう蕎麦のせ
Let's eat, topped with soba.
アチャチャチャチャチャ Party!
Achachachachacha Party!
U wa a a i a i
気分は High トントンダン
Feeling High, ton ton dan.
U wa a a i a i
I know my eye ドンドンパン
I know my eye don don pan.
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
Nerissa! Happy Birthday!
And now, to wrap things...
This year's birthday merch!
Yeah! Wow!
Please take a look at the set. There's also...
...going to be a limited set that comes with an autographed postcard!
Wow!
So let's take a look at all the details.
First up, can you believe it?
I made a Jailbird Onesie!
Wow!
Isn't it so cute?
Ooh, it looks so warm.
It looks so comfy.
It's perfect.
If you want to let out your inner fat flock member...
...you can wear it to sleep, you can wear it out...
...you can wear it at- who cares! You wear it wherever you want.
It's a kigurumi.
So, do consider picking it up...
...please.
All right. And the next item is...
...the Jailbird Beanie!
Do you want to look cool?
Do you want to look nonchalant while also repping the Jailbirds?
Repping that fat flock?
You can with this beeping beanie!
It even has a Jailbird embroidered on it. Look at the little horns!
It's so cute!
It is so cool and cute at the same time.
And now for the third item!
Your look is so cool!
Cool as ice, I might say.
The Jailbird Ice Tray!
You can make six different Jailbird ice cubes!
They're so cute!
Look at all the expressions too!
I can't wait to use this to put this in my matcha lattes!
What do you think?
What are you gonna use it for, sis?
Uh, I don't know.
I think I'm gonna put it in matcha lattes too, but...
I think I could just put it in my wa- I could put it in anything.
You could just take 'em, you could chuck 'em too.
What?!
Not at people! But like, at the floor.
At people would be okay too.
No, no, no, no!
Not at people!
You mean-
Uncle Dad says behave!
Behave!
And with this...
...the Day-Out With Nerissa Acrylic Keychain!
You can take it along with you.
Take Nerissa everywhere you go and take cute photos!
You know, just like uh, you're uploading it to my favorite app...
...Nerissa Ravencroft.
That's the best one.
What?
It's my favorite app, Nerissa Ravencroft. So trendy.
Yeah...
Yes.
This illustration is done by my Mama as well, EB+!
Wow!
So it'd be awesome if you would share photos with this item on SNS...
...using the hashtag #DateWithNerissa.
Pretty please.
Did you just-
Never mind.
And of course...
...there's also a Birthday Set...
...that includes a postcard and a bonus voice pack!
Wow!
Along with these four items.
Only the Limited Edition comes with an autographed postcard.
So don't wait!
Get yours now for your fat flock friends!
Yeah!
Now, what's this Day-Out With Nerissa bonus voice pack like, huh?
Do you have a preview?
I guess I could tell you a little bit about it.
Ooh!
Well, it's actually based off of the illustration.
So, uh, it's a day out.
Similar to the dates that you guys came out with...
I'm going to be going on a date with the Jailbirds...
...to an amusement park!
So you can look forward to the shenanigans that ensue.
Oh, shenanigans.
Always shenanigans.
Touch grass.
Anyways, I worked really hard to come up with all this merch...
...so that everybody could enjoy it.
So be sure to grab yours as soon as it goes live!
The link will be in the description!
Yay!
Well, this turned out to be such a wonderful birthday.
Yeah!
And Advent...
I'm so happy that we could celebrate all together as well.
It made it so special for me.
Yeah!
And we also had Justice as guests too, singing with me!
So, thank you Justice for coming and celebrating with me as well.
And, most of all, thank you Jailbirds!
Yay! Happy birthday!
Thank you everyone!
Have a good day!
Bye bye!