(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Birthday Bedroom Break-In
Nerissa Ravencroft 2025
Now Loading
Nerissa...
When was the last time we saw her?
She hasn't left her room in two weeks!
Don't say this...
She doesn't love us anymore!
GATHER, my friends.
Is that... Jailboss?
Jailboss?
JAILBOSS?
Jailboss (jailboss)
Tonight, we infiltrate her bedroom.
Follow me.
I know a secret passage.
Nerissa! Nerissa!
How DARE you enter my room?
OUTSIDE!
Don't mess with a girl's sleepover!
BEGONE!
ANEMONE
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: ゆよゆっぺ
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Yuyoyuppe
運命はもろく
Fate is fragile,
愚かな結末
a foolish conclusion.
貼り付けにされた
The heart that was
心は泣いてる
crucified is crying.
両手から零れ落ちる雫が
The droplets spilling from both hands
貴方には見えていないのでしょう？
likely are not visible to you, are they?
嗚呼 ここまで
Ah, this far...
悲しい声に 言葉に 覆われて
...covered in sad voices and words.
俯いたまま 微笑む赤い花
Looking down, a red flower smiles.
深く汚れた 痛みが贖罪なら
If the deeply stained pain is atonement...
解り合えない ずっとこのまま
...we can't understand each other, forever like this.
変わらない運命
Unchanging fate,
周期は不条理
the cycle is absurd.
吐き出させられて
Forced to spit it out,
感覚の違い
the difference in sensation.
在り触れた刃を振りかざす
Brandishing a commonplace blade,
貴方には見えていないのでしょう？
likely not visible to you, are they?
嗚呼 消えない傷跡
Ah, scars that won't fade...
風も吹く夜に 知ってしまう花の色を
On a night the wind blows, I see the flower's color
貴方は知ることも きっと無いのですよ
which you surely will never come to know.
底の底まで 堕ちたら黒い景色
If you fall to the very bottom, a black landscape.
俯いたまま 泣いてた赤い花
Looking down, a red flower was crying.
朽ちていく心の中 混ざってる
Mixed within the decaying heart,
有りの侭 生きていたいと
wanting to live just as I am.
悲しい声に 言葉に 覆われて
Covered in sad voices and words,
俯いたまま 散り行く果てまで
looking down, until the end of scattering.
深く笑う 痛みが消えなくとも
Laughing deeply, even if the pain doesn't fade,
足掻き続けよう 何度だって
let's keep struggling, over and over.
想い 想いに 手を伸ばして
Reaching out to our various thoughts and feelings.
Little darling!
My love, where are you?
Hello? Are you over here?
Oh, there you are!
My darling!
Oh, you look so cute laying on my bed like that!
Isn't he just adorable?
I just want to squeeze him...
...but I'll leave him be for the time being.
Jailbirds, I have to welcome you...
...to my room as this is a very, very special day.
Do you know? Do you remember?
That today is my birthday!
In case you don't know me,
let me quick introduce myself.
Hiya darlings! This is Hololive English Advent's
devilish diva, the one, the only,
Nerissa Ravencroft!
And I'm so happy to have you in here
for my room debut!
Being able to celebrate with you guys is so amazing,
but I thought it would be more fun
if I had some friends with me!
So, I've invited some very special people today.
Would you guys please come on in?
Yay! Happy Birthday! Woohoo!
What's up you party animals?! We're in the room!
Whoa! Happy Birthday Nerissa!
And we're here today to celebrate Nerissa! Yeah!
Happy Birthday!
Thank you all for coming!
No, you're here for me, right?
Right, for me!
Wait, wait, here for your bed!
Uh, yes! What do you guys think, by the way?
It looks like you!
I'm glad! I want to show off some details
because this is... I know you guys have been here before,
but this is the Jailbirds' first ever time seeing my room.
So, let me go ahead and point out some of the details.
First, because everyone's so interested in it,
I want to highlight the bed area.
In this area, we have a lot of my personal plushies...
Cat!
...and my cat.
He does have another cat bed, but he likes to sleep there.
It's also very princess-y, right? Just like me, right?
Baby girl coded.
Baby girl coded! I also have a beautiful painting
right above my bed.
Wow! And I see something else there.
Is that a Jailbird?
No, no way!
What? Huh?
That's not a Jailbird, right?
Who knows?
Then behind me, over behind FuwaMoko,
there is this beautiful vanity area.
Yay!
It's my kind of... It makes me feel even more princess-y.
You can see there's a bust of my head because—
Wow! You have a bust made of yourself!
It's important. It's important.
I also have a Renaissance painting
scattered throughout the room, too.
You might notice them.
I have little Advent references.
Oh! I see it!
There's a Pero hiding!
Some are over here.
Up there! I have a Novelite.
And then over here, over by the vanity area,
there's a little Geo.
Yay! So cute!
Lots of little Advent references all around
for you to enjoy.
So... yeah! That's it! That's awesome, right?
That's it? All right, time to leave!
Whoa! Well, thanks for having us!
Thanks so much, we're leaving now.
Yeah! Bye!
You're leaving? What the—? You're not leaving!
I saw your cat.
I mean, okay! So, are you guys gonna have us
do anything then while we're here?
Well, I've prepared a very special game today, actually.
I think you guys are gonna have a lot of fun.
So, it's something a little out of the ordinary.
I'll protect you!
Today, you must treat me like your princesses...
Ah! Like your princess, actually.
No, I'm your princess!
No, okay! You're the princess!
And you are my prince! So, it's going to be a blind date.
You have to make my heart flutter a lot
and make me feel amazing on my birthday.
I guess it sounds like fun then!
I'm the one being rizz'd in this game.
I'm excited to see your unexpected sides.
So, I need to prep everything in my room,
so I need you all to get over there!
Get! No, no, no, just over there!
I'm gonna set up everything, okay?
In the corner!
Okay, I'm gonna set up.
Okay, what do you guys think?
Whoa! A chair!
It exists!
It kind of doesn't match the room's theme though, no?
It's fine. I'm going to be sitting...
...in this chair right here...
...and I'm going to put on a blindfold, too.
Oh! Wait! Why?
Why? Why?
Don't worry, don't worry. It's Piyanas.
Piyanas! Piyanas! Piyanas! Piyanas!
You guys can relax, okay? Relax.
And come close to me. You're so far away.
Oh!
So, on this projector here, there's going to be prompts...
...with various questions and situations will appear.
So, you all have to answer them one by one.
Your voices are going to be altered with a voice changer.
Oh! What? Is it going to be cute?
Yeah! But I'm not going to be able to know who's talking.
So, based on that, I won't have any...
...preconceptions about anyone...
...because it'll just be based on your rizz alone.
So feel free to be extra romantic, okay?
What?! Extra romantic? What's that, Shiori?
Don't worry about it!
We'll do our best to be romantic then, huh?!
Yeah! Oh!
Let's start!
The name of the game is...
Cellmate's in Love!
Yeah!
Cellmate's in Love
The questions for everyone will be displayed on the projector screen...
...so please read them carefully.
But, I must put my blindfold on now.
Oh! Okay!
Okay, so I guess she won't know who's answering.
So, the person should move quietly so she doesn't know the order.
Yeah! And plus we have a voice changer.
Yeah! Hmm...
Okay, well, we should probably line up now, huh?
Okay... who wants to go first?
I don't know...
How about... I think you should go first.
Okay. We'll continue answering in this order then.
Yeah! Okay!
Now, give us the first question!
First Date!
Rissa... it's been over two years since Rissa and I became friends...
...but I think it's time to take our relationship beyond friendship!
Whoa!
I'm scared I might ruin things, but I also really want to tell her how I feel!
So, everyone, gather your courage...
...and finally decide to ask Nerissa out on a date!
What would you say to her, and where would you like to go for your first date?
Try to ask her smoothly!
That was a lot!
Okay, so it's not just a hypothetical situation, right?
That's a lot of points, isn't it?
We all have to figure out how to ask her out.
How Nerissa hears it / Nerissaにはこう聞こえています
Okay, I'm here. Okay...
Nerissa...
You know, I've been thinking...
You're really important to me...
...and I'd like to go out somewhere special together.
And I... when we have some time, just the two of us, you know?
So, I was thinking, maybe we could go to that cafe...
...that you said you liked a few months ago? Oh, your favorite, right?
We could go there, and have a nice evening.
And then maybe, you know, once our tummies are all full...
...then we can go on a bit of a stroll.
Enjoy, you know, the city lights... maybe the water, huh?
Would you like that?
I would like that! That sounds so sweet!
Well then, it's a date. Okay?
Let's do it! So romantic!
Okay, I did my best!
You did great! Yeah!
Okay, good job, good job!
I'll go, I'll just go! Do your best, Biboo!
Yeah! Show her what you're made of!
Hey, can we lower the mic a little bit for me?
I don't think you need that. No, you're fine.
Wait, this is kind of mean, isn't it? What? What?
Deal with it! It's your date! Okay, I'm ready, I'm ready!
Hey, Nerissa...
You and me... movies tonight.
Come or don't. But if you don't...
...you're going to miss out on so much, baby.
You know what we're going to do at the movies?
We're going to pick the scariest movie ever!
And then...
I...
I am going to be such a bleeping wimp.
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to cringe at the jump scares.
I'm going to be so bleeping scared, you're going to have to comfort me.
And then you're going to have to put your arm around my shoulder and be like, "It's okay, sweetie."
You'll be fine.
And then I'm going to... I'm going to nuzzle myself into your chest.
Yeah, while you comfort me. And we're going to bond over fear.
And it's going to be the most amazing thing ever.
Wait, what?
Oh my gosh, that sounds...
Come to the movies with me, or not. It doesn't matter.
That sounds so enthralling.
Whoa! I'm kind of interested.
Sounds like a booty call.
But I'm a little scared, too.
I feel like I'm going to have to be the one comforting you.
I don't know how I feel about that.
That's the point.
Yeah, that's the point.
Well, that's a good... Okay, let's move on to the next person then, how about?
That was a good job.
Yeah, nice try.
Nice try, Koseki.
Who's next?
Then my turn! My turn!
After that you have to show off. Yeah.
Get going! Go, go!
All right, I'm waiting.
That was pretty good. Impressive.
First Date!
Nerissa... well, you know...
We've been close for a little while now.
We've gone to far-off places, right?
But we've never really been able to hang out, just the two of us, you know?
So, I think I'd really like it if it was just you and myself.
That's what I was thinking.
How Nerissa hears it / Nerissaにはこう聞こえています
Maybe we could go get a massage together?
And then afterwards, once we feel so much more relaxed and free...
We could go to a café, a café that's very special to me.
Because I know you're a little into that too.
And then we could just chat and...
...more.
More? Oh!
Oh, that sounds so fun too!
You guys are really speaking to my heart here with these cafés and dates and stuff.
I like it a lot.
I think we have one more contestant, so bachelor number four...
...will you please take the stage?
You bet so. Make it romantic.
Stomps angrily on the ground.
I would go on a date with you.
I- No thank you.
My lady, tips fedora.
Pulls out ten million dollars in cash.
Waves it under your nose. This is all for you.
And you know what? Not only that, but I have ten million roses in the ground here.
Do they all don't die, just like my love for you.
How Nerissa hears it / Nerissaにはこう聞こえています
That's how it's supposed to be.
You are as beautiful as the moon, so bright, so elegant.
So in the night sky. I love seeing you at night, man.
Sorry, what are we doing for this date?
Oh sorry, I completely forgot about the date.
Go on a date with me though!
Okay, you've convinced me.
I think all of you have successfully managed to rizz me on a date.
So there's our first question.
Yay! Good job!
Come back, come back! Let me get my cash again.
I can't tell who my favorite is yet. I think we're going to need some more questions for me to be able to pick.
More?
All right.
Let's do it.
There's more! Yay!
All right, well let's move on to the next question then!
First Date Surprise. You successfully asked Nerissa out, and she happily said yes!
Since it's our first date, we want to make her feel special and happy, right?
Of course!
Yeah, what kind of surprise do we have in store for our first date?
A surprise! Yeah, a surprise!
I'm looking forward to it.
Now the question is, are we going to continue the story of our first date?
Yeah! Maybe! Let's do that! Me too! Okay!
Okay, blindfold back on!
Again? Yay! Oh!
All right, I'm ready to be rizzed.
All right, well we're ready to rizz you.
Let's go in order of rizz then.
Okay, that means here I go!
You're so brave!
So then, during our date, while we're walking along the water at night with all the city lights around us...
Suddenly... you lose sight of me. What?
Where could she be, huh?
You feel a bit panicked,
and then suddenly you see a bunch of mascot characters.
And they're doing a little bit of a dance,
like... ah, oh, ah, oh.
And then, all of a sudden, one of them goes... Wha!
And out comes... me!
A little bit of a surprise, and I have roses.
And I say, "You're the character of my life."
"For you."
So cute!
Wow, that's so romantic,
bachelor number one.
Thank you.
Romance, yeah.
All right.
Next is...
Bijou!
Go on, my little rizz champion.
Oh, hi girls, yeah.
Steal the mic... okay, well, whatever.
All right, Nerissa, after our date, you know,
um, you have to take me home because...
I spilled my drink all over myself
from being scared because you were comforting me, right?
And so afterwards, I take you home to my place.
And you know what we're going to do?
We open the door and there's trash everywhere.
And that is my surprise,
because I know everything about you and I know that you love cleaning.
So, surprise!
My room is dirty and you have to clean it.
And you love that so much.
And that's so romantic for me.
I'm like, "Yeah, woman, clean my house."
And I'll let you...
I'll let you clean my house and you feel so strong,
you know?
You know, I do love to clean,
especially for my friends.
However, I think if I was on a romantic date,
it would not be at the top of my list.
But in the trash, there's like treasures for you
that I put in the trash, like flowers.
There's flowers in there, you'll have to...
you'll have to dig for it.
I think I'd be turned off by that.
I feel like when I found them, I might be like,
"Oh, that's cute," but I might be a little...
You did your best, so let's move on to the next one, how about that?
No one understands me.
That's real romance.
Okay, who's next?
Did you like it?
Good job.
I'm going to do my best!
Whoa!
You know, here at this cafe...
I guess you're really excited for the cakes
that we ordered, right?
And, well...
I wanted to surprise you,
and I know there's one thing that you love very much.
So...
Nerissa...
look into my eyes.
You see this here?
This is my smartphone.
SLAM! Slam on the table.
Today, I'm giving you all my attention
because you're my princess.
And today, it's just you and me.
Whoa!
The rest of the world disappears
when we're together for you?
That's such a good surprise.
I love it so far, bachelor number three.
All right, let's hear the last bachelor, shall we?
That was a good one.
Yeah.
Good job.
Thank you.
I'm sad, I'm sad.
My lady,
as we walk on the moon where our date takes place in,
I reconstructed it from the ground up.
There is an amusement park in your honor,
in your name: Nerissa Ravenland.
And there are jailbirds as far as the eye can see.
And you,
each one serves you to the utmost ability they have.
You can even step on them.
That is my surprise: an entire army just for you.
A fat flock.
Oh my gosh, that is kind of romantic.
Yeah.
But I think they do that for me regardless.
I don't think I need someone to set that up.
But they're moon birds.
They're moon jailbirds.
It's like a whole different species.
Are they like white colored too then?
Yes.
They're also maybe fatter.
Fat on my love for you.
What?
You feed them with your love?
That's how they survive.
Well, thank you, bachelor number four.
No problem.
That was awesome.
These are all awesome dates.
Even mine?
Well, it was a good attempt.
Good job.
Yeah!
Everyone did so well! Yes!
Let's move on to the next question, shall we?
Ah, but...
...even on this special date, you feel frustrated that your 'just friends' vibe has not gone away yet.
Um, now you want Nerissa to see you more than a friend...
...and you want her to think of you as like a more of like a romantic interest.
So it's time to make your move!
How are you going to do it? Say something to win her heart!
Please do win my heart, Advent!
Please!
Cellmate's in Love / Heart-Stirring
Steve!
Steve, William,
Matilda and Steve.
I'm always such a kidder.
Nerissa, my dearest,
I like you more than a friend.
Even I don't know how you feel about me,
and regardless of who you choose,
whatever makes you happy,
I will honor it and I will hope
that you will always be happy with that person,
whether it is the beautiful Matilda...
the other people I've named and forgot their names.
You're just so wonderful
and your smile is precious.
Tips fedora.
Also I might win 10 million dollars of cash
depending on how you answer.
Oh my gosh! So sweet!
That's so earnest too! Wait, I wasn't expecting
that from you, bachelor number four, Steve!
No one ever expects that with a person
with 10 million dollars.
Oh, how sweet! You guys all did so good!
I feel my heart racing for sure.
So, which one made your heart
skip a beat the most, huh?
Well, the honest answer of who
made my heart stop...
would be bachelor number two.
But I don't... it's difficult to say.
Again, it's still hard to pick.
I think we have to ask a few more questions
before I can settle on one of you.
Two more questions. So,
shall we read off the next one?
Okay, let's go to the fourth question then!
Cellmate's in Love / Love Crisis
The sweetest days you longed for with Nerissa...
It's been two years since you finally confessed
your love. Two years.
And embraced something truly special
between the two of you.
Everything seemed perfect, like a dream
you never wanted to end.
But a tiny mistake on your part sparked
a huge fight between the two of you.
With all your heart, apologize
for the wrong you've done,
and strive together to overcome this trial
that threatens your love.
So we've been dating for two years
and you guys have upset me.
So, won't you please apologize
and make it all better?
I'll put my blindfold back on,
so make things right between us, okay, you four?
Alright, bachelor number one, it's your turn.
Okay, here I go!
Nerissa...
How Nerissa hears it.
I'm sorry.
I know I hurt you very deeply with all my...
Well, it wasn't meant to be like this but
ultimately it turned out this way.
My indecisiveness...
My lack of action...
I know that you, the love of my life...
I should've done it.
I should've already proposed to you.
Already have made you mine long before, but...
I'm sorry for hurting you this way.
For hurting you at your core, in your heart so deeply.
Could you ever forgive me?
What a cutie!
Still bachelor number one, you managed
to be so earnest and sweet.
You're really reaching to my heart.
Let's move on to bachelor number two
and see what sort of answer they're going to give.
Hey Nerissa. I know I was gaming with the boys
and then you walked in and you wanted attention.
And I was like, "5 minutes, I can't pause the game,
it's an online game, Nerissa!"
And then you went away crying.
But after the gaming session, I was like, "Hmm,
maybe I did do something wrong..."
Maybe I should've invited her
to play game with me.
So I'm going to do something that I've never
done ever once in my life...
apologize.
Never apologized to anyone ever,
and I'm going to apologize to you now, so listen.
Sorry I guess.
If you want to be my player 2,
I'll play with you instead of the boys.
Mwah! Come here baby girl.
Yeah.
That's... I think that's good, Bachelor Number 2.
Let's move on to Bachelor Number 3.
Oh yeah, she loved that.
Alright, Bachelor Number 3 to the mic, please.
Hey.
I know things have been a little weird recently, huh?
I wanted to say something.
Nerissa...
...I'm sorry.
I know, you know, maybe I was acting a little childish.
I kept on saying things...
...like you're stinky.
Heh?
You know, maybe you took that personally, but...
...it's just, I was teasing you.
Because I love you!
I love you, Nerissa Ravencroft!
I'm sorry.
And I just wanted to say is that... you're stinky.
But...
...I love it. I love your stink!
That's enough!
Let's move to the last bachelor, Bachelor Number 4.
That was pretty good.
What the heck? That was great! What a beautiful stench.
Okay, last one.
Hey, Nerissa.
It's me, one of the boys.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry that...
...the other person and I were gaming instead of giving you attention.
Hello?
We were just having so much fun playing games together.
I should have been focused on you.
I'm crying right now!
Nerissa, I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry, as one of the boys.
This is your fitting apology.
Thank you.
I guess in your universe I have two boyfriends?
I'm dating both you and Bachelor Number 2.
I forgive you for that, by the way.
I'm just gonna forgive you.
Oh, very understanding lover.
It's understanding, we were gaming too hard!
I know, I know!
It was so great!
Sugoi guy over here!
Well, I think I'm getting closer to my answer...
of which one of these lovely bachelors I'm going to pick.
But I think we're going to maybe need one more question.
One?
Oh, one more!
Okay! Wow!
Let's move on to the final question!
And after this one, Nerissa makes her decision about who she chooses!
So Nerissa, please answer carefully, okay?
Choose from the heart, okay?
I will.
Mm-hmm. From the heart.
Yeah, in fact, Nerissa, why don't you read the final question so you can finally see.
Oh, I see. Okay.
Question number five: My Eternity.
This is your moment, bachelors.
Make the ultimate marriage proposal to me.
Marriage proposal? I've never made a marriage proposal before!
Now's the time.
So let me put my blindfold back on...
and I'm looking forward to seeing your answers... or hearing them.
Two years and she still can't see us.
Um, you know... the marriage proposal...
...should we really be going to the mic?
I guess you guys can do whatever you'd like.
Bachelor Number 1, will you approach?
Thinking... slowly... thinking...
Bachelor Number 1, do you not love me or something?
Where are you?
It's such a special day, we've been out to dinner at my favorite restaurant.
Are you standing me up on such a special day?
Nerissa Ravencroft?
Yes.
What's so funny?
Will you marry me?
Yes!
Just like that? Just like that? Please! Please!
Yes! Yes!
She said yes!
YES!
Congratulations!
I mean, we've been dating for two years.
What do you mean?
We're getting married!
We're getting married with Bachelor Number Two!
This is your moment...
Make the ultimate marriage proposal!
Boom.
I tossed something on the ground, pick it up.
I know you're blindfolded, pick it up anyway.
Pick it up.
What?
It was a ring!
I put a ring on your finger!
We're engaged!
It looks like handcuffs!
Someone help!
We're engaged now!
Help! Don't ring!
That's the wrong hand!
I will marry you!
Get out of here!
Go!
Get out!
That was so scary!
I'm so scared!
Gotta go comfort her now.
Yeah, please, no more harassment, Bachelors.
Let's move on to Bachelor Number Three please.
No more Bachelor Number Two.
Bachelor Number Three, please.
Don't let us be apart.
Many seasons that have passed since we met...
Many memories, hard times...
Beautiful times.
Many tears we shed together...
We watched the sunrise.
I'd like to spend many more sunrises...
And sunsets together.
Will you be my everything?
Yes!
Oh, that was so sweet!
Bachelor Number Three...
You're so sweet!
I don't feel like I should clap.
Alright.
You don't have to.
It's okay.
We have one more contestant.
Bachelor Number Four, would you please...
Approach?
What's going on?
My bro.
Yes?
You are like the bro-est of my life.
Wait, what the heck's going on?
Thanks.
We've been gaming for like two years or more.
Yeah, bro, we have.
I know.
Wow.
I love playing farming games with you.
Hello?
I love playing shooting games with you.
You are my number two, or my number one even.
I'll be your number two.
Hello?
You're just... I just love you so much, my bro.
Whoa, thanks, bro.
Will you marry me?
Well, I think I'm disqualified!
Bachelor Number Four, get out of here!
They're married!
Oh my god!
Get out!
And with that, the questions are through.
She can come to the wedding though.
We've had some awesome love stories,
Awesome maybe, if you can call it that, love stories born.
Some good, some bad.
From one to four!
Who did you like the most?
Please give us the number, Nerissa!
Yeah, who is the most romantic?
I'm gonna go backwards, actually.
I think it's obvious which Bachelor did NOT steal my heart today.
Oh, that way, huh?
Bachelor Number Two, step forward.
You're disqualified!
Alright, Bachelor Number Four, step forward.
Somehow I feel like I knew it was you two.
I don't know what you're talking about!
Come on, wifey!
This is the hard part now.
I'm between Bachelors Number One and Bachelor Number Three.
Who stole my heart the most?
Was it the earnest Bachelor Number One?
Or the very sweet Bachelor Number Three who seemed to know me best?
Ah, I can't decide!
But if I had to pick between this impossible decision...
I'd have to pick Bachelor Number Three!
You can join the marriage!
It's okay!
You can join with me!
It's okay, you can join!
Yeah, we're married!
It's okay!
Join the marriage!
But I must say,
Knowing that each of you thought so deeply about a life with me,
Except some of you maybe...
It makes me feel so special on my special day.
So thank you for warming my heart.
Congrats!
Happy Birthday!
Happy birthday, I guess.
Rissa!
You're so fluffy!
I love you!
Ah... what a wonderful birthday this is.
I've even found a wonderful partner!
It feels like this next year of my life is going to be so amazing!
I know, my baby!
Hey, the blind date is over!
Snap back to reality. Oh, let's play Twister!
Oh, yeah!
I got Twister ready so we can all play together!
Looking at it, it might be a bit tricky for all five of us to play at once though.
Yeah, I think you might be right.
What should we do then?
Um... well, how about to make it fun, we can play one at a time?
You know what, actually, I've just thought of a special rule for today!
Let's call the game: Posing Twister!
Posing Twister
As the name suggests, the rule is to strike poses while playing Twister.
For example, if the instruction says:
"Right hand on red, and cat pose", you place your right hand on red and do the cat pose.
Once all four limbs are in position, you can move just one limb to strike the specific pose.
The time limit will be one minute, and if you can keep your balance for the full minute, you can clear the challenge.
But, if you lose your balance at any point, the game is over.
Quick question!
Yes?
Can audience mess with the player?
Yeah, why not?
So, who wants to go first?
I'll go first! Ok, Mococo-chan!
I'll go first! Ok, I'll go, Mococo-chan!
I'll show you how it's done, okay?
I'll try my best to distract you, so good luck!
I've never played Twister before.
Really?
It's her first time then!
Well, you've got one minute, okay?
Do your best.
We ready?
Then let's start!
Okay!
Okay, first up, left foot on green and wolf pose!
Left foot on green, wolf pose!
Okay, next, right hand on red and cat pose!
Right hand on red, cat pose!
That was some pretty fast poses!
Right hand, faster, faster!
Left foot on blue, cow pose!
All right, right hand on red and hero pose!
Right hand on red, hero pose!
Right hand on red and a hero!
Oh, I thought my right hand is on red.
Oh, right hand on red again. I can't help it!
Left hand on yellow and happy pose!
Left hand on yellow, happy pose!
So happy, happy, happy!
Now place your left foot on yellow and express anger!
Left foot on yellow, angry pose!
I'm furious! So much rage!
You did so good!
Rissa, it feels like I'm split apart! Help! Help!
All right, Mococo! You passed with flying colors.
Don't fall, you okay?
Good job, Mococo!
All right, who's next? Mococo?
You get to choose!
Bijou! I want Bijou!
Because you made fun of me at the beginning!
Okay!
Because of that, I'm going to be your biggest distraction, okay?
Okay, how about I tell Bijou what to do then?
Okay! All right, let's start!
Right foot on blue... okay...
Right foot on blue, graceful queen pose!
Now give me a graceful queen pose!
Oh my! Okay, Miss Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Left foot on blue, lion pose!
Left foot on blue...
...now do a lion pose.
(Roaring)
Left hand on red, rabbit pose!
Left hand on red...
...give me a rabbit pose.
Rabbit?
What does the rabbit say?
Figure it out! I'm not a rabbit!
Peko! Peko!
Right foot on green, BAUBAU!
Now place your right foot on green...
...and go BAUBAU!
BAUBAU! BAUBAU! BAUBAU!
Left foot on red, "grr" pose!
Left foot on red...
Oh... figure it out!
Now give us your best grr pose!
Grrr!
Right hand on blue, kawaii pose!
Right hand on blue...
Okay!
Now kawaii! Go kawaii!
はず、かわいいですよ！かわいいから許して！
That's embarrassing! Forgive me because I'm being cute!
Fair enough for me.
You didn't lose your balance, but I didn't think that was a very cute pose at the end.
What about you guys?
But you did your best. Good job, Biboo!
Okay, good pose. All right, you pick who's next, Biboo.
Um... Okay, Shiori, you go next.
Okay, tell me what to do.
All right, boss-mare round!
Okay Shiori, are you ready?
I guess so.
Let's start!
Left foot on yellow, baby pose!
Left foot...
Yeah, left...
...put it on yellow.
Yellow, got it.
And now you're going to show us baby Shiori!
(Baby crying sounds)
Left foot on yellow, horse pose!
Okay, now, again, left foot on yellow.
Horse pose!
Neigh! Neigh!
That's a nice horse! More neigh!
Right hand on blue, coolest prince pose!
Okay, next is right hand on blue.
Got it.
And now give us your coolest prince pose.
Well, will you marry me then, dear?
Right foot on yellow, witch pose!
Okay, and let's top this: right foot on yellow...
Okay.
...and witch pose!
This is my broom somewhere here.
Okay, there's a broom here.
Left hand on red, bear pose!
Okay, now left hand on red.
Okay.
And do a bear pose!
I am already in bear pose. Grrr!
Right hand on yellow, butterfly pose!
Okay, you're going to take your right hand and put it onto yellow.
Okay.
And you're going to do a butterfly pose!
I am wiggling like a butterfly!
I am flying into the breeze!
You got it!
Woo! Good job, Shiori! Thank you!
That was fun! Yeah, you did so good, Shiori!
Wow, you guys are all so good at this!
I know! I don't know...
You'll do great! FuwaMoco, I think you're up!
Okay! I don't know if I'm going to be as good as everybody else.
You've got this! It's my first time too!
Mine too! Okay, FuwaMoco, go on.
Do your best now, BAUBAU!
Okay, let's start!
Right foot on green, hula dance move!
Ah... okay. Right foot on green...
...and do a hula dance move!
Right foot on green.
Yeah, right.
Okay... Woo!
Left foot on yellow, dolphin pose!
Left foot on yellow for a dolphin pose!
I don't even need water! Dolphin!
Oh! So good!
Right hand on red, fighting pose!
Next, right hand on red, fighting pose!
Right hand on red. Good luck!
Good luck with that!
Ah... I can't!
Oh no! You can do it! Fight, fight!
You have to do it! Go, go!
You almost have it! You almost have it!
Your foot! Your foot! Your foot!
Okay, okay, next.
Right foot on yellow, puppy pose!
That's her default!
You can't take your hands off! What do you mean?
Right foot, right foot, right foot!
BAUBAU! BAUBAU!
Well, that's going to have to do!
All right! I made it!
And she made it! You did really good! My cute puppy!
All right, Nerissa, it's your turn now.
Okay, I'm ready to... I've got this.
I'm ready to blow you all out of the water!
What? Whoa!
Think you can? No, I don't actually.
All right, show us your flexibility.
Are you ready? I'm ready!
Let's start!
Left foot on green, sexy pose!
All right, first up, left foot on green with a...
...sexy pose!
Left foot on green, sexy pose!
Alright!
Right foot on yellow, even sexier!
Left hand on blue, wet cat Rissa pose!
Right foot on green, sea lion pose!
Right hand on blue, do one push-up!
Left hand on red, octopus pose!
Left foot on blue, pirate pose!
You guys did so good!
Thank you!
How do you like my posing everyone?
Beautiful!
Can we all do a sexy pose together?
Sexy pose everyone!
One, two...
Again! One, two, three!
Okay, one more! One, two, three!
Very nice ladies!
That's enough fun though.
Yeah, I think we're done with Twister.
Actually, I was thinking maybe we could do karaoke together.
Oh my god! Yeah!
Alright, let's do it! Karaoke!
And now, please enjoy... Dark Breath!
You don't want it more, want it more.
You don't love it now, love it...
Cause I'm あどけなき支配は始まった
Cause I'm, the innocent domination has begun
今も欠けたのは Why you don't know
What's missing even now, why you don't know
危なくないはずよ
It shouldn't be dangerous
そして 息も出来ない響き
And the sound that takes my breath away
成功補導なまま
While being guided by success
捕まえてみなよ 影形もない舞
Try and catch me, this formless dance
I'm so crazy crazy love
半信半疑だったボディ wanna know know
My skeptical body, wanna know know
鼓動に従って
Follow the heartbeat
本性見せてよ 今こそ
Show your true self, right now
Baby don't let me down
None of killing me 足りてないのよ
None of killing me, it's not enough
Yes Dark Breath 感じるでしょう
Yes, Dark Breath, you feel it, don't you?
革命的存在感
Revolutionary presence
逸脱 全て 奪い取れ
Deviate from everything, take it all away
吹き荒って
Blow violently
あざやかな言葉 並べ立てて
Line up vivid words
何もないことくらい Baby I know
I know baby, that there's nothing there
程々にしておきなよ
Don't overdo it
抱え込む事を受け入れた 艶やかな Flower
The glossy flower that accepted holding it all
知りながら 臆病に潜む姿
While knowing, hiding cowardly
He behaves like a spider
翻弄されればいい その身を委ねて
Let yourself be toyed with, surrender your body
目覚めさせるなよ Only I can breathe
Don't wake me up, only I can breathe
I never let you down
Gotta be kidding me 足りてないのよ
Gotta be kidding me, it's not enough
Yes Dark Breath 感じるでしょう
Yes, Dark Breath, you feel it, don't you?
運命的衝動
Fateful impulse
It's Dark Breath 大最高潮
It's Dark Breath, the grand climax
言わせて
Let me say it
未来 未来 なろ見出す
Future, future, finding it out
以外 じゃない I'm a genius
It's not anything else, I'm a genius
前世 全能 like a Jesus
Previous life, omnipotent like a Jesus
待ちわびていた
Waiting for so long
導きのすべて アンソマリー
Everything that guides us, Anthomary
So worry... So worry...
誰もが羨む桃源郷へと Change
Change to the Shangri-La that everyone envies
(Crazy crazy love)
形相は煩土 手段を厭わず
In appearance, it's a land of suffering, not sparing any means
凡才に私呈す音
I present this sound to the mediocre
誰もが気付かれぬけど
Nobody notices, though
Dirty Little Love...
La la pa pa pa...
Gotta be kidding me くせになるでしょう？
Gotta be kidding me, it's addictive, right?
La la pa pa pa...
ノリにのって 揺られてないのよ
I'm not just riding the groove
Oh no...
Yes Step... Presence... Jealousy...
普通じゃいられないの
I can't be normal
It's Gold Breath, let it open more
澄ませて...
Listen closely...
La la pa pa pa...
Wow! Nerissa! Are you ready?
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん？
How about Paipai Kamen?
未来恋の果て 伸ばされた手
At the end of future love, an outstretched hand
テレフォン運命の 鐘の山
A mountain of bells of telephone fate
あいつの気配が するものは
Things that feel like him
未練ばかりで 悔やしあない
I don't regret it, it's just lingering affection
あださいきながら 化けて出る
I'll come back to haunt you while I'm still alive
鏡の前で 早変わり
A quick change in front of the mirror
パイパイ仮面で どうかしらん
How about Paipai Kamen?
今宵も ひとあばれ
Tonight as well, a little rampage
踊れ 踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance, dance
乱れ髪 はずむ胸
Disheveled hair, bouncing heart
透明の罠に 酔いしれて
Drunk on a transparent trap
Shine Spark! Shine Spark!
Shine Spark! ライナミナ
Shine Spark! Rai-na-mi-na
パイ パパイ パ パパパイ パ パイ
Pie Pa-pie Pa Pa-pa-pie Pa Pie
パイパイ仮面は 大富豪
Paipai Kamen is a billionaire
パイ パパイ パ パパパイ パ パイ
Pie Pa-pie Pa Pa-pa-pie Pa Pie
おこがましいわ 舞い上がれ
How presumptuous, soar high
ほら ほら 踊れや
Hey, hey, dance
万歳 万歳 恋のシャワー
Banzai, Banzai, shower of love
切なく 生きろよ
Live with sorrow
瞬間クライマックス
Instant climax
憂き世 忘れて 捨てる
Forget this fleeting world and cast it away
ダンシング・ハイ！ パイパパイヤ
Dancing High! Paipapaiya
ディスコティック・クイーン Ah パイパイ仮面
Discotheque Queen, Ah, Paipai Kamen
Wow! Ha!
Singing this song together, what do we both have in common?
Um, uh... Come on, you say it.
Okay... um... Pie! Pie!
悪い奴だとは 知りつつも
Even though I know you're a bad guy
恋は盲目 とめどなく
Love is blind, without end
愛のために 血も凍らした
For love, even my blood froze
私は どんな道化師さ
What kind of clown am I?
虫かごの 蝶を飛ばさなきゃ
I have to let the butterfly out of the cage
虫けらのままで 終わっちまう
Otherwise I'll just end up as a worm
パイパイ仮面が 毒放つ
Paipai Kamen releases poison
今宵も 羽ばたくよ
Tonight as well, I'll take flight
喰らえ 喰らえ 喰らえ
Eat this, eat this, eat this
ケダモノよ 癖物よ
You beast, you trickster
ぱっと 目ェ覚めた あてられぬ
My eyes popped open, I can't be influenced
Shine Spark! Shine Spark!
Shine Spark! ライナミナ
Shine Spark! Rai-na-mi-na
パイ パパイ パ パパパイ パ パイ
Pie Pa-pie Pa Pa-pa-pie Pa Pie
パイパイ仮面は ボンキュッボン
Paipai Kamen has an hourglass figure
パイ パパイ パ パパパイ パ パイ
Pie Pa-pie Pa Pa-pa-pie Pa Pie
視線の先を 叫んでいる
Shouting at the gaze
ドンドコ 揺らせよ
Don-doko, shake it
ラストアワーに バイブレーション
Vibration in the last hour
さあ 行け 煮染まれや
Come on, go, get soaked
うたかた バブル・モーション
Ephemeral bubble motion
一瞬で 全て入る
Everything goes in an instant
ダンシング・ハイ！ パイパパイヤ
Dancing High! Paipapaiya
ディスコティック・クイーン Ah パイパイ仮面
Discotheque Queen, Ah, Paipai Kamen
今日も あいつは どこかの国で
Today as well, he's in some country
どんな悪さ してるやら
Doing who knows what evil
私は いつでも あんたの見方
I'm always on your side
あいつは...
He is...
疲れ果てた時には戻っておいで
When you're exhausted, come back here
おいでー
Come here!
バイバイ　バイバイ　バイバイバイバイバイ
Bye bye, bye bye, bye-bye-bye-bye bye
バイバイ仮面大富豪
Bye bye masked tycoon
バイバイ　バイバイ　バイバイバイバイバイ
Bye bye, bye bye, bye-bye-bye-bye bye
黄金の蝶舞い上がれ
Fly high, golden butterfly
ホイサ　ホイサ　ドッコイショ
Hoisa hoisa dokkoisho
万歳万歳恋慕（こい）しや
Banzai banzai, how I long for love
デタラメを生きろよ
Live a reckless life
瞬間クライマックス
Instant climax
憂き世　忘れてふける Dancing High
Forget this transient world and get lost in the Dancing High
バイバイバイ
Bye bye bye
ディスコティック・クイーン　あぁバイバイ仮面
Discotheque Queen, ah, bye bye masked one
ぐるぐる＠まわる＠まわルルナ
Spinning @ Round @ Spinning Luna
まわるまわるまわるまわルルナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning, spinning Luna
まわるまわる地球を回してぐるぐる
Spinning and spinning, spinning the earth round and round
またたく間に街中が
In the blink of an eye, the whole town
まわるまわる頭クラクラ
Spins and spins, making my head giddy
幕が上がり祭りの始まり
The curtain rises, the festival begins
まわるまわる迷子になったら
Spinning and spinning, if you get lost
グルグルグルグルまわって　もっとグルグルまわって
Spinning round and round and round and round, spin even more
グルグルグルグルまわって　もっとグルグルまわルルナ
Spinning round and round and round and round, spin even more, Luna
まわりすぎたなら
If you spin too much
世界の暗闇が
The darkness of the world
みんなを包み
Will wrap everyone up
呼ぶ、乱舞　ダイブ　回るから
Calling, dancing wildly, diving, because we spin
まわるまわる地球は回り始め幾億年
Spinning and spinning, the earth began to turn billions of years ago
いつまでもこのまま回るみんなに幸せを
May everyone be happy, spinning like this forever
まわり続けるまわルルナ
It keeps spinning, spinning Luna
ますます社会がグルグルまー
Society is spinning more and more—
あれ？
Huh?
グルグルグルグルまわって　もっとグルグルまわって
Spinning round and round and round and round, spin even more
グルグルグルグルまわってみんなグルグルまわって
Spinning round and round and round and round, everyone spin even more
グルグルグルグルまわって　もっとグルグルまわって
Spinning round and round and round and round, spin even more
グルグルグルグルまわって　もっとグルグルまわルルナ
Spinning round and round and round and round, spin even more, Luna
グルグルグルグルまわって　もっとグルグルまわって
Spinning round and round and round and round, spin even more
グルグルグルグル踊ってみんなグルグル踊って
Spinning round and round and round and round, everyone dance round and round
グルグルグルグルそうやって　もっとグルグルまわって
Spinning round and round and round and round like that, spin even more
グルグルグルグルまわって　もっとグルグルまわルルナ
Spinning round and round and round and round, spin even more, Luna
グルグルまわるまわルルナ！
Spinning and turning, it's spinning Luna!
ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po
ぽぽい！ぽぽい！
Po-poi! Po-poi!
ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po
ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ ぽ！ぽ！
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po Po! Po!
ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po
ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ ぽ！ぽ！
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po Po! Po!
ぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽぽ
Po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po-po
（笑い声）
(Laughing)
mayday, mayday
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Junky
メーデー 恋は届いてる？
Mayday, is my love reaching you?
心がズキッと痛いみたい
It feels like my heart is stinging
ベイビー なんて魅力的
Baby, how attractive
魅せるテクニックはすぐにクラクラ
Your techniques make me dizzy instantly
メーデー それじゃ物足りない
Mayday, that's not enough
次にもっともっと欲張るスター
Next, I'll be an even greedier star
ヘイヘイ もっと焦らしてよ
Hey hey, tease me more
あなたの心に入っていたいの
I want to enter your heart
ア・ミズイ・ア・アマ・アイ・ワナ
A-mizui a-ama I wanna
ア・ハマってあげようか
Ah, shall I fall for you?
ア・自在に感情
Ah, my emotions at will
露出して痛い
Exposing them hurts
はずなのに
Even though it shouldn't
フラフラで酔いちゃいそうな
Feeling dizzy and about to get drunk
甘い匂いに誘われて
Lured by a sweet scent
フラフラで酔いちゃいそうな
Feeling dizzy and about to get drunk
羽の休め場所を探して
Searching for a place to rest my wings
逃げたい わけじゃなくて
It's not that I want to run away
フラフラしちゃうじゃない
But I'm getting all dizzy
分かっても 君の前じゃ絶対
Even if I know, when I'm in front of you, definitely
Help me stay!
メーデー 舵が取れないの
Mayday, I can't steer
気持ちがモヤっと晴れないし
My feelings are hazy and won't clear
メーデー なんていられない
Mayday, I can't just stay like this
まだ秘密の合図 染め模様
Still a secret signal, a dyed pattern
絶対 あれはわけじゃない
That's definitely not the reason
鏡の中だけの勘違い
Just a misunderstanding in the mirror
将来 なんていらないわ
I don't need a future
大人びて見えぬこの感情
These emotions that don't look mature
弾けて 溶け出すような
Like popping and melting away
太陽に見舞われて
Encountering the sun
壊して 私じゃないわ
Break it, it's not me
Don't miss me stay!
イヤイヤ でも寝ちゃうくらいに
No no, but enough to fall asleep
足元 踏まれてて
Stepped on my feet
何でも 私側絶対
Anything, on my side, definitely
Let me stay!
ねえ どうして
Hey, why
愛はいたずらするんだろう
Does love play tricks?
ねえ いつかは
Hey, will it someday
叶いたいもの 消えるの？
The things I want to come true, will they vanish?
本来は案外簡単に
Originally, it's surprisingly easy
否定して壊せちゃうけど
To deny and break it
歪なこの感情が
But these distorted emotions
気が付くと手を伸ばしちゃって
Before I know it, I'm reaching out
その度 苦しくて
And each time, it's painful
...もっと奪ってよ プラスチック・ラブ
...Gimme more of that plastic love
痛い 居たいのさ Cry
It hurts, I want to be here, Cry
落ち着く場所
A place to settle down
ほら 連れ出してよ ほら Mayday
Look, take me away, look, Mayday
グラグラで酔っちゃいそうな名前に...
To a name that seems like it'll make me dizzy...
...誘われて
...being invited
ほらほら 酔っちゃうわ あぁ もう正体...
Look, look, I'm getting drunk, ah, my true identity...
Help me, help me
Rescue me, rescue me
Save me, save me
Mayday, rescue me
だって もっと 目立っちゃいたいのに もっと...
Because I want to stand out more, even more...
...外れ出したいんだ もう Mayday
...I want to start breaking away, Mayday
して
Do it
Huzzah! Whoo! Hey!
Birthday, birthday!
Happy Birthday, Nerissa!
Thank you, Liz!
And, hmm, you better have a freaking wonderful rest of your day,
because I'm monitoring you, alright?
You got it, boss!
Thanks for the invite!
For Justice! Oh!
Ack! And she's gone.
Goodbye, Liz! I love you!
Good day, Nerissa Ravencroft, mother of my child!
Happy Birthday!
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up! Uh-huh!
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up!
一向に待っても二向に待ってもグーグー
No matter how long I wait, I'm snoring
転に待つ少なめ 岬純情
A little less waiting in reverse, Cape pure heart
飯は食わねば あぁ 寝るねるねば
Must eat food, ah, must sleep sleep
I'm sleepy...
ここどこ 迷子で Go Go Go
Where am I? Lost, Go Go Go
ダンスィン ダーリン チャンチャン進化志向
Dancing Darling, orientation for evolution
感傷あり ジンルイ発症どこ
Sentimental, where did humanity originate?
あぁいい感じ 騒騒終盤戦行こう
Ah, feels good, let's go to the noisy final battle
去る者は追わざる パッパピポ
Don't chase those who leave, pappa pipo
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up!
はわはわしちゃってほら
I'm flustered, look
こらこら 出たのだのだ
Hey hey, it came out
ワン ワン ワン ワン ワン！ チキチキワンワン
Woof woof woof woof woof! Chiki chiki woof woof
脳内全世界 あっぱれ
The whole world in my brain, bravo
笑ってないで 踊れば イヤイヤオー
Don't just laugh, if you dance, iya iya oo
バンザイナイナイ 突破せ飲まれど
Hurray, no no, break through even if swallowed
クラウソバッセ 熱い じゃないじゃない パーティー
Cloud sobasse, it's hot, isn't it? Party
ウッハ ウッハ アイアイ 気分はハイ
Uh-ha uh-ha ai-ai, feeling high
トントントン ウッハ ウッハ アイアイ
Tap tap tap, uh-ha uh-ha ai-ai
アイノーマイアイ ドンドンパン
I know my eye, don don pan
繋がってんだ記録なんだ 人類なんだ蓮弁
We're connected, it's a record, it's humanity
冬もいないの去る人か
There's no winter, are you a person who leaves?
報酬インだ働いてんだ 連勤なんだ いついつ金曜
Reward is in, I'm working back-to-back shifts
ワンチャン合意 チャンチャン登場志向
One-chance agreement, orientation for appearance
人類末梢 あるでしょう AI 暴走
Human peripheral, there will be AI rampage
あぁもう殺伐 早々経過進行
Ah, already bloodthirsty, progress quickly
もうユピユピまで One two two ライオライオだんだんさあ
Even to yupi yupi, One two two, raioraio come on
I'm dying! Thank you forever! Wark!
Oh my God, oh my life, ようやくして辿り着いた
Oh my God, oh my life, finally reached it
無限螺旋 欲望して Run away, Run away
Infinite spiral, desiring, Run away, Run away
Happy Birthday Nerissa! Rawr!
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up! Pu-pu-pu-pow!
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up! Whoo!
ハワハワしちゃってほら
I'm flustered, look
こらこら 出たのだのだ
Hey hey, it came out
Next up!
Let's go ahead and introduce this year's birthday merch!
Yay!
Please take a look at the set.
There's also gonna be a limited set that comes with an autographed postcard!
Wow!
So let's take a look at all the details.
First up,
can you believe it?
I made a Jailbird onesie!
Isn't it so cute?
It looks so fluffy.
It looks so comfy.
It's perfect if you want to let out your inner Fat Flock member.
You can wear it to sleep,
you can wear it out, you can wear it...
Who cares? You wear it wherever you want. It's a kigurumi!
So, do consider picking it up, please.
All right!
And then the next item is...
the Jailbird beanie!
Do you want to look cool?
Do you want to look nonchalant while also repping the Jailbirds?
Repping the Fat Flock?
Now you can with this beepin' beanie! It even has a Jailbird embroider on it.
Look at the little horns!
They're so cute!
It's so cool and cute at the same time.
And now for the third item.
Yo, this is so cool!
Cool as ICE, I might say, the Jailbird ice tray!
You can make six different Jailbird ice cubes.
They're so cute! Look at all those expressions too.
I can't wait to use this and put this in my matcha lattes.
What do you think? What are you going to use it for, Shiori?
Uh, I don't know. I think I'm going to put it in matcha lattes too.
But I think I could just put it in my water, I could put it in anything.
You could just take them, you could chuck 'em too.
Not at people, but like, at the floor.
At people would be okay too.
No, no, no! Not at people, you meanie!
Mococo-chan, save us!
Next one!
And with this, the 'Day-Out With Nerissa' acrylic keychain.
You can take it along with you, take Nerissa everywhere you go,
and take cute photos!
You know, just like you're uploading it to my favorite app,
Nerissa Ravencroft.
That's the best one!
Her favorite app says 'Nerissa Ravencroft'!
Yes! This illustration is done by my mama as well!
So it'd be awesome if you would share photos with this item on SNS
using the hashtag #DateWithNerissa, please.
Did you just...
Never mind.
And of course,
there's also a birthday set that includes a postcard and a bonus voice pack,
along with these four items. Only the limited edition comes with an autographed postcard.
So don't wait, get yours now for your Fat Flock friends.
Yes!
Now, what's this 'Day-Out With Nerissa' bonus voice pack like, huh? Do you have a preview?
I guess I could tell you a little bit about it.
Well, it's actually based off of the illustration.
So, uh, it's a day out, similar to the dates that you guys came out with.
I'm going to be going on a date with the Jailbirds to an amusement park.
So you can look forward to the shenanigans that ensue.
Shenanigans! Always shenanigans.
Anyways, I worked really hard to come up with all this merch so that everybody could enjoy it.
So be sure to grab yours as soon as it goes live. The link will be in the description.
Well, this turned out to be such a wonderful birthday!
Yes!
And Advent, I'm so happy that we could celebrate all together as well, it made it so special for me.
Yay! Happy birthday, Nerissa!
And, we also had Justice as guests too, singing with me.
So thank you Justice for coming and celebrating with me as well.
And, most of all, thank you Jailbirds!
Thank you everyone! Happy birthday!
Bye-bye!
Jailbirds, thank you for coming to my 3rd BIRTHDAY here in hololive!
You've truly made the last few years of my life so incredibly memorable.
I can't wait to see where this next year of my life with Advent, hololive, and you takes me!
Thanks for always supporting me, and let's keep doing our best!!!
-Nerissa