(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
birthday!
Aah... aah...
Hello everybody!
Hi, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Hello!
聞こえますか？
Can you hear me?
You can! You're reacting like you can hear me. Hello!
Oh hey! Oh hey! Not funny seeing you here, huh?
Funny seeing me here, hmm? Ha!
Happy birthday Gura. Thank you!
That's right, today is my birthday.
My 9,000-bazillionth birthday.
Wow, you guys, thank you!
Happy birthday Goomba. Thank you!
Happy birthday... Can't hear you.
Are you lying to me?
Okay. No, how would you be lying to me? Because...
Well anyway... well anyway, I hope you can hear me.
Happy birthday Gura.
Wow, look at that sea of green!
Wow, look at all the green!
皆さんありがとうございます！
Thank you everyone!
Oh wow! I wish we could change the color.
Imagine if we could change that to a sea of blue instead of a sea of green.
That would be a lot... uh... well, more aesthetically pleasing... uh... for me...
...but I guess maybe not for everybody.
I'm sure Fauna really likes it when it's green instead of blue, but I don't know.
Fauna's cute.
Um... WOW!
Stop!
すごい！
Sugoi!
Um... I'm nervous again,
but what is new?
You thought that was over,
but it's not.
I'm still incredibly nervous sitting here in my fish tube.
Actually I was thinking about it...
...me and this fish tube that I'm right here in, you know?
What if it's actually like just the very large intestine
of a much larger fish?
Um... mm. Mm.
That could potentially,
that could potentially be what the situation is.
What if we all are just in the large intestine
of a much larger fish on the Earth?
Like a meatball?
Never mind, we don't have to talk about this anyway.
Thank you guys so much!
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you, everyone!
I've been watching all of your, uh,
birthday fan arts coming in, you guys.
Thank you, uh, so much.
I really appreciate, uh, what everybody's been sending in.
I saw the bus!
The Gura bus!
It's been the Gumbo bus!
Did you guys ride in the Gumbo bus?
Did you get to sit inside the Gargura bus?
Fill it with gas!
Nyooooon~
Anyway, it's really hard to see what you guys are saying
'cause there's just so much bup-bup-bup-bup-bup,
which I appreciate, but um... anyway.
Um, can you guys hear me though?
Okay, you can hear me.
We bussin'. We are bussin'. We are fish-like.
Do you think we could... well, never mind.
I was gonna... never mind. We don't have to go that route.
Um... what?
There's a Gura bus. There's a Gura bus.
And I saw videos!
There's a bunch of videos you guys...
...some animations as well.
Um, I want to say thank you for making me feel,
uh, so special on my very special day.
Very, very special day.
What? Is the mic okay?
The mic is, is it peaking?
Hello? Hello?
What is wrong with the mic?
Can you...?
Mic is acting funny. Oh, great.
Um, well, as you guys probably know...
well, situation...
...I'm a little out of my element at the moment,
so I would appreciate... Mic is peaking.
A-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!
I see. I see what you mean.
Why is it doing that? I don't know why it's doing that.
Uh, I'll try not to overwhelm the microphone.
I will speak softer.
Mmm.
Okay, so um...
I hope you guys liked the streams yesterday.
They were a lot of fun. Um, yeah,
that was a lot of fun.
Actually, uh, it's still kind of sinking in
what happened.
Um, so... Oh, I'm...
Real bad Gura.
What do you mean 'real bad Gura'?
Did you like that?
Yeah, the karaoke was a lot of fun.
I don't know how much I should say about it, though.
Of course, I'm like absolutely, uh,
filled to the brim with stuff that I want to talk about,
uh, what Ame did.
Uh, so, uh, yeah, she made me,
she made me a little cake...
...and she decorated it with white chocolate,
and she made little, like, sea creatures,
and she stuck it to the cake.
Um, and the cake had, had coffee in it...
...so after I ate it, uh, I got really energized
'cause there was like espresso in it.
And um... it really helped...
...I don't know, it helped me to stay awake...
...so I could see everything
that you guys were sending me on Twitter
with the hashtag, the birthday hashtag.
Um, what else did we do?
Oh, she made me dinner!
Yeah, she made me, she made me dinner.
She made me, uh... we had steak and rice
and, and broccoli... fancy broccoli. Fancy broccoli.
But I eat really slow.
Um, I was kind of self-conscious about that,
but um... it's okay.
She eats slow, too.
She's not gonna tell you that,
but she eats pretty slow too.
All right. All right.
And Watson eats her rice with soy sauce!
Did you know that?
I prefer my rice plain, uh, just hot steamed rice,
plain, nothing on it.
But Watson likes to eat her rice with soy sauce.
Just a little thing. Did you know that? Hmm?
A slow-eater competition?
Well, I was anxious, but also I do eat slowly.
It's not a bad thing, is it?
Do you guys eat fast or slow?
Wait, why am I doing...? Never mind.
I'm talking to myself.
Soy sauce is pretty good.
It is good, but the problem when you pour soy sauce
on rice is that it makes it unsticky.
So then you can't eat it very easily.
So you have to eat it with like a spoon and a straw
or something, whatever you choose.
Sweet or salty?
It was soy sauce, I don't know, it's just soy sauce.
It was just soy sauce.
If you guys eat fast food, don't you get like, I don't know, indigestion or something?
Anyway, though... I'll talk a bit more about the hanging out with Watson later.
But first, I... as being my birthday in Gura birthday tradition...
I have a gift for you guys.
A gift for all of you.
You might guess what it is, but anyway...
So for all of you, I prepared a little something with the help of a very, very, very, very, very awesome artist that I really look up to a lot.
Is it more streams? Yes, but yes but no, but yes, but not right now.
So I have for you...
Ahhhhhhhhhh... tada!
Oh dear.
Tada!
Emotes!
New emotes!
And see the cool thing about this is all of my... do you see the shrimp emotes? We have Ebi emotes now.
We have now forever, what is it? Immortalized Ebis in the emote list.
Let's take a look. These are by Mariette.
Mariette.
We have... what do we have here?
Gura with a penlight that looks like a gun. That's actually, I specifically asked, I said "Can you make Gura look like... can you make me look like I'm holding a gun, but instead of a gun, it's a penlight?"
And then we have Nyoom!
And then we have celebration!
And then we have comfy Gura!
And then we have Gura is dead!
And then we have Gura is crying happy!
And then we have Gura... Gura is smiling at you, very smug!
And then we have squish the cheek of Gura!
And then we have Gura scared!
And then we have Giga Gura Chad!
And then we have Gura going "Hehehe!"
And then we have my face, because you guys are always looking at me funny.
And then we have Gura "Haha!"
And then we have Gura eyeball!
And then we have Ebi... Ebi-chan!
You guys are holding penlights. You guys are looking at me like I probably just said something really awful and I don't realize it.
And then you're crying, and then your little face is like that when you say something stupid and don't realize it and I call you out. See?
Yay!
Okay you should be able to use them now. Can use them now.
There they are. Nice!
Excellent!
Look at all these Gura Chads. Giga Gura Chads!
Wow, what excellent jawlines you guys have. Wow!
Nice jawbones, guys!
Ebi looks like Patrick, like Patrick Star.
Ebi cute. Ebi-chan cute.
You guys really like the Giga Chad one.
I guess it's not Giga Chad anymore, I guess it's now Gura Chad when you're here. Gura Chad. Gura Chad.
Oh, they're so cute.
This is the same artist that drew Mumei as well as Fauna's emotes, and I really, really like both of their emotes.
I use them a lot, in the Discord especially. I'm always using Fauna Zoom, Fauna "Not like this", and Clover, and then Mumei's loading face, I always use that one.
So I was really excited to be able to get Mariette to help me out with these new emotes. Thank you Mariette if you're watching!
Thank you! Thank you, thank you!
Phew!
Mwah!
Okay.
This year I wanted to do something a little bit different than what we're, I guess, what I'm used to doing for birthdays.
Or I mean, I've only had one birthday, but I wanted to change it up a little bit this year.
You can't find Ebi? エビちゃんどこ？
You can't find Ebi? Where's Ebi-chan?
Maybe there's an issue with Ebi. Ebi-chan. Ebi-chan is coming. I was wondering why I couldn't see Ebi anywhere. Ebi.
I'm sure Ebi is coming. I'm sure Management is helping right now to make sure Ebi's working. No worries, Ebi coming.
Maybe also refresh your page, that might be it.
But anyway, I want to talk about something that's going to happen.
I wanted to do some stuff a little bit differently this year, but I still hope that you guys will like it.
It took a lot of creative minds and patience and a lot of helping hands to make...
This, this, this year's birthday turned into something...
...I think is really great, and I'm really...
...excited for, and I'm ble-ble-ble... I'm saying so much.
So, so, so, so, how old am I now?
Oh God, how many times have I answered this question?
So many, so many times.
Please not Dakimakura. You don't want a Dakimakura.
That's right, there's merchandise. Merchandise releases today.
Are you excited? I'm really excited.
I showed one of the other Myth members the merchandise...
...and she really liked it, so I hope you guys...
...really like it as well.
Okay, anyway, let's go and...
...I didn't think of how to segue this at all whatsoever.
Can you tell that I'm nervous? Where's the shrimp emote?
I don't know. It should be coming anytime though.
I need to... hold on, I need to gather my thoughts. I'm really shaking right now. Hmm.
The personality test that I took said that I do really well under pressure.
And I think I do okay under pressure, but maybe not productively well.
I just keep my cool, sort of. I think I keep my cool.
Mike is funky. It'll fix in a second, it's just suffering right now.
But anyway, I want to sing some songs for you.
I want to, I want to sing some music. That's, that I know how to do.
I'll do that for you guys because that'll help calm me down and stuff.
There, Ebi! Oh, you look so good! Look at!
Oh wow! Ebi! Hello, everyone! Cute!
Ah, looks so good! Yeah! Okay, so yeah...
I want to, I want to sing for you today because that's what I, I like to do.
It is an activity like we that we both like sharing in, right you guys?
So, but we're going to switch it up and I'm I hope you...
...I hope we have a good time today, okay? Be ready to shake those penlights.
Yeah. Okay. Shall we? 行くぞ！
Yeah. Okay. Shall we? Let's go!
みんな、行くぞ！
Everyone, let's go!
みんな、okay, okay. P-p-p-p-p-p... ah...
Everyone, okay, okay. P-p-p-p-p-p... ah...
Close your eyes, everybody. Close them.
Or don't close them. Okay, yeah, close them now. Close.
So much blue. It makes my heart so happy.
I love the color blue. Did you know that? Okay, anyway...
Look at the big aquarium! Wow! Fishies! Fishy, fishy!
And look at the floor. It's water. Water.
Swish, splash. And look at me! That's right, I'm here too.
Look at me! I'm here! You're here! We're here!
To party! Yahoo! パチパチパチ！
To party! Yahoo! *Clap clap clap!*
But first, I just want to say a big thank you to you guys...
...to everybody. Thank you, thank you for supporting Shark...
...and believing in Shark. Just Sharky. Little Sharky.
All of this for little Sharky. That's so crazy.
Thank you guys so much! Ah!
We also recently hit four bubuillion subscribers...
We also recently hit four million subscribers...
...which is insanity. Also, I did some math...
Yeah, I know. Gura doing math.
Look out!
But roughly there are 15 shrimp to 1 pound.
So that technically means that with 4 million shrimp...
Something... something...
There's a big shrimp lurking on the horizon is what I'm trying to say.
And he's made up of millions. 4 million little tiny nano shrimpy's.
That's all of you, you are building the giga shrimp.
So we must be wary and look out for this very large specimen.
Um, you can do the exact math though.
'Cause I actually don't know how big this giga shrimp is.
Giga? Mega? Mega shrimp.
I think I'm gonna stop myself here though.
But anyways...
Er... ooh boob boob boob...
Okay. We all know that I cannot do math.
But I propose a counter-offer.
Huh?
You do the math.
I'll do the sing.
I sing for you.
Hehe.
Do... I'll...
Okay. Um...
I'd better start before it gets too awkward.
Okay.
みな、スタート！
Everyone, start!
Hehe.
君のために選んだ
I chose it for you
幸せのレシピを
A recipe for happiness
始めよう 今夜も
Let's begin tonight too
キャンドルを灯して
Let's light the candles
野菜たちのスープに
Into the vegetable soup
今日の色溶かして
Let the colors of today melt in
口づけのテリーヌに
In the terrine of a kiss
隠し味のジュレ添えて
Add a secret jelly garnish
寂しさを炙って
Broil the loneliness
トマト色煮込めば
If we simmer it until it's tomato-colored
僕と君の想いやがて
Eventually, your feelings and mine
ひとつに香りだす
Will start to smell as one
夢中なスパイスも
Even the spices of infatuation
微笑みのボトルに
In the bottle of smiles
投げ込んでしまえば
If we just throw them in
形の残らない
They won't leave a shape
君との幸せのレシピで
With the happiness recipe for you and me
幸せを作ろうよ
Let's create happiness
幸せのレシピで
With the happiness recipe
愛をもっと味わいたい
I want to taste more of your love
優しさのムニエル
A meuniere of kindness
美しいマリネ
A beautiful marinade
夢心地のスフレ
A dream-like soufflé
匂い立つフロマージュ
The fragrant fromage
こぼれてる心
The heart that's overflowing
一つまみのジェラシー
A pinch of jealousy
いつかみんな混ざり合って
Someday, everything will mix together
綺麗な色になる
And turn into a beautiful color
とびっきりの美味しい
The most delicious...
おやすみのブイヨン
"Goodnight" bouillon
もう一つ今夜は
One more thing tonight
まどろみを頬張って
I'll take a mouthful of slumber
夢に届くように
So that it reaches the dreams
君との幸せのレシピで
With the happiness recipe for you and me
幸せになろうよ
Let's be happy
幸せのレシピで
With the happiness recipe
君をもっと味わいたい
I want to taste more of you
幸せのレシピで
With the happiness recipe
幸せを作ろうよ
Let's create happiness
幸せのレシピで
With the happiness recipe
愛をもっと味わいたい
I want to taste more of your love
幸せのレシピで
With the happiness recipe
幸せになろうよ
Let's be happy
幸せのレシピで
With the happiness recipe
君をもっと味わいたい
I want to taste more of you
味わいだい 幸せのレシピ...
Enjoy the taste of the recipe for happiness...
幸せのレシピ...
Recipe for happiness...
Tatsuro... Tatsuro Yamashita will forever be
one of my favorite musical artists.
Seriously. I can always find a way to
recommend people to listen to his music.
Wait, Gooba... Gooba, I don't know what to stream...
Oh, that sucks. Hey, have you heard this banger before?
Send link, send link, link, link, link...
I mean, I've already told you guys about
how much I enjoy Tatsuro Yamashita's music so...
So, you guys already know.
Actually, lately, my summer playlist has consisted of
Tatsuro Yamashita, various albums, uh,
and then Jeremy Soule as well.
I have like two modes right now.
It's either nostalgia for a 1980s summer or, or,
somewhere in a Skyrim tavern looking to pickpocket.
Did you guys smell that?
You smell that? It smells like... no, wait...
Nam nam, I can taste it too. It tastes like herbs and spices.
ゆらり ゆらり 揺れている 乙女心ピンチ
Swaying, swaying, this maiden's heart is in a pinch
かなり かなり やばいのよ 助けてダーリン クラクラリ
It's really, really bad, help me darling, I'm dizzy
何もかもが 新しい 世界に来ちゃったわ
I've come to a world where everything is new
たくさんの ドキドキ 乗り越え 踏み越え 行くぞ！
Overcoming so many heart-throbs, let's go!
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカいか この想いは 止められない
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ka, I can't stop these feelings
もっと 乙女チック・パワー きるいみんちょ ドキドキな感じ
More maidenly power, killing me, a heart-pounding feeling
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカいか もう ドキドキ 止められない
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ka, I can't stop the heart-pounding
もっと 空町チック・恋 ハレルヤ 二人だけのバラライカ
More sky-town-ish love, Hallelujah, a Balalaika for just us two
すごく すごく 近づいて 乙女心チャンス
Getting really, really close, a maidenly heart chance
ハート ハート 飛び出そう お願いダーリン ハラハラリ
Heart, heart, about to jump out, please darling, I'm on edge
あなただけを 見つめてる 私にしらんぷり
You're playing dumb while I'm staring only at you
気づいてほしいのよ ときめき やきもき 好きよ！
I want you to notice, the throbbing, the impatience, I love you!
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカいか そう 秘密を教えてよ
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ka, yes, tell me your secret
もっと 乙女チック もっと きるいみんやん 微笑みが素敵
More maidenly, more killing me, your smile is wonderful
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカいか よ よしてちゃダメダメよ
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ka, you shouldn't stop it
もっと ロマンチック・恋 シャラララカ 奏でたいのバラライカ
More romantic love, sha-la-la-la-ka, I want to play the Balalaika
女の子は いつだって 夢見る乙女なの
Girls are always dreaming maidens
ぷよぷよな 心で 恋して 愛して S.O.S. S.O.S!
Falling in love with a squishy heart, S.O.S. S.O.S!
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカいか この想いは 止められない
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ka, I can't stop these feelings
もっと 乙女チック・パワー きるいみんちょ ドキドキな感じ
More maidenly power, killing me, a heart-pounding feeling
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカいか もう ドキドキ 止められない
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ka, I can't stop the heart-pounding
もっと 空町チック・恋 ハレルヤ 二人だけのバラライカ
More sky-town-ish love, Hallelujah, a Balalaika for just us two
バラライカ...
Balalaika...
Uh, guys? Something feels... spooky.
Guys?
Oh my God!
会いたいな 会えないな 切ないな
I want to see you, I can't see you, it's so painful.
この気持ち 言えないの 言いたいな
I can't say these feelings, but I want to say them.
チャンス 逃してばかり だって
Because I'm always missing my chance.
だって だって
Because, because...
チュッ!パッ!さあ広げる 二人で
Kiss! Pop! Let's spread it out together.
空を バラ色 夢を
The sky is rose-colored, a dream...
ユニゾンしたい
I want to harmonize.
ほら キャッチ・キャッチ・キャッチ・ミー・キャッチ・ミー 待って
Hey, catch-catch-catch-me-catch-me, wait!
こっちを向いて 好きだと言って
Turn this way and say you like me.
そう ナイス・トゥ・ミー・トゥ・ユー・グッド・トゥ・シー・ユー きっと
So, nice to meet you, good to see you, for sure.
私の想い あなたのハートに
My feelings, to your heart...
飛んで飛んで飛んでゆけ 迷わない
fly-fly-fly away, I won't hesitate!
空に ねぇ なくなっちゃう
Hey, it's disappearing into the sky.
体のバッテリー
My body's battery.
あなたの笑顔で いつも
With your smile, always...
充電満タン パワー爆発しちゃえ
fully charged, power exploding!
お願い お願い お願い マイ・スター
Please, please, please, my star.
まずはお友達から
Let's start as friends.
笑って 見つめて 楽しい
Smiling, gazing, having fun...
毎日したい
I want to do it every day.
ほら キャッチ・キャッチ・キャッチ・ミー・キャッチ・ミー 絶対
Hey, catch-catch-catch-me-catch-me, definitely!
運命だって お似合いだって
It's fate, we're a perfect match.
そう ナイス・トゥ・ミー・トゥ・ユー・グッド・トゥ・シー・ユー きっと
So, nice to meet you, good to see you, for sure.
誰にも負けない 世界で
Second to none in the world.
一番一番一番 恋してる
I'm the most, most, most in love!
ほら キャッチ・キャッチ・キャッチ・ミー・キャッチ・ミー 待って
Hey, catch-catch-catch-me-catch-me, wait!
こっちを向いて 好きだと言って
Turn this way and say you like me.
そう ナイス・トゥ・ミー・トゥ・ユー・グッド・トゥ・シー・ユー きっと
So, nice to meet you, good to see you, for sure.
私の想い あなたのハートに
My feelings, to your heart...
飛んで飛んで飛んでゆけ 迷わない
fly-fly-fly away, I won't hesitate!
ほら キャッチ・キャッチ・キャッチ・ミー・キャッチ・ミー 絶対
Hey, catch-catch-catch-me-catch-me, definitely!
運命だって お似合いだって
It's fate, we're a perfect match.
そう ナイス・トゥ・ミー・トゥ・ユー・グッド・トゥ・シー・ユー きっと
So, nice to meet you, good to see you, for sure.
誰にも負けない 世界で
Second to none in the world.
一番一番一番 恋してる
I'm the most, most, most in love!
君とのドッペルゲンガー
A doppelganger with you
それは予想通り
It's just as expected
いざ始まれば 一人芝居だ
Once it starts, it's a one-man show
ずっと側にいたって 結局ただの観客だ
Even if I'm always by your side, in the end I'm just a spectator
感情のあ、アイムソーリー
Feelings of... ah, I'm sorry
それはいつも通り
It's just as usual
慣れてしまえば
Once you get used to it...
言わないけど
I won't say it, but...
君とのロマンスは
The romance with you...
前世から続きはしないことを
...is not something that continues from a past life...
知った
...I've realized.
もっと違う設定で
In a different setting,
もっと違う関係で
In a different relationship,
出会える世界線選べたらよかった
I wish I could have chosen a timeline where we met differently.
もっと違う性格で
With a different personality,
もっと違う価値観で
With different values,
愛を伝えられたらいいな
I wish I could have conveyed my love.
そう願っても無駄だから
But even if I wish for that, it's useless.
グッバイ
Goodbye.
君の運命のヒトは僕じゃない
I'm not your soulmate.
辛いけど否めない
It's painful, but I can't deny it.
でも離れ難いのさ
But it's hard to let you go.
その髪に触れただけで
Just by touching your hair,
痛いや　いやでも
It hurts, no, but still,
甘いな　いやいや
It's sweet, no, no.
グッバイ
Goodbye.
それじゃ僕にとって君は何？
Then what are you to me?
答えは分からない
I don't know the answer.
分かりたくもないのさ
I don't even want to know.
たったひとつ確かなことが
If there's only one thing for certain,
あるとするのならば
that's for sure,
「君は綺麗だ」
"You are beautiful."
誰かが偉そうに語る恋愛のセオリー
The theories of love that someone talks about so arrogantly,
何ひとつとしてピンとこなくて
none of them really click with me.
飛行機の窓から見下ろした知らない街の夜景みたいだ
It's like looking down at the night view of an unknown city from an airplane window.
もっと違う設定で
In a different setting,
もっと違う関係で
In a different relationship,
出会える世界線選べたらよかった
I wish I could have chosen a timeline where we met differently.
いたって純な心で
With a perfectly pure heart,
かなった恋を抱きしめて
embracing a love that came true,
「好きだ」とか無責任に言えたらいいな
I wish I could irresponsibly say things like "I love you."
グッバイ
Goodbye.
繋いだ手の向こうにエンドライン
An end line beyond our joined hands.
引き伸ばすたびに　疼きだす未来には
In the future that begins to ache every time I stretch it out,
君はいない　その事実に苦いよ
you are not there. That fact is bitter.
いやいや　それ苦しいよな
No, no, that's painful, isn't it?
グッバイ
Goodbye.
君の運命のヒトは僕じゃない
I'm not your soulmate.
辛いけど否めない
It's painful, but I can't deny it.
でも離れ難いのさ
But it's hard to let you go.
その髪に触れただけで
Just by touching your hair,
痛いや　いやでも
It hurts, no, but still,
甘いな　いやいや
It's sweet, no, no.
グッバイ
Goodbye.
それじゃ僕にとって君は何？
Then what are you to me?
答えは分からない
I don't know the answer.
分かりたくもないのさ
I don't even want to know.
たったひとつ確かなことが
If there's only one thing for certain,
あるとするのならば
that's for sure,
「君は綺麗だ」
"You are beautiful."
それもこれもロマンスだね
All of this is romance, too.
悪くないよな
It's not bad, is it?
永遠も約束もないけれど
There are no promises of eternity, but...
とても綺麗だ
...you are so beautiful.
眠らない夜
A sleepless night,
君のせいだよ
...is all your fault.
さっきばかりね
Just a moment ago,
目が合ったばかりなのに
even though our eyes just met,
耳たぶが熱い
...my earlobes are burning.
...for you.
おもいきり... for you.
With all my heart... for you.
やった！
We did it!
やった？
We did it?
やったよ！
We did it!
Ah... はじめてのチュウ...
Ah... my first kiss...
チュウ！
Kiss!
君とチュウ...
A kiss with you...
チュウ！
Kiss!
チュウ？
Kiss?
I will give you all my love.
なぜか優しい気持ちが いっぱい...
For some reason, I'm filled with such a gentle feeling...
...はじめてのチュウ...
...my first kiss...
チュウ！君とチュウ...
Kiss! A kiss with you...
チュウ！I will give you all my love.
Kiss! I will give you all my love.
涙が出ちゃう 男の子だね...
I'm a boy who's about to cry...
...くせに be in love with you.
...even so, I'm in love with you.
Ah, why'd you pick this song? It's embarrassing!
Hey, isn't it blushy-blushy?
Shut it, fish brain!
デートの誘いも もう決めたんだ...
I've already decided how to ask you out on a date...
あしたの夢が ふくらんでくる...
My dreams for tomorrow are expanding...
...この愛を...
...this love...
To you... いつまでも...
To you... forever...
To you...
きっと...
Surely...
きっとさ！
Surely!
はじめてのチュウ...
My first kiss...
君とチュウ...
A kiss with you...
I will give you all my love.
なぜか優しい気持ちが いっぱい...
For some reason, I'm filled with such a gentle feeling...
...はじめてのチュウ...
...my first kiss...
はじめてのチュウ...
My first kiss...
君とチュウ...
A kiss with you...
I will give you all my love.
涙が出ちゃう 男の子だね...
I'm a boy who's about to cry...
...くせに be in love with you.
...even so, I'm in love with you.
はじめてのチュウ...
My first kiss...
君とチュウ...
A kiss with you...
I will give you all my love.
なぜか優しい気持ちが いっぱい...
For some reason, I'm filled with such a gentle feeling...
...はじめてのチュウ...
...my first kiss...
はじめてのチュウ...
My first kiss...
君とチュウ...
A kiss with you...
I will give you all my love.
涙が出ちゃう 男の子だね...
I'm a boy who's about to cry...
...くせに be in love with you.
...even so, I'm in love with you.
Love with you...
Trick or Treat!
Your oshi's waiting in the closet tonight.
No wait, stop, she's dead-set on giving you a fright!
Trick or treat, but now we're all out of candy.
Feeling just a little sick, this chainsaw'd come in handy!
I got a theory, just possessed.
So let's experiment, a little vivisection is best!
Drop the little babies hiding behind your screen.
Is it even spooky Halloween without some mythical beings?
Death is splashing, look at those red cheeks.
I'll fix that after draining all your blood, that's what you see!
Myth or Treat!
Oh, what a cursed five stream
There's no bones about it you'll scream
We'll only show ya on Halloween
Our spookier, terrify-scarier side
Oh, what a ガチ恋 night
Oh, what a Gachi-koi night
Mythic witches with endless fights
Can't escape our idol-less might
No candy inside so your souls must suffice
Bust a funky dance tonight
What a spooky scary sight
Hungry dinosaur, just one tiny bite... please!
Spook-a-bulous with a song
If you're brave then sing along
Not your wife, I am a pumpkin! Ding dong!
In the graveyard we will be
If you're looking for a scream
Singing songs that make you pee! A-R-T-Y
Give you shivers, make you shout
Just like that now Myth is out
Spookily is what we're about
Ah...
I love singing with the other members in Myth. Wah...
Hope you guys liked it too.
I really, really appreciate everybody's hard work to make today happen.
It's a really nice feeling
knowing that I can rely on my friends
and other super creative people to make such fun experiences happen for all of you.
I'm so very grateful.
So thank you, thank you everybody, and also to each of you.
Thank you for your patience and your incredible support.
Another year of shark.
I'm so lucky to be surrounded by such dedicated folks like you.
Thank you everybody. Thank you.
Now, more fun stuff.
Birthday stuff!
Wahoo!
Merchandise baby, merchandise.
Give me the good shark, give me the goods.
I know, I know, I know.
I'm so excited about this year's merch.
I seriously love it so much.
I've been looking at pictures of it every day leading up to this exact moment,
hoping all of you will be just as excited as I am.
Drumroll, みな。
Drumroll, everyone.
Birthday Celebration 2022 On Sale June 21
Tadan!
Guba merch!
Wow!
Guba...
On sale pretty soon, I don't know exactly when but...
Anyways, cute!
Cute, cute, cute.
First, let's start with adorable art by ぱんさん！
First, let's start with adorable art by Pan-san!
Postcard art by ぱん
Postcard art by Pan
Yay!
Featuring えびちゃん
Featuring Ebi-chan
and hydrangeas, my favorite summer flower,
because it's all blue and there's water
and I'm so cute with my little sailor outfit.
Oh I'm so cute. I'm so cute.
Have I mentioned how cute? I'm so cute.
I'm so cute.
I love this art so much.
And the good thing is that it's available as a postcard.
Limited complete sets will include a hand-signed signature by me,
Guba Gubigabugubi.
And this art will also be available as...
A rubber mat! Jajon!
It's grippy, perfect for high-octane activities like...
like Gunpla building.
And bonus points because it's cute. It's cute.
I wonder if you can do other things on it like...
I don't know, gaming maybe?
I don't know, just don't get it dirty.
Well, you can get it dirty for a while, I mean... it's alright.
It's cute!
Okay, next up.
I don't think you guys are ready for this.
I'm... ah...
Okay. Okay.
Dino Gura Plushie Designed by さめあんこ
Dino Gura Plushie Designed by Sameanko
Tadan! Dino Guba!
Dino Guba is here!
He has a big round tummy,
little round yellow toes and scales,
and an embroidered えび on the tushy.
and an embroidered Ebi on the tushy.
Designed by none other than... さめあんこ。
Designed by none other than... Sameanko.
Dino Guba!
Dino Guba is real.
Dino Guba... you can own a Dino Guba.
Dino Guba can now peacefully live in your home
just for you.
And you can pull the hood down and reveal my twin tails!
It smells.
It's squishy.
It's punchable.
It's puntable.
And I might have cried when I first saw
the plushie design,
because Sama-anko is such a god
at creating cute things,
designing anything and everything
that's cute.
Sama-anko is number one.
I hope you will give Dino Gura
a good home.
Also, while I'm here, can somebody
make the Luigi centrifuge meme video,
but it's like Dino Gura instead?
That would be funny.
Maybe I'll do it. I can do it.
Instead of "Whaaa!", it'll be me,
but I'll be doing something else.
Ha...
We're not done yet!
Then we have...
The Gura Bowl!
I am absolutely dead serious when I say
that kitchenware is my weakness.
Also designed by Sama-anko.
The Gura Bowl features me,
Ebi-chan, and Bloop
at the very bottom of the bowl,
ensuring that no crumbs are left behind.
Do you see how cute this bowl is?
Look at it.
I love kitchenware.
Kitchenware daisuki!
I love kitchenware!
In fact, I want more.
I need a Myth dinnerware set.
I need bowls, I need plates,
I need cups. We have cups.
Well, now I need the rest of it.
We need bowls.
More bowls, I say.
Give me more bowls, please.
I won't even use them.
I just want to look at them.
Just let me look at them.
Oh my god.
Well, there's more.
There's more, guys.
To go alongside your very own
Gura Bowl...
Trident fork!
Trident chopsticks!
I repeat: Trident fork!
It's blue! Well, turquoise.
Blue! Turquoise blue!
I've talked to you guys about how much
I wanted to make a trident fork.
Okay, I wanted it to be glowing.
This one doesn't glow, but still...
Look at it.
Trident cutlery set!
Holy moly motherload!
Trident fork and chopsticks set.
Designed by yours truly.
That's right, I designed it
because we talked about it, remember?
Not quite as powerful as my own trident,
but definitely strong enough to lift
your favorite meal into your mouth.
Lift your favorite meal out of
the Gura Bowl and into your mouth.
Okay, and lastly... a voice pack!
Featuring some notification sounds
that you can use in whichever device
you wish to Gura-fy.
Your PC, your phone,
your iPads, your iDevices.
Can I say iPad on stream?
I just said iPad.
Any device that you would like
my voice coming out of, except...
audio thing. Woohoo!
Gura! Woohoo!
Now, okay, I will say that there are
more things in the oven currently,
but they need a bit more time.
Just a bit.
And I hope you look forward to
what I'm cooking up.
Motivado, minna-san! Tweet!
Motivated, everyone! Tweet!
Thank you guys for coming
to my birthday party this year.
I hope you had a nice time.
I hope you like the goods.
I hope you like the songs.
Thank you, Myth, for singing with me
and for hanging out with me
on my birthday.
I'm very lucky to be surrounded by
such a talented group of ladies.
And I appreciate and cherish every moment
that we've been able to spend together
on this Hololive journey.
Thank you to you guys as well
watching this journey.
Let's see where we go next, right?
GG, good next stop!
皆さん、ありがとうございました。
Thank you, everyone.
これからも頑張りますので、
I'll continue to do my best,
よろしくお願いします。
so please keep supporting me.
Okay.
It is time for me to go.
But I'll see you again real soon, okay?
Okie-dokie, everybody!
Bye-bye!
Bye everybody.
Bye-bye, bye-bye!
Bye-bye, bye!
Bye-bye-bye...