(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Let's go Advent!
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
Who are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi
関西 関東 西 東 北 南 チーム友達
Kansai, Kanto, West, East, North, South, Team Tomodachi
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
チーム、チーム、チーム友達
Team, team, team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
Who are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi
お好み焼き 食う 鶴橋
Eating Okonomiyaki in Tsuruhashi
腹いっぱい 飯は美味い
My stomach's full, the food's delicious
一人じゃ寂しいし電話きたり
When I'm lonely alone, a call comes in
かけ直した後すぐ会いに行く
I'll go meet them right after calling back
T-E-A-M T-O-M-O-D-A-C-H-I
チーム友達 混ざり合い
Team Tomodachi, mixing together
契り交わし 飲んでる酒
Exchanging vows while drinking sake
契り 契り 契り 契り 契り 契り 契り 契り
Vow, vow, vow, vow, vow, vow, vow, vow
契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう
Let's vow, let's vow, let's vow, let's vow
契り 契り 契り 契り 契り 契り 契り 契り
Vow, vow, vow, vow, vow, vow, vow, vow
契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう
Let's vow, let's vow, let's vow, let's vow
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
Who are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi
関西 関東 西 東 北 南 チーム友達
Kansai, Kanto, West, East, North, South, Team Tomodachi
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
チーム、チーム、チーム友達
Team, team, team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
Who are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
You know, come to think of it,
it's been two years since we broke out of the cell, huh?
Wait...
It has been...
Yeah, time goes by fast.
Yeah.
We've been through a lot, right?
Mm-hm.
Huh?
What?
Hey, guys!
What's that over there?!
Huh?
Attention.
Justice.
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Initiating final warning protocol.
Five escapees detected from the cell.
Repeat.
Targets are as follows:
The Demon of Sound,
Nerissa Ravencroft.
The Jewel of Emotions,
Koseki Bijou.
The Fluffy One,
Fuwawa Abyssgard.
The Fuzzy One,
Mococo Abyssgard.
The Archiver,
Shiori Novella.
All units,
apprehend the Advent members immediately.
Wait!
No! We're in trouble!
Oh no, where are we?!
Oh my god! They're catching us!
We can't get out!
Oh no! They're so fast!
Wait! Stop!
Where are we even going?
Think! There's got to be a solution for this, right?
Okay, think!
Piggyback ride! Come on!
On! On! Piggyback ride!
Okay, maybe not that one.
Sorry.
There has to be something though, like a Plan B or something we can do.
Bwahaha! Struggling already?
Huh?
Oh my god! It's Pokey!
What are you doing here?
Finally show your face, huh?
Ask nicely enough, and maybe I'll save your skins.
Yeah!
I'll punch you for real! Come on, come on!
Okay... um... please?
I have a solution.
Don't please him! How fast, Pokey?
Hmph! I don't hate that.
If you manage to pass the little trial I've cooked up for you,
I'll whisk you away to a whole other realm...
One where your pesky pursuers can't reach you!
I mean, I guess that's our only option, huh?
Oh well, I guess we will do it.
Alright. I've prepared something special. Arise, my go-karts!
Go-Kart Escape / 逃走ゴーカート
Go-Kart Escape
What if we don't have a license?
Wait, what's with all the Biboo-themed stuff?
Yeah, I actually like that.
See this course? Time to tackle the "Go-Kart Escape Challenge"!
Go-Kart Escape Challenge!
Yes, that's right. Take it from here, ankle-biter.
Eh?!
Who are you talking to, huh?
Ankle-biter?! Yeah, calm down there.
Well, actually...
Alright team, game rules are incoming,
so make sure you better listen, okay?
Yeah! Woo! Nice!
Wait, Bijou, how do you know the game rules?
Isn't it like...
It's the glasses.
That's how she knows.
Rule 1!
Survive 2 laps with zombies on your tail!
Rule 1: Survive 2 laps with zombies on your tail!
Zombies?! Where? Where?
Remember last year we beat up zombies?
Well, one of them went on a path to revenge
and now it's gonna run after you.
Run! Ah!
And now, Rule 2!
Collect items for bonus points,
but watch out because there'll be some that deduct points too!
Rule 2: Collect items for bonus points, but watch out for traps that deduct points!
Bonus points! Points are great! Oh no!
And then, Rule 3!
Victory is ours if we all get 30 points total. Easy, right?
Rule 3: Victory is ours if we all get 30 points total!
30 points! Did you hear that? 30 points! Oh yeah, we can do that!
Alright, and now I will explain the course items.
I must run.
You must run?
Yeah, I must run. She must run with her people go.
I'm gonna live out my dreams while there's a track here.
Just ignore me. Ignore me. Keep listening.
Ah, there are... oh she's so fast! Wow!
Anyway, there are crystals on the field!
The Biboo crystal over there
and two more over there.
They are gacha!
You'll either gain points or lose points based...
...but you don't know, so it's a risk every time.
And then, there is the Big Moai!
Moai! The big Moai!
It will block your path.
It is minus 20 points if you hit it, so don't hit it.
Don't hit it! Yeah, don't hit it.
And then, the Pebble!
I have kidnapped one of my Pebbles to use as a sacrifice.
If you hit it, minus 5 points. But you know what?
I don't think Bijou would mind if you hit it, to be honest.
And the items will change depending on your first lap or second lap.
You're doing two laps. - Two laps!
I guess time to show you how it's done.
Alright, first lap, show us how to do it.
I'm ready!
Go! Go Bijou! - Faster, faster!
She gets the first one! She makes it!
Second crystal, watch out!
Second lap, let's go!
Another crystal! She hit another one!
The zombie's coming! Watch out!
I think you got a bit of bad luck with that crystal at the end.
How many points did I get?
That's a good question. How many points did you get?
I think you got one point.
Bijou's Points: 1pt
What? One point? Was it all negative?
It's a group effort, we can still get points.
Just let the pro do all the work for you.
Show us how it's done, our fearless leader!
I have a plan.
You'll figure it out when I say "plan"!
あの、ゾンビさん、先どうぞ。
Um, Mr. Zombie, please go ahead.
えっ、何？いい子ですね、いい子ですね。
Eh, what? Such a good girl, such a good girl.
Let's go!
It's like driving in New York!
It's not about the points, I just wanted to run them over.
How many points did I get?
Three points!
Shiori's Points: 3pt
That's two more points than Bijou!
I'll get four points!
I'm pretty sure the zombie is not going to run away anymore...
...so I think he's tired.
It's up to you, you gotta outrun it! - I'm the best driver!
Alright, let's go!
Bau bau!
I've got this, okay!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, Fuwawa! Go, Fuwawa! Go, Fuwawa!
Go! Go! Why is it so small?
Oh, this time... it's so big! Fuwawa!
The crystal! The crystal! Go!
Watch out, watch out! Fuwawa, watch out! Watch out!
Yeah! Go! You did it!
Is that the first lap still?
It's the second one now!
I can do this! Bau bau!
Everything's okay! Bau bau!
Hurry, Fuwawa! Fuwawa!
Go, Fuwawa! Go, Fuwawa! You can do it!
Go, Fuwawa! You're doing great! You're doing great!
Oh, watch out! Watch out! Nice drive!
I did it! I'm okay! Yeah!
Bau bau!
I guess the speed isn't that important, but the points are, right?
Yeah! Bau bau, I think you did really well!
Yeah, so far you're our top performer today...
...with 18 points!
18! Bau bau!
Yeah, Fuwawa carry!
Wait, 18? Someone said 17.
18... 14... 18.
Cause you got three, and you got one, so yeah.
So it's 14... 18!
No no, we got 14 points!
14 points! Okay!
I'm gonna get all the points!
Look at me! Bau bau!
Bau bau! I'm gonna get them!
You got this, Mococo!
Go, Mococo! Go, Mococo!
I'll be faster eventually!
It's a slow burn! Yeah!
Yeah!
Whoa! Watch out, watch out!
Yeah! Oh!
I can do this! Bau bau! Bau bau!
Watch out for the zombies! Bau bau!
Watch out! You're doing great!
Watch out, watch out! Oh!
Yeah!
Bau bau!
How did you do, Mococo?
You could never catch me!
I think with you, we have enough!
Yeah, you got 12 points!
12 points!
That's 18... that's 30, right?
High five! High five! Yeah!
I can get negative points!
You can't get negative points.
I can get negative points! It's still up to you!
Don't you hit anything! You're not gonna ruin it all for us!
Well, you know you guys, right?
I have a driver's license, so I'm not worried about this at all.
Better than all of them! Don't trip over the zombies, huh?
I'm not scared of zombies.
That's what you say now!
I'm not scared.
Go Nerissa!
Wait, slow start! Nice, nice drive!
Whoa! Watch out, watch out! Exactly!
Wait, wait! Uh oh! Watch out! There's a zombie! Ahh!
I have a license! I can do this!
Nice, second lap, second lap! Go Nerissa!
Drifty! Oh, look at her!
Yeah! I'm hitting everything! Whoa!
Watch out! Careful, Advent! Yeah!
I don't know if that went well.
But I feel like I probably did better than you guys still.
Let's see if you got negative points!
I only spun out three times.
Yeah, only three times! You hit everything! This is not allowed!
Well, what are my points?
You got... what's the sign for 9?
You got 9 points!
9! Okay!
That means we passed, right?
The math is mathing! We passed!
Yeah! We did it!
High five! We did it!
Whoo! We did it!
What do you say, huh? Yeah! Do we get our deal?
Not bad!
As promised, interdimensional travel! All aboard!
Get in and go!
Wow, what a ride!
But let's crash it!
No, I have a better idea, everyone.
What idea? Yeah?
Let's make a music video!
A music video! Whoa!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is where my story all begins
Livin' it up like crazy
Ready to play come out with me
Carried away so easy
I can't get enough
Free as a bird, no limit
Every word I'm feelin' it
Get up and go, let's do this!
Watch me, watch me, watch me, be your diva
I'm gonna raise your fever
Shakin' up all the crowd
Makin' some noise when I'm not allowed
Livin' my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep indulging in my every whim
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a light
Now pay attention, please
'Cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc
How do you like this product?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now, woah
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion, a mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
Gonna start the rave, when I misbehave, take center stage
Let the fun commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense
There are loopholes unspoken, the rules can all be broken
Amening on a rampage, the world is a blank page
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
They're gonna know me by name! Tonight!
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hands
But they don't understand
That I'm a sign of making, awaking, and taking a bow, bow, bow, bow
Tell me how you like me now
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control, honey
You've got to free your mind, leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is our beginning
It's our genesis
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now, woah
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion, a mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
Tell me what time it is! It's our genesis!
You know what time it is! It's our genesis!
Everybody, look! It's the beach!
It's the beach everywhere!
It's amazing! Yeah! We're here!
Check it out! Swimsuits! Is that Mococo? It's so cute!
Oh, this is nice. Yeah, I like it. It feels nice and breathable.
I want to see everyone close up though. This is our first time wearing something like this, so...
Bijou, won't you show off what you've got to us?
Me first? Okay! Er...
What you lookin' at, huh? What you lookin' at?
Fine, you can look a little bit, okay?
Here we go! See my skirt? You like the skirt? It's so glossy!
Glossy! You're like a highlighter!
Kira-kira! I'm gonna blind you!
Oh! My eyes! Don't do to us at the beach! Who's next?
Yeah, Fuwawa, take over! Go, go, go! It's sister time!
Ah... This is kind of my first bathing suit, but, uh...
What do you think?
Off-shot! Off-shot!
Off-shot!
Yeah! Shiori, come here!
Shiori and her shorts!
Oh! Shiori's...
...at your service!
And look at my little ribbon!
Mococchi! Mococchi!
Okay, you can do this, Mococchi!
Bau bau! Bau bau!
Yeah! Mococchi,
you can do it! Come do it!
Does it suit me? Do you think I'm so cute?
Look at those cute shorts!
Hi! Hi!
She's so cute!
Ah! Oh! Yeah!
Mococchi, so cute!
And Nerissa! Nerissa!
Last, but... there's something a bit special on this outfit.
Don't you think if you go down...
...there it is! There it is!
Well, don't look there too much,
but if you come up, you can see my waist...
...and my... my top!
Armpits!
Yes, the pits! Okay! Hey!
But I see something strange off in the distance.
What is it?
Just, just wait. Let me go see.
Oh! It's a selfie stick!
Everyone get behind me!
Let's take a picture together!
Cheese! Nice!
Why is it so hot? Why is it so hot? You're so cute! Oh!
Oh, that helps!
Whoa! Hehe! Wow!
Oh, wait! Oh! Oh!
There's something down there in the sand.
Something down there? That...
...I think that's an Adventurer.
An Adventurer?
Oh! Someone stepped on them! Whoa!
Oh, you stepped on them! Yeah!
Okay, um...
Let's go to the water!
Yeah! Let's go!
Mococchi, don't drown! Hey!
I can swim! Run in slow-mo!
Oh, let's, let's just keep running on the beach.
Yeah!
I'm going to catch you, Nerissa!
You can't catch me!
Nerissa, wait!
I got you!
Calming up, put this thing down, okay?
Oh, my arm's getting tired.
Selfie arm tired.
Yeah, selfie arm's losing it.
Thank you for being such a tall person.
Yeah, of course.
Oh my god, it's Pokey!
Hey now! Save the beach party for later!
Sandcastles later, survival now!
They already detected your dimension jump.
I thought we were supposed to be safe here.
Yeah!
What's the big deal? Can't we have swimsuits and enjoy our time?
This is Justice we're dealing with! Expect the unexpected!
What should we do next then?
Do we have to run forever?
Don't panic, I have a plan.
Prove your bonds in the next trial, and I may assist you.
The power of friendship?
Nakama power?
Well, since this is a beach episode...
Beach episode! Beach episode! Beach episode! Yeah!
Good. Something's been arranged.
Look down! A & B!
A and B?
Not this again!
Are you serious?
A was A!
That's so lame!
A! A! B! B!
C-Can it! Silence!
To confirm your bonds, you'll take on "Master of Advent."
Master of Advent / Adventわかりて
Master of Advent / Advent Know-it-all
Master of Advent! What's that? Huh?
The rules are simple!
Each participant will be asked a two-option question related to Advent.
You guys are Team Tomodachi, so it should be pretty easy, right...?
Exactly. But incorrect answers mean... your bonds are weak,
so I prepared a penalty game!
Penalty game! Penalty game!
I didn't consent to this.
Yeah, a penalty game.
Now, goth girl, take over.
Each player asks a two-choice question!
Get it wrong, and face a mysterious penalty!
Anyway, I think that we're going to get
one question, two answers, but only one is right.
And if you get it wrong, unfortunately,
I think you're going to get muddied.
Muddied? Not my new swimsuit!
Yeah, I don't want to get muddy in this thing.
Absolutely not!
So when you make your answer, I want you to hop there, okay?
Hop hop hop hop!
I'll go first as an example. Okay?
Okay!
Number one!
Which would Shiori rather be?
A: A vampire, B: A werewolf
A vampire for A,
or a werewolf for B?
On the count of three, okay? Three, two, one, go!
Vampire!
Shiori!
Yeah!
Which would Shiori rather be?
A: A vampire B: A werewolf
I don't want to drink blood, what am I, stupid?
Whoa, that's unexpected.
I seriously thought you were going to say vampire.
You got that dog in you?
I literally have the dog in me, yeah.
Go! Go wash yourself!
Oh god, what is it...?
You too, I'm watching you.
Well, you got us all wet, Shiori, are you happy?
Not yet.
All right, well, next one, how about Mococo?
Moco-chan! My- my turn!
Okay, well, here I go! Um, at the beach...
Which would Mococo do at the beach?
A: Collect seashells B: Make sandcastles
Would I rather collect seashells, A...
...or, um, how was it? Ah, make sandcastles, B?
Okay, Biboo, ready?
Okay, jump on three.
Three, two, one!
I can't remember!
This was seashells and this was sandcastles.
Wait, you chose this way, Shiori?
No, I thought you wanted this one!
I- I made a mistake!
I'd rather collect seashells, but I jumped this
way, so that means this way is right!
This is so unfair!
Moco-chan won! No!
Help me! Biboo! Biboo!
Shiori, see you for now.
Yeah, for now, for now! Bau bau!
Okay, have fun!
That is so mean!
Seriously!
It was a game of chance! How about Fuwawa next?
Okay! It's my turn!
I don't get to get dirty this time, right? Yeah.
Okay, my question!
Which does Fuwawa prefer?
A: Long-haired cats B: Short-haired cats
Do I prefer...
...long-haired cats or short-haired cats?
Okay, I'm the fluffy one! Bau bau! Here we go!
Three, two, one!
No way!
What, really? You prefer short hair? You're the
fluffy one!
It's too easy! It's a trick question! It's so
obvious!
Oh, you're so mean to me!
You deserve it! Oh, you're so terrible!
Think before! Ah, think about it!
Ah, that feels nice! Yeah!
Well, it's going to be your turn next!
Oh, Bijou? Biboo-san, come back!
I don't- I don't want to play this game anymore!
It's so dynamic!
Okay! Okay, is it Biboo's turn now?
It's Biboo's turn now. Okay.
My question is, ooh, okay. Would I rather fight...
Which would Bijou fight?
A: One hundred chicken-sized hippopotamuses
B: One hippopotamus-sized chicken
...one hundred chicken-sized hippopotamuses on A...
...or one hippopotamus-sized chicken on B? Do
you understand?
I understand! Okay, okay!
Jump! Okay.
One hundred... one hundred chicken-sized hippos...
...or one hippopotamus-sized chicken? I'm not
repeating it.
Oh, this is such a good one! Okay!
Ready! And...
...three, two, one! Ha!
Biboo! Biboo doesn't like adds, Biboo likes boss
battles! You should have known!
It's a boss battle! One! That's it!
I- I don't know the question! I just thought 100
was bad!
Ah, unfortunately for you!
Here she comes!
It's gonna be nasty!
Wait, see, see!
You have, you have one chance!
Ask for mercy!
Don't leave me!
Get some!
I told you!
No!
Don't leave me like this!
Don't leave me, okay?! No!
I'm going to the water!
Goodbye! I'm going to the water!
Goodbye! Goodbye!
Your turn now!
She became a mermaid.
She's swimming away.
We'll never see her again.
No, come back to us, Mococo-chan! Come back!
Mococo-chan, we need you!
I am my darkness now.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, my lady.
Last is my turn.
Means I can't get it wrong, which is pretty, feels pretty good.
Um, what's a good question? I'm not really sure.
Um, let's see.
Nerissa is a demon, but she's also half raven.
If I had to pick between worlds and either be just a demon or just a raven...
So demon is B.
Raven is A.
Which would I pick?
All right. Yes. Okay.
On three, okay?
One...
Two...
Three!
I knew you'd never give up being A!
I'm right!
I can't be A!
Yes, you can! You're stinky!
That's not fair!
I'm stinky!
I just think it would be great if I could have powers that aren't dependent on...
Well, we're in this together at least.
Yeah, yeah.
Something that can break, you know?
I thought being a demon is cooler though.
It is.
But wait, demons are friends from the underworld.
You know what's even cooler than being a demon, Shiori and Mococo?
What? I dare you!
Yeah? I dare you!
You've been very bad!
I dare you!
Yeah! There you go!
Mococo-chan, get you!
Yeah, you want Mococo-chan?
I like baths, okay?
Yeah, you like that?
Well, you like it so much, go take one in the ocean!
Go to the ocean!
The ocean you want!
Go!
Don't leave me like this!
Well, we'll never see them again.
Uh-oh.
They're getting lost in the water.
I think they're having too much fun.
Dripping up the sea!
But it's fine.
Don't eat the salt water.
Yeah, don't drink the water.
Glug glug glug. I'm sipping up the sea. Glug glug glug.
I'm, I'm gonna get rid of this.
That was fun.
Hey hey hey hey hey!
That didn't go so well, huh?
Look how dirty you are!
But hey, idols don't give up that easy, right?
You are idols, right?
Let's turn this around and shine again!
Wait, are we still idols after being soiled?
We weren't soiled!
And if you do...
I'll take you somewhere super special—
Don't soil me!
Oh! No way!
—where even Justice can't find us!
Where's that?
Another adventure!
I'm interested!
I want Justice to find me at some point.
Wait, what?
We'll be safe, but you can go.
Okay, just for now! Just for now!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go!
ドンドコソコ アソコ 見つからないぜ
Don-doko soko asoko, can't be found!
パパイヤ マンゴー ココナツ
Papaya, mango, coconut!
かき氷 いちご味
Shaved ice, strawberry flavor...
べろを出したら まっかっか
When I stick my tongue out, it's bright red!
Ai! 写真ざんす 水着 SHOW SAY!
Ai! Time for photos, swimsuit SHOW SAY!
ジャジャジャジャジャジャジャーン
Ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-jaan!
ココナツ (Yay!)
Coconut (Yay!)
カチカチに燃えてるお日様
The sun is burning intensely!
パシュワ ココナツ baby
Pa-shu-wa coconut baby!
待ちわびた季節はサマーサマー
The long-awaited season is summer summer!
パシュワ ココナツ baby
Pa-shu-wa coconut baby!
思い切って買ったビキニ
The bikini I took a chance and bought...
すっごく照れるけど負けらんない!
I'm so shy, but I won't lose!
日焼け止め ココナツ フレイバー
Sunscreen, coconut flavor!
パシュワ ココナツ baby
Pa-shu-wa coconut baby!
紫外線 トコナツ レーザー
UV rays, everlasting summer laser!
パシュワ ココナツ baby
Pa-shu-wa coconut baby!
どっきゅん ずっきゅん 君の視線
Dokkyun zukkyun, your gaze...
心臓 大爆発
My heart goes boom!
サシスセ ソコナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-se sokonatsu baby!
ダディドゥデ ドコナツ べいべー
Da-di-du-de dokonatsu baby!
カキクケ ココナツ べいべー
Ka-ki-ku-ke coconut baby!
サン!サン!サマータイム! (Yeah!)
Sun! Sun! Summertime! (Yeah!)
コー コー コー コー コー コー コー...
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co...
コココ　コーコー　ココ　コ...
Co-co-co-co-co...
ココ☆ナツ
Cocoa Nuts
カキ氷　メロン味
Shaved ice, melon flavor
ペロリ出したら
Stick out your tongue and...
ゾンビだ！
You're a zombie!
Ai!
勝負ゆかた着て、盆DANCEエイサーイ！
Put on your best yukata, it's Bon Dance Eisa!
ジャジャジャジャジャジャジャーン
Ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-jaan
ちょいなー
Choina
むしむし　うんざりね　熱帯夜
Humid and annoying tropical nights
ワッシュワ　ココナッツ　ベイベー
Woshwa Coconuts Baby
ココナッツジュース飲みたいな
I want to drink coconut juice
ワッシュワ　ココナッツ　ベイベー
Woshwa Coconuts Baby
長い夜で
In the long night
短いサマータイム
A short summer time
やっちゃったもん勝ちっ！
The first one to do it wins!
サシスセ　ソコナツ　ベイベー
Sa-shi-su-se sokonatsu baby
ダディドゥデ　ドコナッツ？　ベイベー
Da-di-du-de dokonatsu? baby
カキクケ　ココナツ　ベイベー
Ka-ki-ku-ke kokonatsu baby
サン！サン！サマータイム！
Sun! Sun! Summer time!
コココ　コーコー　ココ　コ...
Co-co-co-co-co...
ココ☆ナツ
Cocoa Nuts
ファイヤー！
Fire!
スススパーキング！
S-S-Sparking!
リリリリリンボー！
Li-li-li-li-limbo!
フィーバー！
Fever!
ソレヤ　ソレヤ　ソレヤ　ソレヤ
Soreya soreya soreya soreya
アチアチのサマー
Hot hot summer
九十九里浜
Kujukuri-hama
アイス激アマ
Super sweet ice cream
キャンプはさいたま
Camping in Saitama
サシスセ　ソコナツ　ベイベー
Sa-shi-su-se sokonatsu baby
ダディドゥデ　ドコナッツ？　ベイベー
Da-di-du-de dokonatsu? baby
カキクケ　ココナツ　ベイベー
Ka-ki-ku-ke kokonatsu baby
サン！サン！サマータイム！
Sun! Sun! Summer time!
コココ　コーコー　ココ　コ...
Co-co-co-co-co...
ココ☆ナツ
Cocoa Nuts
どこそこあそこ見つからないぜ
Here, there, and everywhere, they're nowhere to be found
パパイヤ　マンゴー　ココ☆ナツ
Papaya, mango, cocoa nuts!
Huh? Huh? Oh! Are we in our hideout?
Yeah! We're here! Home!
Wow, it's nice here.
Yeah, this is so fine.
Well, unless I invite them over.
But, isn't this our first time showing it in 3D to the Adventurers?
Yeah! 3D!
Don't you want to see our favorite part?
Yeah! Let's show them! Look over here!
Oh look! Look over here!
Yeah, all the candles! We have all that texture too!
Yeah, very nice! But that's not all!
Yeah! It's mine!
I have a favorite part too, you know.
What's that?
If you look up there...
Whoa! What light through yonder window breaks!
Wow, the moon is beautiful tonight.
月が綺麗ですね。
The moon is beautiful, isn't it?
Well, about my favorite part...
Look behind you.
Eh? Oh! This collection! It's all of my [censored]!
I have a bunch of like trinkets and stuff that we've collected over the years... right? right? and her [censored]!
Yes! And that! Hahaha!
But also, the couch! It's where we sit now! and they're so cute...
Wait, what's wrong? What?
Oh, wait. Weren't Fuwawa and Mococo wearing those?
Yeah, but they're right here.
Fuwamoco? Guys?
Right here!
Where's "here"?
I hear your voice but I do not see a body.
I think they're hiding.
Guys? No! Wait! We're down here!
Oh, they're so cute!
Yeah!
Wait a second.
Yeah?
Are those voices...
...coming from the- from the dogs?
I think this might be FUWAMOCO!
What?
Whoa!
Wait, FUWAMOCO have been turned into Dobermans?
Oh my god!
No!
Oh, no!
Yeah, you know, I think they actually look more like hellhounds like this...
...so it kind of fits!
Oh my god, hellhounds.
Give 'em a big pet.
Yeah!
Yoshi yoshi...
Good dog, good dog...
...good dogs.
You're a good girl, aren't you?
Yeah...
...good girl.
Good girl.
But wait, why- why are they Dobermans all of a sudden?
What happened?
Hahaha! Pokey! Pokey!
Hehehe! Not so fluffy and fuzzy now, hoeh!
Pokey!
Change us back down!
We can't eat donuts like this!
THAT's why you wanna turn back? Hmph, whatever.
I'll give you one final trial! Clear it, and I'll restore them!
Oh...
FUWAMOCO-chan, don't worry, we'll get you back to normal.
Okay, everybody help us, please!
I- I guess we'll give you one donut for the rescue.
Eh? Just one?
One donut?
What?
One each or what?
Sharing is caring!
Yeah.
Eh, I kind of like you like this, though.
Nerissa!
Well, Pokey, what kind of challenge are you going to give us today?
FUWAMOCO Fukuwarai!
FUWAMOCO Fukuwarai?
FUWAMOCO Fukuwarai
Behold, the challenge before you!
Oh!
The carpet has changed.
Whoa, why do they have no faces?
That's kind of scary.
Yeah, it is...
...a little bit spooky.
Hehe, ever heard of Fukuwarai?
It's this old-school Japanese game—
—lemme show you how it's played.
See those two giant faces? Their face parts are all scattered around.
Oh...
I see.
Yeah.
Bijou and Shiori will be blindfolded and carry the face parts!
Blindfold?
Oh, nice!
Oh, yeah, actually that sounds like fun.
Huh. We don't have to do anything.
Big bird, with your words alone, you must guide them.
Lead them to place each piece...
...and restore FUWAMOCO's face!
Me?
Yeah, you.
Oh, well, we're just gonna be over here blindfolded.
Yeah, we're just gonna chill.
Good luck.
Okay, I'll do my best.
No pressure.
I believe in you.
You've got 5 minutes. Better make it count!
Okay, let's all say FUWAMOCO together.
BAU BAU!
Let's do this!
Let's go!
All right, ladies.
So first plan of action...
...come on over, one on each side of me, pretty please.
Okay.
And then I would like you to turn around.
Oh, okay.
So, I have prepared for you...
...blindfolds.
So I'm gonna go ahead and just—
—you can feel free to adjust them as you like.
But, uh...
...that way...
...you won't be able to see anything since I have to direct you.
So go ahead and turn back around.
I cannot see a thing.
Yes, perfect, that's exactly what we want.
Aha.
All right, and then, uh, we're gonna go ahead and start...
...placing these things.
So FUWAMOCO...
...my puppies...
I'll do my best for you, okay?
Do your best!
Oh, you're so—
Let's do this!
Oh, my!
I love—let's do this!
Let's do it!
Okay...
...and start!
So, what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna hand you guys each a piece...
...and then I'm gonna tell you where to go.
Who goes first then?
So you're each gonna do one face.
Okay.
Uh, you're gonna start that way.
Wait, what?
Wait, what's happening?
Where am I?
What's this?
Shiori's just grabbing.
I don't know what to grab.
—let's grab.
Shiori, walk to me.
My paws are a bit little.
This is very small.
No! Yeah, yes, this way.
This way.
Come towards me.
If I accidentally grab something, I'm sorry.
Grab onto...
this.
This.
Yes.
Okay, don't move.
Okay.
Don't move!
Uh, Biboo...
...I want you to walk to the sound of my voice, okay?
Where is the sound of your voice?
Just follow the sound of my voice.
—to your right.
Your right.
Where is he?
Okay, just a little right.
Okay, forward.
Quickly!
Forward.
Okay, now come to me.
Where is "you"?
I want you to grab this.
Oh, okay.
I got it.
Yes.
So pretty much where you are right now...
...uh, not you, Shiori.
Okay, Shiori, come forward a little bit.
This forward?
Or this forward?
The forward towards me.
This forward.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Okay, that's too much.
Back up just a little bit.
You're out of time!
And then I want you to move...
your- your right.
Your right.
Right!
This is right.
Right.
Left!
Okay, back up.
FUWAMOCO-chan!
I don't know if this is gonna work out!
Place it down.
My legs are so strong...
...but now I'm regretting that.
Place it down, Biboo.
Oh, down?
Oh, okay.
Okay, forward a little bit.
Forward?
Okay, and then can you straighten it out?
Like this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just a little bit more.
Okay, yeah, and then can you just scoot
the whole thing over to...
Scoot, scoot, scoot, scoot...
...the right. No, left.
What about me? Should I do the same?
No, other way!
What are you doing?
Okay. Next items, next items.
Stay right where you are.
Stay right where you are?
I am here.
I am here too, okay.
I've got two.
Oh, I feel like this is a head.
I want you both... I want you
both to walk backwards, okay?
Okay.
Maybe straighten out a little bit.
Whoa, that's definitely a cheek.
Okay, back. No, actually you're perfect, Shio.
Biboo, you better get running.
Place... place one down.
Which one of those? This one?
You're going too far! This way!
Wait, where am I going?
This one's okay, right?
No, move it over to the right.
I'm at my right! My right, my right!
Okay, place the other one.
I don't want to... I don't want to continue like this.
Trust me! This way!
This way?
No, where I am.
Yes, I also have to be like this.
Okay, people. Yeah, come towards
the sound of my voice.
Where is the sound of your voice?!
Forward, forward, forward.
Okay, stop. Now come this way a little bit.
Turn... this way.
Do you hear where I am?
Oh yes, yes.
Pretend... pretend you're in
a Nermars game, okay?
Oh yes, I heard. I felt your foot.
Perfect. Okay, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, now I want you to turn a little bit this way.
Which way? This is a lot of ways!
Rotate your body! Rotate!
And this is all wrong!
Okay, so now I want you to place the one
in your left hand down, okay? On the ground.
Like this?
Yeah, okay. Now I want you to walk
slightly in this direction. Just like crab walk.
This is so hard!
See what ear I'm at?
Oh yes.
Like a Nermars game. Think of it
like a game, people.
Okay, I think so.
Place it down.
Like this?!
Don't... stop! I'm doing my best!
Shiori, go to what...
You have one minute. One more, okay?
Okay, I'm done.
Now move to the other side. Yes, yes.
So, people. You are... walk this way.
Okay, walk this way.
Okay, put it down. Right there.
Yeah!
Wait, no, that's wrong! Pick it back up!
Ahhh!
Walk... opposite side.
Opposite side?
Behind you! Move backwards, backwards, backwards,
backwards, backwards, backwards.
Okay, down!
At least my face looks a bit better
than yours, Shio.
Now walk this way.
Which is... this way?
Yeah, yeah. Now walk to your left.
30 seconds!
No, no. Sorry, right. I think
you messed up, Shio.
Sorry! Sorry!
This way! Left, left, left! This way!
Yes! Okay, now forward.
Everything is going so slow.
Forward. Yes. Now put it down.
So good. Yeah, and the last one, please.
Okay. 15 seconds left! Are you done?
And... make it work! Make it work, my brain!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. 15 seconds.
Don't worry about it, don't worry about it.
Okay. Are we done?
Yeah!
Okay, I want you guys to turn on around and we're going
to take off your blindfolds so you can see how you did, okay?
Wait, which one's around?
This way.
This way?
Well, let's take a look.
I bet we did great.
Never thought to look at you.
Mococo, what do you think? Isn't it good?
Hey, Bijou, Shiori! You sure this is Fuwawa and Mococo?
Yeah, look at it.
Something seems a little... off.
Nah, nah, nah. It looks great!
Yeah, it's not like it's upside down or anything.
Seriously, can we have a look down?
I think it looks perfect.
Why are you looking at... I'm not seeing any better.
You're not making it better!
It's perfect! It's perfect!
Wait, wait, wait. What if I put this over here?
I want to put it there.
Don't touch my face!
Put it on the eye. Yeah! Great!
Everything is great!
I like the decision, you see, to... to do it like this,
because I just wanted to see what it would look like just a little lower.
This is not good.
Well, it's good enough to get changed back, Pokey!
Hmph, fine. I'll change them back!
Yay! Bau bau!
We can't be FuwaMoco anymore!
Hah! Hah! Yeah!
Yeah! We did it!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
You didn't make my dream come true.
That's not good, no no no no no!
It's okay, I like you better this way.
This is not on the face!
I'm really glad we could get through this together. Aren't you guys?
Yeah!
The power of friendship!
As Advent, you've gotta keep working together and looking out for one another!
Yeah, that's karma. Yeah, get down.
Howl!
Checkmate, I'm a superstar. Stay insane, but you rock with it, uh.
Yeah, like 24/7 I'm a hot mess ya love-hate.
Get less for oh my god. ホームラン, バタバタ swing my shot,
Get less for oh my god. Home run, fluttery, swing my shot,
oh woah-woah-a yeah.
Like a villainess, villainous, bring home the jackpot.
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Both heroes and villains are the same
派手にブチかまそう
Let's make a grand entrance
But ya ya ya!
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
“Chaotic good” is peak right now. I can show ya how.
But ya ya ya!
Don't get confused, we are not the same. I'm a ruthless dame.
No way, no way, yeah, way oh way, yeah.
“Good vs Evil” is so overdone.
Let's all kick back and party. Just leave it to me.
Whoops!
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips yeah, uh.
That's karma. Tada-ha-ha-ha. Awoooo!
Loosen my lips,
I'm about to say some ish, get it yeah,
That's karma. Tada-ha-ha-ha.
Sorry I'm just better.
Sorry we're go-getters.
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunnin' tricky why you runnin' uh-huh.
Bet'cha think you're clever. Whatever!
Talk about a “kumbaya”!
Hey yo! Check this out!
フルボッコっちゃって 欲望召し上がれ
Get beaten up, eat your desires
アイドルのハート Get down サイコパス さよなら最高ですわ
Idol's heart Get down Psychopath, goodbye, it's the best
Bomb! ドメスティック Bomb! ドラマティック
Bomb! Domestic Bomb! Dramatic
愛しき人々 この指止まれ
Dear people, follow my lead
ハートに ハートは ハイになって ハジけて恥じらい捨てちゃいな
To the heart, the heart gets high, burst forth and throw away your shame
叫びをド派手に誇れ 激動的情緒だ寄越して頂戴
Be proud of your grand shouting, give me those turbulent emotions
進化のパラダイス
Paradise of evolution
惹かれ合う 感覚が共鳴共鳴
Drawn to each other, our senses are resonating
“Good vs Evil”, but I'm which one?
Just stuck here in the middle. That's not any fun.
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips yeah, uh.
That's karma. Tada-ha-ha-ha. Awoooo!
Loosen my lips,
I'm about to say some ish, get it yeah,
That's karma. Tada-ha-ha-ha.
想像から創造 衝動から猛攻
From imagination to creation, from impulse to onslaught
ほらあっという間に華麗に 変幻、変幻自在
Look, in the blink of an eye, a splendid transformation, phantasmagoric
喧しい本能 喰らえ咆哮
Noisy instinct, eat the roar
Talk about a “kumbaya”, ‘baya’!
Sorry I'm just better. Sorry!
Sorry we're go-getters. Oh!
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunnin' tricky why you runnin' uh-huh.
Bet'cha think you're clever. Whatever!
Talk about a “kumbaya”!
Isekai Queen, switchin' g-minor, California Cacophony.
Welcome to Miss Fortune's game.
But ya ya ya! But ya ya ya!
Well, that was Go-Getters!
How did you like our performance!?
To everybody watching right now... We all have some big news!
And guess what? For our second anniversary, we have TWO big announcements!
The first one is...
A BRAND NEW SONG!
Our second original song in the story of Advent, “PRISONER”, will be released on August 31st at 12 AM local time in each region!
It's just Prisoner music video
it doesn't matter, it's gonna sound great!
Yeah!
If you want to find out,
don't go anywhere 'cause you'll be redirected
to the music video right after the stream!
Yeah! Let's go!
And guess what?
We're also about to premiere the new song
right after this!
Yeah! Oh my god!
All right everybody, are you ready?
Places, places! Okay! Places!
Okay.
Locked away where nightmares keep you awake,
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
(You're all mine, all mine, all mine!)
You'll never escape...
(You're all mine, all mine!)
Wayward soul, I'll wrap you up
in darkness that consumes you whole,
hold you in my labyrinth of walls
(Lost in the depths that swallow you, where just your shadows follow you)
Always churning in the deep,
I won't let you sleep
You don't need your dreams now that you belong to me
Throw them all away,
you're too frail to be free
You will always be
My lovely prisoner
Are you shaking?
My eyes will find you, let me clutch you tightly
(You can only be mine)
Poor little prisoner
Are you breaking?
My chains will bind you here forever,
Stay here for all time
in tenebris
in frigore
in carcere
Close your eyes, go deeper
in the emptiness that plagues your mind,
let my dark envelop your light
I will keep you safe and sound,
Hear the blissful silence all around
I'll drag you down below,
never let you go
Everything you've been,
the transgressions of your past,
Throw them all away,
let me hold you at last
My lovely prisoner
What's the matter?
You're never leaving, you are mine forever
Got to keep you right here
Poor, helpless prisoner
Did you shatter?
Why are you grieving your ambitions?
Let them disappear
I can hear your plea,
reaching desperately,
but I'll never, ever set you free
Stay with me
My lovely prisoner
Are you shaking?
My eyes will find you, let me clutch you tightly
(You can only be mine)
Poor little prisoner
Are you breaking?
My chains will bind you here forever,
Stay here for all time
in tenebris
in frigore
in carcere
Yeah! That was our new song,
Prisoner!
What did you think of the track, huh?
Hot song, huh?
Okay, and let's all move on to the second piece of
exciting news. Get close girls!
Hololive English -Advent-
2nd Anniversary Celebration
2nd Anniversary Celebration!
Woo! Unbelievable!
First up, we have
the Framed Art Board!
Frame Art Board
It's a large illustration board framed beautifully.
The luxurious frame features our logo
with foil stamping for the extra shine.
It's a perfect item to decorate your home
and to enjoy looking at every single day
so you can see all of us together,
just like we should be.
Yeah!
Well, next up,
we have a sticker set from 2024 Halloween version!
Sticker Set (Halloween 2024 ver.) (5 Types)
Five different designs, and it includes the
VRChat design released for Halloween,
plus a three-piece sticker set featuring
each Advent member's original design.
And then you can put them on your phone,
stick them on your PC, and have fun with them.
Yeah! Let's go!
All right, next up we got
the Connectable Charm!
Connecting Charm (5 Types)
What's awesome is that all these charms
can actually connect!
Connecting Charm (5 Types)
...to each other,
so you can mix and match for
all kinds of different ways, right?
And have fun!
Yeah! Woo!
Varsity Jacket
Finally, we've got the Varsity Jacket!
Wow!
It's got the Advent logo on the back,
and Pero is embroidered on the front tassel too!
Fun! Woo!
And guess what?
What?
You can actually attach those charms I just showed you
on the zipper of the jacket too!
Woo!
You know, it's a cool item that you can rock
both in your everyday life and at events too!
Yeah! Woo!
And guess what?
What?
It's happening right now!
The merch just dropped at the hololive official shop!
Now! Ta-da!
Hey guys, notice that guy showing up on the bottom,
the bottom left, left of the YouTube screen?
Left! Left!
Go ahead and click it to shop your favorites, okay?
Click click click click click click click click!
This was such a wonderful day together. I had so much fun.
Yeah, we did!
Even though we were running from justice half the time.
Yeah, but that's a typical Friday!
Were we really worried?
No! Better luck next time, Justice!
As if you could ever catch us!
We're Advent!
Yeah!
And don't forget that we've been together for two years now!
Yeah! Can you believe it?
Wait! That's a lot of memories!
Yeah, lots of memories, and we're looking forward to
all of the next years together!
Year three, year four,
year five, year six!
Yeah! Seven! Ten!
Advent is forever!
Rock! Adventure!
Rock! Adventure! Forever!
Rock! Adventure! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live: On the Run!