(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Ayo mulai!!
Let's get started!!
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も
Body and soul...
この手で make you mine
I'll make you mine with these hands
Woah...
Oh baby I need you
I need you ずっと
I need you forever
君を見るたび
Every time I see you
上書きされてく 欲望に
My desires are overwritten
重なる Eyes, eyes, eyes
Our eyes meet, eyes, eyes, eyes
魅了する Smile, smile, smile
Your captivating smile, smile, smile
ねぇ その姿形
Hey, your form and shape
全てが拍車かけてく
Everything spurs me on
恋から 愛, 愛, 愛
From a crush to love, love, love
毎秒 可笑しくなってく
Going crazy every second
手を伸ばせばもう届く距離
Within reach if I just stretch out my hand
危険なエグジット 試したい
I want to try a dangerous exit
穏やかに恋したい
I want to love you peacefully
どんなシーンも私に見せて
Show me every scene
このまま Stay by my side
Just stay by my side
どこにも行かないで
Don't go anywhere
100%
純粋な愛だから
Because it's pure love
止められない感情
Unstoppable emotions
その腕で抱きしめてよ
Hold me in those arms
もっと奥まで連れてよ
Take me even deeper
ずっともっと近くで
Always, closer and closer
熱苦しいほど
So much it's stifling
持て余すだけなら Fly
If it's too much to handle, then fly
Tell me what's wrong with me
名前もない普通だし
It's just nameless and ordinary
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I do need you いま すぐ
I do need you, right now
最初は声を聞く
At first, I heard your voice
それだけでよかった
That was all I needed
だけど次第に
But gradually...
ワガママになった
I became selfish
誰かに微笑みかける
You smiling at someone else
その仕草に苛立ち
Irritated by that gesture
隠せない自分に気づいた
I realized I couldn't hide it
独り占めしたい
I want you all to myself
いっそ鎖に繋いで
I'd rather you be chained to me
二人きりの部屋至近距離
A room for just the two of us, close range
強引な発言 誇示したい
I want to show off my forceful words
想い捨てて眠りたい
I want to throw away my feelings and sleep
その吐息感じさせて
Let me feel your breath
永遠に Stay by your side
Forever by your side
どこにも行かせない
I won't let you go anywhere
100%
私だけに依存してね
Depend only on me
色褪せぬ愛情
Love that never fades
丸ごと受け止めてよ
Accept all of it
もっと私を剥き出して
Expose more of me
たとえ息ができないほど
Even if I can't breathe
熱苦しいほど
So much it's stifling
止められない絶対
Unstoppable, absolutely
Tell me what's wrong with me
名前もない普通だし
It's just nameless and ordinary
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I do need you いま すぐ
I do need you, right now
目を閉じたら
When I close my eyes
止められない愛が
Unstoppable love...
触れたい
I want to touch you
For you
私の歌声だけ
Only my singing voice
このまま Stay by my side
Just stay by my side
二度と離れないで
Never leave me again
100%
純粋な愛だから
Because it's pure love
この路地を抜けろ
Escape through this alleyway
Awake now
(Whoa 僕ら覚醒 アップデート hey)
(Whoa, we're awakening, update, hey)
ギラギラ光らせた いいな いいな そのカラット
Glittering and shining, so nice, those carats
目立っちゃうな自然に視線を独り占め
Standing out, naturally hogging all the attention
この手口は盗めない
This trick can't be stolen
答えなら「好きなだけ」が極まってく
If it's an answer, 'as much as I like' is peaking
一秒前完全アップデート yeah
One second ago, a complete update, yeah
不安ぐっばい 自分以外は敵じゃない
Anxiety, goodbye, no one but myself is an enemy
お利口 ゴミ用 指を立てろ
Clever, for the trash, raise your finger
ハ〜 揺れろ運命
Ah, shake, destiny
Ah〜あたらしいウルトラC
Ah, a brand new Ultra C
その感情を燃料
Fueling those emotions
Oh baby 一瞬
Oh baby, in an instant
I need you ずっと
I need you forever
Oh baby I need you I need you ずっと
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever
逃げるなら今だぜ
If you're going to run, now's the time
勝利を願っちゃって
Go ahead and wish for victory
ハジケチャッテ！
Let's burst out!
This is Hololive!
レッツゴー センセーション Together!
Let's go sensation, together!
Are you ready? もしや天下の才？
Are you ready? Perhaps a talent of the world?
夢眠り去りに 15分
15 minutes after the dream fades
芽吹く目覚め 反射し先見
A budding awakening, reflecting foresight
ほら 誰か 抽選 スキャニング
Look, someone is lottery scanning
Out of video 街はスタンバイなう
Out of video, the city is on standby now
今更正直飽き飽きなんだよ
Honestly, I'm already tired of this
遠回し残酷 私には血の味ね
Indirect and cruel, it tastes like blood to me
運命的に当選
A fateful winning ticket
招ききの山 120
A mountain of invitations, 120
Oh good luck 祈る幸運なんかより
Oh, rather than praying for good luck
確かな自分を力
Trusting my own certain strength
Day by day 正体あらあら
Day by day, the true colors are showing
言いたいこと全部ピンを刺した
Pinning down everything I want to say
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's fine even if you laugh
震えるくらいクラコワ遊び
A thrill that makes you shake, Kurakowa play
Victory to the worldへ
Towards victory for the world
揺れる感情をぎゅっと噛み締めるはずよ
I'll surely keep my swaying emotions in check
見ててみててよ この曲を
Watch me, watch me, with this song
手に入れてしまって
Taking it for myself
Kobo-chan! Ayo nyanyi bareng!
Kobo-chan! Let's sing together!
Ayo Anya-chan! Ayo mana suaranya!
Come on Anya-chan! Let's hear your voice!
Day by day もがいてもがいて
Day by day, struggling and struggling
俺らこそが真理だ カウントとって
We're the truth, take the count
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's fine even if you laugh
震える皆いつかチャンピオンを遊びだけ
Someday you'll all be shaking champions, just playing
Victory to the worldへ
Towards victory for the world
絶対に抜くよ あの光る軌道を
I'll definitely overtake that shining orbit
忘れられないほどの勝利を願っちゃって
Praying for an unforgettable victory
Hah... Siapa di sini...
Sigh... Who's here...
Capek...
I'm tired...
Capek ya...
You're tired, huh...
Kalau capek, enaknya gimana nih, Oro?
If you're tired, what should we do, Oro?
Balas saja!
Just retaliate!
Cakep!
Nice!
Bukannya sudah biasa
Isn't it already common
Ditikam oleh kecewa
To be stabbed by disappointment
Aduh!
Ouch!
Low riskじゃ物足りなくなっちゃったし
Low-risk just isn't enough for me anymore
有り余って笑っちゃうくらい
There's so much left in me, I could laugh
なんも無いなんて言ったってしょうがないし
It's no use saying there's nothing here
お手上げで Hi-Five
Give up, high-five
前ならえで後に続いたってつまんねえ
Following the leader, following behind is boring
夢を語れ、追え!が この街のStandard
Tell your dreams, follow them! That's this city's standard
Tada mitetai dake
Just wanting to watch
なんてのは嘘
That's a lie
Saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya... oh oh
When the world doesn't go as it should... oh oh
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya kau coba lepaskan saja
Maybe it's finally time for you to just let it go
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
No need to ask why anymore
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If indeed you don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry over it, try to get through the puzzle
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja, jalani saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be, just live it
Mau gimana lagi? Walau kadang mati rasa
What else can we do? Even if you feel numb sometimes
Bahkan hingga tak berdaya
Even to the point of being helpless
Dan usahamu terasa sia-sia
And your efforts feel in vain
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If indeed you don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry over it, try to get through the puzzle
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Lepas semua kendali
Release all control
Tancap gas dan berlari
Step on the gas and run
Terima dan sudahi
Accept it and end it
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If indeed you don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry over it, try to get through the puzzle
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja, jalani saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be, just live it
Mau gimana lagi?
What else can we do?
Halo Comic Frontier!
Hello, Comic Frontier!
Halo!
Hello!
Welcome to hololive Indonesia
5th Anniversary LIVE
Chromatic Future!
Yeeay!
Yay!
Wah gila gila gila!
Wow, crazy crazy crazy!
Makasih banyak semuanya udah pada datang ke konser 5 tahun kita ya!
Thank you so much everyone for coming to our 5th year concert!
Wah nggak berasa nggak sih udah 5 tahun aja?
Wow, doesn't it feel like it's been 5 years already?
Kalau gitu, kita mulai dari perkenalan diri dulu nggak sih?
In that case, shall we start with introductions?
Mulai dari aku! Aku! Aku!
Starting from me! Me! Me!
Ah ah mission start!
Aku Vestia Zeta dari hololive Indonesia Gen 3. Nice to meet you!
I'm Vestia Zeta from hololive Indonesia Gen 3. Nice to meet you!
Kaela grinding every time, the blacksmith from hololive ID Gen 3. I'm Kaela Kovalskia, nice to meet you all!
Bokobokoboko Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day.
Ehem! Kobokan mana suaranya?!
Ehem! Kobokan, where's your voice?!
Nah bertiga kami dari hololive Indonesia Gen 3, Holoh3ro!
So, the three of us are from hololive Indonesia Gen 3, Holoh3ro!
Wah nggak nyangka juga deh konser 5th Anniversary hololive ID ini akhirnya ada juga.
Wow, I didn't expect this hololive ID 5th Anniversary concert to finally happen.
Dari lagu pertama aja udah keren banget guys. Kerasa nggak?!
Even from the first song it's been so cool guys. Can you feel it?!
Kasih semangatnya, iya nggak sih, iya nggak sih?
Give them some spirit, right? Right?
Iya, parah sih ada adrenalin, rasakan ya.
Yeah, the adrenaline is crazy, feel it.
Pengen lari aku rasanya nih. Woi, woi, woi, woi!
I feel like running. Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Eh, mau ke mana?
Hey, where are you going?
Stop stop stop stop stop stop!
Nanti keringetan lho, nanti keringetan.
You'll get sweaty, you'll get sweaty.
Eh, Kak Ela gimana?
So, how about you, Kaela?
Aduh, seru banget. Aku nggak nyangka sih
Oh, it's so exciting. I didn't expect
sampai aku bisa ada di sini ya.
I could actually be here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong konser masih panjang banget,
But anyway, the concert is still very long,
jadi kalian tetap semangat ya sampai akhir!
so keep your spirit up until the end!
Semangat! Semangat! Semangat!
Keep it up! Keep it up! Keep it up!
Eh, tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi,
But speaking of the concert,
emang pada tahu judul konsernya apa?
does everyone know the title?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah Chromatic Future!
Our concert title this time is Chromatic Future!
Ada yang tahu nggak artinya apa? Ayo absen!
Does anyone know what it means? Let's hear it!
Nah ini, Kobo paling tahu.
Now this, Kobo knows best.
Ya, yang ngejelasin yang paling tinggi. Let's go!
Yeah, let the tallest one explain. Let's go!
Segitu ya... Ya udahlah. Nih ya guys ya,
Is that how it is... Fine. Here's the thing guys,
buat kalian yang belum tahu,
for those of you who don't know,
Chromatic Future itu artinya tuh masa depan
Chromatic Future means a future
yang berwarna-warni.
that is colorful.
Jadi karena Hololive Indonesia kan udah 5 tahun nih,
Since Hololive Indonesia has been around for 5 years,
kita sama-sama dari hari 1 sampai sekarang.
we've been together from day 1 until now.
Nah, jadi itu untuk ke depannya kita tuh
So, for the future, our hope is that
juga harapannya tuh kita bisa nyiptain waktu
we can create times
dan memori yang berwarna-warni
and memories that are colorful
sama seluruh fans dari Hololive Indonesia.
with all the fans of Hololive Indonesia.
Ya gitu, betul Kaela Kovalskia.
That's right, Kaela Kovalskia.
Cakep, cakep, cakep!
Great, great, great!
Nah, kalian sekarang udah pada tahu kan
Now you all know
karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
since Kaela just explained it.
Kalau gitu konsernya kan udah mulai nih.
Anyway, the concert has already started.
Kalian mau nge-post soal konser ini di medsos,
If you want to post about this concert on social media,
jangan lupa hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture ya.
don't forget the hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture.
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh...
Because we really want to see you guys...
apa sih... pengen lihat semangat kalian!
what is it... want to see your spirit!
Ya, itu betul banget, ya nggak?
Yeah, that's exactly right, isn't it?
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
No typos, no typos!
Asyik, share ke semua, oke?
Awesome, share it with everyone, okay?
Jadi tapi jujur deh, kalian tuh pas dibilang
But honestly, when you were told
kita bakal konser lho di Indonesia, kaget nggak sih?
we'd have a concert in Indonesia, were you surprised?
Halo, ada yang dengerin?
Hello, is anyone listening?
Betul, aku setuju juga.
True, I agree as well.
Aku merasakan empati terhadap adik saya Zeta.
I feel empathy for my younger sister Zeta.
Empati, iya iya.
Empathy, yeah yeah.
Aku juga waktu itu nggak nyangka banget kayak
I also didn't expect it at all, like,
'hah beneran? Ini real-ly?' gitu kan.
'huh really? Is this real-ly?' right.
Kayak 'loh bisa gitu?' Akhirnya mana
Like 'how could that be?' Finally,
udah bersembilan di Indonesia pula ya kan.
all nine of us are in Indonesia too, right.
Keren banget! Keren banget!
So cool! So cool!
Ini kan konser pertama Hololive Indonesia bersembilan.
This is the first Hololive Indonesia concert with nine.
Sebenarnya tuh nggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar
Actually, this is not only the biggest
dan terpenting juga untuk fans Hololive Indonesia,
and most important moment for the fans here,
tapi seluruh dunia juga pasti bakal nonton nggak sih?
but the whole world will be watching, right?
Ya nggak? Jawab!
Right? Answer me!
Iya iya, makasih makasih semuanya.
Yeah, thank you everyone.
Wait, tapi tentu aja ini pencapaiannya
Wait, but of course this achievement
nggak bakal cuma sampai di sini aja kan?
won't just stop here, right?
Jadi next-nya mungkin kita bisa apa ya...
So next, maybe we can... what is it...
dominating the world gitu. We ready!
dominate the world. We're ready!
Ready! Ready! Ready! Ready!
Zeta, selain dari dukungan fans di opportunity ini,
Zeta, besides the fans' support on this opportunity,
kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih
we also want to say thank you
untuk semua sponsor yang mendukung konser ini.
to all the sponsors who supported this concert.
Terima kasih!
Thank you!
Makasih! Makasih! Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
Eh, tapi ngomong-ngomong di konser ini
Wait, speaking of which, in this concert,
kayaknya ada yang beda nggak sih?
is there something different?
Ela kamu nyadar nggak? Kamu paling peka kan?
Ela, do you notice? You're the most observant.
Wait, ya sadarlah.
Wait, of course I notice.
Kalau Kobo mah nggak bakalan sadar.
Kobo wouldn't even notice.
Nih nih nih, yang beda tuh kali ini tuh
Look, what's different this time is
model kita. Ini model baru nih!
our models. These are new models!
Gemes banget! Lucu lucu!
So cute! Cute, cute!
Lucu lucu lucu lucu!
Cute cute cute cute!
Kameranya deketin ke aku! Kameranya deketin ke aku!
Bring the camera closer to me! Closer to me!
Nah mulai, mulai...
Here she goes...
Kaya keimutan Kobo nih, nyenyenye...
Look at Kobo's cuteness, nyenyenye...
Eh, oh, eh, eh...
Wait, oh, hey, hey...
Wait wait wait, kamera diambil Kobo semua nggak sih?
Wait, the camera's all taken by Kobo, right?
Ini ke aku juga, aku juga, aku juga!
To me too, me too, me too!
Jangan Kobo doang!
Not just Kobo!
Sini sini sini! Kamera! Kamera!
Here here here! Camera! Camera!
Stop stop stop stop! Mulai mulai...
Stop stop stop stop! Here they go...
Semua kamera diambil!
Taking all the cameras!
Oke oke oke. Aduh sampai kehabisan napas.
Okay, okay. Man, I'm out of breath.
Jangan berebutan di depan konser!
Don't fight in front of the concert!
Iya iya, Zeta, iya.
Yeah, Zeta, yeah.
Kasihan kalau Zeta udah ngomong.
Poor Zeta when she's talking.
Kalau nggak boleh rebutan kamera sama Zeta,
If I can't fight over the camera with Zeta,
ugh... sokonai! Kita main aja deh sama penonton.
humph! Let's just play with the audience.
Kobo pengen deh coba kita teriakin penonton,
Kobo wants to try shouting at the audience,
karena kan tadi mereka sudah teriakin kita.
because they shouted at us earlier.
Maksudnya kita teriakin intro kita
I mean, we shout our intro
bareng penonton-tachi!
together with the audience!
Betul! Teriaknya bareng penonton,
Right! Shout with the audience,
jangan teriakin penontonnya!
don't shout at the audience!
Iya gitu maksudnya.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
Soalnya kan habis ini kita harus nyanyi.
Because after this we have to sing.
Jadi kita harus simpen suara dulu nggak sih?
So we should save our voices, shouldn't we?
Betul ya. Gak bakal lama itu ternyata...
That's right. It won't be that long...
tenang aja gak bakal selama stream Kaela ya guys.
don't worry, it won't be as long as Kaela's stream.
Ya udahlah mau teriak-teriak ya udah,
Well, if you want to shout, fine,
aku nggak masalah lah aku ikut.
I don't mind, I'll join in.
Gimana nih semuanya? Udah siap belum?
How's it going everyone? Are you ready yet?
Siap gak?
Are you ready?
Siap nih kayaknya. Oke! Kobo dulu ya.
Looks like they're ready. Okay! Kobo first.
Aku mau kita sama-sama teriak...
I want us to shout together...
Baka baka baka!
Oke siap ya!
Okay, ready!
Satu, dua, tiga...
One, two, three...
Baka baka baka!
Suka-suka... Giliran Zeta, giliran Zeta.
Suka-suka... Zeta's turn, Zeta's turn.
Pas aku bilang 'Mission Starto',
When I say 'Mission Starto',
kalian bareng-bareng teriak 'Starto' ya.
you all shout 'Starto' together.
Siap? Aaa...
Ready? Aaa...
Mission...
Starto!
Oke habis ini Kaela.
Okay, Kaela's next.
Oke oke oke. Nah ini ya buat semua penonton
Okay okay okay. Now for all the viewers
sama HoloHero juga, kalau misalnya
and HoloHero too, if I
aku bilang 'HoloHero', kalian bilang 'Hoo-Haa!'
say 'HoloHero', you say 'Hoo-Haa!'
Oke ya, siap ya. HoloHero!
Okay, ready. HoloHero!
Hoo-Haa! Mantap mantap!
Hoo-Haa! Great, great!
Mantap mantap mantap. Keren keren keren.
Great, great, great. Cool, cool, cool.
Akhirnya Gen 3 kompak juga.
Finally, Gen 3 is synchronized too.
Kompak ya, iya kompak kelihatannya.
Synchronized, yeah, looks synchronized.
Masih pada semangat nih ya.
You're still energetic, right?
Soalnya dari lagu pertama kita
Because from our first song
hari ini aja udah kerasa banget.
today, it already felt so strong.
Kalian tuh pada nyangka nggak sih
Did you guys expect
kalau lagu pertama kita tuh bakal 100%?
that our first song would be 100%?
Beh, mana ada yang nyangka?
Who would've expected it?
Aku aja sendiri nggak nyangka juga.
Even I didn't expect it myself.
Langsung dibuka dengan 'Hoshinova' mode.
Opening right away with 'Hoshinova' mode.
Asyik asyik. Keren banget sih.
Nice, nice. It was so cool.
Apalagi tadi Zeta sama Kaela nyanyi '100%'
Especially when Zeta and Kaela sang '100%'
tuh udah kayak real 100% ya.
it felt like a real 100%.
Itu tuh bisa nggak sih gak sekeren tadi?
Could it be any less cool than that?
Aku tuh jadi ingin kayak... ugh ugh gitu kan.
I felt like... ugh ugh.
Kalian pernah nggak sih? Aura farming ya?
Have you guys ever? Aura farming, right?
Aura farming sesungguhnya keren banget
Real aura farming, it's really cool,
emang lagunya Moona.
Moona's song is indeed cool.
Emang kan, Zeta kan soalnya biasanya
Right, because Zeta usually sings
lagu-lagu yang stylish, jazzy jazzy gitu,
stylish and jazzy songs,
tadi pas dinyanyiin '100%' vibes-nya beda.
so '100%' had a completely different vibe.
Terus Kaela juga tadi nge-rap ya...
And Kaela was rapping too...
ta-da-da-da-da...
Iya pokoknya keren banget tadi.
Anyway, it was so cool.
Keren banget ya tadi. Tapi habis ini
It was really cool. But after this
tuh masih ada lagi, 'New Zombie'.
there's more, 'New Zombie'.
Ayo pada tau dong ini lagu siapa?
Come on, you guys know whose song this is?
Tau lah tau lah,
Of course, of course,
senpai kita, senpai kita.
our senpai, our senpai.
Tadi tuh HoloRo perform-nya juga
That was HoloRo's performance,
keren banget kayak lagi di game gitu.
it was very cool, like being in a game.
Betul setuju. Terus tadi ada backdancer-nya,
True, I agree. And there were backdancers,
keren ya guys, keren nggak?
cool right guys? Was it cool?
Keren!
Cool!
Terus ada apa lagi tuh tadi? Lampu laser,
And what else was there? Laser lights,
terus ada efek kembang api segala,
firework effects and all,
banyaklah gimmick-gimmick yang wow.
lots of wow gimmicks.
Itu backdancer nanti aku hire semua ya.
I'll hire all those backdancers later.
Wah udah ngomong konser solo aja.
Wow, already talking about a solo concert.
Ini ngomong adalah doa ya.
Speaking is a prayer.
Tapi konser yang ini belum selesai.
But this concert isn't over yet.
Eh, tapi kalian tahu nggak sih
Eh, but do you guys know
sebelum ini tuh nyanyi lagu apa?
what song was sung before this?
Eh aku mah tahu banget lah,
Oh, I definitely know,
itu lagu terbaru aku, 'Dalah'.
it's my latest song, 'Dalah'.
Iya, udah. Nggak usah dibahas. Udahlah.
Yeah, okay. No need to discuss it. Enough.
Lho kok gitu? Itu tuh maksudnya
Wait, why like that? I meant
judulnya 'Dalah', lagunya judulnya 'Dalah'.
the title is 'Dalah', the song is 'Dalah'.
Oh... iya iya... oh 'Dalah'.
Oh... right right... oh 'Dalah'.
Bilang dong dari tadi.
You should've said so earlier.
Habisnya kamu kan sering 'dalah dalah' gitu,
Because you often say 'dalah dalah',
jadi dikirain emang beneran 'dalah'.
so we thought it was just you being fed up.
Entar 'dalah dalah' pulang dia.
Later she'll 'dalah dalah' and go home.
Kasihan yang nonton.
Pity the viewers.
Kalau gitu 'Dalah' tuh maksudnya apa sih?
If so, what does 'Dalah' actually mean?
Dalah sama kehidupan.
Fed up with life.
Hidup tuh berat ya guys ya.
Life is hard, guys.
Kalau hidup berat ya udah 'dalah' aja,
If life is hard, just be fed up with it,
habis itu lanjutkan hidupmu.
then continue your life.
Iya betul di kehidupan yang dewasa ini ya.
Yeah, that's right, in this adult life.
...untuk...
...for...
...lagu nyantai, easy listening.
...a relaxed, easy-listening song.
Jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan, nyapa fans, gitu ya?
So we were walking around, greeting fans, right?
Asik banget ya tadi ya?
It was so much fun, wasn't it?
Aku juga suka banget tadi bagian reff-nya ya.
I also really liked the chorus part.
Da la da la da la da...
Itu... itu beda lagu gak sih?
Wait... isn't that a different song?
Eh, nggak gitu deh...
Eh, not like that...
Gitu kayaknya...
I think it was like that...
Ya tapi pokoknya asik lah ya kalau nyanyi lagu chill santai-santai kayak gini.
But anyway, it's fun to sing chill, relaxing songs like this.
Iya santai dong.
Yeah, let's relax.
Tapi ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu.
But speaking of relaxing, we actually can't relax just yet.
Hei, santai!
Hey, relax!
Karena kayaknya katanya nggak boleh santai...
Because I heard we're not allowed to relax...
Iya iya iya jangan santai-santai...
Yeah, yeah, don't relax too much...
Jangan terlalu santai.
Don't be too relaxed.
Karena konsernya tuh masih panjang!
Because the concert is still far from over!
Jadi sebelum itu, kalian ada nggak yang mau kalian sampaikan dulu?
So before that, is there anything you'd like to say?
Mulai dari ini nih yang nggak bisa diem.
Starting with this one who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja.
Just three words.
I love you.
Keren. The best.
Cool. The best.
Sangat jelas ya.
Very clear.
Tetap semangat.
Keep up the spirit.
Tetap semangat menjalani hidup ya.
Keep up the spirit in living life.
Udah gitu aja. Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang.
That's all. Anyway, it's still long until the end.
Semangat!
Spirit!
Saranghaeyo!
Gomawayo!
Oke, kalau aku...
Okay, as for me...
Yah, semangat selalu!
Well, always keep your spirit up!
Semangat santai!
Relaxed spirit!
Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai apa tuh? Semangat santai! Semangat santai!
What is 'relaxed spirit'? Relaxed spirit! Relaxed spirit!
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjut ke...
Okay, then let's move on to...
Wait wait wait tunggu dulu!
Wait, wait, wait, hold on!
Sebelum selesai-selesai ini nih ya...
Before finishing all this...
Kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu nggak sih?
Shouldn't we scream together with the audience first?
Iya! Ayo! Ayo! Ayo!
Yes! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Oke oke. Jadi kita teriak bareng ya.
Okay, okay. So let's scream together.
Dalam hitungan tiga...
On the count of three...
Kita sama-sama teriak Chromatic Future.
We'll all shout Chromatic Future together.
Oke ya?
Okay?
Oke oke! Chromatic Future! Gitu kan ya?
Okay, okay! Chromatic Future! Like that, right?
Iya iya kayak gitu kayak gitu.
Yes, yes, exactly like that.
Oke langsung ya.
Okay, here we go.
Sambil lihat sini sini sini sambil lihat.
Looking here, here, look.
Aku ya aku aku yang penonton ini nih, penonton sini nih.
Me, I'll be with this audience here.
Aku ini deh yang tengah yang tengah. Halo!
I'll take the middle one. Hello!
Oke bareng-bareng ya.
Okay, together now.
Satu, dua, tiga...
One, two, three...
CHROMATIC FUTURE!
Everything was easy
I did it all alone
So effortlessly
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Got all problems solved
Without any setbacks
There is nothing uncontrolled
There's no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta soar a little higher
Hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a peacock spreading its wings,
Kan kutaklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness.
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With the magic of the wind, I will invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit
all those who slumber to rise up
Melawan dunia
and fight against the world.
We'll never give up
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
Be stronger than that
Walking step by step
Trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Just believe me, let it go
They'll never bring me down, just believe me
Let it go
They'll never bring us down, just believe me
No matter the cruelties, still I'm a royalty
And when the universe works against me, I would just
Let it go!
If it's spicy, just sip something, let it go
I've been living carefree
There's no bitter words in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Not letting it show
I'm bigger than my feelings, so that'll be enough
There's no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta be better than ever
Hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a peacock spreading its wings,
Kan kutaklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness.
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With the magic of the wind, I will invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit melawan dunia
All who are asleep, rise to defy the world
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than the...
Walking step by step, trusting by your face
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Believe me, let it go
They'll never bring me down, just believe me
Let it go, it'll never bring us down, just believe me
Won't let their cruelty steal my royalty
And when the universe works against me, I will just...
Let it go!
Come on guys, let's do this!
One, two, three, let it go!
hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE: CHROMATIC FUTURE
Acrylic Panel
Acrylic Stand
Holographic Button Badge
Lanyard & Ticket Holder
T-shirt
Acrylic Panel
Acrylic Stand
Holographic Button Badge
Lanyard & Ticket Holder
T-shirt