(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Today's 3D Showcase...
今日の３Ｄお披露目は...
Today's 3D Showcase is...
ラオラが3Dで初登場！
Raora makes her 3D debut!!
チャッティーニランドにやってきたラオラが
Raora arrives at Chattini Land, and...
ジェットパックをかけてミニゲームで大暴れ！
Unleashes chaos in Mini-Games for a jetpack!
泣いて
Tears!
Please give me the ticket!!
怒って
Rage!
I'm done!!!!
セクシーなラオラも見れちゃう！
Sexy? Even a sexy Raora can be seen!
もちろん歌も歌っちゃうよ！
Songs! Of course, she'll sing too!
ゾンバイ子と喧嘩もしちゃって
Unexpected Fights?! Even fighting with Zombiko...
ジェットパックは手に入るのかな？
Can she get the Jetpack?
ラオラ・パンテーラの3Dお披露目、始まるよ！
Raora Panthera 3D Showcase is starting now!
Ciao, Raora!
Are you recording me?
Ah, where should I look? Where should I look?
Ha! What is this place?
Oh! Ha!
Oh my gosh! That's a... that's a giant Chattini in the castle!
Oh my gosh! And look at the one in the fountain!
Oh, that's so pretty!
And there's another one over there!
And another one over there!
Wait a second... Is this? Is this?
Is this Chattini Land?
Whoa!
That's so cool!
Ah, hey! Hey! Hey, cameraman, come here, come here, come here!
How do I look in 3D? Hmm?
Hey, you should take a look too...
You should take a look at my Chattino!
Look at him!
Isn't he so pretty? So cute, right?
Ah! And you also should take a look to...
My tail!
Ooh! Big cat means big tail!
Ha! What do you think? How do I look?
Hey, Raora! Raora! Raora!
Hey! Hey! Whoa! Ugh! Oh...
Chattino! Oh, what did you do?
Oh, come here now!
I'm gonna... I'm gonna use my weapon! Urgh!
You come here! Oh, now!
How dare you! How dare you knock me off like this!
Huh? Hey!
You can... you can talk?
Oh, that's impressive.
Well, I'm guessing you need me for something?
What do you need?
Yeah. There's this thing we want, but... The only way you can get it is by clearing all the Mini-Games here in Chattini Land!
Eh? Mini-Games?
Something you can only get here by clearing mini-games?
Eh, I think I know what it is!
It's... that thing over there!
Eh? Eh? Eh? Whoa!
Ah! I knew it! It's a jetpack!
Oh, the Chattini want one so badly, right?
We can't get it on our own, though, so help us out Raora! Please!
Ah, are you begging me? Hmm...
Well, you know, little one...
No! I told you I'm not giving you the jetpack! So, I'm leaving! Bye-bye! Ciao!
Please! Please! Pleeeease!
Eh? Are you following me? Oh...
Well, I guess it's a special day after all. Hmm...
You know what? I'll give it a shot!
Yaaaaaay!
Ha! Okay! So then, what should I do here?
The game's in this area of the land, so good luck!
Okay then, you know what? I'm gonna do my very best!
Well, I should go then! Ganba-Raora! Raooooooo~!
Oh, wait. The right way is over there.
Eh? Eh? Eh? I mean...
Ah! I'm heading out! Ganba-Raora! Raooooooo~!
この番組は、ご覧のスポンサーの提供でお送りします。
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん？ Love, blah blah blah blah...
Are you doing pure pure until you die? Love, blah blah blah blah...
Love, bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh...
ラビットホール
Love and like パーティションはない、ない
Rabbit Hole
Love and like, there's no partition, none
君だけが特別じゃないんだ
You're not the only special one
反省とか私に求められても
Even if you ask me to reflect
本当病んだり勘違いしないで
Don't really get sick or misunderstand
どうしてなんで期待の戸締まり忘れるの？
Why, oh why, do you forget to lock up your expectations?
総じてなんとやめておきなよって言ったじゃん
Overall, didn't I tell you to just stop?
お嬢様、あちらが出口ですが
Madam, that's the exit over there
やっぱ帰りたくないですか
Still don't want to go home, after all?
ホップ ステップ ワン モア チャンス
Hop, step, one more chance
もうやっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Isn't it fine to just appeal and "rabbit"?
ポップな愛嬌振ったらいいじゃん
Isn't it fine to shake off some pop charm?
みっともないから嫉妬仕舞いな
It's pathetic, so put your jealousy away
発火しちゃってどっすんぼっすん
Igniting and thumping
寂しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do
埋まればいいじゃん　埋めればいいじゃん
It's fine to be filled, it's fine to fill
嫌々愛して生きたくなって
Starting to want to live by loving reluctantly
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんの？
Are you being pure-pure until you die?
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Yeah, isn't it fine to appeal and "rabbit"?
バッドなダンスを待ったらいいじゃん
Isn't it fine to wait for a bad dance?
やっぱり好きとかやってられんわ
As I thought, "liking" isn't something I can do
馬鹿じゃないの？くっそ雑魚ね
Aren't you an idiot? So weak
寂しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do
埋まればいいじゃん　埋めればいいじゃん
It's fine to be filled, it's fine to fill
嫌々愛して死にたくなって
Starting to want to die by loving reluctantly
こちらとフラフラやってんの、OK？
Messing around here, okay?
はーい！
Alright!
Love, bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh...
バーストからインスタントラヴァー
Instant lover from burst
頭+身体がバカに絡まる
Head + body tangled foolishly
ゴーストならアンデッドマナー
Undead manners if it's a ghost
いまだみだら今は火花散らせばそれがアンサーだ
Still lewd, if sparks fly now, that's the answer
バーストからインスタントラヴァー
Instant lover from burst
頭+身体がバカに絡まる
Head + body tangled foolishly
ゴーストならアンデッドマナー
Undead manners if it's a ghost
いまだみだら今は火花散らせばそれがアンサーだ
Still lewd, if sparks fly now, that's the answer
ワン モア チャンス！
One more chance!
もうやっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Isn't it fine to just appeal and "rabbit"?
ポップな愛嬌振ったらいいじゃん
Isn't it fine to shake off some pop charm?
みっともないから嫉妬仕舞いな
It's pathetic, so put your jealousy away
発火しちゃってどっすんぼっすん
Igniting and thumping
寂しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do
埋まればいいじゃん　埋めればいいじゃん
It's fine to be filled, it's fine to fill
嫌々愛して生きたくなって
Starting to want to live by loving reluctantly
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんの？
Are you being pure-pure until you die?
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Yeah, isn't it fine to appeal and "rabbit"?
バッドなダンスを待ったらいいじゃん
Isn't it fine to wait for a bad dance?
やっぱり好きとかやってられんわ
As I thought, "liking" isn't something I can do
馬鹿じゃないの？くっそ雑魚ね
Aren't you an idiot? So weak
寂しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do
埋まればいいじゃん　埋めればいいじゃん
It's fine to be filled, it's fine to fill
嫌々愛して死にたくなって
Starting to want to die by loving reluctantly
こちらとフラフラやってんの、OK？
Messing around here, okay?
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Yeah, isn't it fine to appeal and "rabbit"?
とっくのとうに終わった思いだ
I thought it ended a long time ago
みっともないとか言ってごめんな
Sorry for saying it's pathetic
発火しちゃってもう駄目なんだ
It's already too late, I've ignited
寂しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do
埋まればいいじゃん
It's fine to be filled
埋めればいいじゃん
It's fine to fill
否々愛して死にたくなって
Starting to want to die by loving reluctantly
こちらとフラフラやってんの、OK？
Messing around here, okay?
はーい！
Alright!
や、や、や、悪い子さん
Ya, ya, ya, bad child
ま、ま、ま、お愛顧じゃん
Ma, ma, ma, it's your patronage
さ、さ、さ、始めるよ
Sa, sa, sa, let's begin
もっとこの穴を愛してよ
Love this hole more
や、や、や、悪い子さん
Ya, ya, ya, bad child
ま、ま、ま、お愛顧じゃん
Ma, ma, ma, it's your patronage
さ、さ、さ、始めるよ
Sa, sa, sa, let's begin
もっとこの穴を愛してよ、だっせ！
Love this hole more, so uncool!
Chattini Land Flower Garden Area
Whoa! Look at this place!
I was not expecting to play a game in such a pretty place.
And I wonder what kind of game it's gonna be... Hmm.
Raora!
Eh?
This is your conscience.
Eh? My conscience? Do I have one?
Oh, Mori!
Yo, what's up? Your turn!
Eh? Is that...? Say something, say something!
Ra-ora-ora-ora-ora!
Eh? Is that...? Is that a ghost? What is that? Where is...?
I can't see anyone!
Ra-ora-ora-ora-ora!
Eh? Is that a dog?
Hey! It's your senpai!
Congrats Raora on your 3D debut!
Thank you! We're so happy for you!
Oh, thank you so much! I'm so happy to be here with you!
Congratulations! Yay! Yay!
Cute! Cute! Thank you!
No, you're cute!
No, you! No, you! No, you!
Kawaii! No way!
Cute! No way!
Thank you!
Well, as you may have assumed by our grand entrance over here...
...your opponents for this mini-game are, as you see...
Meena-san, Mori Calliope from hololive English first generation Myth!
Everyone, Mori Calliope from hololive English first generation Myth!
If you don't know me, now you do! Who's over here?
Kronichiwa babe! This is Ouro Kronii from hololive English Promise!
And um, who could this beautiful woman be?
誰ですか？
Who is it?
ですか？ あ...
Is it? Ah...
どっちこっち？
This way, that way?
あ、こっち！
Ah, this way!
どっちこっちこっち？ ゆびゆび！
This way, that way, this way? Yubi yubi!
ホロライブから来ました戌神ころね、よろしくね！
I'm Inugami Korone from Hololive, nice to meet you!
Whoo! よろしく！
Whoo! Nice to meet you!
Yay! 先輩！ 先輩！
Yay! Senpai! Senpai!
はじめまして！
Nice to meet you!
今日は来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming today!
お、日本語上手！
Oh, your Japanese is good!
はじめまして！ イェイェイェー！
Nice to meet you! Yay-yay-yay!
イェイェイェー！
Yay-yay-yay!
Oh very good! Thank you so much Mori!
What kind of game are we gonna play today?
Well, get ready...
...because it's time for...
One, two, three, Say Cheese!
All right.
Now then,
here are the rules.
Chattini jump out of the bush holding a camera!
And when they do so, you gotta enter the frame and then strike a specific pose for them!
Oh, okay, okay. Sounds easy.
Like that, like that! Just move into the camera frame
and strike the pose once the Chattini jump out.
And... oh! This is a good example! Yeah, exactly!
She's a little too hyped for that.
I know.
Bani-hop!
No, no, no, you have to be competitive. You have to be competitive in this game. Yes.
To clear the stage, Raora must strike 5 poses at the marked spots within the time limit!
Oh, sounds easy, right?
I got it!
It sounds so much fun! Let's go!
Yeah, but it's not going to be easy.
Yeah, it's not going to be easy because we're going to be taking part as well and I'm going to get in your way.
No! All up in your business! All up in your... I'm gonna get in your way!
I'm gonna get the ticket, I'm gonna win!
No!
I guess that means we're all going to get into it super close.
Loser! Raora loser!
No, I'm not a loser! You loser!
No, no, no!
Well, I feel like everyone's confident! No you aren't! Hurry up!
A little too confident. No, don't worry, no, it's okay, it's all good, it's all good.
What is it? I'm striking a pose, it's a pose game! It's a pose game!
Got it, got it! Yeah! Oh! Okay!
Are you guys excited?
I'm excited!
Okay, if everybody's ready then...
Let's do this!
Whoo! Let's do it!
Hope you're all ready, troops! Are you guys excited?
Yeah!!
Get ready to start voguing!
Since it would be a shame to go straight into the real thing, let us do some practice first, okay?
Mmm, okay, okay! Let's do it!
All righty, so here we go.
Three, two, one, start!
Okay, let's see. First camera... Here, here! Hey, hey, hey!
I'm sorry! I shouldn't have stepped back! No, no, no!
Okay, what is it?
Yeah! Yeah!
Okay, uh... Okay, let's see.
Next one... Yes, yes! This is Calliope's time to shine!
Okay, uh, where?
Hey! One more!
Whoa! Oh! Where? Where? Where? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Aha!
Dang it! Time's up!
You doing okay there, buddy?
That was so good!
I will touch you and I will hurt you.
Just so we're all on the same page, I will hurt you if I have to.
Hurt me!
I love it!
That's not the response I expected.
Well, I'm fine with it!
Shall we move on to the main event, ladies?
Okay! Yes!
Okay. The time limit for the main event is two minutes. Whoever strikes the right pose in the required spots most is the winner.
Now then,
let's get this show on the road. Three,
two,
one,
Ikuzo!
Let's go!
Start! Let's go!
Where is it?
Whoa!
That was kind of nutty! Let's go!
Let's go! What is it?
No, no, no, no, no! No! Yeah!
You guys are too good at this! Let's go!
Oh man, I'm going to get injured!
No! Away! You hurt me! Dang it!
Next one is mine!
What do you think? As I said, I will hurt you.
No! Raora! No!
Man, everyone's so good.
I know! At, you know, hurting each other.
Dang it!
Oh my god! Oh my god!
What is it?
No, no, no, no, no! Stop! No!
大丈夫先輩？大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay, senpai? Are you okay?
It's okay, it's okay!
Points!
Why is she so strong?
She's rejecting all of my pushes!
MISSED!
Okay. Oh man. Really blocking...
Man, I'm not even gonna try on this one.
Points!
Wow, they're all squabbling.
Calliope takes the lead.
Points!
That's so tiring!
No, not every time.
You can't get it every time, Kronii.
Points!
Come on!
Let me have this one!
MISSED!
TIME'S UP!
おいおいおい。めっちゃ疲れた。
Oi oi oi. That's so tiring.
Yo, why are y'all so strong?
I don't get it.
We are good. We are good. Oh, okay, so good.
Man, I feel like we just came out of a battle.
Raora!
I'm good.
いい勝負。That's what I call a good match.
A good match. That's what I call a good match.
Okay, okay. How was it?
Yo, how do you guys think that you did?
I think I won.
I think I won. Me too.
Oh, no, no, no. We won.
I think Kronii won. With the sheer force of
her muscles pushing people out of the way.
I'm so sorry! But it wasn't even that.
She could not be pushed.
I mean, hey, you know what, competitive spirit.
I can't even argue with that.
Well then. Well done everyone. Well done.
Well, let's see how that weighs up
against the results, shall we?
Yay!
I bet I am the winner.
No, no, no, Raora, no, Raora, no, Raora...
Yes, Raora, yes, Raora, I'm the winner.
Me me me win.
Yes, Kronii, yes, let me win, me me me win.
All right, all right, let's see how we all did then.
Here we go.
Okay, drumroll please. Drumroll.
Kronii! No! Raora!
That's crazy close. She's too strong. Man.
Congrats, congrats!
I knew it anyway. Thank you, thank you.
There was no defeating the... the clock of steel.
This is rigged! It's rigged!
She's too good, Raora. She can't be beaten.
I tried to pick her up and move her and
she just can't be... she can't be moved.
She's immovable. Man, it's really too bad though.
I was gonna give you the ticket if you managed
to win, but oh well, this round's a bust.
All boo, so sad. Oh, I cry.
Oh no... Wait, wait, Mori, wait a second.
There must be a way, right? I need the ticket.
I need to clear all the games.
I mean... Please, please.
It's not... it's not up to me, but you know what,
what to do? I feel kind of bad, you're my cute kouhai.
Please! ころね先輩、ころね先輩どうすればいい？
Please! Korone-senpai, Korone-senpai, what should I do?
や、そうね。Do you like Japanese TV show?
Yeah, let's see. Do you like Japanese TV shows?
Yes, I love Japanese TV shows, yes.
あ、ぷりーずキュートおねだり。
Ah, please do a 'cute plea'.
へ？おねだり？可愛くおねだり？
You want me to beg?
Huh? A plea? A cute plea?
や。おねだり。あ、このカメラ、おっけー？
このカメラ。
Yeah. A plea. Ah, this camera, okay?
This camera.
ちょっと低い、ちょっと低く。
A bit low, a bit lower.
Get kind of low, like you're about to make it...
Okay, up eyes, up eyes, okay?
がんばれ！Do your best. Cute face, cute face, okay?
Cute face. I can't wait. おねだり。キュートおねだり。
Do your best! Do your best. Cute face, cute face, okay?
Cute face. I can't wait. A plea. A cute plea.
Raora's Cute Plea
All right, three, two, one, action!
Please... Please, Korone-senpai.
Please... onedari.
Please... my plea.
Please give me the ticket. Please, I need the ticket.
Please, please Korone-senpai, お願いします。
Please, please Korone-senpai, I beg you.
Please, please give me the ticket.
Oh man, I feel so bad now. I need the ticket.
そこまでやるとは…。All right, all right, since
she's done enough, you've done enough...
To go as far as this... All right, all right, since
そんなに欲しいのね。All right, all right, all right
Raora, you've done it! Look, the ticket!
You want it that much, huh. All right, all right, all right
Look at your hand, look at your hand!
The ticket! I got the ticket! Great job!
Got the Ticket!!
Excellent! やった！Cute onedari.
Excellent! I did it! A cute plea.
Okay, there you go. I got the ticket! Let's go!
Well done. See, no problem. Happy ending. Happy end.
Now, you will receive the Jetpack Chatini if you
gather three tickets. Count them, three.
So good luck on the next games as well.
Thank you, senpais! Thank you! Yeah, no problem.
Thank you so much! Now go do your best!
Okay, I'll do my best! Thank you so much!
Bye bye! Bye bye!
This way! This way! I'll go this way! Yay!
This way! Go straight!
Go straight!
This way, this way!
Let's go!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Good luck!
See you!
Bye-bye! See ya!
Chattini Land Jungle Area
Oh my gosh, this area is really different
from the last one!
It's super dark!
And... what's with all the bars?
It's... it's kind of scary.
(mysterious singing)
What is that?
I hear voices!
A-go? What is that?
Oh my gosh! Moona!
Please, Goddess Moona!
Please, my time has come!
Please take my soul!
Are those... Nerissa and Moona?
Yeah, you're gonna say
you don't recognize us?
Of course I recognize you!
Oh my gosh!
Congratulations on your 3D!
Thank you! I'm so happy!
Finally!
Thank you!
I think we have to introduce!
Of course!
Starting from me!
Hello everyone!
I am Moona Hoshinova...
...from hololive Indonesia Generation 1!
And...
Hiya, darlings!
This is hololive English -Advent-'s
devilish diva...
...the one and only, Nerissa Ravencroft!
Thank you for having me!
Thank you so much for being here!
We came here to bring a game.
A game!
Really?
Yes, it involves cooperation.
Oh, good! What are we gonna do?
Well, the game this time is...
One...
...two...
...three...
Limbo Dance! Panthera!!
The rules are super simple.
The three of us are
gonna do some sexy limbo dance.
Make your way to the stage while doing the limbo!
To clear the stage, Raora must end
with a cool musical performance on stage!
Dancing, yes! The limbo dance, dancing!
As we make our way towards the stage!
So exciting!
Me too! And once we're there,
there's one thing left to do.
We're all gonna sing a super awesome trio song!
Sounds simple, right?
Simple, let's see. I am born for this! Let's go!
But you know... are we really
gonna be able to do this?
I think we might have not
thought ahead too far.
Of course we're gonna do it!
No, but you know... we all have something...
...that I feel like will make limbo
a little bit difficult.
Don't worry, Nerissa! Something that is really hard...
...but it's fine! We can do it!
Save it for the game, ladies!
Okay! Let's do it!
First off, though, we need to do some warm-up.
Yes! Yes! Keep going girls!
Let's warm up a little bit before the game now!
Can They Clear It?!
Right, that's us ready, all together! Yes!
I took off my jacket because it's so hot in here!
Can you do me a favor?
Could you jump a little bit more? Just a little bit.
Why are you asking?
Yes, like that! I love jumping so let's go!
And look at those shoulders too! Show those off!
Very nice! Thank you!
Oh my god! I'm gonna do my very
best in limbo dance!
Let's dance! Let's do it!
Let's get the music going!
GAME START!
Nice music, do you hear that?
Are you ready?
6 Limbo left!!
I'm ready!
It's your 3D debut, so get going!
Well, that's too easy for me! Are you guys ready?
Here we go! Yay!
GOOD!
I'm going next!
Moona!
Too easy for her!
Nerissa!
You can do it!
Oh my god! Easy peasy!
Who's next?
Same order!
Let's keep it going! That's a bit unfair.
Well, I'm gonna do it then!
Show us how it's done!
Good job! Okay!
I can do it! Easy, easy!
Look at you go!
This is a little bit more difficult.
Maybe same order?
Senpai order!
I can do it for you guys.
Okay.
Whoo!
Whoa! Oh, look at her go!
Look at her go! Good!
Next up is...
watch how it's done.
Show me, Queen!
Whoa!
That's so clean, girl! Good!
Let's go, my turn.
Definitely gonna do it.
Come on, Kohai.
Ha! Oh, oh! Success!
Good! So good!
Okay, maybe... switch it off, I'll go first.
Yes, you go.
Oh my goodness! Perfect!
She's nailing it.
Are you gonna be able to do it, Moona?
You can do it, Moona.
I believe!
I can do it.
This is a tough one.
Can do it... Oh! Oh! Success!
You actually did it!
All right, my turn.
Let me show you all my skills.
You can do it, Raora.
Ha! Oh! Fail?
Oh no! Oh good, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
Yeah, you're okay, you're okay.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
No, we have to keep going. There's still two more.
Oh, all right. Right.
Let me rest a little bit.
Oh my god. I'm too old for this.
Come on, grandma. Come on.
You have no idea of the game.
Two more lines, grandma. Two more.
Come on, come on. Let's go.
We have two more to go, right?
Wait a second.
You dropped yours!
Oh no, damn.
Well, I think I'm done with these two then.
Oh, poor it.
I think I still can do this for now.
Time to get serious.
So I'm gonna lock in.
This is impossible, hello?
Yeah, it's a little bit low, but I think we can do it.
Okay, I'll try first.
Whoa! Amazing!
She's too good, Moona.
I don't know if I can do it.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
Come on. You can do it.
You can do it.
Come on, Moona, Moona, Moona!
No, I think I have an idea.
She got an idea!
Whoa! Good? Success!
This strategy. The power of Breadman!
Let's see.
You can do it.
Come on, Raora. You got this.
Okay, I think I can do it.
Whoa! Good? Success!
That's great! That's really nice.
Okay, I don't think I can... I don't know if I can do this one.
I mean, you did so good so far.
You can do it.
One more.
I think I'm too tall for this one. Help me.
I'm gonna hold you. I'm gonna fall. I'm gonna fall.
Oh! Yeah! I did it! Success!
I'm going to follow their way.
I'm going to follow her way.
Let's do this.
Moona, we're gonna put it...
Oh, now she's getting serious.
She's getting serious.
Ha! Whoo! Oh my goodness! Success!
Okay, okay.
Then it's my turn now. How, what to do?
Well, I'm a big cat, so...
Nyan nyan nyan!
So cute! Whoo!
Thank you.
Here we go.
Well, I still think we have one more obstacle yet before us.
Where, where?
Up this slope.
Oh, let's go.
We've got to go up.
All right, everyone.
Don't forget our limbo dance.
Oh yeah, the limbo dance now.
Whoo!
Yes! Let's go to the stage.
Are you guys excited?
So excited! I am so ready!
Whoo!
Oh, that was so hard.
Yeah, but we did it.
To the stage already.
Yeah, we're here.
You're right. Here.
Oh my god. Are you ready for this?
Okay.
I don't know what I'm doing, but let's do it.
We gotta go full power mode.
Yeah!
All right, last part.
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
ムリよムリよ
It's impossible, impossible
どこにいたってムリよ
Wherever you are, it's impossible
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
だれといるの？
Who are you with?
ダメよダメよ
No way, no way
わたし以外はダメよ
No one except for me
甘いよ甘い そんな装備じゃ
It's naive, so naive, with that gear of yours
逃げられるわけ 無いじゃないか
There's no way you can escape, is there?
狙いをつけて 密かに
Taking aim, quietly,
背後から
from behind...
I love you
私のことを 好きになるはず
You're bound to fall for me
I love you
そこに正義が あるの
That's where justice lies
何度も言わせるつもりなの？
How many times are you going to make me say it?
おやおや 抵抗するなら してごらん！
My my, if you're going to resist, just try it!
意外と 我が儘だと 知ってるけれど
I know I'm unexpectedly selfish, but
私の方が 上手なようね
It seems I've got the upper hand
冷たい言葉 優しい視線
Cold words, a gentle gaze
獲物は... 君だよ！
The prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも 行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere
君の君の君の 心盗んでみせるよ
I'll show you I can steal your, your, your heart
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも 行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere
君の君の君の 心を離さない
I won't let go of your, your, your heart
熱いよ熱い 愛のルールは
Hot, so hot, the rules of love
破られるため 在るんだよ
Exist to be broken
ずるい罠へと 誘う 微笑みは
A smile that lures you into a cunning trap
I miss you 好きのせいだし 悪くないでしょ
I miss you, it's because of love, so it's not bad, right?
I miss you それが重度の 恋よ
I miss you, that's what a serious love is
絶対全てを いただくよ
I'll definitely take everything
おやおや 抵抗するなら してごらん！
My my, if you're going to resist, just try it!
てこわい 偽りだって 疑うよりも
Rather than doubting it's a formidable lie
私のこと信じてみてよ
Try believing in me
優しい言葉 冷たい視線
Gentle words, a cold gaze
獲物は... 君だよ！
The prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 君の 瞳が 欲しい
Cutie Panther, I want your eyes
私 きっと きっと盗んでみせるよ
I'll definitely, definitely steal them
Cutie Panther 君の 瞳が 欲しい
Cutie Panther, I want your eyes
私 きっと 素早く逃さない
I definitely won't let you get away quickly
何度も言わせるつもりなの？
How many times are you going to make me say it?
おやおや 抵抗するなら してごらん！
My my, if you're going to resist, just try it!
意外と 我が儘だと 知ってるけれど
I know I'm unexpectedly selfish, but
私の方が 上手なようね
It seems I've got the upper hand
冷たい言葉 優しい視線
Cold words, a gentle gaze
獲物は... 君だよ！
The prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも 行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere
君の君の君の 心盗んでみせるよ
I'll show you I can steal your, your, your heart
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも 行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere
君の君の君の 心を離さない
I won't let go of your, your, your heart
捕まえちゃう！
I'm gonna catch you!
どこにいるの 無理よ無理よ どこにいたって無理よ
Where are you? It's no use, no use, no matter where you are it's no use
捕まえちゃう！
I'm gonna catch you!
だれといるの ダメよダメよ 私以外はダメよ
Who are you with? No, no, anyone but me is no good
捕まえちゃう！
I'm gonna catch you!
どこにいるの 無理よ無理よ どこにいたって無理よ
Where are you? It's no use, no use, no matter where you are it's no use
捕まえちゃう！
I'm gonna catch you!
だれといるの ダメよダメよ 私以外はダメよ
Who are you with? No, no, anyone but me is no good
How was that, Velvet?
That's really nice.
That's how Velvet does it.
So cool, right?
So together. Nice!
So happy!
Thank you for dancing and singing with me.
Ooh, and also, since we already finished our session,
so here's your ticket!
Oh my god! I got it! Look at you! CLEAR!
Got the Ticket!!
Congratulations Raora!
One more left now.
Let's go!
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
It was so fun. Thank you for having us.
Thank you!
Good luck getting that final ticket too, alright?
Yes, that's true.
Oh, true!
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best, I promise!
Thank you girls!
You can do it!
Well, as for us, we should take our leave now.
Bye bye!
We must leave you here.
No! Don't leave me girls!
We need to go.
Nooo!
The limbo dance was so hard that it
became their default walking stage.
Chattini Land Sci-Fi
Oh! What is this place?
Oh my god, this seems like this space came out of
a science fiction movie or something like that.
But now I'm curious, what kind of game
they got prepared for me this time? Hmm...
(Howling) Raora! Raora!
I smell something...
Dog smell! I know who you are. Come out! Come here!
Raora!
Oh, Come here! Come here! Come here!
Oh wow! Yeah! There, there, there, there...
Raora!
I'm so excited, I'm so nervous, I'm so happy!
Your tail's looking really happy too!
No, no, no, no... Okay, let's talk about it.
There's a game to the right! Yeah, that's the game, right?
Wait, but why don't you guys introduce yourselves?
I'm not Mococo, I'm Fuwawa Abyssgard!
I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Mococo!
Together we are...
FuwaMoco! Bau Bau!
And I'm not FuwaMoco! Bau Bau! I'm...
...Koseki Bijou, sparkling gem of
Hololive English Advent! Kira kira, Koseki!
And then...
Rau! It's still me, Raora Panthera from
Hololive English Justice, this time in 3D!
Wait, have I introduced myself before?
I'm not sure about that. Maybe.
Always good for having more! It's okay, it's okay!
So, what's the last game gonna be?
Wait for this next game! Actually, Raora...
...you're the only one in this challenge!
Wait, what do you mean?
But we have a very important role too, right?
Wait, what are you guys gonna do?
We're gonna... stop you!
No, no, no, no, no! You guys gotta let me win!
We're gonna be mean!
No, no, no, no, you gotta let me win! It's my debut!
And it's the last ticket, I need it!
No, no, I don't think so. We're gonna
put you through the wringer, yeah!
Are you ready to hear what the third
final game is? It is...
One, two, three... Run! Run! Raora!!
Run! Run! Raora!!
Oh, okay, okay. What's the rules?
Okay, are you curious?
I'm very curious!
Take a look at the conveyor belt behind you!
What is this? Uh, there is nothing on it, Bijou.
Oh, silly me! There is something on it. Bring it out!
What is that? Huh?
Eww! What is... eww! Is that a pizza?
Pineapple pizza! Broken up spaghetti! Get out of here!
Pineapple pizza
Pasta with ketchup! No, no, no!
Broken up spaghetti
Ketchup spaghetti
Eww! No, thank you! I'm done with this!
I'm so done! I'm leaving! I'm leaving!
Raora, you have to stay!
No, I'm not gonna play this game!
No, I'm not gonna play this game! It's too much for me!
No! No, no, no! It's too much for me! I'm done with this!
Well, do you notice that everything we
brought out here is everything you hate?
Do you hate pineapple pizza, Raora?
To clear the stage, Raora must dodge all the
incoming obstacles during the time limit!
And avoid everything! That's it!
Yup, yup, yup!
No, no, no, you can do it!
Wait a second. And why you guys are here then?
What you guys gonna do?
Well... we'll be using certain things...
...to make life more difficult!
Oh, you can't do this to me!
Hehe, yup. No.
You, you are really a criminal!
No, no, you're not gonna do this to me!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, okay, okay, okay!
Wait, we'll be right back! We'll be right back!
No, no, don't leave me! Hey!
What you gonna do?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
RAORA! RAORA!
Okay, okay, I will play the game!
You have to play the game!
Okay, I will play the game! Hahaha!
Did you like that? 'Cause there's more!
No, don't touch me with that onion! Ugh!
It's bigger than you, Biboo!
Wait, what's that supposed to mean?
I'm bigger than this onion, hey!
Cucumbers are good, right? Yum!
Now, let's get going here!
Let's go!
Onion! Yay!
Are you okay? I'm fine.
Raora's Fate?!
Okay! You ready, Raora?
Um... no, so... hey, hey, guys!
Wait, wait, guys, can we play another game?
Okay, the timer's starting! Level 1!
Dodge for 60 seconds to level up, okay?
Okay, okay, I'm ready.
There's a total of three levels,
so try to escape to the very end!
Ready, set... GO!
GAME START!
I'll do my best! Let's go!
No, no, no!
The onion! Not the onion!
Not the spaghetti!
Big cat, big trouble! Watch out!
Big boss! Big boss!
Ahhh!
FAILED!
Failure again! Oh no!
You want to try again? One more time!
Last time! Yay!
Level 1 Revenge!
How you feeling?
Maybe we were a bit too hard on her.
Yeah, that wasn't fair.
We're gonna set the clock to 30 seconds.
Okay, let's do it then!
I can definitely make it!
Okay, we're gonna go again.
Three, two, one...
GAME START!
CLEAR!
Level one clear! Yay! You did it!
That was too good, but... you can go on?
That was just level one. Level two now!
Level two? Too easy, you know?
Oh, okay, wow!
Let's try level two then! Okay, let's go!
Yeah, you can do it!
I did it for the first time! Yeah!
Ready... Level two! Start!
CLEAR!
Yatta! Level 2!
I did it! Level 2!
I did it for...
...for you guys!
You're not getting tired, are you?
Not slowing down or anything, huh?
Well, you know, maybe you didn't put enough effort.
Oh yeah? OK.
Well, we're gonna make it harder then!
Let's get ready for...
Level 3! Level 3!
No no no no no!
This is the last one.
This DICA is mine!
Can we go to the...
...next level?
But I think this one's gonna be extra hard!
Because you said that we weren't trying hard enough...
...you know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna make this one...
...you only have one try!
And you know what? That's not all.
It's gonna be extra hard!
You guys are cheating! This is not fair!
It's a game! You're so evil!
Alright, I better prepare myself.
Level 3! Let's go!
GAME START!
FAILED!
Just like we said! Waaaah!
Yeah, she went really...
I don't think she's gonna be able to come back from that.
No! It's over! Bau Bau!
GAME OVER
It's okay...
Yoshi yoshi yoshi yoshi...
There, there, there, there...
Well, you know guys...
...today is my 3D debut, right?
So maybe, you know, senpais...
...you guys could give me the ticket anyway?
No! No! No! No!
You have to suffer!
I'm not getting the ticket...
...no ticket for me... I'm so sad.
We have prepared a special stage for you!
Really!?
Yeah! You know, while it was fun, you know...
...torturing you with things you hate...
...that was really cute.
You know, we kind of want to see your cool side now.
My cool side? Really?
You want to see my cool side?
Yeah! Show it off to them!
Maybe you can put all those angry feelings into the next song!
Yeah! Sing! Yeah!
Okay! Let's go!
Let's go go go go!
恋は戦争 / Love is War
Love is War
もう行き場がないわ
There's nowhere left for me to go
この恋の熱量
In the heat of this love
ah...
灰色の雲
Gray clouds
モノクロの喧騒
Monochrome noise
日差しはかげり
The sunlight fades
夕暮れは色を変えていく
The twilight changes color
嗚呼
Ah
世界がにじんで
The world blurs
それでも好きでいられるかなんて
I wonder if I can still love you
わかってる
I know
けどどうすればいいの
but what should I do?
どうしたら どうすれば
What can I do? What should I do?
バカだな わたし...
I'm such a fool...
始めるのよ
I'm starting it
これは戦争
this is a war
嬉しそうなキミをみるなんて
To see you looking so happy
切なる恋
This aching love
それは罪
it's a sin
見せてあげる
I'll show you
わたしの想いを
my feelings
叫んでみた
I tried shouting
メガホンは壊れてたの
but the megaphone was broken
どれだけ背伸びしたって
No matter how much I stand on tiptoes
君の視界に入らない
I don't enter your field of vision
嗚呼
Ah
いつの間にか晴れた空
before I knew it, the sky cleared
全然似合わない
It doesn't suit me at all
気持ちが抑えられなくて
I can't suppress my feelings
どうしたら どうすれば
What can I do? What should I do?
泣いてなんか ないんだからね
It's not like I'm crying or anything
大好き
I love you
たたかうのよ
I'm going to fight
ハートを撃て
shoot through the heart
手段なんて選んでられない
I can't afford to choose my means
スカートひらり
With a flutter of my skirt
見せつけるのよ
I'll show you
君の視線奪ってみせるの
I'll show you I can steal your gaze
迎撃用意
Prepare for interception
戦況は未だ不利なのです
the war situation is still unfavorable
恋は盲目
Love is blind
君の口づけで目が覚めるの
I wake up with your kiss
Nights at Chattini Land
Ah!
I'm sorry Chattini!
I tried my best, but I only got two!
Oh...
Noooo... my jetpack...
Oh!
The jetpack exploded!
I'm sorry Chattini.
Actually, I have a present for all of you!
Present? I wonder what it is? Is it a cucumber?
Ah, mm-mm.
Let me tell you.
Eira, eira, eira.
Good, good, good.
That's the best! It's not a jetpack but it's really nice!
Thanks Chattini!
Well then, before I reveal the best present ever, I've got an announcement to make!
Ta-da!
Raora Panthera Pencil Case & Keychain!
Yes, this is a cute pencil case with me in a Chattini costume!
So I hope you guys can bring it everywhere, at school, in the office...
Literally everywhere!
So please don't miss it out, okay?
Ah, that was such a fun 3D showcase with a lot of things happening!
Did everyone have fun?
Chattini, did you guys have fun?
Oh, thank you!
I'm so happy to hear that!
Thank you!
Since like you guys had a great time with me today I'm so happy!
I'll keep doing my best to bring fun streams and more 3D live performances like this one today, okay?
I appreciate you guys so much!
Thank you Chattini for all your support!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Finally!
It's the long awaited present from me to everyone!
Are you guys ready?
The present is...
my first original song!
Ah, I'm so happy!
It's full of things I like and so many personal touches.
I worked really, really hard on this song so I hope you guys gonna take a listen to it, okay?
Are you guys ready? Are you guys excited?
Let's go to the stage!
Gacha x Gacha ADVENTURE!
(はいはい! はい! Pon! Pon!) (はいはい! はい! Pon! Pon!)
(Hai hai! Hai! Pon! Pon!) (Hai hai! Hai! Pon! Pon!)
Gacha x Gacha RAOOOOOO!!
さあ、さあ、お宝探しだ
Come on, come on, it's treasure hunting time!
今日は、ど〜んな獲物が見つかるかにゃ？
What kind of prey will we find today?
ほら、ほら、みんなも一緒に
Look, look, everyone together
「楽しい冒険、しゅっば〜つ！」 (Un! Due! Tre!)
"Fun adventure, let's go!" (One! Two! Three!)
ハマっちゃったら抜け出せないの〜
Once you're hooked, you can't get out~
食べ物 ぬいぐるみ
Food, stuffed animals
Pizza も Pasta も 全部
Pizza and Pasta, everything
詰め込んだ魅惑の迷宮
A packed maze of fascination
ワクワク止まらない (Proviamo!)
The excitement won't stop (Let's try!)
取れそうで取れなくてイライラ
It's frustrating when you're so close but can't get it
クレーンゲーム
Crane game
「にゃ〜もう！」
"Meow~ geez!"
諦めたままリタイア
Giving up and retiring
するはずないじゃない！
There's no way I'd do that!
「目指せコンプリート！」
"Aim for complete collection!"
さあ、もう一回 止めても無駄だよ
Come on, one more time, it's no use stopping me
もう一回 繰り返すデジャヴ
One more time, a repeating déjà vu
諦めろって言わないで
Don't tell me to give up
三度目の正直
Third time's the charm
だから無問題 溢れる想いが
So no problem, these overflowing feelings
とめらんない！
Can't be stopped!
これって天職！？
Is this my calling!?
楽しいことで満ちてる
Filled with fun things
この先もずっと
Forever from now on
「はい、せーのっ」
"Okay, one, two!"
Gacha x Gacha ADVENTURE!
(ガチャ… ガチャ… ガチャ… ガチャ…)
(Gacha... Gacha... Gacha... Gacha...)
「ゲーム、リスタート！」
"Game, restart!"
グルグル回しまくっちゃえ
Spin it around and around
「ダメだ… 止まんない！」
"It's no use... it won't stop!"
お目当ての獲物が出るまで
Until the prize I want comes out
「お願い… もう一回！」 (Bim bum bam!)
"Please... one more time!" (Bim bum bam!)
ビートに乗ったら止まれないの〜
Once you ride the beat, you can't stop~
音ゲーもお手のもの
Music games are my specialty
Combo も Fever も 全部
Combo and Fever, everything
キメたら完璧 Groove!
If you nail it, it's a perfect Groove!
ズレたらゲームオーバー (Andiamo!)
If you're off, it's game over (Let's go!)
レースゲーム エンジン全開でアチアチ
Racing game, full throttle and hot
白熱バトル！
Incandescent battle!
「いけいけ！ Go! Go! Go!」
"Go go! Go! Go! Go!"
コーナーで差をつけたら
If you widen the gap at the corner
目指すは1位だー！
The goal is number one!
さあ、もう一回 でも今日は終わり
Come on, one more time, but today is the end
もう一回 言いかけて止まる
One more time, I start to say it then stop
楽しかった気持ちが 胸をキュッとするの
The feeling of having fun tightens my chest
ねぇねぇ、もうバイバイしなきゃダメ？
Hey, hey, do we already have to say bye-bye?
まだ帰りたくない これって恋かな！？
I don't want to go home yet, is this love!?
ワクワクで満ち溢れた
Overflowing with excitement
この先の日々も
The days ahead too
「一緒に冒険しよう！」
"Let's adventure together!"
さあ、もう一回 止めても無駄だよ
Come on, one more time, it's no use stopping me
もう一回 繰り返すデジャヴ
One more time, a repeating déjà vu
諦めろって言わないで
Don't tell me to give up
何度でもチャレンジ
Challenge as many times as it takes
だから無問題 溢れる想いが
So no problem, these overflowing feelings
とめらんない！
Can't be stopped!
これぞ天職！！
This is truly my calling!!
何度でもやり直せる
You can start over as many times as you want
そう人生は
Yes, life is
「みんなも一緒に！」
"Everyone together!"
Gacha x Gacha ADVENTURE!
(はいはい! はい! Pon! Pon!) (はいはい! はい! Pon! Pon!)
(Hai hai! Hai! Pon! Pon!) (Hai hai! Hai! Pon! Pon!)
Gacha x Gacha RAOOOOOO!!
「また一緒に冒険しようね！ Ciao ciao!」
"Let's adventure together again! Bye-bye!"
Ah, that was so much fun! How did you like it, Chattini? Did you like it?
Thank you for watching and listening! Today was so much fun!
Thank you so much everyone for all your support! Thank you, thank you Chattini, thank you!
I can't wait to see you all again! Until next time!
Ciao ciao!
RAOOOOOO!
Big cat means big trouble!
Thank you Chattini for all your support! I still can't believe this day finally came! RAOOOOO
This is the very first step towards my idol dream, and I will always do my best!
Let's keep going together to new chapters! BIG CAT means BIG DREAMS!
Thank you Chattini for all your support!
I still can't believe this day finally came!
RAOOOO~
BIG CAT means BIG DREAMS!
This is the very first step towards my idol dream, and I will always do my best!
Let's keep going together to new chapters!