(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D COLLAB
3D STREAM
Catch us if you can!
Itzy-bitzy etc.
Rebellion
Lyrics: Mas Kimura / Music, Arrangement: yuichi yagi
Itzy-bitzy etc.
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
Spreading out like wildfire
Never ever have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Take the chance and with my lighter
Spark the fire
Come burn me out
I'm not a sheep to count
This overkill and saddled stories
Wearing me down
Snap out of the system
Break out, give it everything
This is our time
Where yours to discover
Hello brand new world
Would you welcome the light
And free us from the night
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
...until the end of time
異次元の向こう側へ連れて行ってあげる Rebellion
To the other side of another dimension, I'll take you, Rebellion
Time to get this party started
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
Two steps to the left
Two steps to the right
Then back to where we started
And then over again
Step out of the circle
Break out, we've got everything
This is our time
Rejoice to discover
Blue sky, take us home
To where we belong
And free us from the night
Take us to paradise
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, you desire
Ignite our beating hearts
Jump into the flame of life
それぞれのステージへ
To each of our stages
Dance until the end of time
異次元の向こう側へ連れて行ってあげる Rebellion
To the other side of another dimension, I'll take you, Rebellion
I know that I can still be the future of this story
I know that I can be free, the one and the only
They tell me that I'm crazy
I'll never let them stop me
Within our afterglow
Time to get this party started
Ever, ever, have I ever
In a center, been a dreamer?
Fire, fire, light the fire
Ignite our beating hearts
Jump into the flame of life
新たな世界へ
To a new world
Jump until the end of time
異次元の向こう側へ連れて行ってあげる...
To the other side of another dimension, I'll take you...
Jump into the flame of life
それぞれのステージへ
To each of our stages
Jump until the end of time
異次元の向こう側へ連れて行ってあげる Rebellion
To the other side of another dimension, I'll take you, Rebellion
Time to get this party started
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, you desire
Time to get this party started
Oh!
Whoo! Yeah!
Hello, Advent!
Hello! Welcome to the Advent 3D showcase!
Whoo! Yeah!
Our debut song Rebellion in 3D!
How did you guys like it?
Are you guys hyped? Hype!
Yeah!
Aw, you know we just really couldn't wait to show you
our first performance in 3D, could we?
Oh!
Oh, we're gonna do our best today! I'm so excited!
Yeah! Whoo!
Well, if we open that door, it should lead us to the
EN arena, right?
Yeah! Let's open it right now!
Yeah! Let's go! Let's go!
Wait, why isn't it opening?
Open up! Open up!
Hey, are you pushing hard enough?
Is there a key?
Are you touching the door?
Hee! Maybe back here...
Maybe we missed something?
Hmm...
Uh? Oh wait, guys, what the heck is that?
What? Whoa!
Muahahahahaha!
You've finally arrived, huh?
Ew, it's gross!
Who are you?
I am Pokey!
Have you not seen me on Advent's logo?!
Oh yeah! I've seen you before! Hi Pokey!
Hi! Look at you! You're so cute! Aw!
BE SILENT!!!
Sassy!
So you want to open that door and go stand on the
holoEN stage like real idols, right?
Yeah! Yes!
Well then, I'll open the door
after you complete three challenges!
Three challenges? No!
If you can prove that you're true idols and get
through all the challenges, the door will open!
I guess we have to do it then, huh?
We got it! Yeah!
Okay, so what are the challenges? Because I think we'll
be able to beat them really easily!
Yeah! That's right!
You seem to be pretty confident, huh?
Well then, time to get this party started!
Bring out the donuts!
Whoa! Donuts!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Right now? Okay.
Ready? Everybody ready?
Wait, so...
Okay, here we go! Three, two, one!
Stick out your gyatt for the rizzler.
You're so bau bau.
You're so Bibotax.
I just want to be your Shiori.
How was that?
You just got Bibotaxed in 3D!
3D! Yeah!
Let's go!
Enough! Enough! Enough!
This is a serious challenge! Stop that now!
Wait, Bibotax...
Fuwamoco can pass this easily.
Yahoo! We'll eat them all up!
Donut! Donut!
Well then, if you love donuts so much... How about you get covered in them?!
1st Challenge: Donut Tower Challenge
Honestly, that's pretty... how was that?
What is that? Hey, yahoo!
Alright, donut-lovers, FUWAMOCO, you step forward right now,
Now sit!
Eh? Oh? Oh, whoa, wait, what's going on?
Down...
You guys are doggy in 3D! I know!
Good doggies, your first challenge has already started!
Stack all the donuts on top of FUWAMOCO!
You have 10 seconds to stack them, and keep them still for another 10 seconds!
Easy! Ready? Go!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0!
Okay now, keep it steady for the next 10 seconds!
Whoo! Oh, that was easy! Too easy!
Hardly a challenge! Yahoo!
You call this a challenge?
Yeah, we were just sitting here. Yeah, it was...
Okay, you're done warming-up?
Now it's time for the real challenge!
Eh? Yahoo? That was just a warm-up? That's not fair!
FUWAMOCO, step forward!
Now sit!
Whaiyo! Oh, they're doing it again. Oh no.
Down...
Yeah, you like that, don't you? What is this?
Aww, such good puppies!
Yeah, you did good! Puppy time!
Now show your tummies like good puppies!
Oh, so cute! Bau bau! Whaiyo! This is strange!
This time, you have to count to five seconds after putting each donut on top of them.
Ah? Why? Okay.
Stay still. We got it, we got it. Stay steady.
FUWAMOCO, you need to count, okay?
Okay.
Ready...
Go!
Whai-yo, Two-bo-bo, Three-bo-bo, Fuwa-bo-bo, Five-bo-bo!
Whaiyo! Whoo! Nice! Great job! We did it!
Wait, stand still for a moment.
I have something that, you know, after seeing you in that pose...
...I think I would like to use right now. What do you have?
You remember? My birthday present! It's a piece of paper.
No! You forgot in... this been a year! It wasn't that kind of a birthday present!
It was a really good birthday present. I want to redeem it.
Oh right, now! Get ready!
I got you! No! No!
Yeah, how about Fuwa-bau?
Nothing. But you know, now that I've got one touch, I don't think it was enough.
Can I have one more? No! Maybe for your birthday next year!
You did better than I expected.
Well then, let's move on to the second challenge!
Okay, we're ready to beat the second challenge! Let's go!
Yeah!
Let's go!
What the beef is that?
It's a box!
Whoa!
I don't like boxes.
For the second challenge, I will test your courage!
I want each one of you to cover your eyes and put your hands inside the box.
Then you need to guess what's in the box, just by touching it!
2nd Challenge: What's in the Box Challenge
Okay, how about you go first, Nerissa?
Ah, I mean, I guess, you know, even a child could probably play this game.
You'll be fine.
Ready to try, Nerissa?
Alright, I'll take care of this.
It might be too easy, so maybe I should put on a blindfold.
Alright, I'm ready.
This is what's inside your box!
Kiara Plush Toy
Alright, come on, come on, my old lady.
What is it? What is it?
You have to touch it!
You have to guess within time!
Is it a puppy? I don't know.
Is it a mouse? Is it a kitten?
No! No! No! Meow meow!
Is that your final answer?
You're kind of close.
Is it... is it Kiara?
I have no idea. I don't feel...
You have to touch it once!
You can do it! Use both hands!
Is it Kiara?
Remove your blindfold.
That was so stressful!
Kiara! It wasn't that bad.
I have this at home! I have this at home!
It followed you all the way here!
Every time I touched it, it felt like it was moving!
That wasn't so hard, right?
YOU! THE LITTLE ONE! You go next!
Hey! Who you calling little one, eh?
Don't underestimate the Gamer of Advent! Yeah!
Alright, so-called "Gamer of Advent," this time it's not something cute and fluffy like Nerissa's...
Oh, I'm ready.
Come on, bring it!
これは頭の中だけの話じゃない。Yeah!
This isn't just a story in my head! Yeah!
Wow, Japanese! Your Japanese is so good!
I am now one with darkness.
Let darkness guide you, my queen. Here you go.
Okay, what's in the box, Bijou?
Okay, I'm brave.
Oh, what is this? What does it feel like? It feels hard.
Why were you so scared, Biboo? Huh?
Wait, you... I'm brave.
Okay, this is hard.
Okay, and it's cold.
Yes, I think I know what this is.
Biboo, feel it! Feel it really good!
Okay, I'll feel... I'll feel it up real good.
Whoa... Whoa. Mmm, do you like this? I'll feel it up...
Whoa, Biboo, you're so gentle.
Oh, it feels so good, right?
Oh, shut up, Biboo! Oh!
Is it the pebble?
Is it the rock? Wait...
Whoa!
I'm disappointed. Keep... keep touching more of it.
It's not... it's not a rock?
I said to feel it really good and you didn't. Yeah!
Smack it around a little.
Go... go up, Biboo. Go up.
Come on, both hands. Both hands.
What's this?
Whoa, it goes higher. Yeah!
It's a rock.
The rock. It's a rock, right?
I mean, but you know...
Yeah, you know.
Is it... is it a geode?
Is it a gem?
Geode?
Mountain?
Why is it so tall?
Any more answers? We got there, huh?
Wait, I thought this was going to be easy.
It's okay, it's okay.
I thought you were the best gamer, Biboo.
Yeah, but this is not a rock!
What is it?
Oh, is it a Moai?
It's a Moai! It's a Moai, right?
Yay!
All right, let's remove your blindfold. Come on.
Biboo wasn't feeling it well enough.
I know, it wasn't rock hard enough, huh? Shiori...
I guess it was too easy for you, huh?
I did it! Yay!
Fuwawa, you're next! I'll need to give you a harder one...
Harder than this?
I know your weakness, Fuwawa. Are you ready?
My... my weakness?
Oh... that makes me feel scared, though.
It'll be okay, Fuwawa.
Protect her smile! Yay!
Wait, the song demon guards us! You can do it! Yeah! Yeah!
Protect her smile! You can do it!
I can do this! Let's go!
Let's go!
All right, let me remove your eyes.
No, both her little sisters are cheering her on.
What, both? Me and you?
No.
Good luck, Fuwawa.
Wait, what is it? What does it feel like?
You can do it! You're so close!
You just have to touch it. Touch it!
I want to be brave! I have to touch it!
You can be brave, Fuwawa!
Be brave! Let's go! Fight it! Fight it!
Come on, Fuwawa! You've got it!
Wait, wait, wait! What... what is it?
Wait, wait, wait! What... what does it feel like?
What... what is this? What?
It's... what is it? Is it... is it fizzy?
Is it moving?
Ah, it's thick, kind of sticky!
Ah, Nerissa! It's long! What is it? Move...
Oh, yeah, use both hands. Yeah.
Both hands, both hands.
Hey, yeah, yeah! It goes boing-boing-boing!
Punch it, punch it!
Boing-boing-boing! Punch it, yeah!
This is... Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam!
Yeah, show it who's boss! Yeah!
Pound it out! Yeah!
Now what is it?
Do you think you can guess? Do you have a guess?
I'm gonna pick it up, I'm gonna pick it up, I'm gonna show it whose boss! Yeah, yeah!
Is this... is this... a toy snake?
Yay! Good job! Good job, Fuwawa!
Ha! Good job! Pow!
This demon dog's not scared!
Yeah! Yeah! I'm so proud of you!
All right.
You've conquered something especially scary. Well done, Fuwawa.
Shiori, it's your turn!
Oh, Shiori!
All right, all right! You conquered it.
I can do it, I can do it. Good job, good job. All right.
You're an archiver and a collector, yes?
Yeah.
This creature may be in your collection.
But can you tell me what it is?
Oh! I've seen a lot of creatures.
All right, let me remove my eyes.
Give me your beautiful, beautiful eyes!
Say goodbye to your eyes!
Just for you, beautiful lash-light eyes.
I'm gonna take them.
All right.
Can I move?
Okay Shiori, what's in the box?!
スライム
Slime
Is it gonna bite? It's gonna bite Shiori!
I remember this thing!
Oh, wait, why is it wet?
Oh, what is it? It's slimy!
Oh, sorry! Should I not do that? Sorry.
Did I hurt it?
Yeah, you did.
It's dead now.
Oh, be gentle! You've gotta be gentle.
Oh, gentle?
Oh man, I wanted to punch it.
Punch it! Punch it! Just do it!
All right, all right. It feels... it feels very moist.
It's very cold. It's kind of nice actually. I just want to hug it.
Do you want to rub your face in it?
No!
But I'll rub it against your face!
I think based on the slime you're feeling,
I assume it's Yoric.
Huh? Yoric?
Is it not my goop man? My little goop boy?
What?! How is it not my goop boy?
But it's all wet and gross. What else could it be?
Something gross that's not Yoric? What?
Is it... is it my novel leeches perhaps?
Wait, you guys aren't gross,
so you're great actually.
Oh, what is it if it's not you guys?
Am I hurting it?
Yes!
It's dead now.
I think I killed it.
But so you're saying...
you're saying it's alive, right? Maybe?
No! Guess! What does it feel like?
It feels cold.
What does it feel like to you? Maybe like Mococo's tummy!
No! My tummy is warm!
Are you sure? No, it's cold.
I can't believe it's not Yoric.
Guess! What does it feel like?
Cold? Slimey?
Yes, slimey. And it's not ink?
So what's slimey?
Um, the cucumber in my fridge?
No, no, no! What's slimey? Think more simple.
Simple? I can't think at all right now, it's cold!
Slime? Is that slime?
I thought it was Yoric. That's ridiculous. I'm putting my eyes back.
Good job! Yay!
Wow... Let me check what this is.
It's not even Yoric. Pathetic.
Pathetic! I can't believe it's not butter.
Wow Shiori, you figured it out!
Oh yeah, after five tries, huh?
It's okay, you did it! Good job Shiori!
Okay, I have something extra special
for the last box.
Mococo, get over here!
Something special, like nice? Not like bad?
Of course special like nice.
You're such a special girl.
Okay, I don't like the dark but I'll do my best.
You got this Mococo! We believe in you!
Are you ready, Mococo? This one is really special!
I need a push.
Like a gentle push, but...
Stop, stop push!
Guide me.
Okay, be really careful, okay?
And maybe go right to the front.
Go right to the front.
It's a little scary, so be careful.
フワワ
Fuwawa
It feels warm. What?
What was that?
Was that wet?
Mococo! Stop! Don't scream!
Wait, what?
Don't scream!
Wait, why is it moving? I feel dizzy!
I feel dizzy! Nerissa hold me!
I'm holding you.
I got you.
What's in the Box Challenge
箱の中身は一体なに！？
What is inside the box!?
Oi, oi!
What was that? What was that?
It's okay. It's okay.
It feels like it's moving closer to my tummy area!
What's going on? What was that?
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
You sure?
Yeah, I promise. I promise.
Ah! It's touching me! It feels like it's moving closer to me!
What's going on? What was that?
It's okay. What was that?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
What's going on?
It's okay.
Ah! What's going on? What is going on?
Don't swap it!
Wait, wait, wait! Wait!
Is it punching me? Wait!
I wonder what... Do you have any guesses what could it be, Moco-chan?
Wait, is it... I don't know!
Can I touch it?
Yeah, it's okay. Yeah, it's okay.
Sticky!
Wait! What is going on? Ah! It's... it's just sticky! It bit my fingers!
It's okay. It's okay.
Wait! Is this Mococo? Is this Mococo?
Bau bau! Yeah! Mococo! Yeah!
Why would I not? Mococo! Wait!
Mococo, you got there, huh?
You look weird.
Actually, I licked you.
That's where you're gonna stay.
She put in so much effort.
She tastes good.
Ah, Moco-chan, kind of tasted a bit sweaty today.
So, on a scale of one to five, how would you rate the flavor?
One to five? Like, a three? Sweaty and fuzzy.
It's decent, I guess.
Ten out of ten?
Yeah, three out of ten. Three out of ten. Sticky!
Alright, good job everyone!
You guys did pretty good!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Time for the second challenge, yay!
Mococo-chan, you did a great job.
What a weird challenge.
I'll miss the slime.
We didn't even make it Monopoly's!
That's still kind of mean, huh?
Hey, Monopoly's are great, but they're a little slimy. Bau bau!
Don't get too comfortable. There's still one challenge left!
One more!
Are you ready for the final challenge?
Ah! Yeah! Let's try the last challenge. Are we ready, Advent?
Bau bau! Yeah! Let's go!
Let me out of here! Why am I still in this box? No! This isn't where I should be!
It's your home! It's your home!
It's your imagination, Fuwa-bau-Moco-bau!
Bye bye!
One, two, three, let's go!
Stickin' out your gyatt for the rizzler
You're so Bau Bau
You're so biboo tax
I just wanna be your Shiori
Bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau!
Okay, that was good.
The final challenge is going to be an intense battle! Go ahead and take these special weapons!
Oh look, it's scissor time!
I got my own gnome! He's fluffy too. Bau bau!
お前はもう死んでいる。
You are already dead.
And I have my toe! Yeah, my toe! Ha!
Rock rock! Yeah!
Yeah! I got the spoon!
Let's see if you can beat this guy. Attack, my beautiful specimen!
Zombie Challenge / ゾンビチャレンジ
Zombie Challenge
Is it over?
It's gotta be, right? Like there can't be anymore than that, right?
No way is it over! Come forth, my minions!
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh no!
Oh my god!
Get behind me!
Get them, girls!
No! Behind you!
Yeah! They're spawning!
No! Stop that!
Help!
Get them, girls!
I got you!
No! Fuwawa, you can do it!
No! You got this!
Behind you!
Help her!
Fuwawa, no!
Behind you!
Yeah! Nice!
Nice! Oh my god!
There's so many now!
Get them!
Oh, there's more!
Wait, wait, wait!
It's my turn!
Take this, my gnome!
There's more coming! Hit them!
Get them, Mococo! Mococo, let's go!
Hit them in their belly button!
Step on them!
No! Mococo, get you!
Don't watch out!
Watch out! Watch out!
Behind you!
You're doing the best!
I know it!
Behind her tummy!
Oh, did Mococo die?
Get them, Biboo! Go, get them!
Get them, let's go!
Get them!
Nice! Get them, Biboo!
That's it! Biboo!
Whoa! That's my queen!
I can see you! I can see you!
Rock, paper, scissors!
You're so good! You're so brave!
You're right there!
You did it!
Get them, Nerissa!
Go, go! I got you!
Get them!
Get them! Eat your cookie!
Behind you!
Nerissa, look out!
Would be dead right now!
Whoa! Put them down!
I did it!
I'm trying my best!
Nice!
There's so many!
My spoon!
Get them! Come on!
Over there!
Shiori!
It's Shiori's turn!
I'm tired.
Oh my god! Get them!
Use the rocks!
No! Use the bread!
Yeah! Go!
Oh, Shiori!
Go! Shiori!
Shiori, watch out!
Shiori is coming!
Is it over?
I think we've gotta be good, right?
There's no way there's anymore after all that.
I'm too old for this.
Wait!
Stop!
Where are they?
They're behind us!
Mococo, watch out!
Watch out! Help me!
Use the power of music!!!
Alright, Advent, I think we've got no choice!
Let's do this, Advent!
禁じられた遊び
Lyrics: 宝野アリカ
Music: 片倉三起也
Forbidden Play
Lyrics: Arika Takano
Music: Mikiya Katakura
薔薇の蕾を繋げて
Connecting rosebuds together
銀の鎖越えて
Beyond the silver chains
今宵も独り果てる
Tonight again I perish alone
あなたが憎らしい
I find you detestable
膝を突いてお嘗めよ
Get on your knees and lick
苦い愛の雫を
The bitter droplets of love
天使に施す
Bestowing upon angels
彩の挿絵
A colorful illustration
慈愛と優越感の中
Amidst affection and superiority
心はまた肥えて
My heart swells again
捥ぎれた羽は月光に
Plucked wings in the moonlight
生き返り蠢く
Come back to life and squirm
ああ　闇夜よりも
Ah, even more than the dark night
かぐわしき黒
A fragrant blackness
二人の墓標　十字架の下で
Under the cross of our two gravestones
結びましょう
Let us unite
薔薇の鎖を外して
Removing the chain of roses
白い手首を重ねて
Overlapping our white wrists
触れ合うことの奇跡　あなたが愛おしい
The miracle of touching each other; you are dear to me
瞳を閉じて捧げよう
I'll close my eyes and offer up...
痛い愛の言葉を
...painful words of love
ガラスに滲んだ　赤いアネモネ
Red anemones blurred on the glass
さあ、今、好きと言って
Now, say you love me
緋色の唇で
With your scarlet lips
背徳は　そびえ立つ城壁
Immorality is a towering castle wall
阿るのは神
The one who cajoles is God
そうなふうに　導き続けて
Continue to lead me that way
そして　私の目を
And then, my eyes...
塞いだら　誰より優しく
If you cover them, more gently than anyone else...
名前を呼んで
Call out my name
その時　知るでしょう
At that time, you will know...
永遠の意味を
The meaning of eternity
薔薇の指輪を交ぜて
Intertwining rings of roses
皮のリボン結んで
Tying a leather ribbon
鏡の向こう側
On the other side of the mirror
全てが狂おしい
Everything is maddening
迷い込んで悟りましょう
Let's wander in and realize...
巡る愛の歴史を
...the revolving history of love
涙で飾ろう
Let's decorate with tears
黒いマリアージュ
A black marriage
さあ、今、好きと言って
Now, say you love me
純潔の唇で
With your pure lips
薔薇の首輪を繋げて
Connecting the rose collar
銀の鎖を咥えて
Taking the silver chain in my mouth
今宵も一人果てる
Tonight too, I perish alone
あなたが憎らしい
I detest you
跪いてなめましょう
Let's kneel and lick...
苦い愛の雫を
...bitter drops of love
天使に施す
Bestowing upon angels...
青いドラジェ
...blue dragées
薔薇の鎖を外して
Removing the chain of roses
白い手首を重ねて
Overlapping our white wrists
触れ合うことの奇跡　あなたが愛おしい
The miracle of touching each other; you are dear to me
瞳を閉じて捧げよう
I'll close my eyes and offer up...
痛い愛の言葉を
...painful words of love
ガラスに滲んだ　赤いアネモネ
Red anemones blurred on the glass
心から　好きという
To say I love you from my heart
汚れなき口づけを
With a stainless kiss
Yeah! We did it! We beat all those zombies!
Yay!
Looks like you guys are true idols, huh?
I'm gonna need to hear you sing some more, though!
What? You said that the door would open
if we go through three challenges!
You're totally hooked on us, aren't you?
Well then, let's perform our second original song
and open the door!
Hoi!
Please listen to our new original song...
...Sirens!
Let's play, thought that you liked my wild side
Come gimme, gimme a bite
Bite, why you don't got no white?
Good things come in twos,
I don't think you got a clue
Can't take a hint? Come on, roll the dice
If you want it, then you gotta gotta catch 'em
My boy's games I can't forget,
haven't you noticed?
What you keep down comes back around, our little secret
Open the cage and fly away, my new horizon
Only need one chance
I've been running so long
Don't rush it, chase me until
You can't breathe no when
Living on the edge of a phantom where you drew the line
I love it, the sound of ecstasy
Just sirens, sirens, sirens
You know how I like it, like it
I'm quicker than lightning, sirens
Oh yeah, running don't need a rewind don't care what's wrong
I hear the sirens, sirens, sirens loud
Chasing spin me round and round
Play all night I love the sound
Let me hear the sirens
Up and down and underground
Sirens blasting all around
Oh baby it makes me feel so...
Hit me, I'll hit back, a stronger maniac
Come break me, but careful, don't touch, look up
I got a long list, no just about you
You try to make a move, big thank you
Go look around for help, it's no use
I, I, it's no use
My foolish games, I can't be hidden, haven't you noticed?
What you keep down comes back around and you're gonna like it
Opening the cage I'll fly away, my new horizon
Only need one chance, wanna hear sirens
Just sirens, sirens, sirens
You know how I like it, like it
I'm quicker than lightning, sirens
Oh yeah, running don't need a rewind don't care what's wrong or what's right
Turn it up a notch, make it dangerous
Kicking through the night, we're outrageous
Who said you were big? You can't tame us
Turn it up a notch, make it danger...
Hey!
Sirens, give me adrenaline
My perfect chase, heart race, let's stay this way
Ah hear your call
Come on give me a sign
Sirens, sirens, sirens
You know how I like it, like it
I'm quicker than lightning, sirens
Oh yeah, running don't need a rewind don't care what's wrong
I hear the sirens, sirens, sirens loud
Chasing spin me round and round
Play all night I love the sound
Let me hear the sirens
Up and down and underground
Sirens blasting all around
Oh baby it makes me feel so...
ADVENT-S! How was that performance?
Did you like it?
We're not criminals, we're idols, right?
That was FANTASTIC!!
We need to show the world how amazing Advent is.
You can open the door now,
go, go!
Are we ready, Advent?
We're ready, Advent!
Okay, let's go!
Let's go! Bau Bau!
Alright, everyone's waiting for us, so let's go!
Yeah! Let's go!
Parade, parade, parade, it's time to take the stage
I hear the voices calling out our name
Parade, parade, parade, a new journey awaits
Just hear the sound and we can start again
Leaving only weightless echoes
I run because I heard a voice say go
Far away, let in all the darkness
It's a name shining for us to notice
Memories that fill us up with kindness and love
You reach out and tell me...
Please come close
Let's surprise people who don't know
How rare what they call symbols
Here we are as one
Parade, parade, parade
It's time to take the stage
When disappointment gets in your way
Love will shine and keep you safe
Fill a realm with wishes
Your wings will take you high
These silent prayers will become our light
Guiding us on an endless flight
Finally we found each other
I can stand tall and say
Starting from here, starting right now
Our bright parade, parade
Listen
Full of amazing feelings
We sing
And we're not afraid of what they think
No one can
Take hold what we're imagining
They don't know
Of magic and our destiny
We met
This was an empty story
But now
Too many words to count them all out
Feelings that leave no room for doubt
Take a look at where we are now
All together as one
Parade, parade, parade
It's all so beautiful
The moments of our brightness shining
Lighting up the darkest night
Rain and shine and treasure
A kaleidoscope sky
A journey that is meant just for us
And here I am right by your side
Cause here I am standing by your side
When you look back and up the next time
You'll hear us saying welcome home
Forever we'll be waiting
Parade, parade, parade
It's time to take the stage
We're gonna shine right through the darkness
Open up share your light
Parade, parade, parade
It's time to take the stage
When disappointment gets in your way
Love will shine and keep you safe
Fill a realm with wishes
Your wings will take you high
These silent prayers will become our light
Guiding us on an endless flight
Yeah, yeah
Ready to dive into
A beautiful star that's new
Starting from here, starting right now
Our bright parade, parade
Whoo!
We're finally here! We're on the stage!
Yay! Whoo!
Oh, I've dreamed about this stage for so long!
Yes! So many stars and people here!
Wait, did you realize?
Our senpai were standing right there!
We're finally there!
They stood here! And now we are!
And now we're also senpai together!
Wow!
Well, we have one more song for you guys!
Everybody ready?
Yeah! Ready! Let's go! Whoo!
We're ready to greet the world
We're voyaging forward
With courage run toward a brand new start
Let's go live
Bridging the distance across the sea
Endless breeze
Meeting heart to heart
Waking from a dream
Run up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue
How will we connect
In this new frontier we're journeying through
Starting in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars
Radiant and warm
Charged with energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life
Sure we thought it'd take...
Just when we're running out of stop, straight to the top, that's right!
We're ready to seize the game,
a shimmering showcase,
creating a new phrase where we can shine.
Day by day,
our colorful stories will intertwine.
Get ready to cross the ways,
we're voyaging forward,
with courage to run toward the brand new stage.
Let's go live,
bridging the distance across the sea,
endlessly, follow me,
and we'll turn the page.
Breaking through the doubt,
we know we'll figure out
a way to clear each towering trial.
Sharing all our hope,
we can conquer any challenge with a smile.
We'll link our hearts
as we start to cross the globe.
Knowing
no matter where we are,
no matter how far,
we can be stars, let's go!
I want to chase the wish unwaveringly,
writing out a brand new story.
Share the future that we can see,
making them reality.
Take my hand and reach for the screen,
all we need are glittering dreams.
Our hearts and souls
are fulfilled in the world we build.
We're ready to seize the day,
traversing the path with the shimmering highways
through everywhere.
Step by step,
gathering stories that we can share.
Get ready to lead the way,
with each generation,
a shining sensation, a dream afar.
Let's make fans,
making a moment of history,
joyfully, follow me,
we'll connect the world.
They'll hear our song ringing out
over hills and oceans,
our legend grows and continues.
We'll carry on, starting now,
setting hearts in motion,
connecting all of the world.
Yeah!
Thank you so much to everyone here today!
How have you liked our 3D showcase
with #Advent3D? Let's see your comments!
And we had a lot of challenges
and so much fun performing live to everyone, right?
Thanks to all of you, it was a really exciting 3D showcase!
And we can't wait to see you all
in 3D for future concerts and events!
We hope that you'll continue to watch
Advent really closely and help us here on our journey!
But, but...
Oh?
Last but not least, we have some merch to reveal, don't we, Advent?
Yeah!
So, why don't we go and take our first look, huh?
Oh, I wonder what it is?
Yeah, what could it be?
Tada!
Shiori Novella Matching Belt
It's the belt! That's right guys!
If you ever want something for your pants
or other things that I can't talk about, boy, you can have a Shiori-ish belt!
Yes, so super cool!
What's next?
It's room slippers! Finally, you can have your own candy feet!
Koseki Bijou Room Slippers
Just like me, the pebbles!
Aren't they beautiful?
So pretty, I want my own pair!
Yeah! They'll be comfortable!
Do they make that 'clink' sound when you walk?
Right! You'll have to get it to find out!
Get multiple so you can lick one and use one!
What? Like a lollipop!
Okay, Shiori, let's see what's next! Here we go!
Nerissa Ravencroft Paper Knife
And next is going to be the Nerissa Ravencroft paper cutter knife!
Nerissa Ravencroft
Paper Knife
If you like to cut open letters or you just like to cut open things that are paper...
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
ペーパーナイフ
Nerissa Ravencroft
Paper Knife
this, based on my microphone design, is going to be perfect for all those sorts of needs.
So please consider buying it if you like my weapon design.
And 次は...
And next...
Fuwawa Abyssgard
Fuwawa's Tail Keychain
Hi! Fuwawa!
I have a very fluffy tail holder for you!
So everywhere you go, I'll be shaking my tail...
...and I'll be fluffy forever! Bau bau!
Bau bau! And 次は...
Bau bau! And next...
Mococo Abyssgard
Mococo's Tail Keychain
And next, we have Mococo!
Keyholder with my tail! I'm a tail!
Yeah, I'll be with you everywhere, okay?
Everywhere! Yeah!
And next...
Pokey Hand In Cushion
Next we have, as you met today, Pokey, our cute mascot for all of Advent and the Advent-trix.
It is a hand cushion. So if your hands are cold, you can warm them up...
...or if you're taking a nap, you can lay on it.
It's perfect for all sorts of pillowy transportation needs.
So do consider getting your own Pokey and beat him up!
Don't beat him up!
3D Acrylic Stand
And finally, Advent 3D Acrylic Stand! That's triple the Ds!
These acrylic stands, they're special because they have our 3D pose!
They're big! Posing!
Yeah, you need to get your paws on it, okay? Yeah! Bau bau!
Now, the merch cart will be open after the stream, so get them ASAP!
ASAP! Right now! It is your chance! Now! Yes!
How often are you going to be able to get our 3D debut merch? Not often, I think.
So don't miss out on it, because I'm pretty sure it's limited, right?
It's in 3D! Triple D! It's the time! Now's the time!
Now do we have any messages for everyone?
I just wanted to say thank you so much to all the Advent-trix for making this dream of ours come true!
Bau bau, thank you!
And as for me, I just want to say thank you for supporting us and helping me not die!
So yeah! I don't feel shaky anymore! Whoo!
Seriously, without all of your guy's love and support, we wouldn't be able to be standing on this stage today.
So thank you for loving us, thank you for loving me, thank you for loving Advent and hololive and for being here today for our special first 3D collaboration.
And Mococo... I'm a bit nervous, but... thank you from the bottom of my heart, thank you so much.
You know we really couldn't do it without you. And I really hope that you'll think that 'Wow, I really like Advent, I like them even more after today!'
So please continue to support us and we'll do our best, okay? Bau bau!
And last but not least... Watch out Advent-trix, Advent's at full power now, we're in 3D!
It's not the end, it's just the beginning. So please keep supporting us, okay? Thank you everyone!
Thank you, thank you! I hope you had an amazing time today!
Keep smiling! This was hololive English -Advent-!
Bye-bye darlings! Bau bau! Bau bau bau!