(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Hello, everybody!
Welcome to my 3D debut!
Oh god, what year is it? Where am I?
Well, we're here in my office. Hello, everyone!
Hi!
Whee!
So today we have some exciting stuff happening,
but don't you guys want to see my desk and my office?
Isn't this nice? Ooh! Wow!
Got all these papers here.
Shall we do a spin?
Hyoo!
We're watching the pre-chat and you guys were being so cute.
Thank you for coming.
あ、こんにちわっつ、皆さん、ありがとう！
Ah, konnichiwa-tsu, everyone, thank you!
I'm gonna try to put my feet up on this desk. Let's see if it works.
Kyuu! Yoh! Ta-da!
Just, you know, just hanging around. Just chillin'.
Hey, I want to get some cool screenshots. Make sure you guys take pictures.
You can post them on Twitter with this hashtag. Yeah.
Kick back, relax, you know, just thinking around.
Ooh. Maybe I'll just take a nap.
I've been working so hard for this, for today's showcase,
and now I just want to take a break.
Oh, who's this? There's people here. Oh, pictures. Let's see.
Uh, who was first? Ina! First had her debut.
Ina's debut. So cute. I love her. She does this so well.
I don't know how she does it. And mine looks pretty cool, too, right?
Eh, and then we have Kiara? Kiara what? Or Calli first?
No, it was Kiara first. Yeah. Wasn't it? Ah, the worm.
Oh, sorry, just reading chat. Okay, yeah.
And then after it was Calli and then Gura was yesterday.
Their debuts were so fun to watch. We have a collab happening tomorrow, too.
So make sure to tune into that. But first...
...don't you guys want to see my office? Yay!
I want to see how fast it can go. Bum bum bum bum bum bum...
Very high speeds. Wait, I'm gonna get dizzy. Okay.
All right. Let me scoot on over here. I want to show you guys around my office.
Scoot, scoot. Oh. Oh my god. It's like the first time reveal.
You guys have never seen this before, right? Ooh! Whistle, whistle. Ho!
Oh!
Look at these nice kicks. Cute, cute, cute, cute.
Pop, pop!
Heh, cool, right? Uh, what are those?
So smooth.
What are you looking at?
Oh, oh, and my watch.
Brrrr! We time traveled. What year is it?
Okay, let's see.
Yeah! Ta-da!
Finally, full high quality official 3D. Let's go!
All right. Well, should I show you guys around
over here?
Bubba! Bubba made it all the way to Japan!
Eh, Bubba's so cute!
Oh Bubba, pet-the-pet-the-pet-the.
Eh Bubba, Bubba... maybe Bubba knows some tricks.
Bubba! Bubba can fly!
It's magic!
Bubba, how are you doing that? Maybe it's his cape.
The cape's making him fly.
Eh Bubba, can you do... Bubba do flip.
Let's see if Bubba can do flip.
Holy shit, he did a flip!
Now if you guys ask for it, there it is.
There's the flip.
Bubba, Bubba's so small, right?
I wonder if Bubba can sit down.
Maybe Bubba can sit over here.
Bubba use the chair. Bubba use the chair.
Bubba's a detective now! Wow, how cute!
Eh, I want to see from the desk. Bubba, cute, cute, cute.
Okay Bubba. Bubba jump!
Eh, can Bubba dance? Bubba dance, Bubba dance!
Oh, Bubba, good boy! Good boy, Bubba! So cute, right?
All right Bubba, come on this way.
I want to show you guys around my office a little bit.
Ta-da!
This is a conspiracy board,
and I'm at the center of it all.
But this is... this is evil Ame, right?
We don't look exactly the same, see?
That one's evil. I'm the good Ame.
Aha. Yes, yes, totally.
Right Bubba? That Ame's evil. Bubba, attack!
All right, over here. Fish tank, fish tank!
Yeah, there's no fish in it, but it's pretty, right?
Bubba ate all the fish. Bubba was hungry.
Oh, there's no fish in there yet. They did not die.
They were... Bubba ate them. They're just sleeping.
Um, and then over here the window. Ah, I love having a window in the back.
I mean this one, I need to clean it a little bit, I'm not gonna lie.
It needs a little bit of a scrub.
And then we have the stars up here. Wow!
They're too high, I can't reach.
And then the monitors so I can look at chat.
This is definitely where I'm looking at chat.
And not somewhere else in the room. Yes, right here. Right here.
And of course my mixing set.
And now over here. Oh...
Sus.
These are the ones on the desk were the good Myth members,
but these are the evil versions.
Sus.
And just a little sus. Oh yeah.
Well, we have some things, you know, to get to.
I'll show you a little bit more over here.
These are my boxes I need to unpack.
Did you guys know that box is hako in Japanese?
Doesn't it sound familiar? Like a certain something...
Getting a phone call.
I have a phone? Oh yeah, I do have a phone.
Let me see. I wonder who it could be.
もしもし
Hello?
Huh? Yagoo? Yagoo's on the phone. He's calling me.
Hold on let me sit. Gotta sit for this.
Uh, huh.
はい。なるほど。お。
Yes. I see. Oh.
え？本当ですか？
Eh? Really?
Okay, okay. Uh-huh. Okay.
Really important phone call, item meeting.
Actually, there's a case for us to go check out.
A crime scene.
I mean...
We've gotta go and see what the heck all that was about.
Let's go to detective work!
やったー！ババ、カモン！
Yatta! Bubba, come on!
Huh?
A crime scene right here in the middle of the street?
I guess this is what YAGOO called me for.
Hmm... We should take a really close look,
examine all the clues and try to figure out who might be behind this.
I guess the investigators came by and prepped this scene already for me.
We have the outline of a body here,
and one, two, three, four... four clues.
Well, before I touch anything,
my hands are clean, don't worry, I'm going to take a picture.
Let's take a picture.
Hold on, let me get my camera.
Alright. This is better before I infect everything with my germs and fingerprints.
Let's take a look.
Take a picture here. Gun.
Now let's see here.
A banana?
What's this doing here?
Okay...
Let me just take one of the crime scene in total.
And here we have... what is this, a machete?
A gun? I mean, a knife?
Hmm.
And lastly we have...
a hat. Baseball cap.
Let me see.
Alright, let's take a picture.
Okay, I'm gonna have to get closer now.
Let me get my magnifying glass out of my pocket.
Alright. First, let's have a look at this banana.
This banana really caught my interest.
It looks unopened, uneaten banana. Let me take a look.
I don't see any bruises on it yet.
So, maybe... maybe what happened is
they were walking down the street and about to eat their banana
when somebody attacked them.
Alright, let me take a look at this hat.
Baseball cap.
They were probably wearing this and it's pretty far from their head.
There's no blood on it, so...
let me take a closer look.
Maybe somebody wanted their hat?
Maybe somebody was trying to steal their hat, I wonder,
and tried taking it from them while they were eating a banana...
about to eat a banana.
Alright, let me take a look at this.
Let me see.
We have this machete.
It doesn't look like there's any marks on it,
so they probably didn't even get to use this.
I don't think that that's the murder weapon,
but maybe...
maybe a case of self-defense.
Alright, and last but not least, let's take a look at the gun,
which I suspect to be the murder weapon.
Let's see.
Shiny?
It's like a skin, very shiny skin on this.
Pretty flashy looking gun.
Let me think.
Well, maybe what happened was that they were walking down the street
after just buying a fresh banana,
and they were about to eat it when suddenly
somebody attacked them
and wanted their hat?
What do you guys think?
Could it be maybe somebody was filming like a TikTok video or something?
I mean, look at how their pose was.
Maybe... no, it's probably like "No, please!"
But it kind of looks like they're doing a, you know, (mimes shooting).
Well...
I think I...
...I missed one.
There's something over here.
Hold on, I need to get a closer look.
I'll show you guys.
Whoa! Hehe.
Now I have the view, huh?
Footsteps.
Hold on.
Let me get this for archive purposes.
Whole scene.
Hmm...
Their legs are spread so wide.
What happened?
Huh?
Okay.
Now let's take a closer look here.
Footsteps.
Hmm. These are way smaller than my feet.
Super small footsteps.
Wait. Small footsteps?
Hmm...
I wonder.
Let's think this through.
Small footsteps...
...banana...
...a hat that somebody wanted...
...a shiny gun?
Wait a second.
Why is this ringing bells?
Huh?
Could it be?
Wait, what is that?
I hear... I hear something from up there.
Huh?
What...
...what is that?
WHOOOOOOO!
Wah ha ha ha!
You dare enter my dimension?
This city ain't big enough for the two of us.
Especially with your fat ass!
Oh!
Not this again!
Smol Ame, I could tell it was you from these clues.
Appearing at the crime scene just confirms it.
Smol Ame, I'm putting you under citizen's arrest!
Hehe! You fell right for my trap!
Take this!
Look at this! Ugh!
Keep missing, it's the ping!
I got hit.
Ugh...
Ah, don't worry guys.
These are tranquilizer darts, not real bullets.
Phew!
Usually I would take you back to the office for holding...
...until police arrive, but...
I have guests coming over.
Hmm...
Here, this should do the trick.
And...
...one!
Next then...
...two!
And Smol Ame, you're next.
He-yah!
And don't come back!
Ah.
I think we should head back to the office and celebrate.
Let's go!
Yay!
We did it! Case closed!
Hehehe.
Smol Ame, beat that!
I'm sure she'll be back, she's like a cockroach.
I can't get rid of her.
Ah, well...
...now that we're here, back at the office...
...I am expecting guests, like I said, so...
Uh...
Maybe we should celebrate first.
How about that?
And then we'll have some guests, maybe?
Hmm.
I do have a treat for you guys.
For being such good investigators.
Ta-ta-ta-daa!
Oof!
Oof! This thing is heavy!
Hehe.
Look at this!
Tada!
Whoa!
Whoa. There's a lot of liquid in here, huh?
At least two gallons.
Because there's so many of you guys in chat...
...we gotta get an appropriate amount to make sure it's effective, that is.
Isn't it cool? It's like a rocket launcher.
Like...
Pew, pew, pew! Pew!
I like it.
Alright, well... you guys ready for your dose?
Wait, before we do this, do you guys have any dance requests for me?
Cause we're gonna have a little dance, dance-off sort of.
I wanna know if you guys have any dances that you want to see first before I give you this... injection.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The worm?
Alright, alright. Maybe I'll do a worm. Maybe.
Flossing?
Eh, flossing really? Okay, you know what? That's it.
Stab!
Hey, can you feel the effects yet? Huh?
Hey, do you guys recognize this song?
Alright, you guys asked for a floss, right? The floss.
I can't... I still can't floss. Shit!
If you guys recognize this song, you're a real one. A real one.
The worm. Okay, I'll do a worm like this. How about this?
Okay, a short worm, short worm.
Whoa, it doesn't really work with the triad.
Hey, come here. Oh...
Alright, snap out of it. We got guests coming. Come on!
Hey, did that help you guys snap out of it?
Come on, come on.
We have a guest now.
One guest for right now.
Let's see. Who could it be? Any... any guesses?
No? Maybe... now? Maybe?
Ah!
Hello!
コンカップー！
Kon-kapu!
My name is Genius Vampire, Yozora Mel!
Yay! Thank you for coming!
Thank you for Mel!
Thank you for having me!
I'm so happy you're here.
Yeah! Today we're going to play a game.
Yeah?
Yeah! What?
With... a ball!
A ball! Wah!
What game do you think?
Uh... let's go?
Maybe... baseball?
Baseball?
さっきやってたね。
We were doing that earlier.
Home run!
No, we're not playing baseball. Maybe... soccer?
Soccer ball?
Yeah, should we play soccer?
Goal!
Okay, well... why don't we go see... 一緒に？
Okay, well... why don't we go see... together?
なになになに？
What, what, what?
Okay, we'll kick.
なんだこれ？
What is this?
Ready? Ready? せーの、よっ！
Ready? Ready? One, two... go!
Wah! なにこれ、なにこれ？
Wah! What's this, what's this?
It's Hopscotch!
Oh! ケンケンパ！
Oh! Ken Ken Pa!
ケンケンパ！ Yeah!
Ken Ken Pa! Yeah!
We're going to play Hopscotch.
英語の名前は Hopscotch.
The English name is Hopscotch.
ホップスコッチ？ うん。
Hopscotch? Yeah.
But in Japan it's called Ken Ken Pa.
ケンケンパ！
Ken Ken Pa!
And every time you jump on one, you do... ケンケンパ！
And every time you jump on one, you do... Ken Ken Pa!
ケンケンパ！ ケンケンパ！
Ken Ken Pa! Ken Ken Pa!
So I'll explain the rule to you guys, but...
So I'll explain the rules to you guys, but...
Yeah, so this is how it works.
So you throw the ball and whichever square it lands on, you get the points for that square.
So we're going to try to throw it on like a high number.
But also, we only have five turns.
So whoever wins at the end of five turns that has most points will get a prize. Victory prize!
So whoever wins at the end of five turns with the most points will get a prize. A victory prize!
なるほど、説明しよう、日本語で。
I see. Let me explain in Japanese.
えー、今回はちょっと特殊なルールになっているみたいです。
Um, it seems like there are some special rules this time.
お互い5点を取るまでは... 投げられると。5回までか。
We throw until we each get 5 points... Oh, up to 5 times?
5回まで投げられますと。
We can throw up to five times.
そしてそして、数字のマスはそのまま得点になるので、
And, and, the numbered squares become your score just as they are,
えー、できるだけ多く取りたい人は、10のマスを目指してボールを投げる。
So, those who want as many points as possible should aim for the 10 square and throw.
ことだ。イエーイ！
That's it. Yay!
そして、合計点数が多い方が勝ち！
And, the one with the higher total score wins!
ケンケンパを失敗したり、特定の升からボールがはみ出したりしたら失敗！
If you fail the hopscotch or if the ball goes out of the specific square, it's a fail!
はい。点数は加算されない、ということだね！
Yes. Points won't be added, that's what it is!
イエーイ！落ち着け！イエーイ！よしよしよし
Yay! Calm down! Yay! Good, good, good.
So because Mel is my senpai, Mel gets the first turn. イエーイ！
So because Mel is my senpai, Mel gets the first turn. Yay!
よし！しょうがないな。
Alright! Can't be helped then.
ジーニアス・ヴァンパイアの力を見せてやろう。
Let me show you the power of a genius vampire.
Let's see, let's see.
では、第一球。行きます！なー！
Now, the first ball. Here I go! Naa!
Go! Ah, ah, ah!
マジか。マジか。
For real? For real?
So the rules are if you get it out, it goes to the next person's turn. So I guess it's my turn.
アメリア。へへへ。アメリア。ネクスト。オッケー。
Amelia. Hehehe. Amelia. Next. Okay.
So Ame next.
頑張れゲーマー、レッツゴー。
Good luck gamer, let's go.
Doo! Oh, oh!
うそでしょ！お、お、おお！
No way! Oh, oh, oh!
10 points! Okay.
Now let's see the real test.
No switching feet.
Okay. ケン、ケン、パ。ケン、ケン、パ。ケン、ケン。
Okay. Hop, hop, jump. Hop, hop, jump. Hop, hop.
おー、これをゲット。おー、怖い！おー！
Oh, catch this. Oh, scary! Oh!
オッケー、あと帰るだけだよ。
Okay, now you just have to come back.
ケン、ケン、パ。ケン、ケン、パ。ケン、ケン、パ。
Hop, hop, jump. Hop, hop, jump. Hop, hop, jump.
イエーイ！First point for Ame.
Yay! First point for Ame.
Great! Okay, Mel, your turn.
うわー、狙うは 10 points! 頑張って。
Whoa, aiming for 10 points! Do your best.
頑張って。うわー！
Good luck. Whoa!
Oh, nice! Eight! Eight points!
よし、いきます！ケン、ケン、パ。
Alright, here I go! Hop, hop, jump.
ケン、ケン、パ。ケン、パ。ん！
Hop, hop, jump. Hop, jump. Hm!
Oh nice, やるじゃん！Jump over it.
Oh nice, not bad! Jump over it.
ん！うぉー、よっ！からの、これを拾って。
Hm! Whoa, yo! And then, pick this up.
Nice, nice. ん、ケン、パ。
Nice, nice. Hm, hop, jump.
ケン、ケン、ゴー！ナイス！よっしゃー！
Hop, hop, go! Nice! All right!
Oh, good job. Good job. Okay, Ame turn number two.
Doo! Whoa, seven points! Seven.
Seven. Okay. ヒ、ケン、ケン、パ。
Seven. Okay. Hi, hop, hop, jump.
ケン、ケン、パ。ケン、ケン、拾って。
Hop, hop, jump. Hop, hop, pick it up.
ん、しょ、よっ。
Hm, sho, yo.
ケン、ケン、パ、ゴー！オッケー、ナイス。
Hop, hop, jump, go! Okay, nice.
Nice. Mel turn number three.
負けられない。ふん、ふん。
Can't lose. Hm, hm.
Bowling. あ、お、お、やったー！
Bowling. Ah, oh, oh, I did it!
Nice. Okay, seven points. Seven. いきまーす。
Nice. Okay, seven points. Seven. Here I go.
ケン、ケン、パ. ケン、ケン。
Hop, hop, jump. Hop, hop.
ん！お、お、お、ベー。
Hm! Oh, oh, oh, bee.
Nice. ケン、パ。ケン、ケン。
Nice. Hop, jump. Hop, hop.
ゴー！ナイス、ゴール！
Go! Nice, goal!
どや！どや！Good job. Good job.
How's that! How's that! Good job. Good job.
Okay, Ame next. Okay, no problem. Gah!
お、お、お、アウトー！
Oh, oh, oh, out!
あれ？お、アウト、アウト、アウト、しーっ、マン。
Huh? Oh, out, out, out, shh, man.
It think it's out. It's like on the line, right on the line. What do you guys think? Chat, you guys said out.
Chat says out. チャットがアウトだって。
Chat says out. Chat says out.
どっちだ？あれ？おや？あ、絶対にアウト。アウト。
Which is it? Huh? Oh? Ah, definitely out. Out.
アウト、アウト、アウト、イエーイ、オッケー。
Out, out, out, yay, okay.
Mel's turn. Number four. 難しいね。
Mel's turn. Number four. It's difficult, isn't it.
You guys are supposed to be on my side, chat, come on. テン、テン、テンポイント。
You guys are supposed to be on my side, chat, come on. Ten, ten, ten points.
ゴー、ゴー！うー、なっ！
Go, go! Woo, na!
オッケー、ナイス、セブン！セブン！
Okay, nice, seven! Seven!
Lucky seven.
ケン、ケン、パ。ケン、ケン。
Hop, hop, jump. Hop, hop.
拾って、ん、ケン、パ。
Pick it up, hm, hop, jump.
ケン、ケン、よっしゃー！
Hop, hop, all right!
Oh, nice! やった！Mel, so cute, so cute. Okay.
Oh, nice! I did it! Mel, so cute, so cute. Okay.
Ame turn number four. おー、きゅう！
Ame turn number four. Oh, nine!
きゅう！お、お、お、え、アウト！？
Nine! Oh, oh, oh, eh, out!?
しーっ！おかしい！
Shh! That's strange!
Maybe I'll get a 10 on the next one. Is anybody keep... chat, are you guys keeping track of the points?
しーっ！これはアウト。
Shh! This is out.
アウト、アウト、アウト。
Out, out, out.
Referee, okay. Mel's turn.
Mel, turn number five.
いきます、頑張って。うー、なー！
Here I go, do your best. Woo, naa!
お、お、お、アウト。
Oh, oh, oh, out.
ふー！
Hoo!
Six.
あ、６ポイント！オッケー！
Ah, six points! Okay!
ファイト！せーの！
Fight! Ready, go!
けんけんぱ、けんけんぱ、けんけん...
Hop-hop-jump, hop-hop-jump, hop-hop...
ゲット！ナイス！
Get! Nice!
けんけんぱ、けんけんぱ、けんけんぱ！
Hop-hop-jump, hop-hop-jump, hop-hop-jump!
あー、ナイス！
Ah, nice!
オッケー、アメラストターン！
Okay, Ame last turn!
Maybe if I blow on the ball, right?
ひょ！
Hyo!
い、い、い、オッケー、オッケー！
In, in, in, okay, okay!
８ポイント！It's in guys. オッケー！
Eight points! It's in, guys. Okay!
けんけんぱ、けんけんぱ、けんけん...
Hop-hop-jump, hop-hop-jump, hop-hop...
待って、あー！うわぁ！
Wait, ah—! Whoa!
あー...アメ！
Ah... Ame!
大丈夫？大丈夫？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
わー、おめでとう！
Wow, congratulations!
I think I lost. I have really bad luck. Hmm.
うわぁ！まさかメル勝っちゃったの？
Whoa! Did Mel actually win?
Victory!
Winner Mel
わ！やった！ウィナー！
Wa! I did it! Winner!
ナイス、天才！天才！
Nice, genius! Genius!
Well, your prize, victory present!
これ勝ったらどうなるんですか？
What happens if I win this?
Ah, here! For you! Tadan!
ほー！わ！自撮りカメラ！自撮りカメラきちゃったぞ！
Hoo! Wa! Selfie camera! The selfie camera is here!
She has control of the selfie camera. Oh.
ふふ、アメリアー！
Hehe, Amelia!
アメ・メル... Mel, do you have pose requests?
Ame-Mel... Mel, do you have pose requests?
Picture request for Ame-Mel. Hey, アメルだよ。
Picture request for Ame-Mel. Hey, it's Ame-Mel.
アメメル！アメメル！ふふ。
Amemel! Amemel! Hehe.
なんかポーズ、ポーズとる？
Should we do a pose, take a pose?
Um, pose... ah, Cat! Cat pose! Cat!
にゃーにゃー、にゃーにゃー！にゃー！
Nya-nya, nya-nya! Nyaa!
わ！なになにこれ？
Wa! What's this?
Cat! キャット耳！
Cat! Cat ears!
ねこ耳！にゃー！
Cat ears! Nyaa!
Nyaa! So cute! She's so cute!
アメはい！My girlfriend!
Ame here! My girlfriend!
アメ・メル... ふふ。
Ame-Mel... Hehe.
Best friend!
じゃあ、アメ、チェンジ！
Then, Ame, change!
Oh, my turn! Whoa, すみません。Nice!
Oh, my turn! Whoa, excuse me. Nice!
Oh, sorry, sorry! Okay, パンチ、パンチ、パンチ！
Oh, sorry, sorry! Okay, punch, punch, punch!
パンチ、パンチ、パンチ！キック、キック！
けんけんぱ、ばかばかばか！
Punch, punch, punch! Kick, kick!
Ken-ken-pa, dummy-dummy-dummy!
Kicking you, okay!
And maybe Mel pose. Hmm.
何とる？
What should we take?
Um... oh, a kiss! Chu!
Whoa, so cute! Maybe chat has a pose?
Do you guys want something from us? Maybe a... 清楚ポーズ？
Do you guys want something from us? Maybe a... Seiso pose?
清楚ポーズ？清楚...清楚ポーズ。
Seiso pose? Seiso... Seiso pose.
Oh! Ee! T-pose! No, no T-pose! 何々？
Oh! Ee! T-pose! No, no T-pose! What, what?
Hey, uh, hold hand. Hmm. 手。
Hey, uh, hold hand. Hmm. Hand.
Oh, okay!
I'm grabbing something else. Hehe.
はい、はい！ラブハート！
Yes, yes! Love heart!
ハート！ハート！
Heart! Heart!
ハート！
Heart!
んー、難しい...難しいね！
Hmm, it's hard... it's hard, isn't it!
Okay, alright! 楽しい！
Okay, alright! Fun!
Ah, we're taking... getting rid of the selfie camera.
ハート！オッケー、we'll try again!
Heart! Okay, we'll try again!
ハート！
Heart!
We tried! ラブラブ！
We tried! Love love!
Alright, uh, Mel, do you know how to floss? フロス！
Alright, uh, Mel, do you know how to floss? Floss!
ナイス！ナイス！Alright!
Nice! Nice! Alright!
Well, ah, ありがとう！Thank you for coming!
Well, ah, thank you! Thank you for coming!
アメリア、呼んでくれてありがとう！Thank you!
Amelia, thank you for inviting me! Thank you!
ありがとう！I'm happy! Me too!
Thank you! I'm happy! Me too!
オッケー！イェーイ！楽しい！
Okay! Yay! Fun!
楽しかった！みんなもありがとう！
It was fun! Thank you to everyone, too!
Ah, thank you everyone! メルちゃん、バイバイ！
Ah, thank you everyone! Mel-chan, bye-bye!
大好き！大好き！Love you, Amelia!
I love you! I love you! Love you, Amelia!
よいしょ!
There we go!
またねみんな、
Bye-bye everyone,
ありがとうございました！
thank you so much!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Mwah!
That chu was for Mel,
That kiss was for Mel,
not for you guys.
Okay, don't get too excited.
We kind of lost her, didn't we?
We got her pretty good.
Ah, that was Mel,
Yozora Mel.
She's so cute.
And she has really good songs.
Go listen to them!
Yeah, thank you.
Alright, we do have some more guests.
Any guesses?
Any guesses maybe?
Maybe it could be some of the people
that were in the chat earlier.
I saw the pre-chat.
Alright, let's say hello
to our guest calling in!
Brrrrr!
Moshi moshi?
Hello?
Hello! Hello!
Opening soda? Oh. Oh.
All right, I think we're out of time.
Answer cork
Nice try, that was a hard one. That was really hard. It was cork.
Oh! Oh, it was just a cork!
Yeah!
Oh, when I said champagne bottle, I see. I see.
Got to up the level. You guys were there, you were so close. So close.
I saw you were nodding, I see.
Yeah, yeah. So... Yeah, yeah.
The chat got it. I'm surprised, actually. Thank you, chat.
That was hard, you did a good job.
Oh, thank you.
All right. Let's go for the next one. Okay.
Imit-Ame!
Oh? Jellyfish!
Yeah, that's it! That was really fast!
Answer jelly fish
Yes! It was jellyfish! That was really fast. You guys are good!
All right, next!
You just really looked like one.
Yeah, I think it's the cape. I like how it looks. Like, uh...
...it's also my tassels.
Oh yeah! Oh! Now you look like a real jellyfish!
Evolve! We're doing this, we figured out it looks kind of weird.
One second, my thingy fell out. Okay.
All right, next one. Let's do the next one. I think I'm ready. Yeah. Okay. Here we go.
Oh? Oh? Oh? Um...
...a shopping cart? No.
She's sweeping. She's sweeping.
A janitor? Yeah! Yeah, it was janitor!
Whoa, are these too easy?
No, you're just really good! Please keep them like this!
Answer janitor
We're on the same brainwave.
Ame sweep! Ame sweep!
All right, we still have a lot more. Okay. All right, ready for the next one?
Yes! Ready, ready.
Ready, gotta get this one. Here we go.
Oh, she's lying down. Oh, she's sitting down.
What? What? She's in something.
Inside a box? No... I think that counts!
It was box! It was box!
Answer box
Oh! Nice!
We're a couple of gamers, huh?
The Gamer Squad. Apex squad. Let's go!
Yay! Apex squad! Let's go! Pew pew pew!
I feel like this next one you guys will get really fast too. Okay.
All right. Imit-Ame!
Bunny? Bunny hopping?
A frog?
Oh, oh! What are they called? What are they called? The things that you hop on?
Boing boing boing boing... pogo stick!
Yeah! Pogo stick! Nice! I like the way you said that, Sana.
Answer pogo stick
Pogo stick! Pogo!
Nice, nice! All right, I think this will be the last one. You guys are too good.
Oh, all right. We're gaming.
You're too good.
Okay, let's see. All right. Imit-Ame!
What? Oh!
Takanashi Kiara!
Waaah!
You guys are too good! Yeah, yeah! Nice, that was it!
Answer takanashi kiara
You guys won!
We won!
Well, I guess you got all but one, but still a really good job.
Yeah, you guys are smart.
Oh my god! You're just really good at moving your body.
Yeah, you're good at expressing yourself.
Oh, really? Oh, that's sweet. Don't tell me that, though. Thank you.
All right, well you guys want a prize, and the prize is a pose each! You guys get to request one.
Yay! A special exclusive privilege!
Yeah! Special privilege!
Woah! Special privilege!
All right, let's start here with Sana.
Okay. Ah... Can I, can I request for a somersault? A flip?
Oh no, no, no, no, no. I can't do a flip.
Okay, um... can I request, uh, what's your favorite number, Ame?
My favorite number? I like the number six or twelve, an even number.
A six? Okay. Uh, six jumping jacks!
Ah! I should have picked two or one! That's a punishment!
Nice pose!
Okay, all right, I'll do it over here. Sorry, I had to hiccup. Okay, I'm ready.
One!
Two!
Three!
What was that?
Like a full circle.
It's so cute.
Yeah, okay.
Jumping, jumping.
I used to do this in the cave.
My stamina is really bad.
Thank you.
It's punishment.
Oh, I forgot to do the screenshot, oh no.
Oh no, oh, you need one more, is that what you're saying?
All right, all right, you got it ready?
Wait, more jumping jacks?
Yeah, yeah, I got this one.
Hyah! Okay, hyah!
Did you really get it that fast?
All right, next pose, Mumei.
Hmm, oh god, I gotta think about it.
How about you do the thinker pose again?
I asked you to do it last year.
Thinker! Oh, that's right.
Yeah, I did this at the Bub-sen birthday.
Yes! Okay, uh.
I think I have to like, kneel. Oh wait, let me move over here a little bit.
Oh, okay.
Deep thought.
Oh, whoa, she looks so cool.
Oh, she is super thinking.
Thinking so hard, that would be perfect. Super deep thinking thinker. Penny for your thoughts, ma'am?
Um, you guys are cute.
That's it, that's all I can think of right now.
I knew it.
All right, next up, Ollie's pose.
What would you like, ma'am?
Well, uh, since Vet asked for jumping jacks...
Can I ask for a, for a 20-second plank?
A plank? Or, okay, not like the one where you have to hold for your abs...
But like the one, the meme one, right?
The me— what does the meme one look like?
It was like the, the— it was popular for a while.
I'm gonna plank here.
Yeah, in random spots.
The more random, the more likes you got.
Oh, I want to see it.
Okay, yeah, yeah, it's just this one.
Wait, 20 seconds?
I'm workin' mentally and physically here.
Now do the worm!
I look like a dead fish.
Has it been 20 seconds yet?
I forgot to count.
We'll just say it was 20 seconds.
Good enough, phew!
Okay, thank you guys for the poses.
Thank you for doing them. Oh yeah.
You guys are such streamers.
All right, I'm so happy that you guys could be here with me.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for inviting! Pleasure. You're so cute.
All right, you're cute! I'll see you guys again soon.
Okay, thank you.
Yeah! All right.
Mata ne, thank you!
Okay, bye bye! Otsukaresama, bye bye!
All right, next up we have...
Um, let me check my bulletin board back there.
Ah, that's right.
It's kind of a bit messy 'cause we had so many guests here...
And we haven't cleaned in a while.
I gotta get my vacuum cleaner.
Yeah, that's right. 3D vacuum cleaner stream.
Where is that vacuum cleaner?
What's all this?
Bubba!
Ah, there's my vacuum cleaner.
Right over there, Bubba.
Yeah, these treats are just incentives...
For Bubba to clean the room.
Just kidding, these are actually all of your guys's Super Chats.
I saw like a bunch of rainbow in the preview, in the pre-chat.
And, uh, yeah, I saw so many gifted memberships too.
Thank you so much.
As you can see, all of these Super Chats go straight into Bubba's belly.
Bubba, wait Bubba, come back.
Bubba.
There he goes!
Hah! Go! So Bubba's eating all of them.
So thank you so much for all the support.
This is a Super Chat.
That one's a Super Chat.
And that one's a Super Chat.
All right, well, now we have some time...
While Bubba cleans up all of these bones...
Now we have some time for pose requests and stuff, yeah, from you guys, from chat.
Because I can see the chat.
And I wanted to know if there's anything that you guys want to see in 3D...
Since I'm only here, it's only possible because you guys made it possible.
Yeah! All of your support over the last few years...
Isn't that weird to say?
Splits? Kabe-don?
Oh, wait, what do you usually say in a Kabe-don?
Oh, you come around here often?
I don't know. Okay, okay.
A cartwheel? Oh, I knew you guys...
Doesn't hurt to ask.
I mean, we have to compare, right?
We have to be able to compare.
Alright, hopefully I don't mess this up.
I didn't do a cartwheel today.
Not even during rehearsal or anything.
I was like, "I'm gonna save it."
Okay.
Wait, I gotta warm up.
Wheee!
Kyah!
Yeah, we did it!
A cartwheel's just a side flip, okay?
Just so you guys know, it's like a sideways flip pretty much.
I think.
Nice, nice.
Okay, okay. Any other requests you guys have for me?
We have some time, so I think we're good.
Sorry, my nose is itchy.
The worm? I already did the worm!
My pants? No!
You guys have seen them enough times already.
Crab? Okay, I can do crab.
Akani.
Crab.
This is kind of like a crab.
A JoJo pose.
I mean, some random pose from some generic thing.
Wait, what do they usually do? Like this?
I don't know what to do with my hands.
T-pose. Okay, okay.
Whoa, T-pose.
Ame helicopter!
Oh, Jack-O pose. Wait, how does that go again?
Is this right? Is it something like this? I don't remember, actually.
Something like that.
A ground pound.
I don't think I can do that on this floor.
I could do like a...
A ground pound squat, kind of.
It seems close enough.
A bridge? Oh, isn't that like where you go back?
I feel like I'm gonna mess up something if I do that.
Oh well.
They said no. No bridge.
Okay, something else?
How about you guys pose? 'Cause I'm sure your gamer posture's messed up.
Posture check!
Gamer stretches, let's go.
Do you guys stretch today?
Do you know how important stretching is for your limbs?
You guys just sit and watch streams all day. You don't stretch.
Your neck's probably like...
Like that.
Okay, check, posture check.
Oh yeah, I discovered this when we were practicing. Look.
Wait.
What did I do?
I look like a bird.
Caw! Caw! Oh, I know you guys are gonna ask.
But this does not come off.
The cape always stays on, okay?
It always stays on.
The coat always stays on.
I look like a lizard. Oh yeah.
Ow, my elbow cracked. Whew.
Feels nice.
Nerfed!
Okay, what else?
Do you guys have any other poses for me? This is your last chance.
Last chance!
A dab. Oh, of course.
How could I forget?
I'll do a really epic one.
Did it work?
Not singing any song in particular.
I can't do a backflip, okay? Don't ask.
Maybe if I was on a trampoline.
I used to be able to do one on a...
We gotta get a trampoline here, staff, okay?
In my office, yes, I need a trampoline.
It has so many hidden features though.
You guys probably don't even know.
Not yet, anyways.
Moonwalk.
I can try.
I actually don't really know how to do it, how to moonwalk properly.
What is... can you guys... what is the Griddy? Can you guys teach me?
I feel like I've seen it, but...
Maybe I just time traveled too much, you know? I don't know it properly.
Wait, no, this is...
This is the sprinkler, like the...
Shopping cart, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Macarena.
Hey, Macarena!
Isn't... don't you do a slap during that? I didn't sing anything.
There was no song there.
Oh, this one.
How do you do this again?
Stupid.
Ah, Idol Step.
Wait, how do you do it again? Oh, I'm an idol.
I can do it.
Skiing dance.
Alright.
Now...
Pose, what'd you do for the last one?
Skanking! If you guys don't know what skanking is...
...it's a specific dance where you go like this.
Alright! That was the last pose, so I've been told.
Alright!
Now it's time for... announcements!
I can't believe how fast the time went.
Alright, let's go! Announcements! Yeah!
Alright! As you guys know, always at the end of these things, there's an announcement.
Hmm... What could it be? I wonder. Hehe.
Uh... could it be something in this room? Like a really cool box?
Or that cool vase over there that doesn't hold anything weird in it?
Or... uh... yeah, I actually don't know.
Why don't we take a look at the image! Yata!
Whoa! Ame hat!
That's right, you too can become a detective!
And actually, this picture makes it look super like a hexagon,
but it doesn't look like that when you wear it, okay?
It's very cool and round, and it looks just like my hat. And it's very cool.
You guys... I want you to see it, so...
...you know, if you want to, you can get one,
and it will be on sale tomorrow during all of Myth's items sales.
Yeah, it looks really, really cool. And it's adjustable in the back.
And also, the ribbon comes off.
So, you know, if you're a cool macho man and you don't want to be a cute anime girl,
you can just... and it comes off.
So much excitement! And I still have something else in store.
Something else, soon! But as I said... so yeah, you can buy it now...
...not now, tomorrow, it'll go on sale.
And I have a—I have one actually, I mean obviously, I have one myself.
But uh... I have one and people have been trying it on,
and they're like, "Oh my god, this is so cute!"
Like IRyS tried it on, and Zeta tried it on, and Ina tried it on, and yeah, it's super cute.
So if you guys are interested, you can buy it. Yeah, it's right here.
You know, this is my model for today. You can get... this could be you.
But you'll look way cooler wearing it, I promise. Okay, not I promise. But... um...
Yeah, we still have... we still have some stuff left, huh?
We still have some time left. A little bit of time.
Alright. Shoo, shoo! Go away.
Oh yeah, I just wanted to thank you guys also.
Make sure to check out our group collab stream tomorrow.
It will be live, and we're all going to be there, all five of Myth.
And we have some cool stuff to show you and it's going to be really, really fun.
I'm actually really looking forward to it because... you know, just being together is really fun in general.
And yeah, I'm really happy. It's super weird that I got to be here in Japan doing this.
You know, where I am. So it's super cool.
I used to just be somebody that would do like... you know, really terrible, bad VR stuff.
Sometimes in public, even at an internet cafe once.
And now I get to do it in front of professional staff.
So it's pretty crazy to think about. And I hope that one day...
...you know, even if you don't have the same experience, that you guys get to experience something just as fulfilling.
Because I feel really happy to be here. Yeah.
I'm not gonna cry. I'm not gonna cry.
But yeah, I'm super happy, so thank you, thank you for making it possible to be here.
And... uh... there is one last thing that I want to show you guys, okay?
And share my happiness with you a little bit too. Okay.
Shall we see what it is? Okay, I'm going now.
What's this surprise? Surprise!
More One Night / Lyrics: emon(Tes) / Composition: emon(Tes) • Hige Driver
終わらない終わらないよ
It's not over, it's not over yet
ポッポッポッポッポ
Po po po po po
目覚めた場所 ここはどこでしょう
The place I woke up, where is this?
これから何が始まるのかな
I wonder what is starting now?
気づけば君との旅支度
Before I knew it, I was preparing for a journey with you
モノクロに輝く らくえん
A paradise shining in monochrome
作りましょう 作りましょう
Let's make it, let's make it
あなたと私の世界をさあ 作りましょう
Come on, let's make a world for you and me
始めましょう 始めましょう
Let's begin, let's begin
何から始めましょう
Where should we begin?
踊りましょう 踊りましょう
Let's dance, let's dance
音に乗って 踊りましょう
Let's dance to the sound
終末旅行が始まるぞ
The end-of-the-world trip is starting
ふたりぼっちの世界は 本日も回っている
The world of just the two of us is spinning today as well
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after too
君の隣にいられるかな？
I wonder if I can be by your side?
おねがい
Please
愚かついた 食べ物おくれ
Give me the food that I foolishly reached for
甘いもろこし 食べたいな
I want to eat sweet corn
ふわり ゆらり のらり くらりと
Floating, swaying, aimlessly and lazily
乗り切るべし さあ 今日もまた
We should get through it, come on, today as well
作りましょ 作りましょ
Let's make it, let's make it
あなたと私の世界を さあ 作りましょ
Let's make a world for just you and me
始めましょ 始めましょ
Let's start, let's start
何から始めましょ
What should we start with?
踊りましょ 踊りましょ
Let's dance, let's dance
ノリノリで踊りましょ
Let's dance with high spirits
週末旅行が 始まるぞ
The weekend trip is beginning!
ふたりぼっちの未来が
Our future of just the two of us
本日の課題である
Is today's challenge
大好きな君といれば
As long as I'm with you, whom I love
不正解だって大正解
Even wrong answers are perfectly correct
ふわり もちもちのほっぺに
Your soft, squishy cheeks
いつだって見とれてたいの
I want to gaze at them forever
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after too
ずっとそれに触れていたいから
Because I want to touch them always
週末旅行が 始まるぞ
The weekend trip is beginning!
Wow!
週末旅行が 始まるぞ
The weekend trip is beginning!
もう一回！
Once more!
週末旅行が 始まるぞ
The weekend trip is beginning!
まだまだ！
Not yet!
週末旅行が 始まるぞ
The weekend trip is beginning!
ふたりぼっちの世界は
The world of just the two of us
本日も回っている
Is spinning today as well
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after too
君の隣にいられるかな？
I wonder if I can be by your side?
おねがい
Please
Thank you for coming to my stream!
Stay tuned everyone!
We'll be releasing our cover soon!
Bye-bye!