(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Okay, we've reached the destination.
Right on time!
Is everyone ready?
You bet.
Let's go!
All right then!
Ready...
Set...
JUMP!
Coming in hot!
We're ready to greet the world,
we're voyaging forward
With courage to run toward a brand new start
Let's go live,
bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully meeting heart to heart.
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future is at our door
Yeah!
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far, but we're
Striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible,
we're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
This is it!
Smashing barriers left and right
That's our Myth!
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
It's endless!
So get together, let's reunite
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways
Discovering highways to everywhere
Step by step, yeah!
Gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation
A dream unfurls
Let's make friends, yeah!
Making a moment of history
Joyfully, follow me
We'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song
Ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now
Setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question we'll break through
Don't relent!
We'll keep aspiring to excel
That's our myth!
It's awe-inspiring, going further
Represent!
So light the fire and let's rebel
The future's brighter, we can tell!
We're ready to...
We're ready to change the world!
Yeah!
Medley, medley, medley, medley!
What are you doing?
Oh, you too! Both of you guys are acting
a little strange right now.
We're doing crazy face!
We have a show to do! You guys have a
show to do! Come on!
Ina, come on, come on! Ganbare!
I know the floor is nice, but...
It is really nice. It's smooth.
Oh, sorry! Minna-san! Minna-san,
thank you for coming to the show today...
...to celebrate Myth's, you guessed it,
5th anniversary! Woo!
In that medley, a nice throwback,
we've made so many songs together.
Yeah, nostalgic, yeah!
Putting it all together like that
is really emotional.
And it's not just our 5th anniversary, it's
also Hololive English as a whole, 5 years!
Yeah! 5 years! Woo!
We also achieved so much in the
last five years, you know?
We had three EN concerts!
My voice cracked. HoloEN...
Let's go!
And we had a lot of friends
joined us over the years.
And in the end, I'm just really happy to be
performing with you guys. It's so much fun.
Yeah! We can't get too emotional just yet
though, because we have a show to do!
Just... Yes!
Anyways, anyways, there's a
hashtag right here, right here.
Yes, yes, important.
Take lots of pictures, screenshots and
post them on social media.
#Myth5Years! Make us trend!
Trending, get it trending! Number one!
If you want. You don't have to
if you don't want.
Just kidding! If you don't do it, we'll be
sad. We'll be angry. We'll get you!
Besides that, everybody! This is
important, I'm just checking.
Making sure you guys are all here legally.
Ta-da! Did you guys all receive a ticket?
Oh, I remember that.
Ah, it's me! That's me!
We look so cool!
Yeah, so cool!
Yeah, I think I gave you mine at the
bar. It was kind of spicy, remember?
Oh!
I accosted you on the street, if you
remember correctly. Oh! That's what you're up to.
Yeah... I might have trespassed.
What? Oya oya? Why did you do that?
Ina would never do such a thing!
Don't worry about it.
It was just, just, just...
Okay! Well, my...
Ninomae Ina'nis... sorry...
What did you do? You want to share?
Nothing! I did nothing illegal!
Don't tell me, keep your secret. It's
fine. We're used to it. It's been 5 years.
Now that we know that everybody's here with
their tickets and they're allowed to be here...
...we'll be singing a lot on this stage today
in different combinations and different songs.
But speaking of the stage... Oh yeah!
Look at this stage! Look at this smooth floor!
Okay! Beautiful stage! Gorgeous!
Oshare! Fancy! How much does that cost?
Couch, can I lie on it?
Get your priorities straight!
Look at the chandelier!
Can I swing from the chandelier?
I really like that one!
Oh, what is that?
Are you feeling that?
Is that a heart?
What's the heart for?
Looks expensive.
Ooh, fancy.
Did it just change color?
It just gained some color!
Ah, why I wonder?
Could it be that it's reacting to
everybody's reactions in the chat
and their feelings? It's changing color
according to that!
Are you guys getting excited?!
So you guys have an important job to do now, right?
Yeah, just that they're always doing something.
You guys are always doing something.
It must be that.
It's their power and their energy!
It's flowing through us!
Well, I look forward to seeing how it develops
from here out. So, you know what you're gonna do, right?
You're gonna get out your keyboards and type some things!
Give us your energy!
Give it to us!
Yeah, not like we're trying to shake you down or anything.
I feel it. I'm shaking them down!
Okay, all right, we're choosing violence again today.
Why are you so violent?!
You're just in a violent mood!
It should be wholesome!
And dainty! I'm just really happy to be here.
Five years later, she's done!
Oh no, they know the real me now!
Sorry, I'm sorry!
Why am I always the one that makes it toxic?
It's all deep in our souls. I apologize!
Yeah, because there's not a lot of time for yapping.
We're going to dance and sing our hearts out!
And oh man, we've been doing a lot of that lately.
I think everyone in Myth deserves a trophy.
A little reward! For a reward! Or a treat!
Cookies?
Cookies! Cookies are good too.
Cookies sound good too.
Maybe a cookie-shaped trophy or a trophy made out of a cookie?
Or a trophy-shaped cookie.
Yes! Yes, please!
You hear that, management?
You better be having some rewards for us!
They're so demanding! Yeah, well, that's fine.
In any case, I know how we can kick this off.
Kick it off?
Yeah. So, maybe it's like a little cheesy, but...
I thought maybe we could jump in the air and go 'Whee!'
And then the camera goes 'Vroom!' and we fly
into the air and go to the next song.
I get it, I get it!
Done it before.
Okay, then let's do it!
No punching, no violent thoughts, Ina.
Don't punch the camera, I know what you're thinking!
Just one upper-cut?
Not one! Zero!
Okay, let's do it!
On my count!
Ready? Next song start!
Three, two, one, jump!
ビビデバ / ツミキ
Bibideba / Tsumiki
つまらないデイズ もう散々ね
To hell with these lame days, I'm already done with them
奇蹟願っているだけの人生
Life's just wishing for a miracle
Watch me do-do-do-do-do
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
It's a magic act with no tricks involved
I wanna be free だってまだふりだし
I wanna be free, 'cause it's still back at the start
The party ain't started
Heyタクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey taxi, take me a bit into outer space
夜を見せちゃって
Show me the night
音を立てて
Make some noise
夜を席巻
Sweep through the night
守って
Protect it
人生は
Life, in an instant,
一瞬にして
has melted away
溶ける魔法
Like melting magic
恐れなど なれば
If there's fear,
駆け抜けて 思い通り
Then run through it just as you wish
お邪魔な場所 飛び乗って driving
Jump onto that annoying place and start driving
私は大大変身 make up
I'll undergo a big transformation, make up
わがままの間に間に
Amidst my selfishness
煌めきに注意注意
Beware of the sparkle
Shut up & match the dancing
サヨナラ Goodbye let's don't cry
Sayonara, goodbye, let's not cry
Here we go 喝采喰らって お出迎え
Here we go, receive the applause and be welcomed
御馳走あれ
Enjoy the feast
ビビデバ ビビデバ
Bibideba, Bibideba
ビビデバ ビビデバ Yeah
Bibideba, Bibideba, yeah!
仕方がない しょうがない クラス
Can't help it, let's just dance
ドアを閉めて Tonight
Close the door tonight
ビビデバ ビビデバ
Bibideba, Bibideba
ビビデバ ビビデバ Yeah
Bibideba, Bibideba, yeah!
こんなに明日を願うなら
If I wish for tomorrow this much
宙を飛んで当然でしょう
Then it's natural to fly through the air
DANCE バリバリ どんな問題も快刀一発
DANCE! Vigorously! Resolving any problem in one stroke
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す本当の私の理想
Loving the blank page, the correct answer, and the mistake—my true ideal
あんなんだか世界は限界の気配がして
Somehow, the world feels like it's at its limit
うたた寝なんてご法度
And napping is strictly forbidden
心配はいりません Jumpin' jumpin' out
No need to worry, jumpin' jumpin' out
チキチキバンバン チキバンバン 頂点頂点
Chiki-chiki-ban-ban, peak, peak!
完敗も乾杯も 日々 ギリギリバタバタ
Whether total defeat or a toast, every day is hectic
地味派手に今を発散してしまおうか
Shall we release the present in a plain yet flashy way?
まだまだ響いた匠に脱した
Still echoing, escaped the master
誘発じゃ物足りないわ
Just triggering isn't enough
遂に導き出した君にアンサー
Finally found the answer for you
灰になるまで踊ってよ
Keep dancing until you turn to ash!
ビビデバ ビビデバ
Bibideba, Bibideba
ビビデバ ビビデバ Yeah
Bibideba, Bibideba, yeah!
仕方がない しょうがない クラス
Can't help it, let's just dance
ドアを閉めて Tonight
Close the door tonight
ビビデバ ビビデバ
Bibideba, Bibideba
ビビデバ ビビデバ Yeah
Bibideba, Bibideba, yeah!
お邪魔な場所 飛び乗って driving
Jump onto that annoying place and start driving
私は大大変身 make up
I'll undergo a big transformation, make up
わがままの間に間に
Amidst my selfishness
煌めきに注意注意
Beware of the sparkle
Shut up & match the dancing
サヨナラ Goodbye let's don't cry
Sayonara, goodbye, let's not cry
Here we go 喝采喰らって お出迎え
Here we go, receive the applause and be welcomed
御馳走あれ
Enjoy the feast
ビビデバ ビビデバ
Bibideba, Bibideba
ビビデバ ビビデバ Yeah
Bibideba, Bibideba, yeah!
仕方がない しょうがない クラス
Can't help it, let's just dance
ドアを閉めて Tonight
Close the door tonight
ビビデバ ビビデバ
Bibideba, Bibideba
ビビデバ ビビデバ Yeah
Bibideba, Bibideba, yeah!
こんなに明日を願うなら
If I wish for tomorrow this much
宙を飛んで当然でしょう
Then it's natural to fly through the air
熱狂 feat. Mori Calliope
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion) feat. Mori Calliope
Hurry
Let's get it started
耽溺で結構
Indulgence is fine
Easy peasy, pow
頭の中でこねくり回す
Kneading it in my head
後のペルソナに繋がる
Connected to the persona later
産まれたてのアイディア
Freshly born ideas
多少ムラがあるが疑うこともなく才ある者が群がる
A bit uneven, but the talented flock without a doubt
What about you?
(熱狂) Just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me
(Nekkyo) Just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me
(熱狂) Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
(Nekkyo) Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
(熱狂) Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
(Nekkyo) Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
(熱狂) Can't fight this, uprising outbreak of passion
(Nekkyo) Can't fight this, uprising outbreak of passion
興味本位だけでハマる
Getting hooked just out of curiosity
今夜の事すら有耶無耶
Even tonight's events are left vague
迷わず No hesitation
No hesitation, no hesitation
時間忘れて耽ける An ordinary nightmare
Forgetting time, indulging in an ordinary nightmare
Kick it back, coming up next level
The future's only colored by the cleverest of rebels
放て自在 賭けに正解
Unleash freely, the correct answer to the gamble
狂気乱舞 種が芽吹く
Dancing in madness, the seeds sprout
It's easily misinterpreted shows
乱れず最後浴びる報
Unshaken, receiving the final reward
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Can't fight this, uprising outbreak of passion
Too hot, too loud
I'm burning, unrefined
Find out, that flood of noise is only in our minds
Right now, it's time
No doubt, we're moving on
I'm drawing my ideal world outside their lines
燃えたぎる瞬間
The moment it seethes with fire
掻き消すようなエモーション
An emotion that drowns everything out
Breaking all expectations
忘れ去って化ける On and on and on...
Forgetting everything and transforming, on and on...
拝する眼差し
The worshipping gaze
罪過の眼差し
The gaze of sin
戦う情熱
The passion to fight
Never hitting the brakes to prove I got what it takes
To manifest a realm you never discern as real or fake, so come on!
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Can't hide, it's a new generation creation
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Can't fight this, uprising outbreak of passion
人様に誇れずとも
Even if I can't be proud of it to others
自分の背中押せるような夢があればそれでいい
If I have a dream that pushes me forward, that's enough
たられば終わるよりも只管にもがく
Rather than ending with "what ifs", I'll just struggle
止まない雨はないと信じ今に様変わる
Believing that no rain lasts forever, things will change
Words like "Gifted", "Prolific"
You better be specific
Broad strokes, blowing smoke, blink and you're dismissive
These words illicit visions of a future so exquisite
A masterpiece you never seen, await the few committed
知らない事があれば研究
If there's something you don't know, research it
できない事があれば練習
If there's something you can't do, practice it
姿勢は前のめりの熱中
Leaning forward in obsession
成功の真逆には失敗
The opposite of success is failure
一番の近道は自らの地道
The biggest shortcut is your own steady path
You can do it, Psycho! 時は満ちた
You can do it, Psycho! The time has come
It's about time
Stars aligning, all the stars are aligning
I'm already on my way
険しき道の先も行け
Go beyond the steep path
光が差し込むまで 踏み込むまで
Until the light shines through, until you step in
Must find, all this blind risk of mine
Gotta go with my own way
決意は鮮烈 striking mine
My determination is vivid, striking mine
熱狂
Nekkyo (Outbreak of Passion)
Sepia
誤解すんのよ こんな滑稽な
Don't misunderstand, it's laughable
サッと過ぎ去る毎日(エブリデイ)
How time flashes by every day
Another prisoner of fate no one could fake out
Stay awake now, you know you wanna fire away
Now there's no question where the fault lies
These days I struggle just to empathize
もう戻らないって分かっているんだろう
There's no going back, and you know that
Cast a blessing on my cursed role
And feed this bleeding egotistical soul
Before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
産まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
身の程知らずの嫉妬に塗れた
Dripping in jealousy that's a bit too daring
ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
An ecstasy that's just a little bit lacking
誤解も解けないまま私 人を傷つけて
I hurt somebody without ever opening my eyes
一粒の才すら無いわ
But there's no talent here, it's clear to see
転がり落ちた四五六賽
The rigged dice falls and rolls
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I ever notice your love and affection
Cast a blessing on my cursed heart
Why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか神様 教えてくれますか
Pray tell me, God
言葉少なに 貴方に捧ぐ
I give to you silently
今に消えてしまいそうなこの命を
My life that's about to burn out
嗚呼 愛おしいセピア色した
Ah, and these sepia-toned sights
何より大事なこの景色を
They're most precious of all
もう少し見ていたいよな
I wish I could see them a bit more...
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
If I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The devils on my shoulder never let me be
Obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
Somebody save me my world is caving in
cuz I thought I deserved it all for free yeah yeah
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 愛おしい蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
Should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
ハレハレレ 今踊り踊れ
Hale-hale-le, now dance and dance
恋い焦がれ遊べ 桜って歌え
Play in love and longing, sing like the cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今は鳥を戻せ
Mingle with flowers, now bring back the birds
粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with eccentricity, now dance right here
ひゅるりらっぱっぱ
Hyururirappappa
一寸先はつま先すぎてゆく
Just a step ahead, the toes pass by
よりどりみどり 祭り囃子
A plethora of choices, festival music
あれもこれも 籠を放り込み
Throwing this and that into the basket
欲見にまみれ 生き遂げたい
Covered in greed, I want to live it through
人生より道 回り道
Life is a detour, a long way around
行きたいように 生きらりゃ
If I could just live the way I want
ハレハレレ 今踊り踊れ
Hale-hale-le, now dance and dance
恋い焦がれ遊べ 桜って歌え
Play in love and longing, sing like the cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今は鳥を戻せ
Mingle with flowers, now bring back the birds
粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with eccentricity, now dance right here
ゆるるりらら ゆるりだパッパ
Yurururirara Yururida Pappa
一寸先はつま先は過ぎ去る
Just a step ahead, the toes pass by
酸いも甘いも 祭り囃子
Sour or sweet, festival music
味わい尽くしてしまいましょう
Let's taste it all to the fullest
さあ何から平らげよう
Now, what shall we devour first?
人生気づけば 夜の如し
Life, if you notice, is like the night
命の花を 打ち上げましょう
Let's launch the flowers of life
ハレハレレ 今踊り踊れ
Hale-hale-le, now dance and dance
恋い焦がれ遊べ 桜って歌え
Play in love and longing, sing like the cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今は鳥を戻せ
Mingle with flowers, now bring back the birds
粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with eccentricity, now dance right here
ゆるるりらら ゆるりだパッパ
Yurururirara Yururida Pappa
花よ花よ 誇りなさい
O flower, O flower, be proud
まごうことなく 君のまま
Without a doubt, just as you are
上を向いて ごらんなさい
Please look up
最後の日まで 花であれ
Until the final day, be a flower
ハレハレレ 今踊り踊れ
Hale-hale-le, now dance and dance
恋い焦がれ遊べ 桜って歌え
Play in love and longing, sing like the cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今は鳥を戻せ
Mingle with flowers, now bring back the birds
粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with eccentricity, now dance right here
ハレハレレ 今踊り踊れ
Hale-hale-le, now dance and dance
誰彼も遊べ 桜って歌え
Anyone and everyone play, sing like cherry blossoms
花離れでも 花火上げて
Even if separated from flowers, set off fireworks
粋狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Play with eccentricity, now dance right here
ゆるるりらら ゆるりだパッパ
Yurururirara Yururida Pappa
あー
Ah—
caramel ribbon cursetard
Lyrics: meg rock Music: ミト (mito)
Lyrics: meg rock Music: mito
ああしたい？ こうしたい？ どうしたい？
Want this? Want that? What do you want?
まるで死んでるみたい
It's almost like I'm dead
石の上にも残念！
Three years on a stone, such a pity!
でもそんなんじゃ
But that's not enough
エーアイサーキュレーション
AI Circulation
今日やっと始まっちゃうストーリー
The story that finally starts today
一等星の手のひらのようなイモーション
An emotion like the palm of a first-magnitude star
空から飛び出し いい気味だなんて
Jumping out from the sky, thinking 'serves you right'
君は決め顔で せーの
With your signature look, one, two...
永遠の亡骸だった夢に
In the dream that was an eternal corpse
終わりを告げる朝が来た
Morning has come to signal the end
嘘吐きでできたその涙
Those tears made of lies
見つめ 見つめ 見つけた心
Staring, staring, I found a heart
甘く ほろ苦い キャラメルのように
Sweet and bittersweet, just like caramel
絡まるリボンは 呪いの鎧だけど
The tangled ribbon is an armor of curses, but...
この気持ちはそう この気持ちにしか
This feeling is, yes, only to this feeling...
きっと分かんないから
Surely it can't be understood
君と手と手つないで
Hand in hand with you
ひとつひとつ叶えてゆこう
Let's make them come true one by one
僕らの物語は
Our story
今日も続く 約束
Continues today, it's a promise
彩りどりの 真っ黒な歴史
Colorful, pitch-black history
愛おしい 僕らの歴史
Our precious history
誰も知らない 真っ白なページ
A pure white page that no one knows
更新してゆく
We keep updating
離したくない ほころびは
The flaws I don't want to let go of
離したくない 喜びで
With the joy I don't want to let go of
継ぎ接ぎだらけの この心
This heart full of patches
噤み 紡ぎ つないだところ
Hushed, spun, and connected
憧れ 恋い焦がれ 自己愛 全部 全部 全部 全部！
Adoration, yearning, self-love, all, all, all, all!
プリンみたいに ひっくり返して キャラメル キャラメル マイオフェイバリット
Flip it over like a pudding, caramel, caramel, my favorite
奪いたい ここにいた 切り離したままで 僕をパズルのピース
I want to steal, I was here, separated as a puzzle piece
でもそんなんじゃ嫌だ
But I don't want it like that!
でもそんなんじゃだめ 僕ら決め顔で せーの
But that's no good, with our signature look, one, two...
次の切り札は 自分で選ぶの
The next trump card, I'll choose it myself
運命の赤い リボンを手繰り寄せて
Pulling in the red ribbon of fate
この気持ちはそう この気持ちにしか
This feeling is, yes, only to this feeling...
きっと分かんないから
Surely it can't be understood
君と手と手つないで
Hand in hand with you
ひとつひとつ叶えてゆこう
Let's make them come true one by one
僕らの物語は
Our story
今日も続く 約束
Continues today, it's a promise
君と手と手つないで
Hand in hand with you
ひとつひとつ叶えてゆこう
Let's make them come true one by one
僕らの物語は
Our story
今日も続く 約束
Continues today, it's a promise
彩りどりの 真っ黒な歴史
Colorful, pitch-black history
愛おしい 僕らの歴史
Our precious history
残さず食べて 全部糧にして
Eat it all up, make it all your nourishment
更新してゆく
We keep updating
Yay!
What... what are we doing?
Welcome back, Calli!
Oh, hi! Hey.
You guys look a little tired.
I thought we were posing for the Myth album cover
which is not coming out, by the way.
Misunderstanding, misunderstanding!
Maybe someday, maybe someday...
Did you guys enjoy the song so far?
What did you think?
Yeah!
It was pretty fun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! We did a really cute one, Ina!
Yeah!
Our "caramel ribbon cursetard"!
Yeah, you guys's voices... you guys's?
Your voices fit really well with that.
Oh, thank you!
Yeah, it's a really cute song.
Me and Ina were like,
"What song should we do together?"
and I was like, "Ah, I wonder if Ina would
let me do a Monogatari song?"
So I was like, "Monogatari, please!"
and she's like, "Yes!"
Because you're talking to Takanashi Kiara,
of course I'm gonna say yes!
But we all like Monogatari!
We do, yeah.
I could have done it too, huh?
Sure! Yeah, I would have done it.
We could have had her doing the...
Now I want to see that!
I can do it now! I can do it now!
Ah, we should have done it as three people,
it would have been cute.
But we also got to be cute as can be.
But everybody's solos though!
Yeah!
Well, yeah, except mine...
No, Ina, you were so cute!
You guys know I could rap that fast?
I was actually so surprised!
It's kind of crazy.
Impressive!
Yeah... well, well, well.
I did my best. It was like, enough of this,
like, "Oh, you know, she did it."
And plus the dancing was pretty cool too.
Oh yeah! Gambatta!
Good job!
And Ina too, very impressive!
Oh my goodness, I really challenged myself.
The dancing has leveled up so much!
Yeah!
I can't believe it!
Cute, beautiful!
Demure!
Yeah, that was a lot of fun!
But it was difficult.
Of course, my heart rate shot through the roof.
But we did it!
Of course. And then, me and Ina
did some air guitar!
Yeah! Oh! My original song, 'Sepia'...
it's a very close song to my heart.
And I made the guitar, by the way.
Yeah, yeah, I loved the purple guitar!
Yeah, so cool.
But what's still missing now?
Well, there are a couple songs missing, aren't there?
Yeah, like the Wawa song...
My song, and mine and Calli's combination song...
A lot of music... 'Thunder'!
Why haven't you guys seen 'Thunder'?
I wonder, I wonder, I wonder...
The song for me and Calli was also chosen kind of by...
loosely suggested by me. Thank you for being okay with it.
Nah, it's a nice song, I guess.
I don't want to spoil anything, but it was pretty good.
Yes. And my solo will be...
Epic and hype! So keep watching!
Can you give a hint? Can you give a hint?
I know it's about to happen pretty soon here, but...
No! No hint! Dammit! No! Okay!
All right, all right.
Why? I'm a toddler, why?
Yes, we still have a lot of the show left over,
so don't tune out. There's lots more. Stay with us!
Stay right here! Don't move! Wait!
And continue to watch until the end!
And use the hashtag, don't forget that.
Are we ready to move on?
Move on! Okay, what should we do?
No, what should we do? We should play with the camera.
What do you want to do, Ina? What do you want to do the most?
I know exactly what to do.
What you gonna do? Not something violent, right?
Hehe.
Okay, she's gonna do something violent.
Hyah!
Dear God,
I've come to repent my sins.
Let your blood wash me clean, for I'm...
I'm, I'm...
I'm a rotten girl!
I swore I'd never sin again (Amen),
but my patience's running thin.
The temptation's flowing through my veins,
I'm bound and tied by the shackles of shame.
I promise I'd indulge no more,
but my heart, I can't ignore.
In my dreams they're turning off the beam,
I'm a dirty, rotten girl!
I'm locked underneath the bleachers, just watch.
Look beyond the smoke and mirrors.
Hide-struck, shunned, the nonbeliever,
our reparation would never be complete.
Red hot tension leaves me with whispers.
Snapshot, quiet moans and muffled whimpers.
Come on, can't you feel the fever?
Rising up, rising up to the sky!
And stay they're doing the fear, crushing in my skin.
The Lord's saying, 'Hope, my child, don't give in to sin.'
It's driving me crazy, the urge to forsake the ends...
of some things that are shifting within this wicked bliss.
I swore I'd never sin again,
but my patience's running thin.
Still them calls are breathing down my neck,
I wonder if they're hiding from me,
or they're the fruits before my eyes,
and the taste that's all divine.
My regrets, regretting history,
I'm a staff of a bad girl.
Someone, please tell me what to do,
because, honestly, I just can't stop.
I've been trying so hard and I can't stop.
What was God thinking?
And I, I know I'm supposed to be a good girl, but...
Some hearts just can't control myself.
Every time I see them touching, skin to skin,
my mind goes, my mind goes...
Could it be the light?
I'm pushing you lead us for the light.
With all the broken cycles of our love,
and I'm driven by because somebody saved me.
The urge to forsake the steel, something shifting within this wicked bliss.
The power resting in my hands,
oh my god is set to plan.
In salvation I can live my life
as an ordinary girl.
I can't resist them anymore,
cause I smell so burnt galore.
All the trauma from a couple more
could never be the devil in me.
And I'll be a sinner till I die,
what's the harm if I don't mind.
With the blood that powers me,
I can live a simple life.
チェックワンツー！ チェックワンツー！ Yeah!
Check 1, 2! Check 1, 2! Yeah!
あーあもう無理！文化祭
Ah, I can't take it anymore! The school festival
言葉にダンスに... キャパオーバーです
Words and dances... it's more than I can handle
心配無用のまじない
A charm to ward off worries
きっと報われるその努力
Surely your efforts will be rewarded
笑顔になあれ。
Let's turn it into a smile.
ドキドキしてる
My heart is pounding
ありえないくらい本気だし
Because I'm more serious than ever before
魔法、かかる
The magic takes hold,
今日限りヒーロータイム
it's Hero Time just for today
何とぞね
Please, if you will
Let's go!
baby kiss 照れないで
Baby kiss, don't be shy
気持ち伝えてよ！
Convey your feelings!
（好き！ 好き！）
(I love you! I love you!)
相思相愛 好き！
Mutual love, I love you!
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup runs
髪が乱れても
Even if my hair gets messy
（好き！ 好き！）
(I love you! I love you!)
絶対忘れない 青春の1ページ！
I'll never forget this page of our youth!
あー超気持ちー！文化祭
Ah, this feels great! The school festival
隣で笑ってる君のおかげだ
It's all thanks to you laughing by my side
弱気な私変えてくれた
You changed my timid self
絶対最強のパートナー
Our partnership is the ultimate
マジでありがとう
Seriously, thank you
カクセイしてる
I'm awakening
ファンサの効力マシマシで
Boosting the power of fan service
魔法、強まる
The magic grows stronger,
終わりかけヒーロータイム
Hero Time is coming to an end
延長、ね？
An extension, right?
Let's go!
baby kiss 隠さずに
Baby kiss, don't hide it
気持ち伝えてよ！
Convey your feelings!
好き！ 好き！
I love you! I love you!
相思相愛 好き！
Mutual love, I love you!
おやつ食べたいし
I want to eat snacks
帰宅いいですか？
And can I go home now?
（ダメ！ ダメ！）
(No way! No way!)
ごめん嘘嘘
Sorry, just kidding
こちらこそ帰さない！
I won't let you go home either!
Hi!
TakaMori for five years!
Can you guys keep it going?!
いくよー！
Here we go!
カリちゃんは超可愛い？
Is Cali-chan super cute?
（カリちゃんは超可愛い！）
(Cali-chan is super cute!)
キアラちゃんは超可愛い？
Is Kiara-chan super cute?
（キアラちゃんは超可愛い！）
(Kiara-chan is super cute!)
Big Ups! Everybody!
Danke schön!
Are you ready?
3, 2, 1, Go!
魔法解けちゃうね...
The magic is wearing off...
最後に聞かせてよ
Let me hear it one last time
好き？ 好き？ 好き？
Love? Love? Love?
大きな声で 好き！
With a loud voice, I love you!
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup runs
髪が乱れても
Even if my hair gets messy
（好き！ 好き！）
(I love you! I love you!)
絶対忘れない 青春の1ページ！ Hi!
I'll never forget this page of our youth! Hi!
なーなな なーなな なーなな Yeah!
Na-nana Na-nana Na-nana Yeah!
ダン、ダ、ダン、ダ、ダン...
Dan, da, dan, da, dan...
反吐が出る悪い輩 アンタ等
Disgusting bad crowd, you lot
中じゃ多分もっとも過保護な
Are probably the most overprotected
桑原 桑原 桑原
Kuwabara, Kuwabara, Kuwabara
目にも止まらぬ速さ
With a speed faster than the eye can see
液垂れだんまり逆らう
Dripping, staying silent, defying
押し通す我がまま
Pushing through with selfishness
どこどこ誰だあ邪魔だ
Where, where, who's that? You're in the way
笑わぬもう一人の貴方
The other you who doesn't laugh
さあどっちか どっちか 今更
Now, which one, which one, at this late hour
ハイレタ ハイレタ ハイレタ
I got in, I got in, I got in
此処と其処に何だか
Somehow between here and there
4時44分回ったら
Once it passes 4:44
凡借四水四分様が 構わんちゃばんがら
Lord Bonshaku Shisui Shibun don't mind the noise
家部壊したんなら
If you broke the gate
文字通りお疲れ様や
Literally, thanks for your hard work
ハイレタ ハイレタ...
I got in, I got in...
眠り飽きた先で君を待ってた
I was waiting for you at the end of my long slumber
楯手と矛歩が重なり合ったら
When our shield hands and spear feet overlap
瞳が重なったら
When our eyes meet
心体頭 満ちていく何かが
Heart, body, head... something starts to overflow
背中に今 羽が生えたならば
If wings were to sprout on my back right now
暗闇からさらば えい
Farewell to the darkness, hey
飛び出していく彼方 えい
Flying out to the far beyond, hey
心体頭 懐かしい温かさ
Heart, body, head... a nostalgic warmth
足元に今 花が咲いたならば
If flowers were to bloom at my feet right now
暗闇からさらば えい
Farewell to the darkness, hey
飛び出していく彼方 えい
Flying out to the far beyond, hey
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
I'll live again and again, inside you and you
瞼の裏 闇耳の中
Behind your eyelids, in the dark, inside your ears
胸の奥に居着いてるメロディ
A melody that has settled deep in your chest
リズムに
To the rhythm
嬌声変わらど真ん中
The voice doesn't change, right in the center
積み上げていく塔婆
Stacking up the stupas
鬼とチャンバラ ザ・リリカル・チェンソー・マサカー
Sword fighting with ogres, lyrical chainsaw massacre
荒らぬ大海原 鼻歌すぎしらら
The rough open sea, humming along
祓いたいのなら末代までの札束
If you want to purify, bring a stack of bills for generations
誰かが開けたパンドラ あとは何があっても知らんがら
Someone opened Pandora's box, I don't care what happens next
何百年待ったか 超久しぶりのシャバだ
How many hundreds of years have I waited? It's been a long time
ガキや若葉 まだ此処来んじゃねえぞ
Brats and sprouts, don't you come here yet
莫迦がいま確かに目が合ったな
You idiot, our eyes definitely just met
こういうことだ しょうがない
That's how it is, it can't be helped
眠り飽きた先で君が待ってた
You were waiting at the end of my long slumber
楯手と矛歩が肩を抱き合ったら
When our shield hands and spear feet embrace
光が射したら
When the light shines through
心体頭 満ちていく何かが
Heart, body, head... something starts to overflow
背中に今 羽が生えたならば
If wings were to sprout on my back right now
暗闇からさらば えい
Farewell to the darkness, hey
飛び出していく彼方 えい
Flying out to the far beyond, hey
心体頭 懐かしい温かさ
Heart, body, head... a nostalgic warmth
足元に今 花が咲いたならば
If flowers were to bloom at my feet right now
暗闇からさらば えい
Farewell to the darkness, hey
飛び出していく彼方 えい
Flying out to the far beyond, hey
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
I'll live again and again, inside you and you
瞼の裏 闇耳の中
Behind your eyelids, in the dark, inside your ears
胸の奥に居着いてるメロディ
A melody that has settled deep in your chest
リズムに
To the rhythm
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the Muses whisper "truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
A wild chase, a frantic pace
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
Ah... la da da da da da da
I'm always spinning fate
Whoa, yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on, their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I spin back 'round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance, a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
Ooh la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoa, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
New song, new song, new song!
Yatta! Yay!
We did it! Yay!
It's our first song as a trio, you guys!
Yes it is! True!
It was over a little fast...
Just, oh, now that I'm thinking about it.
Yeah! It's only like two minutes.
That was a workout. Yeah!
I guess it's because of all the zoomers
like it short nowadays, huh?
Huh? That's what everybody says.
Thank you, thank you.
Not me. Certainly not.
But yeah, unfortunately, this was also
the last song for this live!
Eh? Oh... well, yeah.
Yeah, but...
the music video for our fifth-anniversary song
'Fortune Spinner'...
will premiere on the Holo EN Official YouTube channel
right after this concert!
So make sure you stick around, okay?
Don't miss it!
Don't miss it! Make sure you watch it a lot
and loop it a lot, please!
Yeah! Yeah! Onegaishimasu!
Yeah! Yeah! Please!
Sou desu ne! Sou desu ne!
That's right! That's right!
We still have some celebrating to do, though, right?
That's right! I think it's time, because it's the end,
that we kind of celebrate ourselves here.
Five years!
Are we ready for that?
Yes! Yeah! Yes, we are ready, okay!
Let's do it! Let's do it!
Oh! What is that cake over there that is not mine?
Hey! Oh! Come on! Look how big it is!
Come on, come on! Can we eat? Can we eat?
Look how delicious it looks! Yeah!
Oh, now I can't see!
No, now I can't see... where you're talking about it.
It's almost bigger than Ina! Oh yeah!
Hey, stop, stop! Not now, not now!
Hey! Don't pick off the strawberries!
Hold your horses!
Let's eat it later and celebrate later,
later, later.
And look, the trophies! Yeah!
I know! We can do an award show, right?
That's right! Where did we actually get
those trophies?
Yeah! They were listening! Thank you!
They followed our shopping list accordingly.
Okay, five years, we deserve an award!
Yeah! We had so many meaningful accomplishments,
so let's see what they all are, okay?
Okay! Look at it be!
Yeah! Should I start? I'll take mine.
(Sneeze) All right! Our awarding... God bless you!
Thank you... cha cha cha cha!
(Sneeze) Oh! Bless you! Sorry, I'm not trying
to disrupt your awards ceremony!
So much! What did you get? What did you get?
Hi! My award is...
...let's see... uh... I think it says...
Most Meals Cooked Award! She's cooking in Holo EN!
Let her cook! Let her cook! Let her cook!
Let her keep doing it!
She has been cooking low! She has a lot of meals!
Yeah!
Yes, thank you! I think that's what that's about,
mostly.
It's about, you know, me living a healthy lifestyle
and cooking many meals...
...at home! Yeah! I wish I could cook
for you girls someday.
Someday! I hope you guys enjoyed
my performances today!
I am so proud to like stand here with my genmates
even on this day...
...after so many years!
I will continue to work hard, of course...
...so that I can maybe gather even more awards!
Um... I will put this on my shelf at home...
...where my cats will also probably put
a lot of fur on it...
...or knock it down! No! Oh!
They like to do that! Is it out of real glass?
It's kind of heavy.
You've got to be a little bit careful!
But yeah, thank you guys so much!
I love you guys! It's been an honor so far, so...
...let's do our best together!
Thank you for this award!
Who's the next one? Who's next? Who's next?
Is it Ninomae Ina'nis?
Me? Oh, let's see what my award could be!
Most violent? Yikes! Most violent, definitely!
You do it to yourself!
No, no! All right, my award is...
...oh yes, oh yes, I already guessed!
It is... Most Time Spent on the Floor Award!
Oh, that I believe!
Congratulations! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I know you guys probably think I would
never get this award, but you know...
...I worked so hard this year to stay on the floor!
Very unprecedented! And uh, yeah,
not only did I stay on the floor...
...I, you know, really did my best to practice
dancing and singing this year...
...to perform well with you guys, and I hope
that you guys see that as well!
Thank you so much for all your support!
I'll continue to do my best with these girls!
Yeah! Myth! Myth! Myth!
And last but not least... coming up next!
Oh, what could it be?
Our sneezer! Little Caesar's sneezer!
The most sneezes-sneezer!
Most sneezes in the Myth 5th Anniversary showcase!
Most blessed!
Okay, well, actually, my trophy is for...
...ta-da! Best Worst Luck Award!
Especially in games where there are
microtransactions! Yeah!
That's not so positive! I mean,
I've seen it happen in real time!
But the dedication, the determination to pull
a signed card or not...
...I'm not going to give up yet! Real quick,
I'm going to be very sappy.
Well, okay, go ahead. I really liked that line,
'I'm not going to give up yet.'
I'm not gonna give up yet, because...
Because...
I'd like to think that we're not gonna give up yet,
because there's still so much that I want to do,
the three of us together.
Together!
You know?
And I didn't think that I would be here
five years from the start with you guys.
Same!
Yeah.
I really thought I'd be out of here.
Same!
But now I can't see a future where I'm not here
with you guys, so for now...
Oh, that's so nice! That's so...
Oh shucks!
Okay.
So because of that, I'm not gonna give up yet.
I don't want to give up yet, so let's do our best!
Jingle jingle!
Oh yeah, the wrapping-up music is playing!
I'm just gonna start talking about nothing
because it annoys me when they play the jingle...
...to tell me to stop.
This morning I ate a bagel
and I had cream cheese on it.
It was delicious, but it went over my macros!
And so I'm in big trouble with my trainer,
but it's fine! It's fine!
Anyway, you can't get rid of me!
Alright!
You can't get rid of any of us, hopefully!
Everybody, all good things come to an end,
unfortunately...
...but thank you so much to the Holo EN community
for supporting us continuously for five years!
Thank you to the girls today and all the staff-san
that supported us also for this celebration...
...who gave us the trophies!
Yeah, once again, congratulations to us!
To us! Of five years!
Yay! Thank you!
Thanks everyone! Bye bye!
Bye bye! Peace!
Thanks! Don't forget the merch!
Buy the merch! Merch, please!
The merch is out! Nice!
Next is the merchandise announcement!
We have Hololive English -Myth-
5th Anniversary Celebration merch being released!
Let's look at the details. Check it out!
First up, we've got the Mirror Acrylic Panel.
ミラーアクリルパネル
Mirror Acrylic Panel
It's designed so that the illustrations have a
metallic mirrored vibe. So cool!
I absolutely love this illustration.
Hope you guys do too!
Next up, we have the Collection Cards.
コレクションカード 全3種
Collection Card (3 Types)
These cards feature a shiny metallic finish.
メタリック仕様！
A metallic finish!
And you can choose from three different designs.
Also, the backside is matching for us all.
Make sure to get the one from your oshi for sure!
Next up, we have the Coin Medals.
コインメダル 全3種
Coin Medal (3 Types)
Our shiny 5th anniversary commemorative
coin medals!
There's one design for each member.
裏面共通デザイン
Common design on the back
They come in an antique gold-plated finish
inside the original packaging.
Ooh, so shiny!
Oh man, everything looks so good! But I'm especially
interested in what we have to show you guys next.
Next up, we have the Anniversary Hat!
記念帽子 森カリオペ
Anniversary Hat - Mori Calliope
This one uses a soft, fluffy fabric.
The Death Sensei part is removable!
So you can also rock it without him.
Make sure that you check it out!
It's super stylish, I love the shape so much,
and all of my member Dead Beats voted on it together!
Next up we have mine, the Anniversary Hat
from Takanashi Kiara!
Looks like this! Decorative parts are removable,
and it can be worn reversibly!
Inside out, so you'll have a different color,
and it's a bucket hat style design.
Which we didn't have before for me.
Very fashionable, I must say!
Last but not least, we have my hat,
the Anniversary Hat Ninomae Ina'nis!
The ribbon part is removable, and the patches
are super cute too. 記念帽子 一伊那尓栖
are super cute too. Anniversary Hat Ninomae Ina'nis
You can wear it to become Takodachi. Yes!
And yeah, you can mix and match with or without
the ribbon for different looks.
So everyone, be sure to check our merch out!
And that concludes our 5th year anniversary stream!
Out to Myth!