(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Don't, don't know me
unpredictable-dictable
Takin' you all below
takin' you all be-
Don't, don't know me
irresistible-sistible
Takin' you all below
b-b-below we go.
They think they want it? (Huh)
They want it, get, down
We take them down, down, down
Wind them in the borderline
One and no surprise
You ain't gonna win but you can try
Told you you're a no-go
End up in my line
Listen, listen
Run and hide and scream out
I already locked you up
Keep you always fine
Tell me your heart won't hear anything
Aiming my sight right on your heart
Throwing the keys out just tonight
Just love it, the forbidden
You'll never be forgiven
No one to just forget, we got them
Behind our eyes
The borderline
Standing on the edge
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Difficult, you...
got nowhere to go
Show you something real,
my level know you'll never know,
As above so below,
you should know
We got it, hey
Run in the line,
oh my dear
What's wrong, what's right
Resting in a fantasy,
one to be deceased
Sure that you won't ever make it out
I'll follow now
Just do it, do it
Gonna lock you now, now, now
Get down!
Sing your guilty heart
We’re not gonna stop, it’s just us, just us
Get down, get down, da-da-da-da
Look it like that, run it like that
Get down, get down-down-down
Pick me up-up-up, let's go
Going up, up to below
Told you already know
Don't stop, they know it
Run in the light, oh my dio
What’s wrong, what’s right with you?
Run in the night, oh my dio
Come take a bite, never ending and we start
Love it the forbidden
You're never forgiven
Not one to just forget
We rise, oh yeah we rise, oh yes!
Standin' on the edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical, you
Got nowhere to go
Show you somethin' Real, my level no you'll never know, as above so
Below you should know
Just a little unpredictable, beautiful, just the start
Look at us, look at us
Baby go next level almost criminal, as above so
It goes below
Yay!
Hello everyone!
At last we are in 3D and we’ve gotten to perform Above Below!
Above Below!
Did you like our performance? It was awesome!
If you really liked the shot of it, remember we have a hashtag #Justice3D!
Post it on social media and we’d love to see that!
Huzzah!
Now that we’re finally in 3D guys...
Do you want to do an introduction? But full energy with a pose!
Full poses? We have some full poses!
All right, okay! Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue.
Also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, leader of Justice.
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame. Lovely to see you, to see you...
Lovely!
That was so cool!
It's Gigi Murin from Hololive Justice!
Fist her!
On the official Hololive English channel!
It really is!
Hi everyone, it's me, Ancient Automaton from Hololive English Justice, Cecilia...
Immergreen!
In 3D! And then of course we have our...
Ciao everyone! This is Raora Panthera from Hololive English Justice!
Big cat means big trouble!
Yay!
And everyone, take a look at where we are now!
Tada!
Wow! It's our base! It looks so good!
It's mine! I guess I gotta take off my skirt.
What?! Cecilia! Look away! Look away! What is she doing?
Oh my gosh! I can't believe this is happening!
She's naked! Okay.
I'm not naked! These are just very, very normal pants.
I see, understandable. All right, that was wrong, that felt wrong.
Well maybe you shouldn't have done it.
Can we sit though? Yeah, look at this!
HR! HR! Calling HR!
Liz! Liz! What's happening now?
They're fighting again. Ah, as usual.
Stop fighting! Get on your place and shut up!
So guys, what's the plan for today?
How about we get some ice cream?
Ice cream! Liz, ice cream? Well, it is our 3D debut.
So I think it'd be nice to do something fun of course.
Ice cream!
I think we should play a game, maybe a game?
Ooh!
And then whoever wins gets ice cream!
Ice cream!
ATTEEEEEEEENTION!
Great, here comes Deez.
Up and at 'em, maggots!
It's time to get to work!
No slacking off while I, Sergeant Smokey,
am busting my scales off for you!
Hey! Long time no see!
How are you doing? It's been so long!
"Heeeey"?! GET IT TOGETHER!!!
Now line up and stand at attention, peabrains!!
Ah, okay, calm down, Deez.
Let's just do as Smokey says.
It's his first big appearance, so he seems fired up.
Okay, I will do it for you, Liz.
I will do it for you, Liz.
Alright, let's go. Huddle up!
Hey, Smokey!
Enough talking! Do I make myself clear!?
SIR! YES! SIR!
I can't hear you!
Show me your war face!
Headquarters tells me you've been getting sloppy,
so I'm here to set things straight!
Sloppy?
I've got a few brutal challenges lined up
to whip your sorry hides into shape!
Oh! Whoa! What the freak!
Has that always been there?
Let's go look! Let's go look!
Oh the freak! Whoa!
Alright, read the rules!
Here we are. Let's see what it says.
Think Fast, Move Faster!
This is a training exercise for brain and body.
Use the giant keyboard to input the answer.
The trial consists of 10 questions per person.
If you're stuck, you can skip it for later.
Correct answers with more letters get more points.
Per my last email...
Let's see who can rack up the most points!
No whining!
Cecilia, you go first! Get in there!
Okay, I'll go first.
It's okay, get out of my way! Get out of my way!
Watch this guys, don't worry, I got this.
Are you really ready? How ready are you?
Where do I gotta... I gotta write this email!
Alright, let's get started. You've only got 90s.
Okay, okay, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready!
Three! Two! One! Go!
What is Gigi's last name?
M-U-R... I-N.
Murin!
One of Raora's goals is to publish an ○○○ BOOK!
Skip!
Elizabeth is from Great ○○○○○○○!
E-X-A-R-D-I-A. Enter.
Exardia!
Who wrote the play "Romeo and Juliet"?
You can do it! What's his first name?
W-I-L-L-I-A-M... SHAKESPEARE.
Almost there! You're almost there!
Cecilia, you got this! S-P-E-A-R-E!
William Shakespeare!
How many hearts does a fish typically have?
Enter! One!
Granny Smith and Fuji are types of which fruit?
Whoa! Apple!
A-P-P-L-E. Enter!
Nice, nice, nice try!
That's the only exercise I'm gonna do today.
How many points did I get?
Let me calculate it! Do it quick!
Nine points!
Wow, that's a pretty good score! For start on!
Not to end on! A good start!
Next challenger, MOVE IT!!
I guess I'll tap in now.
Come on, let her show you who's the boss!
I'll tap in.
All right. I, the leader of Justice,
shall go next.
Let's get started! Liz, are you ready?
Yes, count me in!
Three!
Two!
One, go!
One of Raora's nicknames is BIG OOO!
You know, you know, you know!
C-A-T! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Enter!
Finally someone who knows my question.
Cecilia likes to drink OOO!
T-E-A!
She likes to drink coffee!
No, coffee!
Gigi's fans are called OOO!
Where is the... G-R-E...
That's a long...
Oh, that's a long word.
L-I-N-G-S! Enter!
A trick question! It's Gremurins!
That's the full name.
OOO OOO painted the Mona Lisa!
Next, next!
What do you call a group of lions?
P-R-I-D-E! Enter!
Go, go, go!
Which country is famous for inventing pizza?
I-T-A-L-Y! Enter!
I think it's the Roman Empire!
What is the fear of confined spaces called?
I don't think I have enough time anyway!
What's my score? What's my score, girls?
I think your score is being calculated.
In my brain of brain...
I'm gonna carry the one... it was four!
Four points?
What the freaking... ah!
No, it's because they tricked you with Gremurins.
Cat girl! Let me see your typing paws!
You got this, Raora! You got it!
Let's get started! Okay!
Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
What color is the flame on Elizabeth's chest?
B-L-U-E! Enter!
Yay!
What is the name of Gigi's mascot?
P-O-P-O! Enter!
What is Cecilia's last name?
I-M-M-E-R-G-R-E-E-N! Enter!
OOO OOO is known as the 'father of modern observational astronomy'.
Skip, skip! Too many words!
How many legs do insects have?
Skip!
What kind of reptile is a Komodo dragon?
Skip, skip! I don't know!
What is the name of the layer of gases surrounding the Earth?
Skip, skip, skip!
They're too long! She doesn't want to spell them!
What is the highest female vocal range called?
S-O-P-R-A-N-O! Enter!
Good job, Raora! I'm sorry!
Gigi, score!
Calculating, calculating...
Ten right? Is it ten right? Twenty? Twenty?
It was four.
Why are you sad?
Why are you sad? You tied with me!
Why are you so silent? I got a really good score!
Don't you think Liz did really well?
I think there is a miscalculation here...
I guess it is me! Okay!
What if they ask really hard questions? I'm scared!
You should be scared! I'm scared of hard questions.
Okay, are you ready Gigi?
I'm ready!
Let's get started!
Three!
Two!
One!
Start!
Which flower best represents Elizabeth?
Skip!
Cecilia's signature greeting is 'Spin to OOO!'
Oh, no! It's got it!
W!
I!
N! Enter!
A. WIN
What is the name of Raora's mascot?
C! H!
A!
T-T!
I!
N!
O! Enter!
A. CHATTINO / CHATTINI
Isaac Newton... famous for the law of gravity!
I!
S! A!
A! C!
N! E!
W! T!
O!
N! Enter!
A. ISAAC NEWTON
This feels way shorter than William Shakespeare!
King of fruits!
Skip! Only one point! Skip! Only one point!
What the—
You got this! Big one! Big one!
I don't care! Skip, I don't care!
Skip, I don't care! Skip, I don't care!
Think about it!
Oxygen!
I think it's gas!
O-X-Y!
You got this, Gigi!
X!
Y! G!
E!
N! Enter!
A. OXYGEN
Isaac Newton vs William Shakespeare,
and they gave the same amount of points?
That's not... I think that's unfair!
Yeah, I think it's unfair to play a game
where we need to read!
Well anyways, you want to know the winner?
You want to know your score?
What's my score?
Want to know, Gigi?
What is it?
It's 10 points!
Good job, Gigi! This is why you
are a member of Justice!
Hmph... Looks like you maggots still
need some serious training...
Now Loading...
Alright, time for the second trial, you knuckleheads.
I got some special training gear for you!
What's this? I was just chilling...
Ooh! Don't hit me! Abuse!
What is that? Ah, yes,
we are going to have a duel!
Gigi! Rules!!
Rule 1: Split into 2 groups!
Rule 2: After 5 dizzying spins with the blindfold on,
it's time for an epic sword battle!
And we have to spin five times!
Spin to win! Oh, you're good at this, Sissi!
And after you spin five times, you will face off
against each other in an epic sword battle!
To the death? While being blindfolded?
Rule 3: The remaining teammate can guide
the blindfolded player using only their voice...
...to help them locate the target.
It's like a co-op game!
First, before you pick a team,
the points for each target!
Head: 5 points!
Head, okay, makes sense.
Each arm: 2 points!
Each knee: 2 points each!
Elizabeth! Gigi! Time for you dirtbags
to beat the snot out of each other!
Ah yes! Huzzah! Alright Gigi,
let's put on our blindfold!
Do it! For Justice! Blindfolds, blindfolds!
Okay, you ready?
I'm ready!
Believe in yourself, Gigi!
Believe in yourself, I'm behind you!
I choose you, Gigi-mon!
When do we spin?
You are the queen! You are the leader!
Grab... ready!
Ready? Set? Spin to win!
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five! Okay, that's it!
Go, Gigi! Right in front of you!
A little bit more!
Well, you have to walk like six steps!
I have the power of anime on my side!
Not that way! Wait, wait, wait!
Left, left! Turn to the left! Turn to the left!
Attack, attack! There she is! There she is!
Yeah, you got her! Roll away, roll away!
Go, go, Liz! Go! She's on the ground!
She's on the ground! Get up!
On your left, on your left!
On your left! Okay! Left!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
Okay, let's...
Go, go, go, go!
Almost got it! Almost got it!
Who am I hitting? Who am I hitting?
That's one, that's two!
Doing really well!
Who am I hitting? Ow!
Okay, okay! You did it!
Well well well, looks like you numbnuts
managed to scrape up 15 points in round 1.
15 points! Yeah! 15 points!
We did it! Oh my god, so many!
15, not 50. 15! Yeah!
Alright, alright, gear up for Round 2!
Okay, okay, okay, give us the doubloons!
Usually you guys are cheating.
What? I am not!
Turn around, turn around.
All right, let's put your blindfold on.
Okay, help me please.
Perfect.
Is it on? Yes, it's on!
Can you see anything? What?
Okay, watch this. I'm here.
Okay, I'm ready.
Let me try... hey, hey, hey!
Okay, okay, wait.
Took you buttercups long enough.
Now square up!
All right, they're here. GG, countdown.
I'm going to do a countdown!
Three!
Two!
One!
Spin them around! One...
...and two! Faster, two! Faster!
And three! Faster, faster!
And four! Faster!
And five! Okay, go!
Left, Raora, left!
Left, left, to your left!
She's bent over! She's bent over!
Stop, down on the ground!
Down on the ground! Behind!
Where did she go? GG, where did she go?
Don't follow me!
Raora, straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Go right, straight, straight!
Keep going straight! Get her!
Low, low, low, go low!
Go low, Raora! Go low!
Forward, forward! Wait, stay where you are.
Okay, now, now, now, now!
Get her!
I can't understand what you're saying!
Forward, straight, straight!
Raora, forward, get her!
Oh my god.
That was something.
That was...
Gigi, score!
15 points! Yeah!
I'm dizzy, I'm dizzy, I'm dizzy.
I am... I am scared of the darkness.
It is okay.
You're still my pretty kitty. Meow.
Your third trial is behind that door.
What's the password?
Oh really? I can say it!
Let's say it together!
8-8-0-0-8! Yay!
Open! Whoa!
Fancy stuff. Where are we?
Wow! So cool! How cool!
Yes! So cool!
Let's go everyone, huzzah!
At attention, you dogs!
It's time for your third trial!
Uh oh, what? Blocks? Oh no!
Wait wait wait, wait a second.
No one said anything about a life-threatening challenge!
Life threatening? Oh him...
Flying is okay, don't worry about it.
He's not going to kill us, right?
Raora, rules!
Okay, so number one.
Balance the blocks while stacking them
according to the color order on the instructions.
There are 5 levels...
...and you earn the same number of points
as the level you clear.
But watch out...
...the higher the level, the tougher the challenge.
If you mess up the placement, the bomb explodes...
...it's game over. So yeah, you lose, game over.
Oh...
Alright, who's ready to get SMOKED?
Well, Gigi, do you want to go first? Die?
Yeah, Gigi, you should go.
I will take the first bomb. I will die...
...for Justice! For Justice!
She died for Justice!
You got some tears in your eye. Look at you.
Smokey: You got 10 seconds to survive levels 1 and 2, then 30 seconds for levels 3 through 5.
She's gonna sacrifice herself for us. That's so incredible.
10 seconds. Can you count?
That's... that's nine more than one. She can count!
We can count to ten for you, okay?
Ten times one, guys.
Can you count to ten?
You at home, can you count?
One... two... No, not yet! There's no time!
GG, you ready? I'm ready!
Okay, Gigi, go! Three, two, one, go!
Level 1
Oh, look at... it's blue and yellow and...
Raora thought it was purple.
I am the purple.
Okay, easy, easy.
DEFUSED - Oh, good job!
Gigi! GG!
Level 2
Yellow, green! Go!
Four seconds! No way, it's impossible!
DEFUSED - Oh no...
They're so far away from each other! We always believed in you!
Level 3
Go Gigi, go Gigi! Red!
This one you will have to do like a thingy at the end.
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!
Okay, now pose! That's you!
6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
DEFUSED - Whoo!
Level 4
That's a difficult one. Why did the ghost do that?
You're doing great. This is not shaped correctly.
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
One-one was a race horse. Two-two was one too...
DEFUSED
Level 5
What? What?! Holy moly!
Why did they put this one so far?
Go Gigi, go! 10 seconds!
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
7 x 7 - 7 x 1 x 2 = ?
Whoa! 44... *EXPLOSION*
No! Gigi! She died for Justice!
That was unfair! How do you do math in two seconds?
That's not fair! Quick math! Quick math!
Smokey: Smells like a barbecue in here. You got 10 points!
Ten?! I can't even count that high! Ten!
Smokey: That's enough, chatterboxes! You're up, Raora.
I don't want to become a burnt mess like Gigi.
Wait, what? I'm clean again! Yeah!
I'm ready to defuse the bomb! You got this!
First, Level 1!
Okay, and in three, two, one, go!
Level 1
Light blue! Easy, easy! You got this!
DEFUSED - Ah, good job!
Level 2
Wow, that's a lot of colors! Gosh!
DEFUSED - Yeah! Whoo!
Level 3
Okay, I got this, I got this!
We have a lot of time, don't worry.
Wait, wait, wait!
We have a lot of time! You got this! You got this!
Okay...
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!
Oh look, she has to do a full-on...
Now, what... too many for my leg.
You just do... you do the pose!
You can do whatever pose you want!
What?! What?!
Okay!
Hi!
I tried to make her do those poses. Huh? Huh?
Yay! Was it cute?
Yeah, very cute.
Purple... wait, I'm in the way, I'm in the way.
And we can huddle.
Really good.
No! Wrong color! Wait, that's the wrong color.
Wrong color! Wrong color!
She got this! She got this!
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
Oh, here we go!
How much wood would a wood... how much wood...
would a woodchuck chuck, if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
Yay!
Purple!
Pink!
We don't need... when we're catching criminals.
So many colors. Okay, that's a lot of color.
That's a lot of color! Okay, okay, okay!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Yellow, yellow, black, blue.
You're almost there! Almost finished!
Almost there! Almost... dark blue, dark blue!
Wait, dark blue! Oh-oh, it's fine, it's fine!
35 plus 6 is 41!
Whoa! She got that so quick!
I'm so good at math!
Whoa! Why is her math question so much shorter?!
Big brain! Big brain! Yay! Good job, Raora!
She did it!
Ice cream for everyone!
Pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat.
Raora scored 15 points. Not bad for a blockhead.
15! 15! Good job!
Thanks!
Yatta! Yatta!
Who's ready to get lit up next?
Okay, I'm all fired up, I'm ready!
Ow!
Stop fighting, okay?
Okay, okay! You know what? Shut up!
I have to calm down, please. Okay, thank you.
Three, two, one, go!
Why is it a traffic cone?
Go, Ceci, go! Go, go, go!
Whoa! Wow! That's like a candy.
That's hard to balance. It's hard to balance.
Yay! Let's go!
Okay, popcorn... that's too many.
That's okay! Purple, purple, yellow...
Wait! You got it! Yay! Got it!
Yay! Woo!
Oh, that looks so yummy.
Yeah, this looks like a parfait! Green, yellow, red...
Wait, I can't... I'm colorblind! It's green! Ah! Ah!
You got this, go, Ceci! Bring it!
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!
Oh, what's your pose? Left or the right?
Oh, I'm so relaxed. Namaste.
Ten seconds left! Five...
Now breathe! Hold it! Hold it! Hold it! Calm now.
Breathe in... woo!
Alright! Level 1.
Okay, red... I can do this, I can do this.
Red, pink, red, almost green, yellow...
Black! Yay, yay, yay!
You're bringing over every single color!
The strategy! The strategy! Balance, balance...
Hey, hey, hey! We did it!
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
The big black bug bit the big black bear, but the big black bear bit the big black bug back!
Yay! Woo!
Look at your mouth stuttering! Big...
Go, go, go! Whoa!
Wait, that was really fast! Guys, guys, guys!
Do it! Do it! Guys, guys, guys!
Yeah! White, white, blue...
We win now! Me! Whoa!
It's crumbling down! Okay, okay, okay!
We did it! Oh, that's black, oh my god.
Oh-oh, oh my god, it's so over! Oh no!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
Colors! I'm colorblind! I'm colorblind!
No! Ohhh!
Hehe, ooh...
Whoa! Zombies! Help me! Wait, you can't see me?
Because I love zombies! This is a...
Did you look? Did you look? Look! Open your eyes!
You gotta face your fear! Whoa!
Nice and smokey... 10 points.
I got ten! Woo!
Ten! Can you count? Can you count to ten?
Can you count to ten?
How many fingers am I holding up?
At least four. At least, at least.
Okay, well...
Leader of Justice, we'll take on this challenge! Ha!
Leader of Justice! Okay, ha!
Yes, it's time for Justice!
Show you what I'm made of! Master!
Alright, alright.
Oh, these blocks are quite far away.
Alright, Elizabeth! Bring it on! Bring it on!
Are you ready, Liz? We're gonna count down for you.
I'm always ready!
Alright, Level 1. Yes.
Three, two, one, start!
Oh, that's easy. Come on, come on. You got this.
Okay, she got it, she got it.
Oh, the blue one's so far away.
She got it, she got it, she got it! DEFUSED!
Aha! Level 2!
Uh-oh. Okay, okay. No, no, that one's good.
Far! Oh, the blue! Ah!
That one's there, that one's there! DEFUSED!
Alright! Yes!
Level 3. Oh, that's a pyramid. That pyramid screen.
You got this. I'll tell, tell you...
...and then you sell it. Or she's already got it.
Wait, wait, what? Go!
What's that? What's there? You got this!
What's this? What are we doing? Woah, woah, woah!
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!!
Okay. Now pose... Simon? Oh. Yes.
This pose doesn't seem fair. Any cool pose.
Oh, do your coolest pose. Why did we get yoga...
...and they just get to do whatever they want?
Yoga and they get a photoshoot. DEFUSED!
Level 1. Oh gosh. What is the...?
Got it! Okay, she's got this, she's got this.
Nice big... Got it!
Oh, she's got it. Fast! That's our Queen!
Level 4: Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear. Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair.
Fuzzy Wuzzy wasn't fuzzy, was he? Wuzzy! DEFUSED!
I'm ready. Fuzzy wuzzy, fuzzy wuzzy was a bear.
Fuzzy wuzzy was a bear. I can't remember the rest.
Boots and cats and boots and cats...
Fuzzy wuzzy, was a bear, didn't see him anywhere.
I'm the Queen of Justice and... what rhymes with just?
That's just... you know what rhymes with justice.
Just eyes! Get out of here. Yeah, just eyes!
Level 5. Alright! Okay, okay, okay, okay. Difficult.
This the light one, and then I need the pink one...
...and the blue one. Oh wait, get out of here!
Got it, you got it! I need this one! I need this one!
And I need... Got it, you got it!
No, no, no! Everything's falling apart!
No, it's not falling apart. No, you can do it...
...you can still do it. Did I get it? No! Alright!
I have a star! Yes! BOOM! What the freak?
No! Get out of here, get out of here.
That's fine. I mean, yeah, that's fine. Well, whatever.
It's... I got to Level 5. Kick them, kick them!
Kick them! I didn't want to do math anyway. It's fine.
I didn't want to do math anyway. It's fine, it's fine.
I got some math for you... 10 points!
10 points! Yay! Whoo! Master! Alright!
That was... I think that's pretty good.
Simmer down, buttercups! You still got the final trial!
Quizzes and tests! We don't want to do math anymore!
We just want to relax. I'm getting tired.
Ice cream, ice cream. Let's go.
I want ice cream now, Boss. What the freak? Hey!
Hey! Hey! I'm the only one still burnt up.
Can I go shower real quick before the next game?
Uh... Hello? Oh.
Now Loading...
Taking you up a low, taking you up all be. Haha!
Alright, I'm all showered up.
I don't smell like a burnt cheeky chicken anymore!
Oh, maybe they're hiding. Hehe. Alright...
I know a way to bring 'em out. JUSTICE! Just like that!
JUS-TICE! GET! GET! THAT! JUSTICE!
Wait, you were hiding this whole time? Oh goodness.
Hello, pretty kitty.
It's time for the final trial, twerps!
Cecilia, rules!
Okay! Yes sir!
The final trial is: Hammer of Justice! Whack-a-Gnome!
Whack-a-Gnome! Whack-a-Gnome!
Okay, here are the rules.
Number one: Defeat the evil gnomes... evil!
Striking them with a giant hammer!
Number two: As we've all learned,
not all gnomes are bad.
Some are friendly, some are nice.
Be careful to hit only the bad ones.
Only the bad ones, okay, okay.
Number three: If you smash a bad gnome,
you get three points.
If you hit the good gnomes,
you get minus three points.
Okay, so we're supposed to hit the bad ones.
Right, okay.
I just know... I know we'll be able to tell.
Okay, okay! And then, be careful to aim carefully.
And then, at the end, how many points
can you score...
...in 30 seconds? 30 seconds!
So they come out of the holes
and then you have to hit them,
and then there's good gnomes and bad gnomes.
But I can't tell... good gnomes and bad gnomes.
Are you a bad gnome?
I just... I can't tell.
Here's the bad dude you gotta feed to the worms!
Woah! Sunglasses inside!
Sunglasses when they're bad ones!
And this is the good one. No friendly fire!
Oh, that's the good one! Okay, okay.
Okay, so red hat, no sunglasses: good.
Not a gnome...
That's a good one! Red hat, no sunglasses,
don't hit this one!
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright, put those muscles to work, big cat.
I got this one guys, I got you, I got you!
Oh, there it is!
Oh come on, pretty kitty,
you can't weigh that much!
Gonna escalate this to get you fired up!
Come on! You can do it!
Believe in me who believes in thee!
Let my voice be your strength, pretty kitty!
Use your god eyes!
You got this!
I can do it!
Whack! I got it! Wait, wait, wait!
Whoa! Wait, wait, wait!
Oh, I'm scared!
Ready to roll?
I am ready.
I have the power of justice and cute girls!
I can do it! You got this! I can do it!
All right, it's time to whack a gnome!
Are you ready?
Yes! Yes, I'm ready!
Three! Two! One!
Start!
Whoa! I'm so scared! It's so close to us!
Hit all the gnomes! Kill the gnomes!
Kill the gnomes!
I don't know how to feel about this!
Oh god! What is that?
This is disgusting! Disgusting!
Why is there a cucumber?
What was the cucumber?
Oh jeez! What was that?
That was not a gnome. Ew.
It was a weird green gnome, huh?
Oopsie daisy... I forgot to mention
hitting cucumbers give you 5 points per hit.
What! Oh! She got a million of them!
I feel like you should have said that earlier.
You got so many points then, probably.
Total scores will be tallied at the end of the game.
Which one of you meatheads is next?! Move out!
Who's next? Who's next?
Liz, I think it's your turn now.
Oh, well, okay then!
Let me just... let me just take off my jacket.
All right. Flame off! Let's go!
All right, let me go get the... the hammer over here.
Time to earn your title, "leader"!
All right, are you ready Liz?
I am ready.
Count down! Three! Two! One!
Go!
30 seconds!
There she goes!
That's the leader of Justice there she goes!
She's so fast!
She's so fast! That's a lot of them!
Get the bad ones! Bad ones!
Kill the gnomes! Bad ones!
Oh, the cucumber! Cucumber!
10 seconds, Liz! 10 seconds!
Five! Four! Three! Two! One!
What the freak!
I feel bad about hitting those gnomes,
my grandad has gnomes in his garden.
You did amazing!
Sympathy ain't gonna help you catch Advent!
Gigi! Show no mercy.
Oh my gosh! All right. Gigi, are you ready?
Okay.
Are you ready for this... to whack all the gnomes?
Come over here and get the hammer over here,
I left it over here.
There we go.
She's built for this.
She does this every day.
Oh, I mean it's, you know, not as heavy as Thorne, so...
You can do this Gigi! Go!
Come on Gigi!
All right, just lift with your legs.
Lift with your legs. Yeah, yeah, go Gigi!
With your legs!
Oh my gloves, I'm strong enough for this.
All right Gigi, break a leg,
or break a gnome in this case.
All right, here we go.
Three, two, one...
START!
No, no, Gigi, you're doing it wrong.
Gigi, I don't think that's how it works.
That's the wrong color, Gigi! Just the purple one!
Take out the purple one! Just the purple one!
I want it! I want it! I want it!
Oh well, she got the cucumber.
Oh yeah, maybe that evens out.
Now I know what I must do.
Gigi, what are you doing?
Why are you looking at me like this?
Gigi, no! No, no, no, Gigi! Hey!
Gigi, no! What are you doing? No, no, no!
Someone, help!
Why can't I hit her?
Oh, she's so good!
I should learn that.
That seems like a good dodge move.
Dodge! Dodge! Dodge!
Ew, what's wrong with the cucumber? Gross!
You must teach me that move sometime.
I will do it.
Hey, when it jumps like that, it's cool.
I don't know what happened, I just lost consciousness.
That cucumber was really impressive.
Thanks.
Button those lips! Cecilia! Get in there!
Okay, I'm ready. Avenge me!
Oh wait, I need the hammer.
Let's cheer for Cece, okay?
Okay, here we go! It's time to whack a gnome!
All right! Three, two, one...
GO!
You know what Smokey? You know what you are
doing to us the entire time?
You're trying to make us play games!
But I'm not going to play your game! I'm not going
to be mashing up your gnomes!
Because I do not discriminate! Bring it on!
All of them! I do not discriminate against gnomes!
Oh, she's on a hysteria!
A hysteria!
DIE! YOU DON'T WANT TO DIE?
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE! GO! GO! GO!
Sorry, sorry.
I've had enough! I've had enough Smokey!
You pitting us against each other, but we will
not play your games any longer!
We'll happily play your games, sir!
Yeah, we'll happily play... No, it's just a joke.
So funny, we have humor too, not just strength.
Are you okay?
Goin' AWOL, huh!? 0 points, you slug!
I don't want anymore! You make us work so hard!
I'm sick of this!
Hey, hey, I'm sorry...
Enough of you!
It's okay.
I rock you. It's okay.
Why do you keep pulling us Smokey?
Someone, somehow, can we escalate this?
Wait, we need to stop this! Stop, stop, stop!
He hit me!
I'm sorry Smokey! We'll make sure
that this is not going to happen again!
We're sorry! We're sorry!
Don't show her the high score!
Just tell us Smokey! Come on!
Tell us Smokey! Come on! End this pain.
After four trials, one of you clowns came out on top...
The winner is... Raora Panthera!
You win, cupcake!
Yay! I'm so happy! I'm a pretty kitty!
Good job, good job! Good kitty, good kitty!
Good kitty, good kitty!
You're such a good cat!
Zip it! It's time for our winner to make
her little announcement.
A sweet little announcement!
We'll be performing the new song right now!
Right now? Yay!
Justice, are you ready?
Yay!
It's going to be so nice.
We've been practicing our singing and
dancing really, really hard...
...to perform for everyone today.
So make sure to watch our
very first live performance!
Ready?
Yay!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice,
final warning, you know my rage is limitless.
On the advent of a new genesis,
I'm infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous.
Look into my eyes, I'll seek you out,
I reveal the truthful lies that you just can't hide.
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations,
what do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by a chain, desiring to do it my way,
this hurricane of a devastating force is coming.
Out of the vein, feel my voltage rising,
and igniting fire...
Snuff it out!
Walking the line on the edge of becoming,
what I never thought I'd be better,
this stand is gonna take them all out.
RENEGADE!
Walking the line fell so far into poison,
and I see me anew, gotcha.
Locked and I'm loaded, take them all out.
RENEGADE!
Just a- just a- just like that, I don't care, uh oh,
I'm so deep that I can't quit, never gonna stop,
'cause I don't have a limit.
My moral compass is out of focus,
RENEGADE, I'll make it a little wicked.
The light goes out! (Huh!)
The light goes out! (Ow!)
Make 'em fall down, make 'em, make it last wish,
make 'em, make 'em fall down and then they cry...
RENEGADE! I'll make 'em-
Make 'em fall down, make 'em, make it last wish,
make 'em, make 'em fall down and then they cry...
RENEGADE! I'll make 'em-
Over, over and under, the water is flooding,
never making some of them see the light and find a way,
burning up in the fallout, I'll stand in the ashes,
far from you... Snuff it out!
Walking the line on the edge of becoming,
what I never thought I'd be better,
this stand is gonna take them all out.
RENEGADE!
Walking the line fell so far into poison,
and I see me anew, gotcha.
Locked and I'm loaded, take them all out.
RENEGADE!
Just a- just a- just like that, I don't care, uh oh,
I'm so deep that I can't quit, never gonna stop,
'cause I don't have a limit.
My moral compass is out of focus,
RENEGADE, I'll make it a little wicked.
The light goes out! (Huh!)
The light goes out! (Ow!)
The light goes out! (Yah!)
The light goes out! (Huh!)
The light goes out!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice,
final warning, you know my rage is limitless.
On the advent of a new genesis,
I'm infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous.
The light goes out!
Yay!
Everyone, mina!
Everyone, everyone!
What did you think of our performance? Ha?
Yay! Be sure to stream RENEGADE!
Let's get us to number one!
Yay!
And also guys, be sure to remember,
share your thoughts, screenshots and favorite moments
from today's training and live performance
with the hashtag #Justice3D!
#Justice3D!
Oh! Oh? What?
Now?
I hate these doors!
It's an alarm!
Please! No, no, no! It's an emergency!
I must take a look!
Oh yes, you're right!
You're right, Raora!
All right, everyone come over! Let's take a look!
What is it?
Hmm...
Advent! Advent!
They're dancing...
...and singing!
Oh, they look so cool!
They're so adorable!
No, no, it doesn't look right...
Look look! They're waving at us!
Yay!
Ah! Ah!
Do you think if we go to the stage we can catch them?
Mococo! Mococo!
Huzzah!
Yes! Yes!
All you punks think about is standin' on stage! Go, get out of my face! And make sure you catch Advent!
We'll get... We'll give them a taste of their own medicine, right guys?
Let's go!
Justice! Just like that!
Justice! Good job!
Justice! Justice! Go go go go go!
Get out of here! Go go go go go! Get out of here!
Huzzah!
Huh... where are they?
I've been here for five hours now.
Five whole hours.
Huzzah!
Six hours maybe.
We did it! We're here!
Whoa!
You're so tall!
You're so great!
Look how pretty!
You're so fast!
I probably got here early, I had to take a shower, you know.
A shower? Why though?
Cucumber dots me, eww.
Well, where are they?
They're gone!
I can't find them! They're gone!
Maybe because you guys are too slow.
Justice!
Do you see them?
No.
Aha!
Aha! I see how it is.
Well, you know what...
Silly!
Maybe we should perform the song we all worked so hard practicing.
Oh!
That sounds like a good idea! Right?
Okay!
All right, let's get in positions, everyone!
In positions! Okay, okay!
Hot two three four, let's go!
手を上げて Clap your hands
Raise your hands, Clap your hands
海の向こうまで Clap your hands
All the way across the sea, Clap your hands
届きますように
May we reach you
手を叩こう
Clap your hands
ほら一緒に everybody Clap your hands
Come on everybody, Clap your hands
空の向こうまで
All the way across the sky
Clap your hands
響きますように
May we resonate
手を叩こう
Clap your hands
光射す
Light shines through
僕たちの未来
Our future
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Alright, Justice!
君をカスタマイジング
Customizing you
待っても意味ないタイミング
There's no use waiting
あの魚みたいに swimming swimming
Like that fish, swimming swimming
引き寄せる rising
Drawing you in, rising
まだ見えない Amazing
Still unseen, amazing
その先には何があるの？
What lies beyond that?
まだ早いよ kicking
It's still too early, kicking
追い付くまで shaking
Shaking until I catch up
でも前を向いて thinking thinking
But looking forward, thinking thinking
変えるよ changing
I'll change it, changing
踏み出すのさ stepping
Taking a step forward, stepping
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ
I'll show you I can grab it, sparkling
My dream
叶う海まで slow beat
Until the sea where dreams come true, slow beat
繋ぐから
Because I'll connect them
ずっと君に
Always to you
ずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to keep watching
手を上げて Clap your hands
Raise your hands, Clap your hands
海の向こうまで Clap your hands
All the way across the sea, Clap your hands
届きますように
May we reach you
手を叩こう
Clap your hands
ほら一緒に everybody Clap your hands
Come on everybody, Clap your hands
空の向こうまで Clap your hands
All the way across the sky, Clap your hands
響きますように
May we resonate
手を叩こう
Clap your hands
光射す
Light shines through
僕たちの未来
Our future
今日はいらない Breaky
No need for breakfast today
リセット五分前 Breaking
Five minutes before reset, breaking
何時でもいいでしょう 24時間中
Any time is fine, all 24 hours
君は何を Feeling
What are you feeling?
解き放て Sparkling
Let it loose, sparkling
暗闇に火を灯せ
Light a fire in the darkness
Burn up
光らせて Stage
Let the stage shine
作るから
Because I'll create it
ずっと君に
Always to you
もっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to see more
手を上げて Clap your hands
Raise your hands, Clap your hands
海の向こうまで Clap your hands
All the way across the sea, Clap your hands
届きますように
May we reach you
手を叩こう
Clap your hands
ほら一緒に everybody Clap your hands
Come on everybody, Clap your hands
空の向こうまで Clap your hands
All the way across the sky, Clap your hands
響きますように
May we resonate
手を叩こう
Clap your hands
重なり合う wave
Overlapping waves
世界を揺らせ
Let the world shake
One two three four five six do it!
終わりがあるフリください Sorry
Give me a pretense that there's an end, sorry
I know
でもまだまだ 泳ぎ足りないの
But I still haven't swum enough
Burn give me crazy
Burn まるで lazy
Burn just like lazy
混ざり合う 全て塗り替える
Everything mixing together, I'll repaint it all
Boom!
手を上げて Clap your hands
Raise your hands, Clap your hands
海の向こうまで Clap your hands
All the way across the sea, Clap your hands
届きますように
May we reach you
手を叩こう
Clap your hands
ほら一緒に everybody Clap your hands
Come on everybody, Clap your hands
空の向こうまで Clap your hands
All the way across the sky, Clap your hands
響きますように
May we resonate
…今を泳ぐように
...as if swimming through the now.
チャッタット チャッタット
Clap-clap-tap, clap-clap-tap
光射す 僕たちの未来
Our future where the light shines through
Breaking Dimensions
JUST-ICE, JUST LIKE THAT
JUST-ICE, GET GET THAT
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah, it's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it this far
Always striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll bleed everyday with new intentions
Break conventions
One bright room
This is it
With flashing barriers, lightning, and rock
Stronger than any other, we're sailing high
So get together, let's reunite
Reach out, reach out, the future's bright before our eyes
Been together for what feels like eternity
The times are changing but we're ready for infinity
Yeah, I thought so I better go far, with me combined
So look at the horizon and then look beyond
We'll marvel at the sky and the strength of our bond
Making a vow to the smiling stars
A powerful moment that's all ours
The seasons change but we keep shining
Now everybody sing!
Keep it going!
We're making our way to the next dimension
A million colors in every direction
We'll give every mile our full attention
Breaking tensions
Breaking through!
With endless energy, stronger ties
A perfect harmony, we devise
So clap along with me, time to rise
The future's bright before our eyes
A new dimension of freedom that we found
Yeah, we've made it
We're breaking out of the monologue bound
We are unlimited
We're gonna spring to life and break the chains
Turn up the hype, can't be contained
We're shaking up the status quo
No time to stop, we're good to go
The whole wide world is listening
So everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we've believed in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question, we'll break through!
For we're aspiring to excel
It's awe-inspiring, going well
So light the fire and let's rebel
The future's bright and we can tell!
YEAH! HA HA HA!
Amazing job today!
YEAH!
Congratulations for the first 3D Collab!
Wait, wait! There's more! One more! One more!
JUST-ICE, JUST LIKE THAT!
JUST-ICE, GET GET THAT!
YEAH!
But we're not done yet!
We have not one, but two big announcements!
Announcement! Drumroll please!
Introducing the official Justice 3D Showcase Celebration Merch!
Alright everyone, get into your merch positions!
Merch positions! Right, okay!
First, we have... Sergeant Smokey's design Multi Case!
Sergeant Smokey! Multi Case!
It's a multi case! And if you also want to be Sergeant Smokey and boss us around...
And then this is for you!
A handy item to store your favorite goodies!
On the left side, you can keep button badges and keychains.
The right side fits small acrylic stands or postcards. Yay!
Yay! Whoo!
There's also a hook on the back to attach even more keychains.
And we'd be so happy if you show off our merch at events, please!
Thank you so much! Yay! Yay!
All right, Raora, your turn. Next.
My turn. Hmm...
All right, everyone! Next, next one is...
the large size 3D acrylic stand!
Large size! Whoo! Large size, baby!
Wait, no, Atlas... just Atlas is large size.
I don't remember if after I repeated it...
and I was like, "Wait, large size? Regular size?"
Big cat means big acrylic!
Oh yeah, that's what happened though! Big acrylic!
Large size!
In fact, Justice is coming to life as 3D acrylic stands!
Everyone loves acrylic stands, right? I love them!
Whether you have a room dedicated to acrylic stands or just starting your collection,
you are going to need all of Justice, okay?
Get them all! Yes!
All of them! Whoo!
Next one. Oh, it's me! Ha ha!
Okay! Whoo!
And as we all mentioned during our 3D showcases,
we each have our own merch too. Oh la la!
All right then, I will start!
Ha ha ha!
This right here is the paper knife and acrylic stand!
It's a lovely set inspired by the design of my sword, Thorn!
Yeah! Whoo!
This paper knife can actually be displayed by resting it on the acrylic stand!
It's so cool! You all get your own Thorn!
No, no! Baby Thorn!
Baby Thorn! So cute!
Oh gosh, I can't... I can't! Oh, it's so cool!
Gigi, you go, you go, you go!
Ha ha ha!
And now, a hand-in cushion for Otomo!
Do you remember seeing it?
Sadly, there is no Oji-san to show you how soft and fluffy it is,
but it is very fluffy and it's made from a very squishy material!
You'll never want to stop squeezing it!
I'm going to squeeze it! It's so cute!
And it's a hand! Yay!
Cici! Whoa! Cici!
Check this out!
It's a Tomo pouch and sock set!
Do you want the socks? Monday, Tuesday, every day of the week, seven pairs of socks!
And then you have your little pouch, the little Tomo pouch to put them in. It's so cute!
It's really cute, you can put anything in it, of course, not only socks.
But I really like it. It reminds me of the Otomo pouch I made once.
I like it a lot! Yay! Please get it! Yay!
Okay, Raora!
You could put your toes in your Otomo socks!
Ha ha! It's my turn!
And this is Raora's pencil case and keychain set!
It's me wearing a Tattino costume, and ah, I'd be so happy if you fill it... so cute!
You like it? Yeah!
I'd be so happy if you fill it with stationery and use it at school or in the office,
or really anywhere you want!
And the keychain can be attached to the pencil case,
so you clip it to your bag or anything you like!
Super cute! Yay!
Everything's really cute! I'm super excited to see you guys!
I'm so excited to see all of Justice's merch!
And if you want to know when can we purchase them?
Well, they will all be available to purchase right after this stream!
So make sure to get them ASAP! ASAP!
And that's our merch announcement! Yeah!
That's the first one, and...
And as Cici just mentioned, there is one more announcement!
And you all know Justice will be performing live for the very first time...
at the Hololive English 3rd Concert! Oh my god!
Taking place at the Radio City Music Hall in New York on August 23rd and 24th PDT!
And right after this stream...
we will be redirecting you into the music video, "All For One"!
Justice is also in there, of course!
And maybe you'll see us doing some stuff! Who knows?
We'll be moving and grooving! Maybe!
So make sure to stay tuned! It's going to be very, very soon!
Gosh, all right everyone! Oh gosh!
It's getting a little sad,
but it's almost time to say goodbye.
But before we go, let's each share our thoughts and thank all our fans for their support.
Uh, Gigi, you go first.
Me? Me? Okay!
Grambs, thank you so much for supporting us all this time!
And can you believe it's been a little over a year now?
And so many more years with Justiciates, Justice, and Grambs! Yay!
Gosh, we... Hello!
Thank you so much!
Gosh, Rosarians, give me a mighty huzzah!
We did it! Oh my gosh, thank you so much for joining all of us on our adventure here at Holo!
I can't... I can't believe it! Oh my gosh, we're 3D now!
And we're going to be in a concert, and... oh... everything's happening!
Like all our dreams are coming true, and it's all thanks to you guys!
Thank you so, so much!
Onwards and upwards! Huzzah!
Thank you very much! Thank you so much, everyone!
Thank you Justiciates! Thank you Toto! Thank you everyone!
Thank you Justice, of course!
It's been a lot of fun, we worked very hard, and I'm so excited and happy that you all got to see it finally!
And we're also really excited to be in the EN 3D concert, so yeah!
Thank you from the bottom of our heart for supporting us thus far!
Please keep supporting us for much, much longer! Thank you!
Ciao, Totini! Sora, Tora, Tat!
Thank you so much for supporting Justice for a whole year and many more to come!
This... this has been a dream come true for me, being in 3D, dancing with you guys!
So much fun, so I really, really appreciate it.
Thank you so much from the bottom of my heart.
Big Cat Means Big Justice! With Justice! Way!
Once again, thank you all for watching our very first 3D collab stream today!
Please keep supporting Justice!
Justice! Just like that!
Justice! Get, get, get!
Justice!
Bye-bye everyone!
Make sure to eat-y noms, hydrate, and all that jazz!
All right, bye!