(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
T-T-T-Team Tomodachi
チーム友達、チーム友達
Team Friends, Team Friends
俺たち何？え？(チーム友達)
Who are we? Huh? (Team Friends)
関西関東 西東
Kansai, Kanto, West and East
北南、チーム友達
North and South, Team Friends
チーム友達、チーム友達
Team Friends, Team Friends
チーム、チーム、チーム友達
Team, Team, Team Friends
俺たち何？え？(チーム友達)
Who are we? Huh? (Team Friends)
お好み焼き 食う鶴橋
Eating Okonomiyaki in Tsuruhashi
腹いっぱい 飯は美味い
Stuffed, the food is delicious
一人じゃ寂しいし電話きたり
I'm lonely alone, so I get a phone call
かけ直した後すぐ行く会いに
I'll go see you right after I call you back
T E A M T O M O D A C H I
チーム友達混ざり合い
Team friends mingling
契り交わし飲んでる酒
Sharing a pact, drinking alcohol
契り 契り 契り 契り
Pact, Pact, Pact, Pact
契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう
Let's make a pact, Let's make a pact...
契り 契り 契り 契り
Pact, Pact, Pact, Pact
契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう
Let's make a pact, Let's make a pact...
チーム友達、チーム友達
Team Friends, Team Friends
俺たち何？え？(チーム友達)
Who are we? Huh? (Team Friends)
関西関東 西東
Kansai, Kanto, West and East
北南、チーム友達
North and South, Team Friends
チーム友達、チーム友達
Team Friends, Team Friends
チーム、チーム、チーム友達
Team, Team, Team Friends
俺たち何？え？(チーム友達)
Who are we? Huh? (Team Friends)
チーム友達、チーム友達
Team Friends, Team Friends
You know, come to think of it,
it's been two years since we broke out of the cell, huh?
Yeah, time goes by fast. / Yeah.
We've been through a lot, right?
Huh? What? Hey guys! What's that over there?
EMERGENCY
Attention. Justice. Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Initiating final warning protocol.
Five escapees detected from the cell.
Repeat. Five escapees detected from the cell.
Targets are as follows:
The Demon of Sound: Nerissa Ravencroft
The Jewel of Emotions: Koseki Bijou
The Fluffy One: Fuwawa Abyssguard
The Fuzzy One: Mococo Abyssguard
The Archiver: Shiori Novella
All units, apprehend the Advent members immediately.
Oh my god! Holy... We're in trouble!
It's the B-word! Run!
Oh my god! They're catching us!
Hey! Be careful!
Oh no! They're so close! What are we doing?!
Think, there's got to be a solution for this, right?
Piggyback ride! Come on!
Okay, maybe not that one.
There has to be something though, plan B...
Bwahaha! Struggling already?
What are you doing here?
Finally show your face, huh?
Ask nicely enough, and maybe I'll save your skins.
I'll punch you for a "mlem". Come on, come on!
Um, here, I have a solution.
Oh! Whoa! Don't race us so fast, Pokey!
Hmph! I don't hate that.
If you manage to pass the little trial I've cooked up,
I'll whisk you away to a whole other realm...
One where your pesky pursuers can't reach you!
I mean, I guess that's our only option, huh?
I guess so. Oh well, guess we will do it.
Alright. I've prepared something special. Arise!
Go-Kart Escape (逃走ゴーカート)
Go-Kart Escape
What if you don't have a license?
Why... What's with all the Biboo-themed stuff?
Interesting choice. Why do I like that?
See this course? Time to tackle the
"Go-Kart Escape Challenge"!
Oh my god! Escape! Escaping! Okay!
Yes, that's right. Take it from here, ankle-biter.
Hey! Who are you talking to, huh?
Who you calling ankle-biter? Hey! Settle down.
Actually, all right team, game rules are incoming,
so make sure you better listen, okay?
Wait, what's that? Shiori, Shiori, can you...?
Yeah! Oh, nice!
Wait, Bijou, how do you know the game rules?
It's the glasses. That's how she knows. Yeah!
Rule 1: Survive 2 laps with zombies on your tail!
Zombies? Zombies?! Where? Where?
Remember last year we beat up zombies?
Well, one of them went on a path to revenge...
and now it's gonna run after you.
Oh, okay. Run! Oh no!
Rule 2: Collect items for bonus points,
but watch out for traps that deduct points!
Oh no! Points? What the... points?
Rule 3: Victory is ours if we all get
30 points total! Easy, right?
30 points?! Did you hear that?
30 points! Oh yeah, we can do that.
All right, I will explain the course items...
I must run. You must run? Yeah, she must run.
I'm gonna live out my dreams while
there's a track! Just explain, ignore me!
Okay! So listening! Uh... Oh, she's fast.
Anyway, there are crystals on the field.
It's the Biboo crystal over there. And...
And two more over there! They are gacha.
Oh, you either gain points or lose points...
...but you don't know, so it's a risk every time!
Gacha! Yeah! And then...
...there is the big Moai! The big Moai!
It will block your path. Oh! Whoa! Hi!
It is minus 20 points if you hit it...
...so don't hit it. Or hit it if you want.
Yeah, don't hit it! And then, the Pebble!
Look at the Pebble! I have...
...kidnapped one of my Pebbles...
...to use as a sacrifice. If you hit it...
...minus 5 points. But you know what...
...I don't think they would mind if you hit it.
To be honest. Okay, yeah!
And the items will change depending on...
...your first lap or second lap.
You're doing two laps. Two laps! Okay!
By the way, too many! You can run another laps?
Yeah! Are you okay? Yeah, I'm great!
I guess time to show you how it's done.
Sure, go on, go on! Alright, first lap!
Show us how to do it! I'm ready!
3... 2... 1... GO!
Go! You're so fast! Oh, first lap!
She gets a crystal, she makes a loop!
Second crystal! Watch out, watch out!
She's going so fast! Zombie's speeding up!
Second lap, let's go! Another crystal!
She hit another one! Moai! The zombie!
Go, go, go, go, go! The zombie is speeding up!
The crystal at the end... minus 3 pt. Yeah!
I think you got a bit of bad luck...
...with that crystal at the end.
It's okay, that was a pretty good run.
You went so fast! You almost hit the zombie...
...but you're okay! Yeah, you didn't die!
How many points did I get? How many points?
That's a good question. How many points...
...did you get? I think you got one point.
What? One point? Oh, wasn't that negative?
Did I have bad gacha luck? It's okay.
It's a group effort, we can still get points.
Yeah, I contributed one! One is great!
We'll let the pro do all the work for you, right?
Yeah, yeah! Pro Mococo! Yeah, yeah!
I'm counting on you guys! Okay!
Next up is... Shiori! Show us how it's done!
Our fearless leader! I have a plan.
You have a plan? What's your plan?
You'll figure it out when I say 'Plan'.
Okay, good luck, Shiori! Shiori!
あの、あの、ゾンビら... 先どうぞ？
Um, um, zombies... go ahead?
え？ 何？ はい。 行こうですね、行こうですね。
Eh? What? Yes. Let's go, let's go.
You got this! 3... 2... 1...
Let's go! GO! Let's go! You're so...
Yeah, that's like a... no! Come on, let's go!
Oh! Crystal... minus 1 pt. Touch me! Hit me!
Watch me! Watch me! Watch me! Moai!
No, no, no, no! Yeah, the zombie! Go, go, go!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Look at her go!
She's like driving in New York!
Only taking points! That's okay.
I can figure it out. How many points did she...
Oh! Watch out! Okay, okay, okay!
You can't figure it out... oh! No!
Minus 3 pt. You didn't catch him...
...but you sure gave him a run for his money.
Look at that driving! It's not about the points.
I just wanted to run them over. Understandable.
It's okay, how many points did I get?
Let's see... Three points! Oh, three points!
That's two more points than Bijou!
No, that's pretty good. Better than one!
So we have four! Alright, it's up to Fuwa...
...do you think you can do it?
I'll get four more points! You can do it!
I know you can! Yeah! I'm gonna tell you...
...the zombie is not gonna run away anymore.
I think it's tired. It's up to you!
You gotta outrun it! I'm the best driver! Yeah!
Go, Fuwa, go! 3... 2... 1... GO!
Go! Let's go, Fuwawa! Oh no, you're going slow!
What do you mean? I want to go faster!
This is very safe driving! Yeah, yeah!
You missed the crystal! It's okay...
...the zombie's taking its time too!
It's already start!
Wait, I have to go!
Okay, baby!
Yeah!
Oh, no!
Oh, the zombie!
My crystal!
It's okay, it's okay.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, Fuwawa! Go, Fuwawa!
Oh, no!
I'm so slow this time!
You'll be fine!
Get the crystal, get the crystal!
Watch out, watch out, Mococo! Watch out!
Hey, don't die!
Hey! Fuwawa!
Is it the first lap still?
This is the second one now.
I can do it! I can do it!
A zombie escaped!
Faster, faster, faster!
I can do it! Fuwawa!
She's dead!
Again, again, okay!
Oh, wait! Oh, yeah!
Monster!
I can do it! Okay!
Yeah! Fuwawa!
I guess the speed isn't that important...
...but the points are, right?
Fuwawawa, I think you did really well.
Yeah! So far, you're our top performer today...
...with 18 points!
18! Fuwawa!
Whoa, Fuwawa carry!
Don't worry, we're at 18!
Wait, what was the math?
Wait, 17? 18?
14, 18, 'cause you got 3, I got 1...
So yeah, 14, 18.
No, no, we got 4 more points.
4 more points! Okay!
Next is Mococo!
Count the points, okay? Count on me!
Mococo! Okay, Mococo!
Go, go, go, go! You got this, Mococo!
Yeah, okay!
Ah! Hahaha! Whoo!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is where my story all begins!
Livin' it up like crazy
Ready to play? Come at me
Carried away so easy
I can't get enough
Free as a bird, no limit
Haven't you heard? I'm fearless
Get up and go let's do this
Watch me, watch me, watch me...
be your diva
I'm gonna raise your fever
Shakin' up all the crowd
Makin' some noise when I'm not allowed
Livin' my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep on dancing in my everything
Oh
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
(o-oh o-oh o-oh o-oh)
can't help it if I start a fight
Now pay attention please
cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc
How do you like that plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
w h i s p e r s bangin' down your window
reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings
I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Whoa~
M i d n i g h t, draw me to the dark side
D a y b r e a k, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is:
This is our genesis
Gotta start the riot, boy I misbehave, take center stage
Let the fun commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense
unposed, unspoken, the rules can all be broken
I'm runnin' on a rampage, the world is a blank page
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
They're gonna know me by name! COME ON!
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hands
But they don't understand
that I'm a star in the making, awaking and taking a bow, bow, bow
Tell me how you like me now~
Come and watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control
Ready? You've got to free your mind, leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is:
It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
cause this is our beginning
it's our genesis
w h i s p e r s bangin' down your window
reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings
I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Whoa~
M i d n i g h t, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is:
This is our genesis
You know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
You know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Everybody, look! It's the beach! Yeah! We're everywhere! It's the beach! Yay! We're everywhere!
Whoa, look at this! Look at the sand! It's everywhere! It's amazing! Oh my god! Look at that!
Nerissa: Oh this is nice.
Fuwawa: Yeah, I like it.
Mococo: It feels nice and breathable.
Nerissa: I want to see everyone close up though.
This is our first time wearing something like this, so Bijou, why don't you show off what you've got?
Bijou: Me first? Okay!
Alright, what are you looking at, huh?
What are you looking at?
Fine, you can look a little bit, okay? Okay, here we go.
It's my skirt. You like the skirt?
Mococo: Wow!
Bijou: It's so puffy! See?
Shiori: You're like highlighters!
Nerissa: Wow!
Bijou: KIRA KIRA! I'm gonna blind you!
Oh! Look at my dogs too! Look at them! Watch me!
Fuwawa: Whoa, watch out! Bijou: Shiori, take over!
Shiori: I'm go-go, monster-stare! (Advent laughing)
This is my first bathing suit buy!
This is my first swimsuit purchase!
What do you think?
Shiori, come here!
Shiori on the shore? No...
Shiori on the... at your service!
And look at my little ribbon!
Okay, you can do this, Mococo-chan!
Fuwawa! Fuwawa!
I... this is so big!
Look at those cute shorts!
She's so cute!
But there's something a bit special
on this outfit.
Don't you think? If you go down...
Oh, there it is! There it is!
Oh, I see it! Wow!
Don't look there too much.
But if you come up, you can see my waist...
and my top... armpits!
Oh yes! The pits!
But I see something strange off in the distance.
Just wait, let me go see.
Oh! It's a selfie stick!
Everyone, get behind me!
Let's take a picture together!
Nice!
Why are you so tall?
Oh, that helps!
There's something down there in the sand.
Something down there?
I think that's an adventuress?
Oh! Step on it!
Oh, step on that!
Let's go to the water!
Mococo-chan, don't drown!
I can swim!
Running in slow mo!
Let's just keep running on the beach!
Let me go put this thing down, okay?
My arm's getting tired. Selfie arm tired.
Thank you for being such a tall person.
Oh my gosh, it's Pokey!
Hey now! Save the beach party for later!
Sandcastles later, survival now!
I thought we were supposed to be safe here.
Yeah, what gives? Let's enjoy our time.
This is Justice we're dealing with!
Expect the unexpected!
What should we do next then?
Do we have to run forever?
Don't panic, I have a plan.
Prove your bonds in the next trial.
The power of friendship? Nakama power?
Well, since this is the beach episode,
we have to do it, right?
Good. Something's been arranged.
Look down! A & B!
A & B? Not your alphabet?
That's so lame! / A! B!
C-can it! Silence!
To confirm your bonds,
you'll take on 'Master of Advent'.
Master of Advent
(Adventわかってて)
(Understanding Advent)
The rules are simple! Each participant
will be asked a two-option question.
You guys are Team Tomodachi,
so it should be pretty easy, right...?
Team Tomodachi? Advent forever!
Exactly. But incorrect answers mean...
your bonds are weak.
Penalty? Not again!
I didn't consent to this!
Yeah, a penalty game.
Now, goth girl, take over.
Anyway, I think that we're going to get
one question, two answers.
But only one is right. If you get it wrong,
I think you're going to get muddied.
No! I don't want to get muddied in this thing!
So when you make your answer,
I want you to hop there, okay?
I'll go first as an example.
Number one: Which would Shiori rather be?
A vampire for A, or a werewolf for B?
On the count of three, okay?
Three, two...
One, go!
Why side B?!
I don't want to drink blood!
What am I, stupid?
Whoa, that's unexpected.
Right? I seriously thought you were gonna say vampire.
No, you got that dog in you!
I got the dog in me, yeah!
Okay, okay!
Well, you haven't been going for vampires all time.
Does this mean my... I don't want... I like mine!
No! No!
Go! Go!
Wash yourself!
You too.
I'm watching you.
Well, you got us all wet, Shiori.
Are you happy?
Not yet.
All right, next one.
How about Mococo?
Moco-chan!
My turn!
Okay, well, here I go!
Um, at the beach...
would I rather collect seashells (A)...
...or, um, how was it...
...ah, make sandcastles (B)?
Okay, figure it out!
Ready?
Okay! Jump on three!
Okay! Three, two, one...
...which is it?!
I can't remember!
This was seashells...
...and this was sandcastles.
Shiori is getting dirty!
Huh? Yeah, Shiori!
No, I thought you wanted this one!
I made a mistake!
I'd rather collect seashells...
...but I jumped this way!
So that means this way, this way!
This isn't fair!
Moco-chan go!
Shiori, zip it for now.
Yeah, for now, for now.
Yee-haw!
That is so mean!
Seriously!
It was a game of tag all along!
How about Fuwawa next?
Okay! Get in line!
I don't get to get dirty this time, right?
Okay, my question:
Do I prefer long-haired cats...
...or short-haired cats?
Okay, I'm the fluffy one, BAU BAU!
Here we go! Three, two, one!
No way!
Fuwawa, you prefer short hair?
But you're fluffy!
It's too easy!
This is a trick question!
It's too obvious!
Oh, you're so mean to me!
You're just so unfair!
Okay, Biboo's turn!
Ah, that feels nice.
Yeah.
Well, it's going to be your turn next.
Oh, my turn?
Nerissa, come back!
I don't want to play this game anymore!
It's too chaotic!
Okay! Okay!
Is it Biboo's turn now?
It's Biboo's turn.
Biboo's turn. Okay!
My question is... ooh, okay!
Would I rather fight one hundred...
...chicken-sized hippopotamuses on A...
...or one...
...hippo-sized chicken on B?
Do you understand?
I understand!
Jump back!
Okay... one hundred hippo...
One hundred chicken-sized hippo!
Are you sure now?
One hippo-sized chicken.
I'm not repeating it!
Oh, this is such a good one!
Okay! Ready...
...in three, two, one!
Biboo!
Biboo doesn't like adds.
Biboo likes boss battles!
You should've known!
It's a boss battle!
One!
That was so hot! That was so fun!
Ah... Unfortunately for you...
Oh, Mococo-chan, here she comes! Here she comes! This is gonna be nasty!
We'll see! We'll see!
You only have one chance to ask for mercy!
Don't! Don't spray me!
Get Shiori! Get Shiori!
Ah! No! Don't only spray me!
Don't only spray you? Ah!
Don't look at me like this! Don't look at me! Okay? No!
I'm going to the water!
Goodbye! Goodbye! Bye-bye!
Your turn now.
She became a mermaid.
She's swimming away.
We'll never see her again.
Come back! Come back, Mococo-chan! We need you!
I'm a mermaid now! Bye!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Wait! Wait! My turn!
Last is my turn!
Means I can't get it wrong, which is pretty... feels pretty good.
Ahem. What's a good question? I'm not really sure.
Ahem. Let's see.
Nerissa is a demon, but she's also half raven.
If I had to pick between worlds...
...and either be just a demon or just a raven.
So, demon is B.
Raven is A.
Which would I pick?
All right. Yes. Okay. On three, okay?
One, two, three!
I knew you would never give up laying eggs!
I can't lay eggs!
Mococo, that's not the case! How stinky!
I just think it would be great if I could have powers...
...that aren't dependent on...
...something that can break, you know?
I thought being a demon is cooler though.
It is, but...
We're in this together at least.
You know what's even cooler than being a demon?
Shiori and Mococo...
What?
I dare you! I dare you!
Yeah! I dare you! I dare you!
I've been covered in mud! I dare you!
Yeah! There you go!
Mococo-chan is with you!
Yeah! You want a bath? Want a bath?
I like baths, okay?
Yeah, you like them? Why you like it so much?
Go take one in the ocean!
Go to the ocean if you want! What?
Look at this! Go! Go!
Well, we'll never see them again.
They're getting lost in the water.
I think they're having too much fun.
It's fine. Don't! Don't eat the salt water!
Yeah, don't drink the water!
I'm gonna get rid of this.
That was pretty fun!
We're all in this together, okay?
Hey hey hey hey hey hey!
That didn't go so well, huh?
Look how dirty you are!
But hey, idols don't give up that easy, right?
You are idols, right?
Let's turn this around and shine again!
And if you do...
I'll take you somewhere super special—
where even Justice can't find us!
We are not Justice! Don't tell me!
No way!
That sounds great!
I want Justice to find me at some point.
Well, you can go. Okay, just for now.
Just for now!
どこ? そこ? あそこ? 見つからないぜぃ?
Where? There? Over there? Can't find it, right?
パパイヤ マンゴー ココ☆ナツ!
Papaya, mango, Coco☆Nuts!
カキ氷 イチゴ味 ベロを出したら まっかっか!
Shaved ice, strawberry flavor, if you stick out your tongue, it's bright red!
Ai! 猛暑 残暑 水着SHOW! SAY!
Ai! Intense heat, lingering summer, swimsuit SHOW! SAY!
ジャジャジャジャジャジャジャーン
Ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-jahn
ココ☆ナツ いえい!
Coco☆Nuts, yeah!
カチカチに燃えてるお日さま
The sizzling, burning sun
パシュワ ココ☆ナツ ベイベー
Pashuwa Coco☆Nuts baby
待ちわびた季節はサマーサマー
The season I've been waiting for is summer, summer
パシュワ ココ☆ナツ ベイベー
Pashuwa Coco☆Nuts baby
思い切って 買っちゃった ビキニ
I took the plunge and bought a bikini
すっごーく 照れるけど
I'm super embarrassed, but...
負けんない!!
I won't lose!!
日焼け止め ココナッツ フレイバー
Sunscreen with a coconut flavor
パシュワ ココ☆ナツ ベイベー
Pashuwa Coco☆Nuts baby
紫外線 ドコ夏 レーザー
Ultraviolet Dokonatsu laser
パシュワ ココ☆ナツ ベイベー
Pashuwa Coco☆Nuts baby
どっきゅーん ずっきゅーん
Dokkyun, zukkyun
君の視線
Your gaze
心臓 大爆発☆
Heart, big explosion☆
サシスセ ソコナツ ベイベー
Sa-shi-su-se Soko-Natsu baby
ダディドゥデ ドコナツ ベイベー
Da-di-du-de Doko-Natsu baby
カキクケ ココナツ ベイベー
Ka-ki-ku-ke Coco-Natsu baby
サン! サン! サマータイム! Yeah!
Sun! Sun! Summertime! Yeah!
コココココココココ...
Ko-ko-ko-ko-ko-ko-ko-ko-ko...
ココナツ！
Coconuts!
カキ氷 メロン味
Shaved ice, melon flavor
ベロを出したら
If I stick out my tongue...
ゾンビーだ！
I'm a zombie!
勝負ゆかた着て
Wearing a competition yukata...
盆 DANCE ISAY!
Bon DANCE ISAY!
ジャジャジャジャジャジャジャーン
Ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-jan!
ちょいなー ちょいなー ちょいなー ちょいなー
Choina, choina, choina, choina!
むしむし うんざり ねえ 太陽
Steamy and annoying, hey, sun
明日は ココナツ ベイベー
Tomorrow is Coconuts Baby
ココナツジュースのみたいな
I want to drink coconut juice
明日は ココナツ ベイベー
Tomorrow is Coconuts Baby
長い夜で 短いサマータイム
Long nights and short summer time
やっちゃったもんがち！
The one who does it wins!
サシスセ ソコナツ ベイベー
Sa-shi-su-se Soko-natsu Baby
ダディデュデ ドコナツ ベイベー
Da-di-du-de Doko-natsu Baby
カキクケ ココナツ ベイベー
Ka-ki-ku-ke Coco-natsu Baby
サン！サン！サマータイム！
Sun! Sun! Summer time!
YES!
ファイヤー！
Fire!
スススパーキング！
Su-su-sparking!
リリリリンボー！
R-r-r-r-rainbow!
フィーバー！
Fever!
ソヤ ソヤ ソヤ ソヤ
Soya soya soya soya!
アチアチのサマー
Hot, hot summer
コジュリハマ
Kujukuri-hama
アイス激アマ
Ice, super sweet
キャンプはさいたま
Camping is in Saitama
どこ？ そこ？ あそこ？ 見つからないぜぃ？
Where? There? Over there? Can't find it?
パパイヤ マンゴー ココ☆ナッツ！
Papaya, mango, Coco☆Nuts!
え？ え？ あ！ ここ、私たちの隠れ家？
Huh? Huh? Oh! Are we in our hideout?
やったー！
Yay!
ねえ、ここを3Dでアドベンチャーのみんなに見せるのって初めてじゃない？
Wait, isn't this our first time showing it in 3D to the Adventurers?
そうだね！3D！3D！
Yeah! 3D! 3D!
みんなのお気に入りの場所、見たい？
Do you want to see our favorite part?
うん！
Yeah!
見て見て！キャンドルだよ！
Look! Look! Look at the candles!
わあ、きれい！
Ooh! So pretty!
そう、キャンドルがいっぱい！ロマンチックな雰囲気だよね！
Yeah, all the candles! We have a romantic vibe here!
超きれい！
Super pretty!
私にもお気に入りの場所があるんだよ。
I have a favorite part too, you know.
お、何なに？
Oh, what is it?
あそこを見て...
If you look up there...
あの窓から漏れる光は何だろう...
What light through yonder window breaks...
わあ、今夜は月がきれいだね。
Wow, the moon is beautiful tonight.
月、すごくきれい！
Moon is so beautiful!
月が綺麗ですね...
The moon is beautiful, isn't it?
さて、私のお気に入りの場所は...
Well, about my favorite part...
後ろを見て！
Look behind you!
このコレクション！全部私の...
This collection! It's all of my...
長年集めてきたもの、全部だよ！
Everything that we've collected over the years and stuff!
だよね、だよね。
Right, right, you know.
それから、彼女の...！
And her...!
そう！それも！
Yeah! And that!
あと...このソファ！すごく大きいね！
What also... your couch! It's so big!
大きい！巨大だよ！
It's so big! It's huge!
見て、フワモコの首輪があるよ！
Look, FuwaMoco's collars are here!
すごく可愛い！...あれ、どうしたの？
And they're so cute! Wait... what's wrong?
待って...モココ、それつけてなかった？
Wait... wasn't Mococo wearing those?
あれ、私つけてなかったっけ？
Wait, wasn't I wearing those?
うん、でもここにあるってことは...フワモコ？みんな？
Yeah, but they're right... FuwaMoco? Guys?
みんな！ここだよ！ここにいるよ！
Guys! We're here! We're here!
声は聞こえるけど、姿が見えないよ！
I hear your voice, but I do not see a body!
みんな、待って待って！下を見て！
Guys, wait, wait, wait! Look down!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
Oh, they're so cute! Wait a second...
Yeah...
Wait, those voices coming from... from the dogs?
I think this might be FuwaMoco!
What? Wait, Nerissa! FuwaMoco have been turned...
...into Dobermans?!
Oh my god! Are you guys okay?
Yeah, you know, I think they actually look more...
...like hellhounds like this, so it kind of fits.
Yeah! Oh, they're so cute! So cute!
Yeah, give them a big pet.
Yes, yes, good dog! You're a good girl, aren't you?
Yeah, good girl! Good girl!
But wait, why... why are they Dobermans...
...all of a sudden? What happened?
Hahaha! Pokey! Pokey!
Hehehe! Not so fluffy and fuzzy now, hoeh!
Pokey, change us back now!
We can't eat donuts like this!
THAT's why you wanna turn back? Hmph, whatever.
I'll give you one final trial! Clear it...
...and I'll restore them!
Mococo-chan, do this so we can go back to normal!
Okay! Everybody, help us, please!
I... I guess we'll give you one donut for the rescue.
Eh? Just one donut? One each or share it?
Eh? But I kind of like you like this, though.
Well, Pokey, what kind of challenge...
...are you going to give us today?
FUWAMOCO Fukuwarai!
FuwaMoco Fukuwarai? Eh?
Behold, the challenge before you!
Eh? Oh, the carpet has changed! Wow...
...why do they have no faces? That's kind of scary.
Yeah, it is a little freaky. I like it.
Hehe, ever heard of Fukuwarai?
It's this old-school Japanese game —
lemme show you how it's played.
See those two giant faces?
Their face parts are all scattered around.
Bijou and Shiori will be blindfolded...
...and carry the face parts!
Blindfolded? Oh, nice! Oh yeah...
...actually that sounds like fun.
We don't have to do anything.
Big bird, with your words alone, you must guide them.
Lead them to place each piece...
...and restore FUWAMOCO's face!
Me? Yeah, you.
Well, we're just going to be over here blindfolded.
We're just going to chill. Good luck!
Okay, I'll do my best! No pressure! No pressure!
Yeah, it's all up to you!
You've got 5 minutes. Better make it count!
Okay, let's all say FuwaMoco together!
Or not... or not! Let's do this!
Let's go!
All right, ladies. So first plan of action:
Come on over, one on each side of me, pretty please.
Okay.
And then I would like you to turn around.
Oh, okay.
So, I have prepared for you blindfolds,
so I'm going to go ahead and just—
You feel free to adjust them as you'd like, but...
...that way you won't be able to see anything...
...since I have to direct you.
So go ahead and turn back around.
Ha! I cannot see a thing.
Yes, perfect. That's exactly what we want. Aha!
All right, and then we're going to go ahead...
...and start placing these things.
So FuwaMoco, my puppies, I'll do my best for you...
...okay? Do your best, Nerissa! Let's do this!
Let's do it! Woohoo!
Okay, and start!
Okay. So what I'm going to do is...
...I'm going to hand you guys each a piece...
...and then I'm going to tell you where to go.
Who goes first then?
So you're each going to do one face. Okay? Okay.
So, you're going to start that way. Wait, where am I?
Whoa, what? Where am I? What's this?
Shiori's just grabbing...
...I don't know what I just grabbed.
Okay. So, Shiori, walk to me.
Just walk to the sound of my voice.
I'm coming. This is really slow.
Yeah, this way, this way. Walk towards me.
Okay, okay. Walk towards me.
Okay. If I accidentally grab something, I'm sorry.
Okay, grab onto this. This?
Yes.
Okay. Don't move. Okay. Okay.
Don't move! Biboo, I want you to walk...
...to the sound of my voice, okay?
Where is the sound of your voice?
Right here. The sound of my voice!
Where is 'here'?
Right, your right. Your right.
Okay, just a little right.
Okay, forward.
Quickly! Okay, now come to me.
Where is you? Okay.
So, I want you to grab this. Oh, okay, I got it. Yes.
So, pretty much where you are right now...
...not you, Shiori.
Okay, Shiori, come forward a little bit.
This forward or this forward?
The forward towards me. This forward?
Okay, that's too much. Back up just a little bit.
And then I want you to move your right.
Your right. Right? This is right.
Left? Left! Okay, back up.
Oh, Mococo-chan, I don't know...
...if this is going to work out!
Place it down.
I tried to be strong but now I'm regretting that.
Okay. Place it down, Biboo.
Ah, down? Oh, okay.
Move forward a little bit.
Okay, and then can you straighten it out?
Like this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just a little bit more.
Okay, yeah, and then can you just scoot the whole thing over to the right?
Scoot, scoot, scoot...
No, left.
What about me? Should I do the same?
No, other way! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
Okay, next items, next items.
Stay right where you are.
I am here where I am.
I'm giving you two, okay?
I got two.
Oh, I don't believe this is happening. Oh!
Oh my god! Nerissa!
Do you have eyes? Ah, ah, ah, do you have eyes?
Yes.
I want you both to walk backwards, okay?
Okay.
Step... maybe straighten out a little bit.
Whoa, that's definitely... okay.
Back... No, actually, you're perfect, Shiori.
You better get running!
I know I'm perfect.
Place... one down.
Which one?
I don't know!
This one!
You're going too far!
This way! Forward again! Forward again!
What? Where do I go?
This way!
It's okay, right?
No! Move it over to the right!
My right? My right? My right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
I don't think I can do this!
Okay, okay, place the other one down!
I don't want to! I don't want to have to continue like this!
Oh my god! Trust me here!
This way! No, where I am!
This way!
Yeah, our faces have to be like this for real!
Oh my god, Bijou! Okay, Bijou, yeah! Come towards the sound of my voice!
Where is the sound of your voice?!
I think she's over here.
Forward! Forward! Forward!
Okay, stop. Now come this way a little bit.
Turn... this way!
Which way?!
Do you hear where I am?
Oh yes, yes!
Pretend... pretend you're in an immersive game, okay?
Oh yes, I heard... I felt your voice!
Perfect, perfect. Okay, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, now I want you to turn a little bit this way.
Which way? This way?
Wait, sorry, the other way!
Like, rotate your body!
Rotate me!
And this is all wrong! Oh!
Okay, so now I want you to place the one in your left hand down, okay?
On the ground.
Like this?
Yeah, okay. Now I want you to walk slightly in this direction.
Just like, crab walk.
What direction?!
See what ear I'm at?
Oh yes!
Like an immersive game. Feel it like a game, Bijou!
Okay! I'm feeling it!
Okay, place it down.
Like this?
No! Oh no!
I'm doing my best!
Is it done or what?
You have one minute!
One more, okay?
Okay, I'm done.
Okay. Now onto the other one.
So, Bijou, you're... walk this way.
Okay! Which way is this way?
Put it down! Right there!
Wait! No, that's the wrong way! Pick it back up!
Walk... opposite side!
This side?!
Okay! Uh... behind you! Move backwards, backwards, backwards...
backwards, backwards, backwards!
Okay, down!
At least my face looks a bit better than Fuwawa's.
Okay, now walk this way.
Which is this way?
Yeah, yeah. Now walk to your left.
No, no, sorry, right! I think you messed up!
So... sorry!
This way! Left, left, left! This way!
Yes! Okay, now forward.
Forward... yes!
Now put it down!
So good! So good!
Yeah, and then this... please!
No time! 15 seconds left!
Are you done?
Wait, I think I... make it work!
Make it work by brute force!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! 15 seconds!
Don't worry about it! Don't worry about it!
Are we done?
Yeah! One! Done!
Okay, I want you guys to turn on around,
and we're going to take off your blindfolds
so you can see how you did, okay?
Wait, which one's around?
Around?
This way!
Well, let's take a look.
I bet we did great!
There's no way to look at it.
Pokey, what do you think? Isn't it good?
Hey, Bijou, Shiori! You sure this is Fuwawa and Mococo?
Yeah, look at it! Something seems a little...
Nah, nah, nah, it looks great!
It's not upside down or anything!
Wait, can we have a donut please?
I think it looks perfect.
Why are you adjusting it?
I'm not doing anything!
It's not making it better!
It's perfect! It's perfect this way!
Wait, wait, wait! What about this over here?
Don't touch my face!
Put it... put it back!
Look at... look! Yeah! That's great!
I mean, the precision you see here...
I mean, the precision you see to do it like this,
because I just wanted to see what it would look like just a little lower.
This is not good!
Well, is it good enough to get changed back, Pokey?
Hmph, fine. I'll change them back!
Yay! Bau Bau!
Hi! Ho! Yay! Bau Bau!
やったー！完成！
We did it! It's finished!
見て見て！すごい！
Look, look! It's amazing!
かわいい！何これ！？
So cute! What is this!?
待って、これめっちゃかわいい！
Wait, this is so adorable!
大好き！
I love it!
待って、私の夢を叶えてくれなかったの？
Wait, you didn't make my dream come true?
そんな！ダメダメダメダメ！
No way! No, no, no, no, no!
大丈夫、こっちの方が好きだよ。
It's okay, I like you better this way.
顔に刺さってるんだけど！
It's stuck right in my face!
どうかなこれ？
How's this?
みんなで乗り越えられて本当によかった。
I'm really glad we could get through this together.
そうでしょ、みんな？
Aren't you guys?
うん！友情の力だね！
Yeah! The power of friendship!
友情！
Friendship!
Adventとして、これからも協力し合って助け合っていかないとね！
As Advent, you've gotta keep working together and looking out for one another!
そうだね！
That's right!
Yeah, that's karma, yeah, get down
Checkmate, I'm a superstar
Stay insane, but you rock with it, ah
Like 24/7, I'm a hot mess ya, love-hate
Get less bored, oh my god, home run, bat-a-bat-a-swing my shot
Like a villainous villainess, villains bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains, they're all the same
派手にブチかまそう
Let's go out with a bang
Yeah, that's karma
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
"Chaotic good" is peak right now
I can show ya how
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
No way, no way, way-o-way-ya
"Good vs. Evil" is so overdone
Let's all kick back and party
Just leave it to me
Whoops
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
That's karma, ta-da-ha-ha-ha
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it, yeah
Sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running? Uh-huh
Bet'cha think you're clever
Whatever!
Talk about a "kumbaya"
フルボッコ ボッちゃって
Beat 'em up, beat 'em up
欲望 召し上がれ
Eat up your desires
愛ハート Get down
Love heart, Get down
Sayonara サイコですわ
Sayonara, I'm a psycho
ドメスティック
Domestic
ドラマティック
Dramatic
愛しき人々
Beloved people
この指とまれ
Join in with me
ハートにハート ハイになって 弾けてハジライフ 捨てちゃいな
Heart to heart, getting high, burst out, throw away your shame
叫びを解き放て 勝ち取り 頂上へ 押し通せ 頂戴
Unleash your scream, win and reach the top, push through, give it to me
道化のパラダイス ダイス
A fool's paradise, dice
惹かれ合う 感覚が 共鳴共鳴
The feeling of mutual attraction, resonance, resonance
Good vs. Evil, but I'm which one?
Just stuck here in the middle
That's not any fun
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
That's karma, ta-da-ha-ha-ha
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it, yeah
想像から創造
From imagination to creation
衝動から猛攻
From impulse to onslaught
ほらあっという間に 華麗に 変幻自在
Look, in the blink of an eye, brilliantly kaleidoscopic
毒々しい本能
Poisonous instinct
喰らえ咆哮
Consume the roar
Talk about a "kumbaya"
Sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running? Uh-huh
Bet'cha think you're clever
Whatever!
Talk about a "kumbaya"
異世界
Isekai
クイーンサイズ
Queen-size
チューニング・マイナス
Tuning minus
カリフォルニア・カコフォニー
California cacophony
Is it today you're gonna make a?
Welcome to Miss Fortune's game
以上、『Go-Getters』でした！
Well, that was Go-Getters!
私たちのパフォーマンスはどうだったかな？
How did you like our performance?
今見てくれているみんなへ...
To everybody watching right now...
重大発表があります！
We all have some big news!
なんと！2周年を記念して...
And guess what? For our second anniversary...
2つの大きな発表があります！
We have two big announcements!
1つ目は...
The first one is...
完全新曲です！
A brand new song!
Adventの物語、第2のオリジナル曲...
It's the second original song in the story of Advent...
『PRISONER』！
PRISONER!
8月31日にリリースされます！
Will be released on August 31st...
各地域の深夜12時に配信開始です！
...at 12 AM local time in each region!
え、誰が囚人なの？私たち？それとも他の誰か？
Wait, who's the prisoner? Are we the prisoner? Is someone else the prisoner?
It's just Prisoner...
No matter, it's gonna sound great!
Yeah!
If you want to find out, don't go anywhere,
cause you'll be redirected to the music video
right after this stream!
Yeah!
Good job!
And guess what?
We're also going to premiere the new song
right after this!
Yeah!
Alright everybody, are you ready?
Places, places!
Okay! Places!
Locked away where nightmares keep you awake,
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace.
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape),
You're all mine, all mine...
Wayward soul, I'll wrap you up in darkness
that consumes you whole,
hold you in my labyrinth of walls.
(Lost in the depths that swallow you,
where just your shadows follow you)
Always churning in the deep, I won't let you sleep.
You don't need your dreams now
that you belong to me.
Throw them all away,
you're too frail to be free.
You will always be my lovely prisoner...
(Are you shaking?)
My eyes will find you,
let me clutch you tightly
(You can only be mine),
poor little prisoner...
(Are you breaking?)
My chains will bind you here forever,
stay here for all time...
(In tenebris, in frigore, in carcere)
Close your eyes, go deeper in the emptiness
that plagues your mind,
let my dark envelop your light.
I will keep you safe and sound,
hear the blissful silence all around.
I'll drag you down below, never let you go.
Everything you've been,
the transgressions of your past.
Throw them all away,
let me hold you at last...
My lovely prisoner...
(What's the matter?)
You're never leaving, you are mine forever
Got to keep you right here
Poor, helpless prisoner...
(Did you shatter?)
Why are you grieving your ambitions?
Let them disappear...
I can hear your plea,
reaching desperately,
but I'll never, ever set you free.
Stay with me.
My lovely prisoner...
(Are you shaking?)
My eyes will find you, let me clutch you tightly
(You can only be mine),
poor little prisoner...
(Are you breaking?)
My chains will bind you here forever,
stay here for all time...
(In tenebris, in frigore, in carcere)
Yeah!
That was our new song, Prisoner!
What did you think of the track, huh?
Hot song, huh?
Okay, and let's all move on to the second piece
of exciting news.
Come close, girls!
Hololive English -Advent-
2nd Anniversary Celebration!
Yeah!
First up, we have...
the Framed Art Board!
It's a large illustration board, framed beautifully.
The luxurious frame features our logo
with foil stamping for the extra shine.
It's a perfect item to decorate your home
and to enjoy looking at every single day,
so you can see all of us together,
just like we should be.
Yeah!
Well, next up, we have a Sticker Set
from 2024 Halloween version!
Yeah!
Five different designs,
and it includes the VR Chat design released
for Halloween,
plus a three-piece sticker set
featuring each Advent member's original design.
And then you can put them on your phone,
stick them on your PC, and have fun with them.
Yeah!
Alright! Next up, we got...
the Connectable Charm!
Yeah!
What's awesome is that
all these charms can actually connect...
to each other!
So you can mix and match 'em
all kinds of different ways, right?
Have fun!
Yeah! Woo! Hahaha!
Finally, we've got the Varsity Jacket!
Wow! It's got the Advent logo on the back
and Fuwawa is embroidered on the front... tastic... too!
What? What?
And guess what!
What?
You can actually attach those charms
I just showed you on the zipper of the jacket too!
What?! You know, it's a cool item
that you can rock both in your everyday life
and at events too!
Yeah! And guess what!
What?
It's happening right now!
The merch just dropped
at the hololive official shop!
Now! And hey guys,
notice that guy showing up on the bottom of...
the bottom left, left of the YouTube screen?
Go ahead and click it to shop your favorites, okay?
Click! Click-click-click-click...
This was such a wonderful day together!
I had so much fun! You guys were
running from Justice half the time.
Yeah, but that's a typical Friday... but we really were
sprinted! No, better luck next time, Justice!
Yes! As if you could ever catch us!
We are Team Pon!
Yeah, don't forget that!
We've been together for two years now!
Yeah, can you believe it?
That's a lot of memories... lots of memories!
And we're looking forward to all of the next years together!
Year three, year four, year five, year six!
Yeah! Infinite! Together forever!
Yes! Woo! Rock on!
Infinite adventure! Bye-bye!
T-T-T-チーム友達
T-T-T-Team Tomodachi
チーム友達、チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
俺たち何、え？(チーム友達)
What are we, huh? (Team Tomodachi)
チーム友達
Team Tomodachi
関西関東 西東 (チーム友達)
Kansai, Kanto, West, East (Team Tomodachi)
チーム友達、チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
俺たち何、え？(チーム友達)
What are we, huh? (Team Tomodachi)
チーム友達
Team Tomodachi
関西関東 西東 (チーム友達)
Kansai, Kanto, West, East (Team Tomodachi)