(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Now don't go trying to hide somewhere in the dark
Behind those pretty eyes, I see your broken heart
Waiting for the day you get away from this reality
Oh, it's such a tragedy
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Now don't go trying to hide somewhere in the dark
Behind those pretty eyes, I see your broken heart
Waiting for the day you get away from this reality
Oh, it's such a tragedy
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Now don't go trying to hide somewhere in the dark
Behind those pretty eyes, I see your broken heart
Waiting for the day you get away from this reality
Oh, it's such a tragedy
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Now don't go trying to hide somewhere in the dark
Behind those pretty eyes, I see your broken heart
Waiting for the day you get away from this reality
Oh, it's such a tragedy
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Locked away when nightmares keep you awake
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
You're all mine, all mine
(You'll never escape)
Now don't go trying to hide somewhere in the dark
Behind those pretty eyes, I see your broken heart
Waiting for the day you get away from this reality
WAH!
Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening.
It's me Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert!
I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador
for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun
sharing all the great memories
and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time,
but I still get excited
every time I'll spot
something WAHnderful on AmiAmi
– it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch
of your oshi on AmiAmi
be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you
for everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, Thank you AmiAmi!
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer
with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
It's Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Feel free to share screenshots and reactions!
動画の撮影・録音は禁止いたします
Audio and video recording are strictly forbidden.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights.
ALL FOR ONE In-Stock Merch
Essentials Pack, Light Stick, T-shirt
Made-to-Order Merch
Badges, Coasters, Tapestry, Mug, Happi
ALL FOR ONE Fan Messages and Artwork
Radio City Music Hall, New York City
hololive English 3rd Concert - All for One
Ooh
Just look around and see, it's so incredible
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom
My heart goes boom, boom, boom
The world is brighter because you believe in...
All for one, we're stronger together
One for all, we're rising forever
Every heart is beating, joining in the light
All for one, we're taking flight
All for One!
Now we're standing here, it's all because of you
Every single dream is coming true (MYTH)
Through the highs and lows, we're never alone
This is where we belong, our home sweet home
All for one, we're stronger together
One for all, we're rising forever (PROMISE)
Every heart is beating, joining in the light
All for one, we're taking flight
All for one, we're stronger together
One for all, we're rising forever (ADVENT)
Every heart is beating, joining in the light
All for one, we're taking flight
All for one, we're stronger together
One for all, we're rising forever (JUSTICE)
Every heart is beating, joining in the light
All for one, we're taking flight
All for one, we're stronger together
One for all, we're rising forever
All for one!
One for all!
hololive English 3rd Concert: ALL FOR ONE
Welcome to hololive English 3rd Concert...
ALL FOR ONE!
Let's start with a bang!
Just look around and see, it's so incredible
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom
My heart goes boom, boom, boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud
Our time is right now, we're on the edge of destiny
For all the time I can dream with you
Every miracle we hope for might come true
We come together reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly you're here by my side
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're All For One!
Let's sing!
All For One!
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's All For One!
Let's sing!
All For One!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day
The rest of our lives!
Hey!
All that we waited for
The dream we're striving toward
We're singing All For One!
All For One!
Everything's in motion
Get up and start the celebration!
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
You're joining hands for the world to see
Uh-huh, feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom
My heart goes boom, boom, boom
In this whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud
Our time is right now, we're here together finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly our hearts beat as one
Every voice singing loud and clear
So glad to be here together, we're All For One!
Let's sing!
All For One!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in 'cause it's All For One!
Let's sing!
All For One!
Step up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night
The rest of our lives!
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway
Your light will lead our way
We're shining All For One!
All For One!
Everything's moving, it's joy and it's hope
We'll gather and we'll sing of our endless ride
Feel the music in your passion, it's all right here right now
So let the good times roll, oh-oh
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I believe in you, if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams
One, two, three, four, five!
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're All For One!
Let's sing!
All For One!
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's All For One!
Let's sing!
All For One!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day
The rest of our lives!
All that we waited for
The dream we're striving toward
We're singing All For One!
All For One!
Nerissa Ravencroft
Shiori Novella
Koseki Bijou
Fuwawa Abyssgard
Mococo Abyssgard
Then open up your eyes, hear the music start to rise
Gotta break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be living life so fast and free
Gotta keep your eyes on me, this is where my story...
It's our story
Ready to go, you're makin' me act like crazy
Ready to play, come at me
Hit it away so easy, I can't get enough
Freeze the burn, no limit
Heaven, hell, and feel it
Get up and go, let's do this
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Watch me be your diva, I'm gonna raise your fever
Shakin' up all the crowd, makin' some noise when I'm not allowed
Livin' my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep on dancin' in my element
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Now pay attention, 'cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis!
Come and take some havoc
How do you like this bad habit?
I'm embracin' my madness
Can you hear us?
Whispers are spinnin' down your window
Rumors reachin' a crescendo
No humble beginning, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Midnight, join me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
Mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
I'm gonna start a raid when I misbehave, take center stage
At my command, you know I'm gonna get intense
No pulse is smokin'
The rules can all be broken
And runnin' on a rampage, the world is a blank page
Let's go!
I'm writin' my story in flames and in glory
They're gonna know me by name
This is my promised land
The future's in my hand
But they don't understand that I'm just now makin', awakin', and takin' a bow
Bow, bow, bow, tell me how you like me now
Go! Go! Go! Come on!
Show! Show! Show! Show! Yeah!
Come on!
Come watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go, I'm gonna show you how to lose control
Ready? You got the freedom on mind, leave your strings behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is
It's our genesis!
Gonna open up your eyes, feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
Who I was meant to be, livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me, 'cause this is our beginning
It's our genesis!
Whispers are spinnin' down your window
Rumors reachin' a crescendo
No humble beginning, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Midnight, join me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
Mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Yeah, you know what time it is! It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is! It's our genesis!
さぁ 散らばってしまった話を
Come, of the stories that have scattered...
空に手を伸ばし始める
I begin to reach my hand out to the sky.
知った 踊りすぎる禍々しさに
I learned, of the ominousness that dances too much,
縛られた足をくすぐるの
it tickles my bound feet.
嗚呼 堕ちて汚れた意識を
Ah, take my fallen, soiled consciousness...
名前と綴りにかけて
and stake it on my name and its spelling.
躰 戻ってだた身体の
Body, returned as just a body...
夢見ていた目蓋が開く
the eyelids that were dreaming open up.
心の奥から蠢く記憶が
Memory wriggling from the depths of the heart...
混ぜた呪いと祈り
Mixed curses and prayers,
絡めた愛を
entwined love...
知ってるの
I know.
始まりと終わりに向かって
Towards the beginning and the end,
海に描いていくのは 波の呼び声だけ
what I paint on the sea is only the call of waves.
あぁ 貴方
Oh, you...
そこに居たら教えて欲しいの
if you're there, I want you to tell me.
私が在る此処の道は
The path where I am,
どんな色だろう
what color would it be?
あぁ この調べの旋律を
Ah, this melody of the tune,
空に手を伸ばし始める
I begin to reach my hand out to the sky.
散らばった記憶の
The path of blood...
血の道が
of scattered memories,
愛を分かつとして鳴き叫んでる
is crying out as it divides love.
始まりと終わりに向かって
Towards the beginning and the end,
海に描いていくのは
what I paint on the sea is...
救われなかった君の声
your voice that wasn't saved.
愛おしい
So dear...
今も其処に居たら教えて
if you're still there, please tell me.
君の手をいつかまた
To hold your hand...
握れるのこの...
once again, this...
It's finally time!
We're here!
Well, shall we?
We shall.
You go first.
I go first?
Okay. You know the drill guys!
I say "Wah", you say "Wah"!
Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening! This is Ninomae Ina'nis of hololive English -Myth-!
You got this! You got this!
I just finished my song, I'm tired!
Okay, and we have...
WHAT'S UP!
I am Chaos, the advent of... still race-trapped in a cage of ice...
your world-wide order-up, Hakos Baelz of hololive English -Promise-!
WITNESS ME!
Guys, how was that for an opener?
Did you guys enjoy it?
I can't hear you!
And of course, everyone watching from home, hello!
We see you guys!
We see you!
Hello, hello, hello...
Oh man, we have arrived at hololive English 3rd Concert "All for One"!
Ninomae Ina'nis, how do you feel?
I feel... fantastic!
Fantastic!
Feel fantastic!
Miraculously preserved!
You know, I can't believe it's already the third live.
First, we connected the world.
Second, we broke the dimension.
And third, we are ALL FOR ONE!
Did you guys like— I guess this is the first time
we're all together performing All For One.
Yeah.
Oh man, I almost cried.
I know! You know that we were like, we were like...
"Oh my God, it's so emotional!"
"It's so emotional!"
But I hope you guys enjoyed the opener
that we had, Advent!
Yes!
And then we had, we had Ina's solo...
It was so good! Did you guys like it?
All right, you know, since it is the very first—
this is the first MC of the first...
First MC of the first day...
...of the first day!
We're just getting started! We're just getting started!
We need to test those penlights!
Yeah, test the penlights!
See if they work!
How about we split down the middle here?
And we go purple— not purple.
Violet over here!
It keeps happening, okay?
It's violet over here, and red...
...and over here I want to see red!
All of you!
Oh my goodness! Oh my goodness!
Oh my God, the sea of penlights!
Oh yeah, you know, not only that, you know,
we're just getting started.
There's the whole show today and tomorrow.
So make sure to share it with everyone,
share your excitement with hashtag holoAllForOne!
Post it!
Yay!
Screenshot! Yay!
Oh man, it's exciting.
Do I get to do the next part? Do I get to do it?
Finally! I'll let you do it this time.
Okay!
Although it is kind of sad news.
Wait, wait, no. It's just...
I've never done it before. I'm really excited, but...
She's excited, but it's not— it's kind of sad
because it is now time to announce that...
I have terrible news!
Oh! What is it, Hakos Baelz?
Unfortunately, if you are watching from home,
this is the end of the free segment!
How could this be? Absolute tragedy!
This is a tragedy!
But do not worry. If you're at home
and you just saw this bangin' opener
and you want to continue watching the rest of the concert,
check the link in the description!
Get your tickets and continue watching the concert!
Yay! Bye everyone! Bye!
Not you guys. You guys are stuck here until the end!
All right? You're not going anywhere!
All right! You guys better be ready
with your unlimited energy!
Yeah, I think we should, you know, test a little bit.
Are you guys ready?
Ready?
All right, you know the drill!
Do they know the drill? Do I know the drill?
You know the drill.
I know the drill. Believe it at that.
Well, anyway...
Okay! All right, on the count of—
countdown from three!
Three!
Two!
One!
ALL FOR ONE!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Cecilia Immergreen
Gigi Murin
Raora Panthera
Ooh~
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom,
My heart goes boom, boom, boom
The world is brighter because you believe in...