(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
WAH!
Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening! It's me Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert!
I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun sharing all the
great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time,
but I still get excited every time I spot
something WAHnderful on AmiAmi.
It's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi
on AmiAmi, be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you for
everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, "Thank you AmiAmi!"
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer with everything
you've got, okay?
WAH!
On the Run!
Zom-Raid Time!
hololive! hololive! hololive! hololive!
Let's go! 1, 2, 3, 4!
hololive! hololive! hololive!
ALL for ONE!
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
Yeah!
Rise up
Coming closer now
Bring it on
Get down
Dynamic
Fighter
Fearless
Step it up, step it up now
We've got the power, unstoppable fire
burning up inside, so
Nothing breaks us down,
no matter what we're gonna breakthrough
Never stop, gotta keep it going on and on,
as we go crashing through the dark
And we're gonna break the rules,
nobody can do what we can do
Move, move, break out the moves now,
moving to the groove, keep it extra cool
Extraordinary, gotta let them know
who's in control, yo step it up,
break it down, let's go, getaway
Louder, louder to the beat
Fly higher, higher to the sky
And here we go, we don't have no time to waste
This is the heart, the life, the mind
Infinite reality, I heard a whisper
Calling me, calling me
I see it now, we found ourselves, until we
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Start again, we're never gonna stop
何か輝く　響き合って
Something shines, resonating together
Hey! Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not, here we go
Supernatural, you love us finally
無限に広がる　ステージ響かせて
Let the infinitely expanding stage resonate
And now sing along
Never end, and taking over, keep it going on and on
Sha-la-la and reach out to the moon
Not afraid, there's nothing left to lose
Us, us, something more
Yes turn it up into the new world
We are unbreakable now
We know what's going on, take a risk from head to toe
Ready or not, level up to be
Burnin' burnin' burnin'
Focus on us, step by step, I'm getting out
Shout it to the limit, till the end, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Infinite reality, I heard a whisper
Calling me, calling me
I see it now, we found ourselves, until we
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Start again, we're never gonna stop
何か輝く　響き合って
Something shines, resonating together
Hey! Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not, here we go
Supernatural, we're finally down
Hold back, don't let nobody get
in the way of us no more
Loss of light, evolutionary, hey yo come on, get up, get up
Never lose the way, invincible now,
going higher and higher, the energy grows
Burning up, under control, here we go,
la la la la, keep it up, we're coming out
La la la la, let it go, start again
This is us ruling the world
Start again, we're never gonna stop
何か輝く　響き合って
Something shines, resonating together
Hey! Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not, here we go
Supernatural, finally
無限に広がる　ステージ響かせて
Let the infinitely expanding stage resonate
And now sing along
Never end, and taking over, keep it going on and on
Sha-la-la and reach out to the moon
Not afraid, there's nothing left to lose
Us, us, something more
Yes turn it up into the new world
We are unbreakable
We are unbreakable now
愛したもうな　小鳥たちよ
Do not love me, little birds
愛したもうな　私のこと
Do not love me
聖なる王女　数多の座に
The holy princess, on her many thrones,
滅びの船に眠る
sleeps in the ship of destruction.
Everybody! Are you ready to rock? Let's go!
結び立てた　約束は
The promise we made,
呪われた　幽霊船に
upon the cursed ghost ship,
綴る　夜の　蝶の
I compose, the night butterfly's...
そこに　棘が残る
where a thorn remains.
快楽だけがあるのなら
If there is only pleasure...
だだだだ　ないでしょう
There's no no no no way, right?
無謀の火を　分け盗ってよ
Steal a portion of that reckless fire
命を以て　後悔に被せてやろう
With my life, I'll cover it with regret
やまない雨の弾丸で
With the bullets of the never-ending rain
穿つほどこの身を焦がす
Piercing so much, this body burns
天上の炎が　反吐を路地に晒す
The celestial flames expose the vomit in the alley
然らる宝石なのだなら
If it's to be such a gem...
私なもの　そう私なもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine
歌ってみせて　命の証を
Sing for me, the proof of life
あなたと求むる　すべてを
Everything that I seek with you
掲げる　不敵満ちて
Hold it high, full of fearlessness
すべてを　目に焼き尽くすなら
If I'm to burn everything into my eyes
泡沫とともに　沈め
Sink along with the bubbles
日々の火纏い　溶けだす
Wrapped in the fire of days, melting away
娯茶番な回想の火を
The fire of trivial recollections
風は笑う
The wind laughs
満月の金魚浄
Goldfish cleansing of the full moon
七つの港を今日に
The seven ports today
高く伏すとも
Even if I lie down high
捕りと実を狙う
Aiming for the catch and the fruit
愚かのに　暴きだす
Foolishly exposing it
ふさわし持ち主を
The rightful owner
身に踊る　頃合いか　忍べ
Is it time for it to dance on me? Stealthily...
陰の底で　忍び寄る　絶望の渦丸手
In the depths of the shadows, the whirlpool of despair creeps in
二度の　戸惑い箱
A second box of hesitation
食べちゃえば　諦めちゃえば
If you eat it, if you give up
檻の中から　逃げられるのにまだ
You could escape from the cage, yet you still...
縋ってる　よっぽど重いから
Cling to it, because it's so heavy
私なもの　そう私なもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine
自分自身を　信じ込ましたはずで
I was supposed to have convinced myself
縛り付けていたって　気づいた
I realized I was tying myself down
無謀の火を　取り寄る怪奇
The mystery that brings the reckless fire
目を覚ませて　あなたの悪夢から
Wake up from your nightmare
連れ出す　気分だよ
I feel like taking you away
ショートして
Short circuit
私なもの　また私なもの
Mine, again, it's mine
毒の薔薇　ぶちまけたとしても
Even if I scatter the poisonous roses
枯れない　魂までは
Until the soul that never withers
迷い中　永遠の微風を
In the midst of lost, an eternal breeze
そんな幻　そっとしておいてでしょう
That kind of illusion, just leave it alone, right?
情け深いは　損じゃん
Being compassionate is a loss, isn't it?
迷子　夜景に顔を向けて
A lost child, turning their face to the night view
言わくを　宿した船
The ship that harbored the legends
火花だけ　残していく
Leaving only sparks behind
神はもういない
God is no longer here
ただ――
Only...
Hello New York!
Are you ready to put your hands up?
I want to see all your hands!
Let's go!
Put your hands up! Put put your hands up! はあと様！
Put your hands up! Put put your hands up! Haato-sama!
Put your hands up! Put put your hands up!
右端にも左端にもなくググッ
Neither on the right end nor the left end, gugugu
手に持つ少な目いずずっ
Holding a small amount in hand, izuzuzu
飯は食わな場　寝る寝る寝るなタイム
Don't eat food, don't sleep sleep sleep time
すびゃ！　ここ　どこ　まえ　こと　ごごごっ
Subya! Here, where, front, thing, gogogogo
ダンシン　ダーリン　シャンシャン進化進行
Dancing darling, shan-shan evolution progress
感謝あり　チームは所属どこ
Gratitude, which team do you belong to?
いい感じ　そうそう出発進行
Good feeling, yes yes, departure progress
去る者追わず　ぱぱぴぷぺぽー
Don't chase those who leave, pa-pa-pi-pu-pe-po
Put your hands up! Put put your hands up! はあと様！
Put your hands up! Put put your hands up! Haato-sama!
Put your hands up! Put put your hands up!
牛もほら　これださな
Cows too, look, take this out
ワンワンワンワン　ワン！　ワオ！
Wan wan wan wan wan! Wao!
脳内全開　やっほーパレード
Brain fully open, yahoo parade
笑わないで　踊ればアイアイアイ！　ワオ！
Don't laugh, if you dance, ai ai ai! Wao!
パンドラ開いた　止まっての
Pandora opened, stay still...
ほら　酔わせて
Now, get me drunk
さい さい さい さい 高 パーティー
Great, great, great, great party!
Oh-wa-a-a-ai 気分は High コンプラ
Oh-wa-a-a-ai, feeling high, compliance!
Oh-wa-a-a-ai アイ・アム・マイ・コントロール・パンチ
Oh-wa-a-a-ai, I am my control punch!
繋がってんだ　キロコンなんだ　神 MMD だね
We're connected, it's a kilocom, a divine MMD!
メンヘラ　思い出　色　猿　人　Girl
Mentally ill, memories, colors, monkey, human, girl!
御愁傷様　働いてんだ　年金なんだ
My condolences, I'm working, it's a pension!
四隅な暇　毎日が　ゲス　ゲス　気の毒
Four corners of free time, every day is lewd, a pity!
乱　芯　タービン　ジャン　ジャン　胴脱しん
Chaos, core, turbine, bang, bang, body removal!
じ　人類　滅亡　しましょう　主は AI 暴走
Le- let's lead humanity to extinction, rogue AI!
アモス　三振　早々　警戒進行
Amos, three strikes, quickly, precautionary progress!
指　指　まで　One Two Three オン　ナイオン　ナイオ
Finger, finger, until 1-2-3, online, online!
Access is denied
Okay New York, you're gonna hate me for saying this...
let's go vintage!
Oh my God, it's my life ようやく真に辿り着いた
Oh my God, it's my life, finally reached the truth.
ごめんなさい　無神経で　オレ　オレ　オレ　オレ
I'm sorry for being insensitive, me, me, me, me!
Everyone, we're just getting started...
so give me your energy!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your, put your, put your hands up!
毒味　ほら　これだろ　サヨナラ
Taste the poison, look, this is it, goodbye.
So 1, 1, 1, 1, 1 and what the f*** is that? WOOHOO!
脳内　全開　ヤバパパパパパーティー
Brain wide open, crazy pa-pa-pa-pa-party!
笑わないで踊れば　アイアイアオウ！
Don't laugh, just dance, eye-eye-awoo!
参道　開いて　ドーパパパドパミン
Open the shrine path, do-pa-pa-pa-dopamine!
ほら　酔わせて
Now, get me drunk!
さい さい さい さい 高 パーティー
Great, great, great, great party!
Oh-wa-a-a-ai 気分は High コンプラ
Oh-wa-a-a-ai, feeling high, compliance!
Oh-wa-a-a-ai アイ・アム・マイ・コントロール・パンチ
Oh-wa-a-a-ai, I am my control punch!
Put your hands up! Put your, put your hands up!
New York! Are you ready for some spice?
Na-na-na, na-na-na-na-na-na
(K-I-R-A)
Oh no
Fell into the abyss unknown
Left me bleeding, heartless, all alone, ayo, ayo
No control, ayo, ayo
Don't you dare apologize
Turn my back and felt a cold knife
Listen up, 'cause here's some advice (ay, ay, yeah)
You're out of time.
Way out of line.
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down to just what I want now
Keep calling me a sinner? No, I don't think so
Ready, ready, ready, ready... I got you twisted
Ready, ready, ready, ready... Just missed it
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You're gonna hear them all sing... Now sing it!
Ready, ready, ready, ready... L-L-L-Lifestyle
Ready, ready, ready, ready... I'm a killer!
Don't back it up, don't back it up, keep that aim
I got thoughts that will drive you insane
Come over if you like, we'll have a lot of fun...
but I got a lot of bite
I do what I want, make sure you don't forget it
Army on my back, think I'm just sadistic?
Not living in the line, or I am the line
And I want to see the way you bleed
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down to just what I want now
Keep calling me a sinner? No, I don't think so
Ready, ready, ready, ready... I got you twisted
Ready, ready, ready, ready... Just missed it
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You're gonna hear them all sing... Now sing it!
Ready, ready, ready, ready... L-L-L-Lifestyle
Ready, ready, ready, ready... I'm a killer!
I want it all, so give me some more...
flames burn me up down into my core
Oh, you wish that I'd stay down, but then I just rise
You're not my enemy, baby you're dead to me
Hear my voice screaming out loud, no doubt, yeah!
Yeah!
Tearing it down to just what I wanna
Keep calling me a phenomena
Steady, eddy, eddy, ya
Persistent
Oh!
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You're gonna hear a monster singing
Steady, eddy, eddy, ya
Analyze, analyze
Oh!
La la la la la la
Chimera eddy eddy ya-ya
Chimera eddy eddy ya
They're gonna know I'm cheating on Calli!
IRyS! You're cheating on Calli with me!
Did you know? Oh yeah!
Oh no, yabai!
Oh no, this is bad!
Wait, we're not doing anything wrong.
We're not... we're not doing anything wrong.
No, no, no, no, no. We were just, uh, hugging as friends.
It was just te-he te-he. Yes, ne?
It was just te-he te-he. Right?
Kikiriki!
IRyS!
Okay, let's introduce ourselves, yeah?
Yes! You!
Start with the cheater? Oh no.
The cheater? You also cheated!
Okay, okay. Go ahead.
Hi! Kikiriki!
Hi! Uh, I wish I was someone else right now...
...but I'm Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth! Yay!
And you?
Hi-RyS! It's IRyS from Hololive English Promise!
Can I get a Hi-RyS? Hi-RyS!
Let's go! Thank you!
We just performed a really hype performance...
Yes!
...of Chimera!
Chimera!
This is not my first time performing with you on your song.
Yeah, they put us together a lot these days. Kind of a trend.
It is.
Kiara-RyS is a trend!
Yay!
I'm sure they... they can't get enough of us, right?
Yeah, no, of course they can't.
That's why we're here now too. We're spice. We're sexy.
Oh, yes we are.
Yes, we are! Of course we are!
Well, you know, it's the first time...
That's right. Which means...
Which means... Oh!
Um, we're gonna do the sad news, right?
Yes.
But I want to deliver the sad news.
It's our first time, so I want to do it too!
I want to do it!
Well, in that case, we battle it out!
We're battling it out? In front of all these people?
Yes, it's no problem. They're gonna cheer for us.
Well, when we think of battles, what do we think of?
I think, like recently, a lot of the EN members have been doing arm wrestling.
Yeah.
And I'm very well known for being a noodle-arm person.
What about you?
I am very strong!
Oh!
Everyone knows that IRyS is very strong. Yeah, sure.
Well, you know, I usually am left-handed,
but I will use my right hand to give you a chance. Okay?
Okay, senpai. Okay, okay, okay.
I will take that challenge right now! Let's do it!
Okay, come here. Come here.
Okay. Count us down!
Three! Two! One! Go!
Yes! Let's go!
I just beat her! Her non-dominant arm!
Yeah, that was my right hand though.
My left hand is my dominant arm. So that wasn't completely fair.
Oh. Let's do another game.
Another game? Yes!
I mean, yeah, that's true, it wasn't fair.
In that case, what... what do you have in mind?
There's this game called, uh, like Blue Light, Red Light...
Not Blue Light. Red Light, Green Light.
Red Light, Green Light! Okay.
Okay, then you perhaps stand on that side,
and I go towards you.
Okay. All right, all right. Gotcha.
Okay, then I... I can win this!
I will get you, okay?
Red light! Oh, green light!
Oh, sorry. We're starting, we're starting.
Red light!
Green light!
Red light, green light!
Red light! Green light!
Red light! Green light! Red light! Green light!
Got your butt! No, my butt! No, my butt!
Okay, yay!
But that means it's a draw.
A draw? Which means...
We get to stay together!
Phew!
Tee-tee ending!
Wholesome ending!
Kiara, it's not like this was scripted or anything. I swear I actually...
No, no, no! The only thing that was scripted was our entrance.
That... Oh, that...
Okay, then let's do it!
Let's do this! Okay!
Everybody watching on YouTube...
Are you aware...
...that if you don't have a ticket, you might be not able...
...to watch anymore of this?
What?!
Yes, guys! This is the last...
...of the free part on YouTube!
If you want to watch more...
...you have to buy the streaming tickets!
They're available in the description and the official website!
Probably down there!
Yeah, you can go get the streaming ticket!
Yeah, you would be crying like me until you buy them!
Yes!
Do what she says, I recommend it!
Once you buy them, you'll be happy...
...and you'll be able to watch the rest of the concert!
Buy it! Buy it!
Besides that, one more thing.
Now that you've got your tickets and you're ready to take even more screenshots...
...make sure to share them and your thoughts on social media...
...using the hashtag #holoAllForOne!
Yes! So...
I think we should... speaking of All for One...
...I think it's time for us to, you know, say the thing.
Yeah, the thing!
You guys are all aware by now, right?
Because of yesterday, it's called All for One.
We say it together.
We say it together, yeah?
All of us!
All of us! Onegaishimasu!
All of us! Please!
Are you in or what? Okay!
All for One! All for One! Okay! Okay!
Ready? Okay!
Three, two, one...
ALL FOR ONE!
Official Hashtag #holoAllForOne
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!
Together, we’re all for one!