(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live On the Run!
It's Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME
Show your hype, share your thoughts, and ask Ollie about hololive production events in New York!
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
Official Hashtag #holoAllforOne
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
In-Stock Merch July 18th (EDT)
Made-to-Order Merch Sales Period: August 3rd - September 8th (EDT)
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
On the Run! hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live
It's Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME!
Show your hype, share your thoughts,
and ask Ollie about hololive production events in New York!
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait for a while until the performance starts.
Attention For Visitors
- Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
- Cheering loudly is ok.
In-Stock Merch: Essentials Pack (28 Types) ¥8,800 each
In-Stock Merch: Light Stick ¥4,800 / T-Shirt (L, XL) ¥4,000
Made-To-Order Merch: Random Button Badge ¥550
Made-To-Order Merch: Acrylic Stand Coaster (15 Types) ¥1,650
Made-To-Order Merch: Tapestry ¥3,300 / Acrylic Panel ¥4,400 / Mug ¥2,200
Made-To-Order Merch: Happi ¥7,480
I am supporting hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
On the Run! hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live
Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
The concert will be starting soon. #holoAllForOne
Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
In-Stock Merch: Essentials Pack
In-Stock Merch: Light Stick, T-Shirt
Made-to-Order Merch: Random Button Badge
Made-to-Order Merch: Acrylic Stand Coaster
Made-to-Order Merch: Tapestry, Acrylic Panel, Mug
Made-to-Order Merch: Happi
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE Fan Support Messages
ALL FOR ONE x HYTE Pre-order today at hyte.co/allforone
Every order has a chance to get a rare version of the set!
Pre-order today at hyte.co/allforone
WAH! Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening.
It's me Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert!
I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun sharing all the
great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time,
but I still get excited every time I'll spot
something WAHnderful on AmiAmi
- it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi on AmiAmi
be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you
for everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, Thank You AmiAmi!
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
Made-to-Order Merch
Sales Period 10 PM August 3rd - 5 AM September 8th (EDT)
Tapestry ¥3,300 | Acrylic Panel ¥4,400 | Mug ¥2,200
Happi ¥7,480
hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live On the Run!
It's Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME
Show your hype, share your thoughts, and ask Ollie about hololive production events in New York!
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
In-Stock Merch Essentials Pack (28 Types) ¥8,800 each
Light Stick ¥4,800 / T-Shirt ¥4,000
Made-To-Order Merch Random Button Badge ¥550
Acrylic Stand Coaster (15 Types) ¥1,650
Tapestry ¥3,300 / Acrylic Panel ¥2,200 / Mug ¥2,200
Happi ¥7,480
[Fan Messages Montage]
hololive English
EN ALL FOR ONE
All For One!
hololive English 3rd Concert
ALL FOR ONE
All For One!
Mori Calliope
Mori Calliope / Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis
Hakos Baelz
IRyS / Ouro Kronii / Hakos Baelz
Shiori Novella
Nerissa Ravencroft
Shiori Novella / Nerissa Ravencroft / Koseki Bijou
Mococo Abyssgard / Fuwawa Abyssgard
Gigi Murin
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame / Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen / Raora Panthera
Welcome to hololive English 3rd Concert,
All for One!
Let's start with a bang!
Just look around and see,
it's so incredible
So many smiles in the sea of lights
Take one step with me,
and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom,
my heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter
because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud,
our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together reaching up
for far and wide
And suddenly you're here by my side
When our voices in hearts unite,
we're gonna shine bright
Together we're all for one,
let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one,
let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day,
the rest of our lives (Hey!)
All that we waited for,
the dream we're striving toward
We're singing all for one! All for one!
Everything's in motion,
get up and start the celebration
Come see the wonders here
beyond imagination
You're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom zoom zoom,
my heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy world when dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud,
our time is right now
We're here together finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here
that words cannot convey
Hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly our hearts beat as one
Every voice singing loud and clear,
so glad to be here together,
we're all for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in 'cause it's all for one,
let's sing! All for one!
Turn up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night, the rest of our lives (Hey!)
Raise up your hands and sway,
your light will lead our way
We're shining all for one! All for one!
Bringing you memories, joy, and hope
We'll gather and sing of an endless light
Feel the music in your passion,
it's all right here right now
So let the good times roll
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams
One, two, three, four, five!
When our voices in hearts unite,
we're gonna shine bright
Together we're all for one,
let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one,
let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day,
the rest of our lives (Hey!)
All that we waited for,
the dream we're striving toward
We're singing all for one! All for one!
Time to open up your eyes
Hear the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
Livin' my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep advancing in my abandonment
Oh oh oh
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Oh oh oh
Now pay attention 'cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis!
Come and see, break some habit
How do you like this bad news?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers are banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginning, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Midnight, drive me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I may have in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
Ah, ah, ah
You can start a wave when I misbehave, take center stage
At the box office, but you know I'm gonna get insane
No holds on smokin'
The rules can all be broken
And running on a rampage
The world is a blank page
Let's go!
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
They're gonna know me by name
Ah, ah, ah
Is this my bottom line?
The future's in my hand
Ah, ah, ah
But they don't understand
That I'm designing, making, awaking and taking
Around, round, round, round
Tell me how you like me now
Come on!
Shout! Shout! Shout! Shout!
Can you watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your voice go, gonna show you how to lose control
Ready?
You got the 3, 2, 1
Keep your restraint on high
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is
It's our genesis!
Open up your eyes, feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
Point to who was meant to be
Living life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
As this is our beginning
It's our genesis!
Whispers are banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginning, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Midnight, drive me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
Our urban extraction
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is
Yeah, you know what time it is
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is
さあ 散らばってしまった話を
Now, for the story that has been scattered
空に手を伸ばし始める
I'll begin to reach my hands toward the sky
知った おどろきすぎる禍々しさに
Knowing the overwhelming and ominous surprise
縛られた足をくすぐるの
Tickling my bound feet
ああ 落ちて汚れた意識を
Ah, the consciousness that fell and became tainted
名前と筒抜けにかき消して
Drowning it out completely with a name
混ぜた呪いと祈り
Mixed curses and prayers,
絡める愛を
with an entwining love.
始まりと終わりに向かって
Heading towards the beginning and the end,
海に還って来るのは 波の飛沫 越えただけ
returning to the sea, just crossing the spray of the waves.
貴方そこにいたら教えて欲しいの
If you are there, I want you to tell me,
私があることの道はどんな色だろう
what color is the path of my existence?
ああ、この調べの旋律を
Ah, this melody's tune,
空に手を伸ばし始める
I begin to reach my hand to the sky.
散らばる砂漠の血の道が
The scattered blood path of the desert
愛を貪り そして泣き叫んでる
devours love and screams out.
始まりと終わりに向かって
Heading towards the beginning and the end,
海に還って来るのは 救わなかった君の声
returning to the sea is your voice that wasn't saved.
愛しい 今度こそそこにいたら教えて
My beloved, if you're there this time, tell me.
君の手をいつかまた握れるの？ この...
Will I be able to hold your hand again someday? This...
I'm good! Okay! I'm good!
Ina! Hello!
It's finally time! We are here!
We are here!
Ha... Well, shall we?
We shall. You go first.
I go first?
You go first.
Okay.
You know the drill, guys!
I say Wah, you say Wah!
WAH! WAH! WAH!
Good morning, afternoon, evening! This is Ninomae Ina'nis of hololive English!
You got this! You got this!
I just did my song, I'm so tired...
Okay, and we have...
WHAT'S UP!
I am Chaos, the embodiment of a stillness trapped in a cage of ice!
Your world-wide idol rat, Hakos Baelz of hololive English Promise!
WITNESS ME!
Guys! How was that for an opener?
Did you guys enjoy it?
I can't hear you!
And of course, everyone watching from home. Hello!
We see you guys!
Hello, hello, hello...
We have arrived at EN 3rd Live All For One!
Yeah!
Ina, how do you feel?
I feel fantastic.
You know, I can't believe it's already the third live!
First, we connected the world...
...Second, we broke the dimension...
...And third, we are...
All for One!
So you guys liked it? I guess this is the first time
we're all together performing "All for One"!
Yeah!
Oh man, I almost cried.
I know! You and I were like, "Uuuuuh!"
Oh my god, so emotional.
So emotional.
But I hope you guys enjoyed the opener.
We had... we had Advent.
Yes!
And we had... we had Ina solo!
It was so good! Did you guys like it?
Oh my goodness! All right!
You know, since it is the very... is the first...
...is the first MC of the first MC of the first...
on the first day.
We're just getting started.
We need to test those penlights!
Yeah, test the penlights!
See if they work!
How about we split down the middle here?
Split down the middle.
And we go... Violet... no, not Purple... Violet here!
It keeps on taking, okay?
It's Violet here and Red over here!
Hello over here! I want to see Red!
Yeah!
Oh my god! So cool!
Oh my goodness! Look! Oh my god,
I always get so emotional seeing the penlights.
And yeah, you know... not only that,
we're just getting started.
There's the whole show, today and tomorrow.
So make sure to share it with everyone,
share your excitement
with hashtag #holoAllforOne!
Post it! Yeah!
Oh man, exciting.
Wait, what are we to do next part?
Do I get to do the next part?
Fine, let you do it this time.
Yay!
Okay. Although it is kind of sad news.
Wait, wait, no, it's just... I've never done it before.
I'm really excited.
She's excited, but it's not... it's kind of sad because...
...it is now time to announce that...
I have terrible news!
Oh, what is it, Hakos Baelz?
Unfortunately, if you are watching from home...
...this is the end of the free segment!
How could this be? Absolutely distraught!
This is a tragedy!
But do not worry!
If you are at home and you just saw this banger
of an opening...
...and you want to continue watching the rest
of the concert...
...check the link in the description, get your tickets,
and continue watching the concert!
Yeah!
Not you guys! You guys are stuck here until the end,
all right?
You're not going anywhere.
All right, guys better be ready with your unlimited energy!
Yeah, I think we should, you know, get a test a little bit.
Are you guys ready? Ready!
All right, you know the drill.
Do I know the drill? You know the drill.
I know the drill. Believe that's it.
Anyways! All right, on the count of...
countdown from three!
Three, two, one, All for One!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Cecilia Immergreen
Gigi Murin
Raora Panthera
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！