(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
hololive Indonesia 1st Generation
Mini 3D Live Stream
デン・デレン・デレン・パパパパ・パパパパ・パパパパ・ハァー！
Den deren deren papapapa papapapa papapapa haaa!
Wuaaah! Semuanya!
Whoa! Everyone!
Halo semuanya!
Hello everyone!
Hai!
Hi!
Wah banyak nih, wah!
Whoa, there are so many!
Wah banyak nih! Halo!
Whoa, there are so many! Hello!
Kita baca lho!
We're reading the chat, you know!
Iya nih!
Yeah!
Wih banyak nih, lucu banget ah...
Wow, there are so many, so cute...
Kita tuh habis jalan-jalan tau,
Jepang tuh seru banget ya ternyata.
We just went on a trip, you know,
Japan is really fun after all.
Iya bener!
Yeah, true!
Kalian sempat lihat apa aja?
Makan apa aja? Huuu...
What did you guys get to see?
What did you eat? Ooooh...
Banyak banget!
A lot!
Oleh-olehnya juga banyak! Ihiii!
There are many souvenirs too! Tee-hee!
Tadi ketemu siapa kita? Ketemu siapa?
Who did we meet earlier? Who did we meet?
Ketemu Bapak!
Met Father!
Ketemu Yagoo! Waaa!
Met Yagoo! Waaa!
Tadi ketemu Bapak Yagoo, tau gak?
We met Father Yagoo earlier, you know?
Yeee! Datang-datang, wiiih!
Yay! Just arrived, wooo!
そうですね...
That's right...
Terus ketemu Abachaa sama E-chan.
Then we met Abachaa and E-chan.
Tadi kita tuh apa ya, ngobrol-ngobrol gitu
ditanya gitu kan,
Earlier we were, how should I put it,
chatting and being asked,
“Wah apa nih yang poin-poin penting
dari stream kalian?” gitu.
“What are the important points
of your stream?” like that.
Charm point kalian! Gitu...
Your charm point! Like that...
Makanya, beuh keren deh,
kalian harus tau nanti ya.
That's why, whoa it's cool,
you guys have to see it later.
Sebelum kita ngomong charm point,
perkenalan dulu ya.
Before we talk about charm point,
let's introduce ourselves first.
Apa sih? Em... formalitas-formalitas.
What is it? Um... formalities.
Formalitas? Oh ya.
Formalities? Oh yeah.
Siapa dulu nih?
Who's first?
Dari tengah, Moona?
From the center, Moona?
Oh ya udah deh, dari Moona.
Oh okay then, from Moona.
Oke, idol agak-agak... rada idol dulu ya. Oke.
Okay, idol-ish... being a bit like an idol first. Okay.
Moon-moon, Moona Hoshinova!
Halo Indonesia, 1期生のムーナ・ホシノヴァです！
Hello Indonesia, I'm 1st gen Moona Hoshinova!
はい！
Hi!
Trus, Risu!
Next, Risu!
Hai hai, Puru-puru, Kamban-risu!
Hi hi, Puru-puru, Kamban-risu!
Halo hololive Indonesia no 1期生です、
Hello, I'm hololive Indonesia 1st gen,
Ayunda Risu houuuu!
Ayunda Risu hooo!
Yaharyaa! Obisaa!
hololive Indonesia 1期生、アイラニ・イオフイフティーンです！
hololive Indonesia 1st gen, I'm Airani Iofifteen!
よろしくお願いします！
Please be kind to me!
Ih sexy! Oh sexy! Oh sexy!
So sexy! Oh sexy! Oh sexy!
Ambo aku... aku... ini ditayangin apa sih...
Take mine... I... what is being shown...
Aku ada titipan buat Ollie nih,
Ollie ya buat kamu ya, nih.
I have something for Ollie,
Ollie this is for you, here.
Kita titipan ini semua aja nih!
Let's just give all of this!
Ya udah semuanya aja deh.
Nih Ollie buat kamu ya, Ollie.
Okay let's just give all of it.
Here Ollie, this is for you, Ollie.
Oke, thank you. Oke.
Okay, thank you. Okay.
Also, before we start, as usual there is hashtag
#Area15Mini3DLive!
Jadi buat kalian yang mau screenshot,
yang mau komen,
So for those of you who want to take screenshots,
or want to comment,
bisa di hashtag #Area15Mini3DLive.
you can use the hashtag #Area15Mini3DLive.
Gampang guys, tinggal kopas.
It's easy guys, just copy-paste.
It's so easy! It's so easy!
Just use the hashtag #Area15Mini3DLive
for the screenshot
and anything you want to talk about really.
Jadi hari ini kita stream apa sih?
Kita sebenarnya stream mini,
So what are we streaming today?
We're actually streaming a mini,
mini, mini ya, mini.
mini, mini, yeah, mini live.
We're gonna do a mini 3D, yeah mini.
Kita mau...
We want to...
...Tri mini, 3D Live ya guys, mini-mini ya pokoknya.
...Tri-mini, 3D Live guys, it's just a mini one.
Jadi ini karena namanya tuh mini, ini tuh namanya bukan real konser.
So because it's called mini, this isn't a real concert.
Jadi tuh ini kayak apa ya, versi mini and dancing and having fun at the same time.
So this is like, a mini version and dancing and having fun at the same time.
So basically this is a fun singing stream.
Karaoke in 3D!
Karaoke in 3D.
Jadi gini nih sama-sama kan nyanyi, bakal nendang, bakal berko- oh gak kita komedi hari ini.
So here we are singing together, we'll kick, we'll- oh no, we're doing comedy today.
Bakal ber-idol ria.
We'll be idling around.
Yes, kita tuh bakal...
Yes, we will...
Apa nih? Mmm... menunjukkan...
What is it? Mmm... showing...
...apa ya, potensi-potensi bernyanyi.
...what is it, singing potentials.
Potensi! Siapa tahu gitu...
Potentials! Who knows...
...siapa tahu ya, abis kita menunjukkan yang mini ini...
...who knows, after we show this mini one...
...potensi kita nyanyi sama potensi kita dance, kita bisa dapat yang lebih, yang bukan mini.
...our singing and dancing potential, we might get something more, something not mini.
Iya, kita dapet yang beneran!
Yes, we'll get the real one!
Yang beneran!
The real one!
Yang lebih besar guys, yang lebih besar!
Something bigger guys, something bigger!
Besar!
Big!
Yang lebih besar lagi!
Something even bigger!
Besar!
Big!
Lagi itu juga guys...
Also that guys...
Terus nih, kan kita ada 3D nih, 3D...
And then, we have 3D, 3D...
...First Generation hololive Indonesia 3D!
Bagaimana kesan dan pesan kalian?
What are your impressions and thoughts?
Karena kita tuh ya, kita tuh ya biasanya tuh kan cuman...
Because we, we usually only...
...apa sih, cuman kepala doang.
...what is it, only heads.
Goyang-goyang waku-waku.
Shaking and getting excited.
Dan sekarang tuh, sekarang full body gitu loh!
And now, it's full body!
Full body!
How's your impression of your 3D, your own 3D live?
Ada aku!
Me first!
You first.
Aku pokoknya intinya senang deh bisa ini nih, gerakin tangan nih!
Basically, I'm just happy to be able to do this, move my hands!
Kan kalau joget biasa kan oke lah.
Regular dancing is fine.
Tapi kan kalau pakai apa sih, apa ini namanya? Sign language kan cuman boleh ini nih...
But when using what is it, what's it called? Sign language, you could only do this...
...di rumah susah guys.
...it's hard at home, guys.
Jadi Yopi mau apa sih, ngajarin kalian dikit aja.
So Yopi wants to, teach you guys just a little bit.
Oke, so American Sign Language, "thank you" is like this.
Okay, so American Sign Language, "thank you" is like this.
Put your chin here, "thank you".
Di dagu ya guys, di dagu.
On the chin, guys, on the chin.
Di dagu ya guys ya, dagu.
On the chin guys, chin.
Itu-itu nggak kayak dagu.
That-that doesn't look like a chin.
Chin, here! It is chin in 3D, okay?
Indonesia juga thank you-nya sama. Indonesia "terima kasih" juga di dagu, sama.
In Indonesia, 'thank you' is also the same. 'Terima kasih' is also on the chin.
Iya, dagu.
Yes, chin.
Cuman bahasa Jepang beda. 日本語は違うんですけど、
But Japanese is different. Japanese is different, but...
日本語「ありがとう」はこれですね。
Japanese "thank you" is this.
だからせめてみんなに「ありがとう」言うね。Oke?
So at least I'll say thank you to everyone. Okay?
Arigato! I love you!
Thank you! I love you!
Next, Moona kalau gitu, Moona! Gimana nih gimana nih Moona?
Next, Moona then, Moona! How about it, Moona?
Ah, Moona senang banget!
Ah, Moona is so happy!
I'm so happy that finally I can show you how I'm dancing and singing at the same time.
Because usually when I do the MoonUtau, I usually, you know, singing...
...and my body just like want to moving, but you cannot see it.
...and my body just wants to move, but you can't see it.
And now, you can see it! So I'm really happy for that.
Yey! Mantap!
Yey! Great!
Mantap!
Great!
As for me, as for me I want to go a little bit to the front.
As for me, I want to go a little bit to the front.
Sumimasen kameraman.
Excuse me, cameraman.
Ah, this is hand.
Ah, this is a hand.
This is magic hand!
This is a magic hand!
Ini nih, oke.
This is it, okay.
Sumimasen.
Excuse me.
Sumimasen, sumimasen!
Excuse me, excuse me!
Jadi gitu deh, kita kan kemaren cuma nyanyi-nyanyi doang nih. Kita mau pose-pose nggak nih?
So that's how it is, yesterday we were just singing. Shall we do some poses?
Iya bener!
Yes, exactly!
Pose! Pose! Pose!
Mau pose apa nih teman-teman?
What pose do you want us to do, friends?
What do you want, like what kind of pose you want to request us?
What do you want, what kind of pose do you want to request?
Iya pose, mumpung bertiga nih, mumpung bertiga nih!
Yeah poses, while all three of us are here!
Oh, oh! Pahanya sangat glowing ya bestie, pahanya glowing sekali!
Oh, oh! Her thighs are so glowing bestie, her thighs are very glowing!
Sasuga desu ne.
As expected.
Sugoi!
Amazing!
Sasuga!
As expected!
Pose apa nih? Pose Jojo? Gimana? Nggak tahu.
What pose? Jojo pose? How do you do it? I don't know.
Pose Jojo!
Jojo pose!
Apa ya, apa ya?
What else, what else?
Apa? Mau pose gini guys? Kita baca kok, kita baca.
What? You want this pose guys? We're reading (the chat), we see it.
「T-pose」 itu gimana? 「T-pose」?
How do you do a 'T-pose'? 'T-pose'?
Katanya 「T-pose」.
They're asking for a 'T-pose'.
Oh anu-anu itu, apa sih perkenalan Sencho yang ampe gini loh...
Oh that one, what is it, Sencho's introduction that goes like this...
Gimana? Gimana?
How? How?
Hajimemashite desu!
Nice to meet you!
Desu! Desu!
Hajimemashite desu!
Nice to meet you!
Yei!
Yey!
Ada yang ketagihan goyang kachinya kamu nih!
Someone is addicted to your 'kachi' dance!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Ada yang 「Pargoy」 itu gimana sih?
Someone asked for 'Pargoy', how do you do that?
Nggak tahu, Pargoy gimana ya?
I don't know, how is Pargoy?
Pargoy? Gini kali?
Pargoy? Like this maybe?
Lupa, nggak tahu guys, gini...
I forgot, I don't know guys, like this...
Pergi... apa-apa yang gini apa sih? Yang gini?
Go... what is this? What is this one?
Oh! Eh jongkok bareng kan kita kemarin cuman berdua yang ini.
Oh! Hey, let's squat together, yesterday it was just the two of us doing this.
Sini sini sini!
Come here, come here!
Se!
One!
Hei! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Gak bisa turun-turun ya guys ya.
Can't go lower, guys.
Segini aja.
Just this much.
Waduh beliau ini...
Oh, this person...
Beliau ini sungguh sekali.
This person is really something.
Apalagi nih dari tadi nggak...
What else? Since earlier we haven't...
Apa ya? Apa ya?
What is it? What is it?
The Box Slay!
Slay! Slay!
Aing... apa nih apa nih? Ngapain ngapain?
I... what's this? What should we do?
Yagoo... nice!
Terus selanjutnya... waduh waduh ini nih.
Next... oh boy, this one.
Kita ngapain lagi nih? Apa ya? Panjang banget.
What are we doing again? What is it? It's so long.
Iya apa ya?
Yeah, what is it?
Kita harus begini.
We have to do this.
Ya udah deh, kita kan udah mau gerak nih.
Alright, we're about to move.
Ada game nggak hari ini?
Is there a game today?
Harusnya sih ada! Harusnya sih ada!
There should be! There should be!
Kita kan udah nunjukin badan-badan kita nih aslinya kayak gimana.
We've shown our bodies, what they really look like.
Sayang banget nggak sih kalau cuma ngobrol doang?
Wouldn't it be a waste if we just talked?
Gimana kalau misalnya kita bikin game?
How about we play a game?
Nice! Boleh!
Nice! Sure!
Skuy lah! Are you guys ready for the game?
Let's go! Are you guys ready for the game?
Yes!
Jjeng jjeng!
Tada!
なりきりトーク対決! Roleplay Talk Showdown!
Roleplay Talk Showdown!
Apa nih? Roleplay Talk Showdown!
What's this? Roleplay Talk Showdown!
Siapa nih yang kira-kira aktingnya paling jago?
Who do you think is the best at acting?
Siapa ya? Nggak tahu!
Who? I don't know!
Biasanya ya kalau yang sering bikin konten nih...
Usually, those who make content often...
Nah, Risu nih paling jago ya.
Well, Risu is the best.
Tapi berbeda 2D sama 3D.
But 2D and 3D are different.
Ih kan bisa pakai body language sekarang.
Hey, you can use body language now.
Ya, jadi pada acara kali ini...
So, in this event...
Peserta harus mendalami karakter yang diberikan.
Participants must immerse themselves in the given character.
Jadi kita ngobrolnya tuh sekitar 2 menit lah.
So we'll talk for about 2 minutes.
Cukup kan ya? 2 menit?
Is that enough? 2 minutes?
Cukuplah! Gampang kan ya?
That's enough! It's easy, right?
Jadi mulai aja kali ya?
So, should we just start?
Ok!
Tema pertama! Jjeng jjeng!
First theme! Tada!
お題 赤ちゃんで、日本で食べた美味しかったもの Act like a baby, talk about delicious food you ate in Japan
Theme: Act like a baby, talk about delicious food you ate in Japan
Wih apa nih? Act like a baby...
Whoa, what's this? Act like a baby...
...talk about delicious food you ate in Japan.
Akachan de... jadi ngomong kayak bayi...
Like a baby... so talk like a baby...
...terus ngomongin makanan yang kalian makan di Jepang.
...and then talk about the food you ate in Japan.
Nah!
Alright!
Aaa... atsu... ano... omama... onene...
Aaa... hot... um... food... sleep...
Enen... itai desu... oppai... ha?
Milk... it hurts... milk... huh?
Mama... Moona... eto... I...
Mama... Moona... um... I...
...eto I eat a lot of food...
...um I eat a lot of food...
...I eat a lot of food lately and it was...
...tamagoyaki! Tamagoyaki kana?
...tamagoyaki! Tamagoyaki, I guess?
Wakaranai yo, demo... oishii!
I don't know, but... it's delicious!
Achinna! Achinna! Achinna!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Anone, atashi no ichiban no... kore oishii desho?
You know, my favorite... this is delicious, right?
Atashi ne... ichiban... ano... daisuki na tabemono ne...
Me... my most... um... favorite food...
Anou... achi! Awublublublu... chokopan!
Um... hot! Awublublublu... chocolate bread!
Chokopan! Atishite!
Chocolate bread! Me!
Uwah! Chokopan oishii yo deitai desho!
Uwah! Chocolate bread is delicious, right!
Itai wai! Itai wai! Hai!
It hurts! It hurts! Yes!
Hoi! Itai deshu!
Hoi! It hurts!
Chokopan oishii... itai na...
Chocolate bread is delicious... it hurts...
Itai itai itai itai deshu! Itai deshu! Itai deshu!
It hurts it hurts it hurts it hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Are... are wa nan desuka?
What... what is that?
Kore wa nanda? Oden desu ne.
What is this? It's oden.
Anone, kino ne... kino janakute sa...
You know, yesterday... not yesterday...
Ano sa, kono suujitsu mae ni... kore konnyaku ne.
Um, a few days ago... this is konnyaku.
Moona ni agetan dakedo, Moona ga 'umm umm' tte ittanda kedo...
I gave it to Moona, and Moona said 'umm umm'...
Yoppinne kekko suki da yo kore ga.
Yoppin really likes this.
Atashi mo kimi no koto suki da yo!
I like you too!
Ah! Atsu! Honto? Atashi mo...
Ah! Hot! Really? Me too...
Odeshu... nakayochi deshu!
It's oden... we're close friends!
Dou desuka? Dou desuka?
How is it? How is it?
Atashi nakayoshi daisuki na no! Suki!
I love being close friends! I love it!
Atashi suki-suki na no kore oden.
I love this oden.
Aaa! Itai deshu! Mada sabetai no deshu!
Aaa! It hurts! I still want to eat!
Owattane! Bye!
It's over! Bye!
Ah mou! Itai deshu! Ah mou!
Ah, geez! It hurts! Ah, geez!
Alright, so... that's about it.
We're baby! We're baby!
Gimana? Seru nggak sih? Seru nggak sih?
How was it? Was it fun? Was it fun?
Susah sih... pokoknya kalau sama Moona ya sulit rasanya.
It's hard... anyway, if it's with Moona, it feels difficult.
Kenapa sulit?
Why is it difficult?
Mau ngomong apa? Dia udah pro dari tadi, dari tadi dia udah pro.
What to say? She's been a pro since earlier, she's been a pro since earlier.
Tapi nih kita tanya nih mumpung banyak yang ke sini.
But let's ask, since many are here.
Kita tanya nih ke komentar nih. Komen, komen! Siapa nih?
Let's ask the comments. Comment, comment! Who is it?
Gimana menurut kalian? Kalian paling suka pas bagian mana?
What do you think? Which part did you like the most?
Yes! Bagian mana?
Yes! Which part?
Ada? Ada? Siapa nih?
Anyone? Anyone? Who is it?
Oh ada bagian pas 'cucu'nya tuh suka.
Oh, someone liked the milk part.
Cucu! Mama cucu! Mama cucu!
Milk! Mom, milk! Mom, milk!
Mampus, mampus!
Oh no, oh no!
Namanya juga itu ya, begitulah.
That's just how it is, I guess.
Oke, oke deh.
Okay, okay then.
Kalau gitu aman nggak, guys? Aman nggak ya?
Is it safe then, guys? Is it safe?
Aman, aman.
It's safe, it's safe.
Udah ya.
That's it.
Ada lagi nggak? Ada lagi nggak?
Anything else? Anything else?
Lanjut.
Moving on.
Oke, next game!
Okay, next game!
お題：ヤンキーで、お互いの3Dの身体で好きなポイント
Topic: Act like delinquents, talk about favorite parts of your Genmates' 3D bodies.
Act like a street delinquent, talk about favorite parts on your Genmates' 3D bodies.
Okay, guys, ready? Ready?
We both, we're ready!
Start! Start!
You know, guys... Jadi, guys...
You know, guys... So, guys...
So I, I saw... Do you know...
...you know Reine, right?
Reine... her body unit! Woah!
Woah! Really, really!
Oh my God, bohay!
Oh my God, curvaceous!
Anjay! Tahu nggak? Tahu nggak? Tahu nggak?
Damn! Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Yang bohay lagi, Kaela!
Another curvaceous one, Kaela!
Oh my God, Kaela! Sis, tahu nggak? Tahu nggak?
Oh my God, Kaela! Sis, do you know? Do you know?
Lihat bajunya itu, anjir!
Look at her clothes, damn!
It's so crazy! Gila!
It's so crazy! Insane!
Stop, stop, guys. Selain itu, we have a lot...
Stop, stop, guys. Besides that, we have a lot...
...we have a lot of members...
...that have a really nice body, you know!
That... that is the most... chef's kiss.
Gimana, gimana? Chef's kiss?
How is it? Chef's kiss?
You know, you know, I have one... one of my favorite...
Her name is Iofifteen!
Kenapa? Kenapa?!
Why? Why?!
Her... her bottom! Woah!
Sugoi! Sugoi! Sugoi!
Incredible! Incredible! Incredible!
Eh, ada Moona, Moona!
Hey, there's Moona, Moona!
Woah! This... this is so sugoi!
My bestie, sugoi!
Gitu kan, yankee?
That's how it is, right, delinquents?
Kayak yankee, kita kurang garang gitu.
Like delinquents, we're not fierce enough.
Kurang garang gimana dong?
How are we not fierce enough then?
Ada yang panjang!
There's something long!
I know! I don't think that...
Gimana?!
What about this?!
Gimana, guys? Gimana?
How was it, guys? How?
What do you guys think of the acting?
Gimana? Oke?
How was it? Okay?
Punggung... pelindung siapa?
Back... whose protector?
Okay, thank you!
Sugoi, sugoi! So thank you...
...since it's sugoi, so I think...
...we try... maybe one more?
One more, guys? Ready?
Ready! Ready!
お題：みこ先輩風で、今後3人でやりたいこと
Topic: Act like Miko-senpai, talk about future plans as holoID Gen 1.
Act like Miko-senpai, talk about future plans as holoID Gen 1.
Sebentar... Miko-senpai itu gimana ngomongnya?
Wait... how does Miko-senpai talk?
One, two, three, start!
Annya! Annya! Aris kawaii desho!
Annya! Annya! Aris is cute, right!
Nye... next year I want... I want to try live...
...Ito kawaii desho?
...That's cute, right?
Next year I want, I want to try live... nye!
I can talk... I can talk elite! Elite Miko talk!
Faq you! Faq you! Faq you is love!
Next year! Next year!
Next year, live concert holoID Gen 1, nye!
Nye... nye... Yopi pun sana...
Nye... nye... Yopi will also be there...
...tote kuru nye...
...bring it, nye...
Nani ga ii nye?
What's good, nye?
Freedom!
Next year ID nye... Next year...
...I want to eat more rice, nye!
Next year, we are doing a live 3D, nye!
Freedom! Freedom! Let's hope, nye!
Eli-chan, Eli-chan! Mona will come.
Nice, nice.
Not promise.
Not a promise.
Wah kayaknya... kayaknya ini masih ada... masih ada satu lagi nih.
Wow, it seems... it seems there's still... there's still one more.
Boleh.
Sure.
Last one! One more!
Yes! Last one!
One more! One more! One more!
Tada!
お題
Topic
オーバーリアクションで、ホロライブに入って良かったこと
Exaggerated reactions: Things you're glad for after joining Hololive
Okay. Using exaggerated reactions, talk about what made you thankful for being in Hololive.
Risu, Risu... apa... "exaggerated" itu apa?
Risu, Risu... what's... what's "exaggerated"?
Lebay!
Over-the-top!
Lebay! Okay, siap?
Over-the-top! Okay, ready?
One, two, three, start!
Sebenarnya teman-teman, Risu sangat bahagia bisa berada di Hololive! Sebenarnya, aku sangat bahagia!
Actually everyone, Risu is very happy to be in Hololive! Actually, I'm very happy!
Sebenarnya Moona itu... bahagia banget!
Actually, Moona is... very happy!
You know, hopping like this and dancing like this, it's so... wow!
Yeah, thank you! We are so happy! I'm so happy!
I'm so grateful to be in Japan! Thank you!
Yagoo! Yagoo-sama! Thank you!
Yagoo! Master Yagoo! Thank you!
Terima kasih Yagoo! Yagoo! Yagoo!
Thank you Yagoo! Yagoo! Yagoo!
Yagoo! Yagoo! Arigato Yagoo!
Yagoo! Yagoo! Thank you Yagoo!
Thank you!
Selfie dulu sama bapak, selfie dulu sama bapak.
Let's take a selfie with the boss, a selfie with the boss.
Selfie! Aku di mana?
Selfie! Where am I?
Selfie dulu sama bapak!
Selfie first with the boss!
Yagoo!
Aku dong, aku dong, aku mau!
Me too, me too, I want one!
Oh mau, ya udah, ya udah. Gimana?
Oh you want to? Okay, okay. How?
Cheese!
Thank you all of you, Bapak! Yes, thank you Yagoo!
Thank you all of you, Boss! Yes, thank you Yagoo!
Abai... abai ka na? Daijoubu.
Is it... is it weird? It's fine.
Habis guys. Bagaimana performa kita tadi?
That's it guys. How was our performance just now?
Gimana guys? Memuaskan? What do you guys think?
How was it guys? Satisfying? What do you guys think?
Siapa nih yang paling jago acting-nya? The one that really good at acting?
Who was the best at acting? The one that's really good at acting?
Who has the best acting?
Saya? The best acting? Saya?
Me? The best acting? Me?
A-chan? A-chan? Saya! Saya!
A-chan? A-chan? Me! Me!
Yagoo! Kenapa Yagoo?
Yagoo! Why Yagoo?
Kok Yagoo sih?
Why Yagoo?
Yagoo cuma nungguin.
Yagoo was just waiting.
Dia cuma lagi ngintip. Iya nih.
He was just peeping. Yeah.
Risu katanya, oh Moona juga, Lofi... Yagoo... Yagoo-nya ngintip.
They're saying Risu, oh Moona too, Lofi... Yagoo... Yagoo is peeping.
Sepertinya pemenangnya Yagoo ya. Acting talk battle ini dimenangkan oleh Yagoo!
It seems the winner is Yagoo. This acting talk battle is won by Yagoo!
Omedetou! Omedetou! Omedetou!
Congratulations! Congratulations! Congratulations!
Wah kaget, tahu nggak sih, dia kayak...
Wow I'm surprised, you know, he's like...
Namanya idol itu...
When it comes to idols...
The best girl pasti jago acting.
The best girl must be good at acting.
Bener! Best girl jago acting.
Right! Best girl is good at acting.
Akushing desu. Yeah.
Acting. Yeah.
Kalau gitu kita udah gerak-gerak nih. Kita udah ngomong banyak.
In that case, we've moved around a lot. We've talked a lot.
Tapi ini masih ada lagi nih. Still have something, so we want to prepare.
But there's still more. We still have something, so we want to prepare.
Yes, don't go anywhere. My eyes on you.
Yes, don't go anywhere. My eyes are on you.
Don't forget the hashtag!
Yes, the hashtag #Area15Mini3DLive. Don't forget!
Byebye! Jaa ne! Ayoo!
Bye-bye! See ya! Let's go!
Karena kita udah di kantor...
Because we're already in the office...
...berarti kita tuh udah officially gitu.
...it means we're officially, like,
Officially gitu, officially menjadi...
Officially, like, officially becoming...
...anggota.
...members.
Anggota!
Members!
Tapi males ah kalau di kantor...
But I'm lazy if we're in the office...
...nanti kita disuruh kerja, aku nggak mau.
...later we'll be told to work, I don't want to.
Iya sih, bener juga sih.
Yeah, that's true.
Terus kita mau ngapain di kantor? Bosan.
Then what are we going to do in the office? Boring.
Nggak usah, nggak usah di kantor, bosan.
No need, no need to be in the office, boring.
Ke kamar aja, kamar siapa kek gitu.
Let's go to a room, anyone's room.
Aku capek.
I'm tired.
Oh, tapi... tapi masih mau di sini.
Oh, but... but I still want to be here.
Iya masih sih, ah...
Yeah, still, ah...
Kalau... kalau misalnya kamar, mana ya?
If... if it's a room, where?
Kayaknya kamar-kamar Moona boleh tuh.
I think Moona's room would be good.
Hah? Mau! Mau!
Huh? I want to! I want to!
Ya! Joss, let's go!
Yes! Great, let's go!
Ya udah, let's go!
Alright, let's go!
Wah, akhirnya!
Whoa, finally!
Yeay! Wuih!
Yeay! Whoa!
Kamarnya bagus sekali!
The room is very nice!
Inilah kamar Moona.
This is Moona's room.
Yey!
Yay!
Mana-mana? Gajah?
Where is it? Elephant?
Oh iya belum. Gajah!
Oh yeah, not yet. Elephant!
Gajah nggak ada sih.
There's no elephant.
Nggak ada sih, miskin.
There isn't one, I'm poor.
Nanti besok pecahin celengan, ganti lho ya.
Break the piggy bank tomorrow, replace it, okay.
Aduh, mohon maaf.
Oh, sorry.
Iya, iya, nanti ditagih.
Yes, yes, I'll bill you later.
Mana tahu di kamar Iofi ada.
Who knows, maybe Iofi's room has one.
Oh gitu.
Is that so.
Tapi bener dulu, mau lihat dulu deh, ini ada apa sih?
But seriously, I want to see first, what's in here?
Jadi... jadi ini ada tempat tidur.
So... so here's a bed.
He-eh, ini tempat tidurnya Moona.
Uh-huh, this is Moona's bed.
Terus di situ tempat... tebak apa hayo?
And there's the... guess what?
Tempat apa?
What place?
PC-lah, PC!
The PC, the PC!
Tempat kita main macam-macam.
A place for us to play various things.
I say!
Hey, hey, hey, START:DASH!!
産声の小鳥たちも
Even the newborn baby birds
いつか空に羽ばたく
Will one day flap their wings into the sky
大きな強い翼で
With big, strong wings
飛ぶ
They'll fly
諦めちゃだめなんだ
You mustn't give up
その日が絶対来る
That day will surely come
君も感じてるよね
You feel it too, don't you?
始まりの鼓動
The heartbeat of a beginning
明日よ変われ！
Tomorrow, change!
希望に変われ！
Change into hope!
眩しい光に
In the dazzling light
照らされて変われ！
Be illuminated and change!
START!!
悲しみに閉ざされて
Locked in sadness
泣くだけの君じゃない
You're not someone who only cries
熱い胸　きっと未来を
Your hot heart will surely
切り拓くはずさ
Carve out the future
悲しみに閉ざされて
Locked in sadness
泣くだけじゃつまらない
Crying alone is no fun
きっと　（きっと）
Surely (Surely)
君の　（夢の）
Your (Dream's)
チカラ　（いまを）
Power (Now)
信じてるよ　だから START!!
I believe in it, so START!!
Hey, hey, hey, START:DASH!!
雨上がりの気分で
With the feeling after the rain
高まる期待の中
In the midst of rising expectations
つまずいたことさえも
Even the things we stumbled on
思い出にしよう
Let's make them memories
明日が咲くよ！
Tomorrow will bloom!
希望が咲くよ！
Hope will bloom!
楽しいメロディ
A fun melody
口ずさみ咲こう！
Let's hum it and bloom!
DASH!!
喜びを受け止めて
Accept the joy
君と僕つながろう
Let's connect, you and I
迷い道　やっと外へ
The wandering path, finally out
抜け出したはずさ
We should have broken free
喜びを受け止めて
Accept the joy
君と僕進むだろう
We'll probably move forward, you and I
それは　（それは）
That's (That's)
遠い　（夢の）
A distant (Dream's)
かけら　（愛しい）
Fragment (Dear)
かなたへと　僕は DASH!!
Toward the distance, I DASH!!
またひとつ夢が生まれ...
Another dream is born...
悲しみに閉ざされて
Locked in sadness
泣くだけの君じゃない
You're not someone who only cries
熱い胸　きっと未来を
Your hot heart will surely
切り拓くはずさ
Carve out the future
DASH!!
...受け止めて
...accept it
君と僕 繋がろう
You and I, let's connect
迷い道 やっと外へ
From the maze, finally out
抜け出したはずさ
We must have escaped
喜びを受け止めて
Accept the joy
君と僕 進むだろう
You and I will move forward
それは
That is
熱い
A hot
夢の
dream's
欠片
fragment
輝き
Shining
彼方へと
towards the distance
僕はダッシュ
I'm dashing
Hey!
START:DASH!!
いけないボーダーライン
Forbidden Borderline
Lyrics 西直紀 Composition コモリタミノル
Lyrics: Naoki Nishi, Composition: Minoru Komorita
見つめ合って 恋をして
Looking at each other, falling in love
無我夢中で 追いかけて
Chasing frantically
だけど もっと知りたくて メラメラしてる
But I want to know more, I'm burning up
願うほどな 素顔で
With a face as honest as my wishes
想うほど 熱になる
The more I think, the hotter I get
だから もっと飛び込むの 未知の世界
So I'll dive further into the unknown world
恋とか
Like love
夢とか
Like dreams
誰でも 信じるけど
Anyone would believe in them
そこそこ 攻めなきゃつまらないよ
But it's boring if you don't push the limits
ギリギリ 愛 いけないボーダーライン
On the edge, love, the forbidden borderline
難易度Gでも 全て壊してみせる
Even at difficulty G, I'll show you I can break it all
ギリギリ 舞 さらなるGへと
On the edge, dance, towards an even higher G
意識が溶ける 体を制御不能な
Consciousness melts, my body is out of control
イッちゃうかもね
I might go all the way
叫び合った 友達と
With friends I've shouted with
求め合った あの人と
With that person I've sought
また会える 日のために ギラギラしてる
I'm dazzling for the day we meet again
光るほど 影はでき
The more it shines, the more shadows form
燃えるほど 灰になる
The more it burns, the more it turns to ash
走るほど 見えてくる 危ないライフ
The more I run, the more I see this dangerous life
自由も
Like freedom
平和も
Like peace
望めば 生まれるけど
They're born if you wish for them
もっと もっとしてたら腐っちゃうよ
But if you have too much, they'll rot away
ギリギリ 愛 危ないボーダーライン
On the edge, love, the dangerous borderline
非常事態なら 限界越して魅せる
In an emergency, I'll show you I can surpass limits
ギリギリ 舞 限界突破なら
On the edge, dance, if it's breaking through limits
塗り替えたい 破壊と再生 行こうわ
I want to rewrite destruction and rebirth, let's go
まだまだいける
I can still go further
ギリギリ 愛 いけないボーダーライン
On the edge, love, the forbidden borderline
難易度Gでも 全て壊してみせる
Even at difficulty G, I'll show you I can break it all
ギリギリ 舞 さらなるGへと
On the edge, dance, towards an even higher G
意識が溶ける 体を制御不能な
Consciousness melts, my body is out of control
イッちゃうかもね
I might go all the way
ギリギリ 愛 いけないボーダーライン
On the edge, love, the forbidden borderline
燃え尽きながら まだ輝いてみせる
While burning out, I'll show you I can still shine
ギリギリ 舞 あなたのために
On the edge, dance, for your sake
未来のために 何度だって咲いてしまう
For the sake of the future, I'll bloom again and again
抜け出すことで
By breaking out
生まれ変わる
I'll be reborn
愛したくて
Wanting to love
生きて帰る
I'll return alive
Dan-dan kokoro dan-dan atsuku
Step by step, my heart gets hotter and hotter
夢いっぱい叶えてみせる
I'll show you I can grant all my dreams
Dan-dan 進む Dan-dan はじける
Step by step, I move forward and burst out
未来をしっかり見てるよ
I'm looking straight at the future
(Hi! Hi! 進め!)
(Hi! Hi! Move forward!)
まだまだ Let's go!
Keep going, Let's go!
(Hi! Hi! 進め!)
(Hi! Hi! Move forward!)
ほらほら Let's go!
Come on, Let's go!
大事なことはなんだっけ? (なんだっけ?)
What was the important thing? (What was it?)
小さな努力 風をくるんだ
Small efforts wrapped in the wind
隙間を愛してぶつかろう (ぶつかろう)
Love the gaps and collide (Collide)
今夜良いですと一生懸命なんだよって
Tonight is good, I'm working my hardest
もっと近くで語り合いたいな
I want to talk more closely with you
熱い吐息見つめどこまで
Hot breaths, looking how far we've come
走っちゃってまで (走ればいいさ)
Even if we keep running (Just run)
限界きれない (Alright!)
No limits (Alright!)
これからの Wonderful Rush
From now on, Wonderful Rush
みんな幸せになるため
For everyone to become happy
新しい世界 探しに行こうよ
Let's go find a new world
迷ったら Wonderful Rush
If you get lost, Wonderful Rush
僕は輝きを信じて
I believe in the brilliance
遥か遠くの道だろう ぎゅっと掴んで
It's a path far away, so grab it tight
Unexpected な結晶
Unexpected crystal
お目掛けに急展開
A sudden turn of events right before your eyes
最大階? 最新式? (全部まとめて Super Jump!)
Highest floor? Newest style? (Bundle it all and Super Jump!)
なんだかどれも不思議だよ 楽しく感じる
Somehow everything is mysterious, it feels fun
この時は瞬間のようで永遠のようだね
This time feels like a moment, and an eternity
一緒に飛ぼう Dan-dan!
Let's fly together, step by step!
行くよ! もっとね!
Here we go! More!
小さな努力! そうだった!
Small efforts! That's right!
今が好きで! 愛なんだ!
Loving the now! It's love!
ぶつかるんだ! そんなんだ!
Colliding! That's how it is!
用意で! ずっと!
Get ready! Always!
一生懸命! そうじゃな!
Working hard! Isn't that right!
気を付けて! 大胆に!
Take care! Boldly!
一生懸命! Jump!
Working hard! Jump!
もっと気持ちを分かり合いたくて
I want to understand each other's feelings more
隣にいる君 いつでも
You, who are right beside me, anytime
一緒にいるから (一緒がいいね)
Because we're together (Together is good)
始まりの Wonderful Stage
The beginning of a Wonderful Stage
みんな次の場所探すんだ
Everyone is looking for the next place
誇りあう季節 新鮮な景色
A season to be proud of, a fresh landscape
Wonderful!
Wow! どうしようか? Dreamish come true!
10-sen Let's go! Dream 3 2 1 Zero!
Wow! What should we do? Dreamish come true!
Top speed Let's go! Dream 3 2 1 Zero!
Hi! Super Jump! Oh yeah! Bakka!
Lucky Jump! まだまだ Let's go!
Lucky Jump! Keep going, Let's go!
Hi! Super Jump! Oh yeah! Bakka!
Lucky Jump! Wonderful Rush! Hey!
もっと近くで語り合いたいな
I want to talk more closely with you
熱い吐息見つめどこまで
Hot breaths, looking how far we've come
走っちゃってまで (走ればいいさ)
Even if we keep running (Just run)
限界きれない (Alright!)
No limits (Alright!)
これからの Wonderful Rush
From now on, Wonderful Rush
みんな幸せになるため
For everyone to become happy
新しい世界 探しに行こうよ
Let's go find a new world
迷ったら Wonderful Rush
If you get lost, Wonderful Rush
僕は輝きを信じて
I believe in the brilliance
遥か遠くの道だから さあ出発だよ
Since it's a path far away, come on, it's time to start
みんな次の場所探すんだ
Everyone is looking for the next place
誇りあう季節 新鮮な景色
A season to be proud of, a fresh landscape
胸弾む Wonderful Stage
A heart-pounding Wonderful Stage
僕が歌うのはきれいな
What I'm singing is a beautiful song
遥か遠くの道だから さあ出発だよ
Since it's a path far away, come on, it's time to start
シャボン弾ける...
Bubbles bursting...
未来をしっかり見て
Look straight at the future
フー！ハイ！
Woo! Hai!
secret base 〜君がくれたもの〜
Lyrics・Composition 町田紀彦
secret base ~What You Gave Me~
Lyrics/Composition: Norihiko Machida
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢
The end of summer with you, dreams for the future
大きな希望 忘れない
Big hopes, I won't forget them
10年後の8月
August, ten years from now
また出会えるのを信じて
I believe we'll meet again
最高の思い出を
Our greatest memories
出会いはふとした瞬間 帰り道の交差点で
Our meeting was a sudden moment, at a crossroad on the way home
声をかけてくれたね 「一緒に帰ろう」
You called out to me, "Let's go home together"
僕は照れくさそうに カバンで顔を隠しながら
Embarrassed, I hid my face behind my bag
本当はとてもとても 嬉しかったよ
But really, I was so, so happy
あぁ 花火が夜空綺麗に咲いて ちょっと切なく
Ah, fireworks bloomed beautifully in the night sky, a little bittersweet
あぁ 風が時間とともに流れる
Ah, the wind flows along with time
嬉しくて 楽しくて 冒険もいろいろしたね
It was happy and fun, we had all sorts of adventures
二人の 秘密の 基地の中
Inside our secret base
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢
The end of summer with you, dreams for the future
大きな希望 忘れない
Big hopes, I won't forget them
10年後の8月
August, ten years from now
また出会えるのを信じて
I believe we'll meet again
君が最後まで心から 「ありがとう」叫んでいたこと 知っていたよ
I knew you were shouting "Thank you" from the bottom of your heart until the end
涙をこらえて 笑顔でさよなら 切ないよね
Holding back tears, saying goodbye with a smile, it's painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を
Our greatest memories
あぁ 夏休みもあと少しで終わっちゃうから
Ah, because summer vacation is almost over
あぁ 太陽と月仲良くして
Ah, the sun and moon get along well
楽しくて 寂しくて 喧嘩もいろいろしたね
It was fun and lonely, we had all sorts of fights
二人の 秘密の 基地の中
Inside our secret base
君が最後まで心から 「ありがとう」叫んでいたこと 知っていたよ
I knew you were shouting "Thank you" from the bottom of your heart until the end
涙をこらえて 笑顔でさよなら 切ないよね
Holding back tears, saying goodbye with a smile, it's painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を
Our greatest memories
突然の 転校で
Because of a sudden school transfer
どうしようもなくて
There was nothing I could do
手紙書くよ 電話もするよ 忘れないでね 僕のことを
I'll write letters, I'll call you, please don't forget me
いつまでも 二人の 基地の中
Inside our base forever
君と夏の終わり ずっと話して 夕日を見てから星を眺め
Talking with you until the end of summer, watching the sunset then the stars
君の頬を流れた涙はずっと忘れない
I'll never forget the tears that flowed down your cheeks
君が最後まで大きく手を振ってくれたこと ずっと忘れない
I'll never forget how you waved your hand so much until the very end
だからこうして夢の中で ずっと永遠に
So like this, inside a dream, forever and ever
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢 大きな希望 忘れない
The end of summer with you, dreams for the future, big hopes, I won't forget them
10年後の8月 また出会えるのを信じて
August, ten years from now, I believe we'll meet again
君が最後まで心から 「ありがとう」叫んでいたこと 知っていたよ
I knew you were shouting "Thank you" from the bottom of your heart until the end
涙をこらえて 笑顔でさよなら 切ないよね
Holding back tears, saying goodbye with a smile, it's painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を
Our greatest memories
うわああああ！
Whoaaa!
Menyedihkan sekali. Moona tadi terharu.
It's so sad. Moona was moved just now.
Tahu nggak, tahu nggak liriknya tadi
"Natsu yasumi wa owari" apa gitu...
You know, you know the lyrics earlier
were "The summer vacation is ending" or something...
Owatchau kara.
Because it's ending.
Owatchau kara, iya ini udah mau habis natsu yasumi-nya.
Because it's ending, yeah,
the summer vacation is almost over.
Oh iya natsu yasumi-nya. Natsu yasumi...
Oh yeah, the summer vacation. Summer vacation...
Hah... Guys, mau pada duduk nggak? Capek.
Hah... Guys, do you want to sit down? Tired.
Iya nih, duduk yuk yuk yuk yuk kita duduk...
Yeah, let's sit, let's sit, let's sit down...
Nah, jadi teman-teman...
So, friends...
Bagaimana? Sudah bernyanyi berapa lagu tadi? Satu...
How was it? How many songs have we sung so far? One...
Empat.
Four.
Empat ya? Empat. Empat. Empat.
Four, right? Four. Four. Four.
Langsung tuh, nggak ada break.
Hayolo langsung empat LIVE, teman-teman.
Straight away, no break.
Look at that, four songs LIVE, friends.
Moona capek langsung tek-tek-tek-tek.
Moona is tired from going at it one by one.
Iya langsung masuk, keluar, wheee!
Yeah, straight in, out, wheee!
Masuk, Peko!
Entering, Peko!
Nah, jadi gini, guys.
So, it's like this, guys.
Kalian, kalian pilih lagu-lagu ini kenapa sih?
You guys, why did you choose these songs?
Hmm... Kalau tadi tuh yang pertama banget ya...
Hmm... As for the first one...
Lagu apa sih? Start:Dash!! itu...
karena kita bertiga kan ya? Bertiga.
What song was it? "Start:Dash!!"...
because there's three of us, right? Three.
PIONEER.
Oh my god, bestie kita Pioneerrr!
Oh my god, bestie, we are Pioneer!
Masa sih?
Really?
Tahu nggak sih, Risu bela-belain belajar dance!
Do you know, Risu went through
the trouble of learning the dance!
My god, kalian harus tahu!
My god, you guys have to know!
Jadi, kalian kalau nyadar ya,
di showcase-nya Risu, dia nggak ada nge-dance.
So, if you notice, in Risu's showcase,
she didn't dance.
Iya.
Yes.
Iya, pas ini kita: "Risu, kamu nggak mau tahu, nge-dance!"
Yes, this time we said:
"Risu, like it or not, you're dancing!"
Ini Risu, Yopi mau terima seriusan dikit ya.
For Risu, Iofi wants to be a bit serious.
Kalian kalau mau nangis, nangis aja semua.
If you want to cry, just cry, everyone.
Jadi, yang nggak biasa nge-dance itu
di antara kita bertiga itu Risu...
So, the one who's not used to dancing
among the three of us is Risu...
...karena kayak kita, Risu, Start:Dash!! kui-kui
dia awalnya cuma kayak nyanyi doang...
...because like us, Risu, for "Start:Dash!!",
at first she was just like singing...
Ah, bisa kayak nyanyi doang gitu. Ternyata...
Ah, I thought I could just sing. Turns out...
Ternyata... Bagaimana kalau kita nge-dance? Wah!
Turns out... How about we dance? Wah!
Risu kayak "Hah?", terus Moona bilang...
Risu was like "Huh?", then Moona said...
Kamu, kamu masuk ke dunia entertainment, idol, hololive...
You, you entered the entertainment world, idols, hololive...
Saatnya kamu belajar dance.
It's time for you to learn to dance.
Isimi!
Iya, gitu. Isimi, tahu nggak?
Yeah, like that. Isimi, you know?
Awalnya, awalnya Risu nggak bisa banget, guys.
At first, at first Risu couldn't do it at all, guys.
Sekarang udah bisa. Kalian lihat kan tadi? Hebat!
Now she can. You saw it earlier, right? Great!
Hebat lho.
Great, really.
Tadi tuh last minute kita sempet-sempet latihan juga.
Earlier, last minute, we managed to practice too.
Iya, kita sempet latihan.
Yes, we practiced.
Kita sempet latihan lama.
Kita latihan dilihat Yagoo tahu nggak tadi?
We practiced for a long time.
We practiced while being watched by Yagoo, you know?
Kata Yagoo: "Ganbatte ne, minna.
Ganbatte ne, minna," katanya.
Yagoo said: "Good luck, everyone.
Good luck, everyone," he said.
Sampai-sampai Moona bilang: "Yagoo, TONIGHT, IDOL!"
To the point Moona said: "Yagoo, TONIGHT, IDOL!"
Hebat bukan?
Isn't it great?
TONIGHT, IDOL! TONIGHT, IDOL!
Terus Yagoo cuma kayak ketawa gitu ya.
Then Yagoo just laughed.
Udah idol banget nggak sih, guys?
Lihat nih stage-nya, tuh, wheee!
Aren't we like totally idols now, guys?
Look at this stage, wheee!
Terus ya, terus ya. Kita tuh nggak cuman nge-idol nih.
Kita nggak cuman nge-idol.
And then, and then. We're not just being idols.
We're not just being idols.
Kita ada PENGUMUMAN!
We have an ANNOUNCEMENT!
Oh, ada pengumuman apa nih?
Oh, what's this announcement?
Yes, we have a little bit announcement. Wah!
Yes, we have a little bit of an announcement. Wah!
Apa nih? Apa nih?
What is it? What is it?
Sudah siap? Sudah siap? Penasaran? Oke.
Are you ready? Are you ready? Curious? Okay.
Tiga, dua, satu...
Three, two, one...
INI DIA!
HERE IT IS!
hololive Indonesia 3D Acrylic Stand
On Sale September 20 (JST)
Wah, apa nih?
Wah, what's this?
Wah lucu banget! Acrylic Stand!
Eh ada aku! Ada aku juga!
Wow, so cute! Acrylic Stand!
Eh, there's me! There's me too!
Oh my god, Acrylic Stand! Acrylic Stand, bestie!
Acrylic Stand-nya itu ya kalau nggak salah ya,
bukan yang kecil.
The Acrylic Stand, if I'm not mistaken, is not the small one.
Oh yang gede?
Oh, the big one?
Yang besar! Ini, guys, guys, guys, gimana, gimana?
The big one! This, guys, guys, guys,
how is it, how is it?
Itu tuh, size body approximately
220 mm until 235 mm.
That, body size approximately 220 mm to 235 mm.
Yah, yang tinggi, yang tinggi.
Kayak gini, guys. Ah, cantik banget.
Yeah, the tall one, the tall one.
Like this, guys. Ah, so beautiful.
Risu gimana, Ris? Risu gimana, Ris? Gimana, Ris?
Risu, how about it, Ris? Risu, how about it, Ris?
How is it, Ris?
Ini... Kalau Risu gini ya.
This... Risu is like this.
Ekornya tuh, ekor pinggangnya tuh nggak bisa dinaikin.
The tail, the tail at the waist can't be raised.
Ayo pinggangmu! Pinggangmu!
Come on, your waist! Your waist!
Emang dari sananya!
It's like that from the start!
Terus, terus, ada apa lagi?
Then, then, what else is there?
Atau mau nyanyi dulu? Jelasin dulu deh. Oke.
Or want to sing first? Explain first. Okay.
So this is a 3D Acrylic Stand special with our 3D model and with our pose...
...because usually when we only have 2D models we don't really have any dynamic poses.
For this is the first time.
Yes, this is the first time. This is the first time
we have like literal dynamic, man, look at the pose!
Look at the pose! Pose! Pose!
Nah, kayak gitu. Misalkan aku kayak gini kali ya.
So, like that. For example, I'm like this, I guess.
Aku kayak gini. Oh Yopi yang gini kayaknya.
I'm like this. Oh, Iofi is like this, I think.
Waduh, ini keren banget!
Wow, this is so cool!
Tapi...
But...
Tapi gak cuma ini lho.
But it's not just this.
Oh, ada lagi?
Oh, there's more?
Not just this, we have another one!
Yes!
What is it?
Apa lagi nih?
What else is there?
Jyan jyan jyan!
Ta-da!
Jadi temen-temen...
So, friends...
There are three special items.
"Everyone's Best Friends, Risusaurus" - Plushie
And "My Bestfriend Moomo" - Plushie
And "Kyawaii Chiyopi" - Plushie
Let's go, let's go!
Ah, ini dia! Look at this!
Ah, here it is! Look at this!
Ini kecilnya segini lho.
It's about this small.
Jadi nih, size aslinya tuh seperti ini.
So, this is its actual size.
So this is the real size of it.
You can see the size on the screen, right?
So there's a reason why we show this on our 3D showcase.
Because we want to let you know how cute our plushie is.
And this is Chiyopi, this is Yopi.
This is Yopi.
Ah, this is Yopi!
This is Yopi!
Ini gak tau siapa.
I don't know who this is.
This is alien!
This is an alien!
This is Chiyopi, this is Yopi.
Chiyopi is small, Yopi is big.
Yopi!
Don't forget to buy it, it's on sale starting from September 20th!
Yes!
Cekidot!
Check it out!
Please buy it because it's so cute.
If you also, this is like a version of a plain one...
You can add glasses to it as well!
You can buy the glasses by yourself.
And also this Risusaurus, it's actually Risu in a dinosaur pajamas.
So this is basically mini Risu just like Chiyopi.
Yes! Chiyopi!
Big Yopi!
Chiyopi!
Risu! Risusaurus!
And Moomo!
Biar deket di hati guys.
To stay close to your heart, guys.
Waduh, ini Chiyopi gak ekstrim gitu kan?
Wow, this Chiyopi isn't extreme, right?
Aduh ada ini, waduh cium-cium. Wangi-wangi!
Oh, there's this. Give it a kiss. Smells good!
So if you are really interested, you need to buy it.
We've been waiting for 17 months...
To actually release this, so please buy it, make it sold out.
You can check on the link, usually it's in Hololive Indonesia Twitter.
You can check in the website and also in the description of the video.
Please buy it! Buy five for your family, okay?
Who love your wife, who love your kids, buy!
Sayang anak, sayang istri, beli! Sayang waifu!
Love your kids, love your wife, buy! Love your waifu!
Betul teman-teman.
That's right, friends.
Aduh, udah disayang seperti anak sendiri.
Oh, it's already loved like my own child.
Terus, kita kan udah promosi, udah nyanyi, udah ngelawak.
And now, we've promoted, sung, and joked around.
Kita ngomong yang agak berat-berat dulu kali ya?
Should we talk about something more serious now?
Ini mau disimpan dulu nggak?
Should we put these away first?
Terima kasih, thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you so much.
Aduh ada yang nangis-nangis ya, bentar.
Oh, someone's crying, wait a second.
Aku tuh di aslinya tuh aku gak nangis, kalian sih!
I wasn't actually crying in real life. It's because of you guys!
Itu ya teman-teman, karena ini tuh adalah...
That's it, friends, because this is...
Karena ini tuh live kita bertiga...
Because this is our live session as a trio...
Terima kasih atas dukungannya sejauh ini.
Thank you so much for the support up until now.
Kita udah 2 tahun lebih ya teman-teman.
It's been over two years already, friends.
Semoga ini adalah awal untuk Hololive Indonesia...
I hope this is just the beginning for Hololive Indonesia...
Supaya bisa lebih berkembang lagi teman-teman.
So it can grow even more, friends.
Ingat ini cuman Mini 3D Live...
Remember, this is just a Mini 3D Live...
Semoga kita bisa mendapatkan live yang benar-benar live.
But I hope we can have a real full-scale live concert.
Terus setelah kita...
And after us...
Kita juga berharap untuk gen-gen yang selanjutnya.
We also have high hopes for the next generations.
Kita tunggu di panggung yang selama ini kita impi-impikan.
We'll wait for you on the stage we've been dreaming of.
Jadi semangat, ditunggu gen selanjutnya. Oke?
So keep up the spirit, we're waiting for the next gen. Okay?
Terus dari kalian nih, aduh.
And from you guys... oh.
Mau nangis.
I'm going to cry.
menunjukkan suara mereka yang terbaik dari diri mereka sendiri.
showing the best of themselves through their voices.
Karena itu, aku tunggu, Moona tunggu untuk gen selanjutnya,
Because of that, I'll be waiting, Moona will wait for the next generation,
dan juga sebagai penutup...
and also as a closing...
mari kita menyanyikan lagu dari hololive Indonesia untuk semua orang.
let's sing a song from hololive Indonesia for everyone.
Yes! Siapa yang udah siap?
Yes! Who's ready?
Aduh bentar gimana nih, siap belum nih komentarnya dari tadi loh.
Wait a sec, how's it going? Are you ready? Look at the comments.
Komentarnya lagi nangis! Bentar-bentar, hololive Indonesia!
The comments are crying! Wait, hololive Indonesia!
Kok aku pengen bikin kalian nangis lagi?
Why do I want to make you cry again?
Kita aku pengen call and response dong biar kayak idol-idol.
I want to do a call and response like idols.
Apa-apa? Gimana-gimana?
What? How?
Kayak gini, kayak gini, aku gambarin dulu nih yang di komentar.
Like this, I'll describe it for the chat.
Gamba-Risu gitu. Oke-oke, dari siapa dulu? Risu nih aku.
"Gamba-Risu" like that. Okay, who's first? Me, Risu.
Call and response all right! If I say "Puru-puru"...
you say "Gambari-su", all right?
Okay, from now, one, two, three!
Puru-puru!
Gambari-su!
Wih gila! Hahai! Selanjutnya Moona ya.
Whoa, crazy! Hahai! Next is Moona.
Yes, kalau Moona bilang "Moon-moon", kalian bilang "Moona-dayo", oke?
Yes, if Moona says "Moon-moon", you say "Moona-dayo", okay?
Moon-moon!
Moona-dayo!
Yeeey! Hebat! Keren! Terakhir ya.
Yeeey! Great! Cool! Last one.
Terakhir, silakan. Aduh bentar.
Last one, please. Oh wait.
Ioforia!
Obisa!
Jadi teman-teman, panggung yang sudah kita impi-impikan sudah menanti.
So friends, the stage we've been dreaming of is waiting.
You guys ready? Yes, I am ready!
Satu, dua... id:entity voices!
One, two... id:entity voices!
Dengarkanlah suaraku...
Listen to my voice...
id:entity voices
Berdiri di tengah terangnya kilas cahaya
Standing in the middle of the bright flashes of light
Ohayou Konbanwa kami serukan kepada dunia
Good morning, good evening, we call out to the world
Mengudara hari ini
Broadcasting today
bagian dari diri yang manakah
which part of myself
Yang harus kutunjukkan tak dapat pernah memutuskan
should I show, I can never decide
Lalu suatu hari pesan-pesan berdatangan
Then one day, messages started arriving
Kata-kata terima membuatku kehilangan arah
Those words made me lose my way
Senyuman di balik layar
Smiles behind the screen
sangat berarti untukku bertahan
mean a lot for me to persevere
Tak pernah ingin mengecewakan siapapun di luar sana
Never want to disappoint anyone out there
Namun di saat banyaknya suara
But when there are many voices
Manakah yang harus kudengar?
Which one should I listen to?
Mencoba mendengarkan suara di dalam hati
Trying to listen to the voice inside my heart
Inilah diri yang ingin kuselalu tunjukkan
This is the self I want to always show
Berbagai suara yang berpadu kan menjadi satu
Various voices blending together will become one
Identity!
Hari-hari berlalu dan sekarang ku di sini
Days pass and now I'm here
Berdiri di tepi panggung ini menyambut dunia
Standing at the edge of this stage welcoming the world
Tetapi ku tak sendiri
But I'm not alone
bersama lainnya sekarang
with others now
Seakan seperti keluarga bersatu dalam perbedaan
Like a family united in difference
Namun di saat banyaknya perbedaan
But when there are many differences
Dapatkah harmoni tercipta?
Can harmony be created?
Bergandengan tangan berjuang raih mimpi bersama
Holding hands struggling to achieve dreams together
Semua bersorak dengan suara gembira
Everyone cheering with a joyful voice
Menyebarkan kebahagiaan
Spreading happiness
di mana pun itu bergemuruh
wherever it rumbles
Panggung yang lebih besar kini menunggu
A bigger stage is now waiting
Waktunya telah tiba tanpa adanya ragu
The time has come without any doubt
Dengan semua warna suara...
With all the colors of voice...
Ini sebenarnya...
This is actually...
Inilah langkah awal rasa bimbang di hati
This is the first step for the uncertainty in my heart
Inilah jati diri yang ingin kuselalu tunjukkan
This is the identity I always want to show
Berbagai suara yang berpadu
Various voices blending together
Dalam perbedaan takkan pernah tergoyahkan
Unyielding amidst our differences
Dan menjadi satu id:entity
And becoming one id:entity
おはよう! こんばんは!
Good morning! Good evening!
お疲れ様でした!
Good work today!
おはよう! こんばんは!
Good morning! Good evening!
Kita kan jumpa lagi!
We will meet again!
Yay!
I love you!
Love you!
Bye bye!
Thank you!
ありがとう!