(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while until the start.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
Made-to-order merch
Messages from fans
フリューからのニュース！
News from FuRyu!
ホロライブEnglishのメンバーたちが
Hololive English members...
キュートなパペットぬいぐるみに なったよ！
...have become cute puppet plushies!
寝そべりぬいぐるみも見逃しなく！
Don't miss the lying down plushies too!
全国のラウンドワンクレーンゲームで ゲットしてね！
Get them at Round One crane games nationwide!
フリュー！
FuRyu!
フリューからのニュース！
News from FuRyu!
全国のラウンドワンクレーンゲームで ゲットしてね！
Get them at Round One crane games nationwide!
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment until the show begins.
Attention For Visitors
I am supporting Breaking Dimensions!
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ #BreakingDimensions
Official Hashtag #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive English 2nd Concert Made-to-order merch
Sales period: 10 PM August 10th - 5 AM September 17th (EDT)
hololive STAGE World Tour '24 -Soar- x hololive English 2nd Concert Mutual Items On sale now!
Original Keychain / Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand
Acrylic Panel / Laptop/Tablet Case
Breaking Dimensions
hololive English 2nd Concert
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ
#BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
Official Hashtag
#BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
hololive English 2nd Concert
Made-to-order merch
hololive STAGE World Tour '24 x hololive English 2nd Concert
Mutual Items
Original Keychain
Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand
Acrylic Panel
Laptop / Tablet Case
Breaking Dimensions
hololive English 2nd Concert
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRYU
Starting around JANUARY 2025 at ROUND1 across the US!
PUPPET PLUSHIES
LYING DOWN PLUSHIES
hololive plushies up for grabs in CRANE GAMES!
フリュー
FuRYU
Further updates will be posted on ROUND1 website,
be sure to check regularly!
hololive campaign at ROUND1 starting October 2024!
ENigmatic Recollection Launch Party
August 30th 19:00 PDT
ENigmatic Recollection
hololive x HYTE Breaking Dimensions
NOW AVAILABLE GLOBALLY FOR
PRE-ORDER ON HYTE.COM
ommonah BREAKING DIMENSIONS
hololive English 2nd Concert
Order Online ommonah.com
All about your Oshi, One app holoplus+
Official Hashtag #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the
performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
Breaking Dimensions
hololive English 2nd Concert
BREAKING NEWS !!
from FuRyu
Starting around JANUARY 2025
at ROUND1 across the US!
PUPPET PLUSHIES
LYING DOWN PLUSHIES
hololive plushies up for grabs in
ROUND1 CRANE GAMES!
フリュー
FuRyu
BREAKING NEWS !!
from FuRyu
Starting around JANUARY 2025
at ROUND1 across the US!
hololive plushies up for grabs in
ROUND1 CRANE GAMES!
Further updates will be posted on ROUND1 website,
be sure to check regularly!
hololive campaign at ROUND1
starting October 2024!
NOW AVAILABLE GLOBALLY FOR
PRE-ORDER ON HYTE.COM
Order Online
holoplus+
hololive production's Official App
Holoplus+ hololive production's Official App
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
Official Hashtag #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive English 2nd Concert Made-to-order merch
T-shirt, Face Towel, Folding Fan
Mutual Items: hololive STAGE World Tour '24 -Soar- hololive English 2nd Concert
Penlight Color Variants: 12 colors
Made-to-order merch
Original Keychain, Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand
Made-to-order merch
Acrylic Panel, Laptop/Tablet Case
Breaking Dimensions
Digital Message Board
(Laughing)
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue.
Also known as the Scarlet Queen,
the Harbinger of Order,
Leader of Justice.
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Lovely to see ya, to see ya, lovely!
Gigi Murin!
It's Gigi Murin!
And today, again, you can call me "The Fister"!
And I'm Cecilia Immergreen, the ancient automaton.
Spin twin!
Ciao-ciao, bambini!
This is Raora Panthera.
And we are JUSTICE!
JUSTICE! JUST LIKE THAT!
JUSTICE! GET GET THAT!
Yesterday's concert was amazing, right?
But we still have one day left.
I'm so-so excited to see what our senpais
have in store for us today.
What about you guys?
Today's performance is going to be even more hyped and exciting.
So get ready!
Let's do this!
Everyone!
Three! Two! One!
BREAKING DIMENSIONS!
壁をぶち破れ！
Break through the wall!
Are you ready!?
A-D-V-E-N-T!
Are you ready for this?
Come on everyone!
It's time to break out!
A-D-V-E-N-T!
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
Spreading out like wildfire
Never ever have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Take a chance and with my lighter
Start the fire
Counting me out
I'm out of sync
This overkill
Of saddled stories wearing me down
Step out of the system
Break out, give it everything
This is our time
We're yours to discover
Hello brand new world
Would you welcome the light
And free us from the night
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, you desire
Ignite us!
Dance to the flame of light
新しき世界へ
To a brand new world
Dance till the end of time
異次元の向こう側へ
To the other side of another dimension
連れて行ってあげる
I'll take you there
Rebellion!
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
One step to the left
Two steps to the right
Then back to where we started
And then over again
Step out of the circle
Break out, we've got everything
This is our time
We're yours to discover
Blue sky, take us home
To where we belong
And free us from the night
Take us to paradise!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, you desire
Ignite us!
Dance to the flame of light
それぞれのステージへ
To our respective stages
Dance till the end of time
奇跡の向こう側へ
To the other side of a miracle
連れて行ってあげる
I'll take you there
Rebellion!
Jump into the stream of life!
Cho! Cho!
踊ろ 世界へ
Let's dance to the world
Jump into the other side!
Cho! Cho!
異次元の向こう側 突き抜け手をあげろ
Go beyond the dimension, break through and raise your hands
Last time!
Jump into the stream of life! Dance, dance!
空え 誰のステージへ
To the sky, to whose stage?
Jump into the other side! Dance, dance!
異次元の向こう側 突き抜け手をあげろ
Go beyond the dimension, break through and raise your hands
And let's get this party started
Fire, fire, light the fire
Higher, higher as you desire
Time to get this party started!
Let me hear you New York!
Ticked out from the sky to the deepest hell
If you survived down below where the darkness dwells
So deep that you can't even hear the bells
All along what a mess couldn't even tell
Yeah, the second coming, yeah, the lightning
I've cut into the sky so frightening
異次元に生きる人間に
To humans living in another dimension
Actions all have consequence.
Oh you humans so naive and desperate.
Enough to think that luck and fate have favorites.
禁忌を感じたいのなら さらけ
If you want to feel the forbidden, expose it
抗って その運命
Resist that fate
If you reach for it, I'll burn ya
With the dragon's heart of fire
Heed the mark of chaos the gainer
Dive straight into desire
Ever, after, higher
そら 全て 支配か
Look, is everything controlled?
それでも 抗い かかってこい
Even so, resist and come at me
地獄を 見せろ 激動
Show me hell, upheaval
Come we go!
Bring it, bring it, Gekidou
New gene make it rain
If you want to be the King
Bring it, bring it, Gekidou
New gene make it rain
If you want to be the King
Now let's tonight my awakening
So strange that you can't stop shivering
Don't stay silent for second in
All your climbing up my body in unison a pattern
Hey, listen now, wait up for me
Baby, I should look around
奇跡の光は 永遠の愛
The light of miracles is eternal love
禁忌を感じたいのなら さらけ
If you want to feel the forbidden, expose it
抗って その運命
Resist that fate
地獄の業火さ 業火
It's the hellfire, hellfire
Chaos off and change the kind of...
天まで上りたいか
Do you want to climb to the sky?
Take off on the depth for the fire.
If you really want to win and take everything.
Look within and begin. Gekidou, you feel.
A burning wrath that makes the heart freeze.
You face creatures from a deep dark sea.
Your faith will grow like lava and bloom from a seed.
また 殻を 破り
Breaking the shell again
聞こ その願い
Listen to that wish
If you reach for it, I'll burn ya
With the dragon's heart of fire
Heed the mark of chaos the gainer
Dive straight into desire
Ever, after, higher
そら 全て 支配か
Look, is everything controlled?
それでも 抗い かかってこい
Even so, resist and come at me
地獄を 見せろ 激動
Show me hell, upheaval
Let's break out!
Bring it, bring it, Gekidou
New gene make it rain
If you want to be the King
Bring it, bring it, Gekidou
New gene make it rain
If you want to be the King
King.
もぐもぐ
Munch munch
一日の始まり 悪戦苦闘 もう...
The start of the day, struggling, enough...
気がついたらだいだいたいおいしくなる
Once I realize it, mostly everything tastes good
君が泣いてもお腹はすくよ
Even if you cry, I'll still get hungry
消化できなかった ごめんごめん
I couldn't digest it, sorry, sorry
酸いも甘いも勝手に食べて
Eating the sour and the sweet as I please
ご迷惑おかけしております
I apologize for the inconvenience
パッケージ開けてエナジーのジュース
Opening the package, energy juice
心を無にして飲み込みます
Swallowing it with an empty heart
ああ 五臓六腑方のレストランって
Ah, the restaurant for my internal organs
嘘パチのメニューにおちょぼして
Acting refined with the fake menu
君ともぐもぐ
Munching with you
もぐもぐ
Munch munch
十二支の真ん中でもぐもぐ
Munching in the middle of the zodiac
(Oh yeah!)
地味も八百八辺の群れも
The mundane and the crowds of eight hundred and eight
満腹になる未来を願っているよ
I'm wishing for a future where everyone's full
もぐもぐ
Munch munch
世界が終わる前にもぐもぐ
Munching before the world ends
MOGU MOGU YUMMY まじ神
Mogu Mogu Yummy, seriously divine
ヤムヤムありのまま
Yum yum, just as it is
MOGU MOGU YUMMY まじ神
Mogu Mogu Yummy, seriously divine
この世は味わうんだ うまうま
I'm going to taste this world, yummy yummy
ビターも酸味もピオサンド
Bitter and sourness, a sandwich
ときめき棒のオロロソース
Throbbing stick's Ororo sauce
おざっぱな味付けをおめにみてよ
Please overlook the sloppy seasoning
おいしくなったら OK OK
If it tastes good, then OK OK
良いもん悪いもんいっぱい食べて
Eating lots of good things and bad things
汚れた口元ぬぐいます
I'll wipe my dirty mouth
おにぎり チーズケーキ 豪華なフルコース
Rice balls, cheesecake, a luxurious full course
罠を疑いきを告げます
I suspect a trap and sound the alarm
ああ 妄想遊戯後のバイキングで
Ah, at the buffet after the fantasy play
毒入りと絶品より分けて
Distinguishing the poisoned from the exquisite
君ともぐもぐ
Munching with you
もぐもぐ
Munch munch
誰もいない教室でもぐもぐ
Munching in an empty classroom
(Oh yeah!)
地味も八百八辺の中
The mundane and the eight hundred and eight
泣かない君と生き残れたらいいな
I hope I can survive with you who doesn't cry
もぐもぐ
Munch munch
数年後のこの場所でもぐもぐ
Munching in this place years from now
MOGU MOGU YUMMY まじ神
Mogu Mogu Yummy, seriously divine
今夜の晩ご飯は
Tonight's dinner is...
MOGU MOGU YUMMY まじ神
Mogu Mogu Yummy, seriously divine
次はお前の番だ
Next is your turn
MOGU MOGU YUMMY まじ神
Mogu Mogu Yummy, seriously divine
ヤムヤムありのまま
Yum yum, just as it is
MOGU MOGU YUMMY まじ神
Mogu Mogu Yummy, seriously divine
この世は味わうんだ うまうま
I'm going to taste this world, yummy yummy
ヤムヤム
Yum yum
How are you, darlings?
Hello, New York! Second day, huh?
Yeah! How are you doing tonight, New York?
Are you guys having a great time?
Yeah! How's the concert so far?
Do you like Rebellion?
Oh, I don't think that was loud enough. Yell more, please!
Yeah, come on! It's our first time as Advent performing together.
Yeah, did you like it?
Oh, you ripped my ears.
That's what I thought.
Well, I guess we should do some introductions first, maybe?
Yeah, like who are you and who am I?
Yeah, I'm not really sure anymore, honestly.
I'm not really sure either. Well, why don't you go first?
All right! Shiori Novella here at your service.
hololive's Archiver.
And who am I?
Hiya, darlings! This is hololive English Advent's Nerissa Ravencroft.
The one and only Nerissa Ravencroft.
Thank you for having us here tonight, New York!
Yeah, let's make some noise tonight!
Well, you know... Oh yes, that's music to my ears.
Honestly, same. This venue... can we just take a moment to appreciate it?
It's gorgeous!
It looks also kind of haunted.
Yeah, it does look a little bit haunted.
What should we do with it? We should summon a ghost.
You... I mean, I'm already a demon, so...
I choose... why don't we summon a prettier ghost?
You said you're a demon! That's fine!
My heart! You just killed me in front of everyone!
Even in the haunt! No, I'll make it up to you.
Here, here, just turn around.
I got her nose!
No!
I can't breathe! Help me!
I got your nose!
Give it back!
Okay, here you go.
Thank you.
Well...
We wanted to do some call and responses with you guys, if that's okay.
So how I like to summon ghosts is by being like really annoying.
So I think we should recite the lyrics, right?
Yes!
So we're gonna say "Fire Fire",
and then right after, you're gonna say "Light the fire", got it everyone?
That's supposed to make ghosts come out.
Alright.
One, two, three.
Fire, fire!
I don't think that was loud enough. Let's do one more.
Yeah, yeah. Okay, countdown.
One, two, three.
Fire, fire!
That's what I'm talking about!
I can feel the spirits.
Um, I want to do one more actually, selfishly of me.
Oh, okay.
I mean, it's not really a call and response, but I just want the audience for- for me, for myself...
...I just want to hear you all say "Ope". I'm gonna do a countdown.
Can you all just say "Ope" for me?
But- but can you tell us the origin of "Ope"? Like a really quick summary.
"Ope" is just an- an expression, like "Oh", of surprise.
It's like "Oh!"
Yeah, "Ope!"
Oh!
Ope!
You don't have to sound surprised. You can just say "Ope" though.
Okay, on three. I won't make you do it twice,
so you got one try. Can you get it for me?
One shot, okay, okay.
One, two, three!
Yeah! Heck yeah!
Well, you know, we're here for "Breaking Dimensions".
Yeah. Talk about what- what does "Breaking Dimensions" mean to you?
Yes, and we're to be gone!
You okay? Yeah, good. Just keep talking.
Okay, okay. Wow, wow. What- what "Breaking Dimensions" means to me...
...but, uh... I feel like it's a physical achievement because this is our first concert.
Yeah, really. And I kind of feel the same.
It's like, I feel like this is solidifying our existence being here, right?
Yeah.
Like, you know, we've been in Hololive for about a year, but now it feels really, really official...
...standing before you, seeing you guys out in the audience, up there, and online too.
Yeah. Hi guys.
Hey, I'm walking here!
Yeah, move it! I'm walking here!
But it's- it's really great to be here because like, it feels- it feels so real, right?
Yeah, it really does feel real. It's real!
You guys, it's like I could touch you.
The accident wasn't my fault!
But I'm so happy to be here with all of Advent, but especially with my...
...beloved Shiori Novella.
Who's a good girl? Who's my little PogChamp?
Who's my PogChamp? What's wrong with me?
I don't know, there's a lot.
Yeah, I... same, honestly.
Okay, cool.
Well, we're having a great time.
Uh, we do have some potentially maybe bad news...
...which is if you are at this point of the concert watching online...
...this is where the free portion of the show ends.
That's right!
No more sneak-peeking! No more sneaking and no more peeking, in that order.
Yep. So if you're gonna want to watch the rest of the concert and you're online...
...be sure to head over to SPWN and you can get a ticket and watch the rest of the concert...
...if you want to see uh, my solo performance today, as well as everybody else's amazing performances.
Yeah! It's gonna be so many wonderful songs.
So that's right! Go for purchases, let's go!
Yeah!
But, I... should- should we do the thing?
Oh, that's right! Yeah.
Alright, let's fuse. Okay.
Everyone, I hope you enjoy...
...Breaking Dimensions!
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended!
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.