(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Ladylike
KIRA
Under the moonlight we kiss goodbye
You walk up wearing your disguise
Never gave me something, and don't think twice
And I told you all the things I would do
But does it matter when you chase after
the pleasure you can have?
Now look where you ended up at
Cause out of seven billion people
you won't find another me
If you want it all I tell you now
my love don't come for free
Oh baby, baby, yeah, yeah,
you've got to treat me like a lady
Yeah, yeah, cause I don't need no man to save me
Boy I'll make you crazy, so look into my eyes
And be real with me tonight
Treat me like, treat me like, ladylike
Treat me like, ladylike
All your sweet talk and flattery, boy,
that shit don't fly
I got 20-20 vision, I see through every lie
Stay deceiving as you see fit, you're just that type of guy
The stupid girls believe it, but I'm another kind
Should've known that you'd get what's coming too
Everything that you had wasn't meant for you
Got 'em all up sick like a virus,
don't infect yourself this time
Cause out of seven billion people
you won't find another me
If you want it all then tell me baby
what's it gonna be
Oh baby, baby, yeah, yeah,
you've got to treat me like a lady
Yeah, yeah, I'll throw you out the way you came in
Cause solitude don't phase me
So look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
I am, hands up and set it up
Cause all that you've got is one chance
to turn it around
And I've had enough
If you want to earn it then work it,
boy, don't let me down
Baby, baby, baby
You've got to treat me like a lady
Yeah, yeah, cause I don't need no man to save me
Boy I'll make you crazy, so look into my eyes
And be real with me tonight
Oh baby, baby, yeah, yeah,
you've got to treat me like a lady
Yeah, yeah, I'll throw you out the way you came in
Cause solitude don't phase me
So look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
Treat me like, ladylike
Yeah
4BLOOD
KIRA
Na na na...
I'm alive, still breathing,
stop to hide, done grieving
Realized that to survive,
someone's got to stand and fight
And I've tried to believe in,
only time stops the bleeding
I'm not waiting anymore,
I know what I came here for
Cause feelings are temporary,
but broken hearts keep scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me,
I'm chasing and hunting
And this time I'm coming for blood
Ahhh...
Be the last one to laugh when you run out
of breath catching up
Ahhh...
I'm a breath and a half, baby,
you don't even know me at all
I'm alive, still kicking,
break the rules, rewrite the system
And my story wasn't done,
sharpen knife and cut the guns
Cut the cord, burn the witch,
and you'll regret what you're missing
And I'll take it to the grave,
that's the price that you pay
Cause feelings are temporary,
but broken hearts keep scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me,
I'm chasing and hunting
And this time I'm coming for blood
Be the last one to laugh when you're run out of breath catching up
I'm a threat and a half baby you don't even know me at all
Na na na...
Ha yeah
Woo...
Cause feelings are temporary but broken hearts keep the scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me
I'm chasing and hunting and this time I'm coming for blood
Be the last one to laugh when you're run out of breath catching up
I'm a threat and a half baby you don't even know me at all
Na na na...
You don't even know me at all
Yay! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
hololive EN -Myth- Takanashi Kiara
And well, welcome everybody first of all to my concert!
I hope you enjoyed the first two songs.
How was it? How was it? How was it?
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I hope I already got you hyped up. This is gonna be a really fun show.
But a fun show also needs some special guests, some people to talk to,
maybe some call-ins, some games.
And don't worry, I got you covered. I have invited a very special friend
to play a very special game together with.
And my friend is none other than my ODENZ member,
Nenechi!
hololive 5th Generation Momosuzu Nene
Yay! 聞こえますかー？
Yaaay! Can you hear me?
ハッピーバースデー、キアラちゃん！
Happy birthday, Kiara-chan!
ねねち！
Nenechi!
ありがとう！あ、そうだ、お誕生日だった。
Thank you! That's right, it's my birthday,
そうだ、そうだ、そうだ。
I almost forgot,
ねねち、英語で自己紹介お願いします。
Nenechi, can you introduce yourself in English, please?
はい！
Sure!
hololive 5th Generation, Momosuzu Nene!
Yay!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming!
こちらこそありがとう！
Thanks for having me!
Thank you.
So Nenechi and I will be playing "Idol Shiritori"!
じゃあ、ねねちとはね、アイドルしりとりという私が考えた天才のゲームをやります。
It's a brilliant game that I came up with,
Yay! That's right! After all,
if I'm the top idol in hololive English,
もちろん！
Of course!
then for hololive Japan, it would have to be Nenechi!
あーありがとう！
Gosh, thank you!
Nenechi is hololive Japan's number one idol in my heart.
So I thought that the following game would be very fitting.
So I thought of this game, the rules are the following.
First of all, the name is "Idol Shiritori".
The normal Shiritori works the following: I say a Japanese word,
and they usually are built up in syllables.
So the syllable that it ends with, Nenechi will have to think of
a new word that starts with that syllable.
And then we keep on connecting and connecting until someone makes a mistake
or says a word that already has been said. But here is the twist:
we can only use idol words, or cute or girly words, feminine words.
So anything that's cutesy and idol-y.
Yeah, I think us two, we shouldn't have any issues with that.
うちらだったら問題ないよね、アイドルしりとり！
Idol Shiritori should be a piece of cake for us, right?
できるよ、できるよ！ I can! Okay!
We can do it! I can! Okay!
Okay, then let's give it a shot! ねねち準備OKかな？
Okay, then let's give it a shot! Nenechi you ready?
いよー！
Ready!
なるべくあの、早めのペースでやりましょう。
Let's try to keep the pace up.
Okay! All right!
よし、じゃあ始めよう！ スタート！
Here we go! Start! Start!
ドキドキ！
doki-doki (exciting)
き...キラキラ！
ki...kira-kira (sparkling)
ランデブー！
randebu (rendezvous)
ランデブー？
randebu?
ブ...ブ...ブ...
bu...bu...bu...
ブーメラン！
bu...buumeran (boomerang)
ん、で終わったな！
You said a word that ends in "n"!
あ、そうだ。
Oh right!
ブブー！アウト！ねねちアウト！
Bzzt! You lose! Nenechi you lose!
あーしまった！ちょっと待って。
Darn it! Hang on...
もう一回やりたい、もう一回やりたいな。
Gimme another chance! Come on!
Round 1, I win! One point for Takanashi Kiara. Okay, okay, okay,
じゃああの、3ラウンドやりましょう。 Okay!
then let's do three rounds. Okay!
じゃあ次、ねねちから...
Okay, you start, Nenechi,
ねねち、先攻どうぞ。
Okay, you start, Nenechi.
おっけい。
Okay.
よし。じゃあ、好きなタイミングで、どうぞ。
All right. Hmm... Whenever you're ready, go ahead.
はい！
Kay!
ねねち！
Nenechi!
ち...ち...ち...ちーず！
chi... chi... chiizu! (cheese)
ず... ちーずふぉんでゅ！
zu... chiizu fondyu! (cheese fondue)
あ、いいな。かわいいね。
Ah good one. Yes, very cute, no?
でゅ？でゅ？あ、難しいな。
dyu? dyu? Right, that's a hard one.
「ゆ」でいいよ、そこは。
You can use yu.
ゆ？
yu?
おっけー。ゆ... ゆびわ！
Okay.. yu... yubiwa! (ring)
おー！わんだふる！
Oh! wandafuru! (wonderful)
る... ルビー！
ru... rubii! (ruby)
えー... び... ビーナス！
Uh... bi... biinasu! (Venus)
す... す... す... す...
su... su... su...
するめ！
surume! (dried squid)
え？
What?
あれ、するめって、魚？
Isn't that a type of fish?
するめは、うん、おつまみ。
It's a type of... drinking snack.
いや、かわいくない！
Okay, that is not cute!
不成立だよ、それ！
I don't think that counts!
かわいい言葉思いつかなかったんだもん！かわいくない！
I couldn't think of anything cute! That's not cute!
あー！ブー！ブー！
Argh! Bzzt! Bzzt!
逆に「す」から始まるかわいい言葉って何？
Is there something cute that starts with su?
ん？スクール水着！
Hm? sukuuru mizugi! (school swimsuit)
おー、かわいいわ。
Oh, that is cute.
ま、もうこの時点で勝ちなんだけど、ワンモアやる？
Well, it looks like I win already, but wanna do one more?
次は３ポイント制じゃない？
Let's make the next round three points.
３ポイント？
Three points?
おっけ、おっけ.次勝った方が３ポイントね。
Okay, sure! Whoever wins gets three points.
勝つ！
I'll win!
次ねねちが勝ったら...
If you win the next round, then...
うん。同点。同点。
Uh-huh. It's a tie.
同点？おっけー。平和な終わり方だね。
A tie? Okay, sure. So nobody loses in the end!
そうしよう、そうしよう。
Sounds good!
おっけ、おっけ.じゃあ、次は私から始めます。
Okay, great. Then I'll start the next round.
はい。
Kay.
せーの。
Here I go.
フラミンゴ！
furamingo! (flamingo)
んー。
Um...
ご... ゴールテープ！
go... gooruteepu! (finish line ribbon)
え？何それ？
Wait, what's that?
何それ？
What's that?
これ英語じゃないのか。
I dunno what it is in English.
なんて言った？ごれぷ？
What did you say? gorepu?
ゴールテープ。
gooruteepu.
あ、ゴールテープ！
Oh, gooruteepu!
運動会の最後の方のやつね。
Oh, okay. The thing at the end of a race!
かわいいか？
Is that cute?
かわいいでしょ！
It is totally cute!
まあまあ、おっけおっけ.進めよう。
Okay, we'll count it! It counts! Let's keep going.
ん？
Hm?
あ、じゃあ次は「ぷ」？
Oh, so next is pu?
ぷ... ぷ... ぷ...
pu... pu... pu...
[pu struggling intensifies]
ポンデリング！
puanderingu! [sic] (mochi donut)
ポンデリング？！
puanderingu?!
んー...
Hmm...
あったよね、そういうの？あったよね？
That's a thing right? Right?
はいはい。
Yeah, yeah.
ぐ... ぐ... ぐ... ぐ...
gu... gu... gu... gu...
ぐ...
gu...
ぐ、難しいな。
guy that's a hard one.
グーテンモルゲン、キアラ！
Guten Morgen, Kiara!
ええっ？！
What?!
グーテンモルゲン、キアラ？
Guten Morgen, Kiara?
ら...
Ra...
ランドセル！ランドセル！
randoseru! (child's backpack)
あ、いいな！
Ooh, good one!
ナイスナイスナイス！
Doing good, doing good!
る...
ru...
る？
ru?
ルッコラ！
rukkora! (arugula)
ルッコラ？
rukkora?
よくわからんけど、おっけー、おっけー。
Dunno what that is, but sure!
ら...
ra...
ラミィ先輩！
ramii (Lamy)-senpai!
おっけ、おっけ。
Okay, okay.
い...
i...
い... い... い... い... い...
i... i...
いぬ！
inu! (dog)
お！
Oh!
ぬ... ぬ... ぬ... ぬ... ぬ... ぬ...
nu... nu... nu...
ぬー！！！ [despair]
nu!!! [despair]
わかんないよー、ねねちー！
I can't think of anything, Nenechi!
わかったよ。
Okay, fine.
負けたよ。
I lost!
ということで！
And with that!
平和な終わり方やん！
We end the game tied!
いえーい！
Yay!
一番いいのでは？
I think it's best this way,
そうかもしれない。
Probably for the best!
Because I lost, so we decided that we both...
...we both win in the end. Yes.
I may have won twice and she may have won once but in the end...
...we're orange so all is good,
we love each other,
world is beautiful, world is peace. Yay!
ということで、ねねち、ありがとうございました！
Okay, thanks for coming, Nenechi!
はい！
Yeah!
いえーい！
Yay!
ありがとう、グッバイ！
Arigato, goodbye!
はい！
Yeah!
今度は、オレンズで二人で踊ろう！
Oh, let's get together as the O'riends sometime and dance!
そうしよう！
Yeah, let's!
いえーい！
Yeah!
バイバイ！サンキューねねち！
Bye bye! See you, Nenechi!
サンキュー！
See you!
じゃあ、次の曲行きまーす！
So, let's go to the next song!
じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
SPARKS / Takanashi Kiara
Lying down on the floor late night
and you don't know, don't know, don't know what to do
Hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if you start now, don't know, don't know what to do
The storm hits hard and you're losing the way
Take a chance
And dance in the rain
Cause you got the heat
Never throw it away
Don't forget, don't forget
What I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So go ahead
And do it, do it
If you want it, let's get to it
Everybody's gonna know your name
Cause Sparks like the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up
And never be afraid
Gonna make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks like the flame
So don't wait, start a fire today
Don't stop, don't stop
Just go your own way
Never looking back
Take the fast lane now
In the driver's seat
Strap-in, gas pedal down
We're going so fast
That it should be allowed
That's how we like it
You heard what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So take a step
And move it, move it
Unless you try, you won't get through it
Everybody's gonna know your name
Cause Sparks like the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up
And never be afraid
Let's go of the past tonight
Choose the future only you define
Even when the flames burn too bright
You'll rise from the ashes, you'll rise!
Here we go!
Cause Sparks!
Don't stop, don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up
And never be afraid
Gonna make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks like the flame
So don't wait, start a fire today
Don't stop, don't stop
Just go your own way
Oh yeah!
Digital Girl
KIRA
Hello, nice to meet ya
My name is Perfection
I come from the net inside your personal computer
A tool for the dreamers
Make you a believer
I'm so worldwide, worldwide, holy virtual diva
But sometimes I do
Don't you think of the things they told you?
There must be more than this
There must be more than what you know too
I wasn't made to feel
But lately I can't help it
If there's a way out of here
I've got an idea
Bring it all down
I'll make it come around
I'll burn this whole facade to the ground
I'm sick of windows
I need some physical
Hot love locked in a digital world
Whine about your issues
Watch the life become too short
Right, I got it for you
How do you think I feel?
None of this is real, singing I love soft sets
Digital girl
So I woke up with a headache today
Just kidding, I don't feel pain
To be honest I don't even gotta sleep
And that's the difference between you and me
And I know, I know, I know, I know
Everybody wants it till they gotta commit
Look into my eyes, change your mind so quick
You won't believe the things that I've seen and...
No day is like the other
Be anything I wanna
There is no suffering, wars or existential crisis trauma
But I feel something inside of my heart
And it's telling me to go before I fall apart
Bring it all down
I'll make it come around
I'll burn this whole facade to the ground
I'm sick of windows
I need some physical
Hot love locked in a digital world
Whine about your issues
Watch the life become too short
Right, I got it for you
How do you think I feel?
None of this is real, singing I love soft sets
Digital girl
What is yours and what is mine, am I ever gonna die?
Please don't uninstall my love, please don't uninstall my love
Break it all down, I'll make it come around,
I'll burn this whole facade to the ground
I'm just sick of windows, I need something physical,
hot stuff block in a digital world
One bit issues, won't you let me show all right,
I've got you, for you
How do you think I feel? None of this is real,
sea of life, sucks as a digital girl
Break it all down, I'll make it come around,
I'll burn this whole facade to the ground
I'm just sick of windows, I need something physical,
hot stuff block in a digital world
One bit issues, won't you let me show all right,
I've got you, for you
How do you think I feel? None of this is real,
sea of life, sucks as a digital girl
Higher! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
The Bigaku / Matsuura Aya
Wow!
Yeah!
Hey hey come on dance! Wow!
告白できなくて
Unable to confess,
へこんじゃった midnight
Feeling down at midnight
Come on!
あいつは一丁前の 優しい男
He's a first-class, kind man
Hey hey come on dance! Wow!
だらだらやってないで
Don't just idle around,
すぐ行こうぜ midnight
Let's go right away at midnight
Baby 優柔不断な 一丁前の私
Baby, I'm a first-class indecisive person
恋しているから せつないけれど
I'm in love, so it's painful, but...
愛し合ってても くらい くらい くらい
Even if we love each other, it's dark, dark, dark
Wow!
恋する女と その男の美学
The aesthetics of a woman in love and that man
朝目覚めたら そこで Kiss & Kiss & Kiss
When morning comes, then Kiss & Kiss & Kiss
Come on!
恋する男と その女の魅力
The charm of a man in love and that woman
淋しい夜は 涙 流しても それでいいんだよ
On lonely nights, it's okay even if you cry
Yeah!
迅速 みんなそうさ 結婚式の実際
Quickly, everyone's like that, the reality of a wedding
あいつは優柔不断な 可愛い男
He's an indecisive, cute man
Hey hey come on dance! Wow!
きらきら midnight 恋しちゃってちょうだい
Sparkling midnight, please fall in love
Baby 覚悟は半分 一丁前の私
Baby, my resolve is halfway, I'm a first-class person
都会で夢見る 恋の火蓋が
The beginning of love dreaming in the city
世の中 気合で 右肩上がり
In this world, with fighting spirit, things are looking up
Wow!
恋する女と その男の化学
The chemistry between a woman in love and that man
反応したら そこで Kiss & Kiss & Kiss
If there's a reaction, then Kiss & Kiss & Kiss
Come on!
恋する男と その女の魔力
The magical power of a man in love and that woman
孤独な夜は 二人 離れずに 夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, the two of us will dream without parting
Hey come on baby baby you don't dance ah
都会で夢見る 恋の火蓋が
The beginning of love dreaming in the city
世の中 気合で 右肩上がり
In this world, with fighting spirit, things are looking up
Wow! One, two, three, go!
恋する女と その男の化学
The chemistry between a woman in love and that man
反応したら そこで Kiss & Kiss & Kiss
If there's a reaction, then Kiss & Kiss & Kiss
Come on!
恋する男と その女の魔力
The magical power of a man in love and that woman
孤独な夜は 二人 離れずに 夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, the two of us will dream without parting
Wow!
Yeah!
Hey, hey! Come on, dance!
Wow!
金曜日のおはよう
HoneyWorks feat. Gero
Friday's Good Morning
おはようのオーディションして
I practice my "Good Morning" audition
髪型もバッチリOK
My hair is also perfectly OK
金曜日は頑張らなくちゃ
I have to do my best on Friday
だって二日会えないからね
Because I won't see you for two days
8時0分 2両目
8:00 AM, the second train car
お気に入りの特等席
My favorite special seat
隣の人は眠そうですね
The person next to me looks sleepy
そんな日常
That's my daily life
8時7分開くのは
Opening at 8:07
向かいのドア 息を呑む
The opposite door, I hold my breath
言いかけてたその言葉は
The words I was about to say
今日も逃げた
Escaped again today
きっかけシンプルでいいのに
The trigger should be simple enough
意気地ないな
I have no courage
勇気のテスト乗り越えなきゃ
I have to pass the test of courage
逃げるな自分
Don't run away, me
おはようのオーディションして
I practice my "Good Morning" audition
弱虫な自分に勝って
Winning over my cowardly self
金曜日は頑張らなくちゃ
I have to do my best on Friday
だって二日会えないからね
Because I won't see you for two days
眠そうな君を見てる
I'm looking at you looking sleepy
それだけで満足しちゃって
Just that makes me satisfied
だめだって頑張らなくちゃ
I can't do that, I have to do my best
そっと声に出してみた
I tried to say it softly
8時0分 2両目
8:00 AM, the second train car
座られてた特等席
My special seat was taken
ついてないな空模様まで
I'm not lucky, even the weather
泣きそうです
Looks like it's going to cry
8時7分準備まだ
8:07 AM, I'm not ready yet
ちょっと待ってドキドキが
Wait a second, my heart is racing
震え混じりその言葉は
Those words, mixed with trembling
かき消された
Were drowned out
雨宿り立ち尽くす僕に
To me, standing still taking shelter from the rain
「傘をどうぞ」
"Here, have an umbrella"
君は少し恥ずかしそうに
You, looking a little embarrassed
下を向いた
Looked down
「ありがとう」震えていた
"Thank you", it was trembling
練習してない言葉
The words I hadn't practiced
言えたから頑張らなくちゃ
Since I said them, I have to do my best
だって二日会えないからね
Because I won't see you for two days
大好きな君を見てる
I'm looking at you whom I love
それだけで満足しちゃって
Just that makes me satisfied
月曜日も頑張らなくちゃ
I have to do my best on Monday too
そっと声に出してみた
I tried to say it softly
夢では自然に話せるのに
In my dreams, I can talk normally
勇気のテスト乗り越えるから
I'll pass the test of courage
少し待ってて
So wait for me a bit
おはようのオーディションして
I practice my "Good Morning" audition
髪型もバッチリOK
My hair is also perfectly OK
8時7分に君を待ってる
I'm waiting for you at 8:07
だって今日は言えるから
Because today I can say it
おやすみも言いたいけれど
I want to say "Good Night" too, but
ちょっと待って大好きな
Wait a second, my favorite
言葉なんだって君に会えるからね
Words, because I can see you
Alright everybody! How was that?
Did you like the previous songs?
It was "Zetsubigaku" from Matsuura Aya,
and "Kinyoubi no Ohayou" from HoneyWorks, yeah!
Um, especially the "Zetsubigaku"
I was really excited to perform for you guys
because it's a Hello! Project song
that probably a lot of you guys don't know,
but did you like it? Did you like it? Did you like it?
It's pretty cool. Yeah.
Matsuura Aya is good!
So, next up, we will have more guests,
more guests, more guests!
guests...
Previously it was Nenechi.
Who could possibly be my next guests?
What do you think guys? Hmm...
Hmm... Well, more friends are coming!
None other than my beloved Turduckin Holotori members!
Subaru Oozora! Pavolia Reine! Yahoo!
Happy Birthday! Happy Birthday Kiara!
Happy birthday!
Thank you! Thank you!
嬉しいな。Very happy.
I'm so happy. Very happy.
Thank you too for coming,
for flying over here like the birds you are.
Yeah!
Well, I'm already doing gestures,
but I wonder what are we doing with you guys?
Oh, what could it be?
Charades! We're playing charades!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
いこう！
Let's go!
The typical... the typical game that you have to play when you're in 3D.
Well, I think we have like a synergy,
Holotori synergy.
So whatever movement I do,
you will understand, right?
Yeah, of course! Okay, of course!
Okay, actually,
the words are provided by none other than Gawr Gura,
who is somewhere behind the scenes.
So she will feed me with the words,
I will act them out, and you guys will guess them.
Shall we begin?
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Okay, word number one.
Snail
Ready? Go! Let's go! Go go go!
Go! Cat?
Uh... Dog?
Animal?
Worm?
Turtle? Turtle?
Oh, almost.
Rabbit?
Slow? Slow?
Log? Log? Snake?
Almost! Breathe it! Breathe!
Slimy! Slimy!
Is it slimy? Slime?
Snail! Snail!
Snail!
Yay! Okay, okay. Snail! Katatsumuri.
Yay! Okay, okay. Snail! Snail.
Katatsumuri. Yeah! Snail! Okay, let's go for the next word.
Snail. Yeah! Snail! Okay, let's go for the next word.
Next... Eh? Um...
Tooth Brush
Brush my teeth!
Everything!
With... with toothbrush!
Yes! Next! Next!
Ping Pong
Catch ball!
Baseball!
あ、わかった！I don't know.
Ah, I got it! I don't know.
Oh, oh, oh! Ping pong! Ping pong!
Yay!
Nice! Yay!
Um... hmm...
KFP
Chicken?
Phoenix?
Ah, juggling?
Circus? K... K...
Dance? Dance! Chicken dance!
KFP! KFP! KFP!
Okay, okay, okay. Last word I think, last word.
Last word, last word. Last word, right?
Okay, last word is...
Subaru
Chicken dance? Chicken dance!
Everybody chicken dance!
Ah, yes!
Idols! Idol Kiara! Idol Kiara!
Idol chicken dance!
No! No! No! Um...
Pretty hip! Pretty... ah...
Um... ah...
No! No! Ah!
Wait, maybe...
Kiara pretty dance?
No! No Kiara! No!
泳いでる? 祭?
Swimming? Festival?
Me? Me?
Ah, you? You! You you you! You you you!
You you you! Hahaha!
Okay, okay. 待って。One more.
Okay, okay. Wait. One more.
You!
You! You!
Me?
Yeah!
Huh?
You, me!
Wait! Reine, I...
...I think this could be seen as...
...as me losing after such a winning streak.
I think I lost.
スバル先輩だよ！
It's Subaru-senpai!
スバル先輩！
Subaru-senpai!
Me? Me?
It's Subaru-senpai!
Subaru-senpai!
This is the- the- the Duck Dance!
Duck! Duck! Duck!
Yeah, sorry!
Now I see it, now I see it!
Ah, now you see!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
So you shaking your hips, though!
Yeah!
But it's okay...
...we still did four out of five.
Wow!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
あー、ターダッキン is best-o. Yeah!
Ah, Turducken is the best. Yeah!
Yeah! Turducken!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Best-o!
Best!
Thank you too very much for coming!
Yemekon!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
I love you!
So cute you!
You're so cute!
Love you!
Bye bye!
I love you!
Love you!
Bye bye! Hehe!
FEVER NIGHT / Takanashi Kiara
I'm tired of the same song
Every day like it's on repeat
I need a risky breakdown
Oh honey, the night is calling
Go-meters steady, simple melody
Can you make it original?
Take me away like it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music baby?
Meet me underneath the strobe lights
Come alive, move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Let this new sound take over me
Intoxicating, DJ keep playing
Lately I'm dancing alone
So robotic, so emotionless
But then I see you across the dance floor
So now honey, follow me
I need a thrilling red-hot melody
Oh, something to keep me up all night
Don't look away, now it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music baby?
Meet me underneath the strobe lights
Come alive, moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
この心の音を合わせて
Synchronizing the sound of our hearts
Follow my heartbeat, ba-da-ba-da-ba-da-ba-bi-da
聞かせてあげる
I'll let you hear it
心の ba-da-ba-da-bi, 合わせて follow my heartbeat
Heartbeat ba-da-ba-da-bi, synchronizing, follow my heartbeat
Crazy for your rhythm
I'm in a trance with the way that you moving
You got me shouting, glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild
Don't care who's watching us, so baby
Meet me underneath the strobe lights
Come alive, moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Baby, can we dance until the day like crazy?
About the sound I'm making with you
HINOTORI
Takanashi Kiara
瞬く星の揺りかご
The twinkling stars' cradle
欠けた台詞を繋ぎ合わせたメモリー
Memories of piecing together broken words
聖なる注釈が伝う神話のことわり
The sacred annotations follow the logic of myth
祈りに耳を澄ませ
Listen closely to the prayers
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声が聞こえる
Tell me, I hear your voice
争う言葉 刻を焦がす
Conflicting words scorch through time
焔 降り注ぐ空に見惚れて
Entranced by the sky where flames rain down
乱れ咲く紅は Dedication
The wildly blooming crimson is my dedication
数多重なる試練も
Even through countless overlapping trials
引き抜いて見せる
I will pull through
I will live to keep on fighting till the dawn
例えば 先の見えない
For instance, if I strayed into
零の境界 迷い込んだとしても
The border of zero where the future is unseen
何度も 繰り返される
A solitude ending
孤高の終焉 そこに残した反戦
Repeated over and over, leaving resistance behind
Don't break, I will never give up
Don't break, 羽が朽ちても
Don't break, even if my wings decay
消せない強さは 時の標
An indelible strength is the sign of time
灰が舞い上がる大地 響かせ
Letting it resound on the earth where ash dances
燃ゆる黎明の中 目を覚ます
I wake up in the burning dawn
刃 交わる切っ先
The sword tips that cross
交わした契りは
And the vows we exchanged
Rise and true, come to light at break of day
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go wrong, what awaits me in the dark?
Could you tell me please where I need to go?
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声が聞こえる
Tell me, I hear your voice
漲る決意は 影を晴らす
An overflowing determination clears the shadows
焔 降り注ぐ空に見惚れて
Entranced by the sky where flames rain down
乱れ咲く紅は Dedication
The wildly blooming crimson is my dedication
数多重なる試練も
Even through countless overlapping trials
引き抜いて見せる
I will survive
Raising flames, show me the path to luminous
And in the next life too, I promise I will find you
Yay! How was that?
Yeah, we just, for the first time ever, performed 'Fever Night' and 'HINOTORI'.
Yeah, the classic 'HINOTORI'. I bet you all wanted to see it once again.
But 'Fever Night' is new, very new. My newest single.
So I hope you're listening to it a lot. Are you?
Of course. Please be always streaming Kiara's songs.
Thank you very much for your support.
So, you thought I was done with call-ins, huh?
No, no, no, no, no. There's more.
There's more, there's more, there's more.
Wait a second,
aren't we missing certain Myth members?
Yes, we are! Of course we are!
So please come and say hello to Gura and Callie!
Wee-wee-wee-wee!
Ai, ai, ai, what'd you do? Howdy! Howdy Kiara!
Hello! Hello! Hello! Happy birthday, Kiara!
Happy birthday! Thank you! It is indeed...
You are of birthday. Well, you could say it's not my birthday,
but it's my birb-day! Birb-birb-birb-birb-day!
Ah, I get it. You made a funny word joke. Sasuga Tenshou.
Looking so cute. Oh my god, yes, finally!
Finally, like, I can do my whole, I can show off my body in 3D
for a whole stream, yeah! It's so detailed and beautiful.
Oh, thank you for looking at me. What's your favorite part? Tell me window.
Uh, I like the bow on the back. Yeah, the bow's cool, right?
You never get to see that. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you can only see that in 3D. Right, and the little wings too, so precious.
Ooh, cute. So you gonna pull out your sword? You gonna get your sword out someday for us?
Oh, that's a good question. Well, maybe another time.
Maybe, maybe at a 3D debut stream, which this is not. Right. Yeah, right, right.
Alright, well girls, we are the same generation, so one would assume that you know a thing or two about me, right?
Yeah, of course! We've only met met many times. Yes, especially us, yes, yes.
But also me and Gura have now met in real life, thankfully. Yay! Yay!
So you have, hopefully, a lot of knowledge about me. And I will test that with the Kiwawa Quiz!
Kiwawa Quiz, let's go! Wee-wee-wee-wee! Skrah!
I have five questions for you girls. And if you answer at least four of the questions correctly,
then I shall take you out to dinner sometime! For free! Oh, cool! I was gonna ask for a prize.
Of course there's a prize! Yes, there's always a prize at KFP. So, are you ready for the first question?
Get it on! By the way, you can work together if you want. Oh!
What it is? Let's do it. Yeah, put the two the two biggest brains in Hololive Myth together.
This should be no problem. What do you call yourselves again? The bone heads? No. Bone bros! Bone bros!
The Bone Bros will solve all the questions. Bone heads and feathers.
No, we got this on lock. It's just math. Just don't ask us about math. Oh no, no, I don't even know math either.
So, the first question! Are you ready? It's easy. Question number one...
What does KFP stand for?
Kiara Fried Phoenix! Oh, excuse me, your birdness! Kiara Fried... no, no, no, Kiara Fried Phoenix.
Did you say Kiara Kentucky? No, I've never heard of that place. I said Kiara...
you guys misheard, sorry. That's your ears' problem. I said Kiara Fried Phoenix. I know KFP. I've eaten KFP before.
I should almost give you a minus point for that answer. No, no, no, please don't take away my degree in Kiaralogy, please, I beg you.
Okay, alright. I'll give you that point. That was easy, though. It will get more difficult. Maybe, maybe, maybe.
Uh-oh. Alright, next question! I wrote it down. Let me see. What is it? Ah, yeah, okay.
Question number two! Imagine some quiz lights, quiz show lights. (Ring sound effect)
A new rule: I will only allow correct answers. If you lock in one wrong answer, that's a no point!
Alright Gura, don't fuck this up. Yeah, alright... like, okay.
What's the name of Kiara's 2nd single?
Okay, so question number two: What was Takanashi Kiara's second original single?
Heart Challenger! Yeah! Yeah! I was gonna say that too! Let's go!
Sorry Gumbus, I'm a little faster. You need to give her some time to shine. Gura needs to shine.
Okay Gura, the next one's yours. I'll be faster. No, it's gonna get harder. I'm leaving the hard ones for Gura, actually. It's all part of my plan.
Smart, smart. Crafty. By the way, what was Kiara's first song, by the way? Extra point?
Hinotori! My third, my third... sorry, third. Did you... probably acoustically misheard.
Oh, I thought you said first. No, third. I thought you said first.
Thanks... sorry, I can't...
Yeah, my TH always sounds like an F.
It's okay, it's cute.
My... number three of my song was...
but that's not the question.
Sparks, yes. Okay.
Sparks let the flame... whoa...
In the dark there's an ember... burning up...
Just keep on... just keep on the flame...
Okay, no, that was not the first question.
The first question is coming now.
Can I see it? It was...
Okay, okay. Now this one, let's see.
Question number three! Dun-dun-dun-dun!
What's the name of the mouse/rat...
...that I lived with in Japan?
Name of the mouse/rat Kiara lived with in Japan?
I know this!
Oh!
I'm gonna let Gura answer.
Let's see.
I feel like I've been told this before.
Oh shit.
If you know this, oh no.
Do you need to phone a friend?
Casper.
Heck yeah! Gura! Gura!
Sorry, I can't help myself.
It's okay!
It's an easy one, man!
Actually, just recently, just recently
I uploaded a video...
...a lore video that explains the whole
story behind Casper on my channel.
So if you guys are curious, you could go watch that
if you want to learn more about Casper.
Casper the friendly ghost.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
At first I hated him, then I loved him. Okay.
Okay, fourth question!
If you get this one right...
...then you already have a free dinner with me!
Thank you for carrying, Calli.
No problem.
No, you got this, girl. You definitely
got the next one.
Dude, I don't know if I do got this. I don't know.
Okay, question number four! Dun-dun-dun-dun!
How many re-debuts did Takanashi Kiara have?
Now think before you yell it out loud. Re-debuts.
How many re-debuts has Kiara had?
Re-debuts...
Mmm-hmm.
Wait, what counts as a re-debut?
Well, not debut, but debuts
after the re-debut.
I do have a history with re-debuts.
It hasn't been one in a while...
...but there was a time where I had
many reasons for many re-debuts.
Man, I might know this.
My brain wants to say two, but I don't know.
Okay girl, let's brainstorm.
Brainstorm. Fast. Yeah, 10 more seconds.
Oh shit. You remember the first one?
When the channel got...?
The next one was the German one, right?
Wait, wait, wait. It's two.
Okay, so I think it's two.
You're thinking it's two. Are you sure?
Yeah.
Oh!
I think it's two.
Correct answer! Yeah!
Okay, okay. Well, I still have
one more question though.
A winner chicken dinner from the chicken.
Let's go.
I think we're four for four so far.
Yes we are.
Yeah! But I guess my questions
were a little bit too easy.
So... for the next question, you will
have to answer correctly, otherwise...
Damn it. Is it all or nothing?
It will be, yeah, it will be all or nothing.
Changing the rules on us.
All right, all right.
Can we double down? Do we get dessert too?
Of course! Of course!
All right, let's do it.
Excellent. Excellent.
Last question. And... how should we do this?
I want your separate answers. So...
Huh? What happened?
Wait, she's changing the rules... okay.
I want... no, I just want to see if you both get it right
without hearing the other's answer first.
Okay, I'll take off my headphones.
I'm taking 'em off.
Okay, okay. But wait, no, how do I
give you a sign that you should come back?
Whatever, just bring it back
in 30 seconds, okay?
Okay, do like... throw up some kind
of weird hand symbol.
Okay, I'll do this.
Do a little heart, yeah.
And then I'll come back. All right, bye.
I'm taking off my headphones.
Bye-bye.
Gawrgura. I actually have a feeling
you'll get this one right.
Really? Oh, okay.
Spell out for me without thinking too much.
You have to say it quickly.
Auf Wiedersehen. Go!
Good-bye. Go!
Spell auf wiedersehen
Auf... A-U-F. Auf.
A-U-F. Wiedersehen.
V... I-E-D-E-R... Wiedersehen...
V-I-E-D-E-R... wait...
S-E-H-E-N... S-E-U-N... S-E-N...
Auf Wie... A-U-F...
Auf is the first part.
Wiedersehen... V-I-E-D-E-R...
S-E-N... S-E...
It's hard to follow.
It's hard to follow you. Final answer, go!
A-U-F.
Mmm-hmm.
V...
I-E-D-E-R-S-E-E-N.
Wrong! Bzzzt!
No!
Okay Calli, come back! Calli, come back!
All I heard was wrong.
Is it that hard of a question?
Throw it at me, Kiara.
Throw it at me.
Now Calli recently... had...
Spell auf wiedersehen
A lot of fun learning German with me, so you might...
...you might get a choice.
Fuck.
The German question.
Yes! Alright.
Yeah, good luck, buddies.
Spell, and you have to do it quickly.
Spell it, and you have to do it quickly.
Okay? No thinking.
Spell my ending greeting...
...Auf Wiedersehen!
No! Stop! Don't! Ah!
A...
V...
I...
No, wait! No!
Shit! Damn it, Gura! Come on!
Auf Wiedersehen...
...uh...
Oh shit, that's too hard of a question!
I thought this was a Kiara quiz, not a spelling bee!
Chicken!
A, V...
...arrivedeci...
...arrivedeci, grazie...
...mamma mia!
Final answer?
A, V...
No!
I'll give you ten more seconds.
Wait! No, wait, it's not arrivedeci...
...it's Auf Wiedersehen.
A, V... bonehead!
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong!
No!
What the fuck?!
I mean, beep that out, beep that out, whoever's editing this.
It's okay, on my channel it's allowed.
Okay, thanks.
Well, you know what? I said double down...
...but I'm still gonna treat you for dinner! Yay!
Yay! Thank you!
Winner winner chicken dinner, from the chicken.
As in the chicken is the dinner's from the chicken, not the dinner is the chicken.
That's right.
It doesn't mean that the dinner is, um... is a chicken.
It's from the chicken, so winner winner chicken...
...I'll shut the fuck up now.
Thank you, Kiara! Happy Birthday!
Thank you! I'll bring the cakes soon!
Wait, what's the answer?
You can't just leave us hanging!
Oh, okay. It's A-U-F...
Yeah, spell it!
...space, W-...
...I-E-D-E-R...
Ah, fuck!
...S-E-H-E-N!
Oh, Auf Wiedersehen.
I'm gonna start saying that from now on. Auf Wiedersehen.
And perfectly, since I just spelled it out...
...I will say to you girls, Auf Wiedersehen! Bye bye!
Bye! Auf Wiedersehen!
Next time ask me to spell shrek'd, it's a lot actually more difficult.
Next time ask me to spell 'shrek'd', it's actually a lot more difficult.
Yes! Bye bye!
Happy Birthday! Happy Birthday!
Alright, on to the next songs! Go!
Heart Challenger Takanashi Kiara
Heart Challenger - Takanashi Kiara
Alright guys, no time for break! Here comes...
Alright guys, no time for a break! Here comes...
...Heart Challenger! Let's go!
Bam bam!
Woo! Hey!
Wow!
Yeah!
ドキドキ　止まらない
My heart is pounding, it won't stop
もうすぐ　乙女の勇気
Soon, a maiden's courage
チョコ　コーヒー　必要なの
Chocolate, coffee, I need them
来れば　バレンタイン
Valentine's Day is coming
甘くて　ほろ苦い
Sweet and bittersweet
切ない　君への気持ち
Painful feelings for you
Make me Made me コスチュームチェンジ
Make me, made me, costume change
お気に入りに着替えて
Changing into my favorite outfit
花くすぐる香りに
With a scent that tickles the nose
ハート　ときめいちゃう
My heart starts fluttering
Let's start 作るよ　ラブ込めて
Let's start, I'll make it with love
とびっきりのチョコレート
An extraordinary chocolate
燃え袖をギュッと握ったら
When I tightly grip my 'moe' sleeves
三回　深呼吸の合図
The signal of three deep breaths
カラフルな恋の味
The taste of a colorful love
溶けちゃう前に受け取って　please
Please receive it before it melts
鳴り響く鐘の音
The sound of bells ringing out
校舎の窓辺で二人
Two of us by the school window
ねぇ　早く言わなくちゃ
Hey, I have to say it soon
照れちゃうけど　好きです
I'm embarrassed, but I like you
この思い　君まで届け
Let these feelings reach you
With me! Bam bam!
Woo! Hey!
Wow!
Yeah!
チクタク　進んでく
Tick-tock, time moves on
気持ちは　止められないの
My feelings can't be stopped
チョコっと　勇気出して
Gather a 'choc-o-lot' of courage
贈るラブレター
Sending a love letter
大好き　何十回
I love you, dozens of times
書いても　伝えきれない
Even if I write it, I can't express it all
Make me Make me 意気地なしなんて
Make me, make me, saying I'm a coward
空の彼方　飛んでけ
Fly away to the far reaches of the sky
何度もお目目チェックして
Checking my eyes over and over
君に会う時は
When I meet you
百倍増しで　可愛くなりたいの
I want to be a hundred times cuter
鏡の前　にらめっこ
A staring contest in front of the mirror
Let's go!
違う嘘一つで
With just one different lie
ハートを虜にしたい
I want to captivate your heart
くるくる変えてみても
No matter how many times I change it
髪形が決まらない もう！
I can't get my hairstyle right. Jeez!
告白のシミュレーション
My confession simulation
ドキドキ騒ぎ出しちゃう
My heart starts pounding
隙を狙い込めて
I'll aim for an opening
一発勝負！明日は
And give it my all! I hope tomorrow...
絶対に晴れますように
...will definitely be a sunny day!
Woo!
I'm here to tell you that I love you through and through
There's no one else in this world that I would trade for you
燃え袖ギュッと握ったら
When I tightly grasp my oversized sleeves
ミッション開始の合図
It's the signal to start the mission
カラフルな恋の味
The colorful taste of love
溶けちゃう前にお受け取って Please
Accept it before it melts, please!
鳴り響く鐘の音
The sound of ringing bells
校舎の窓辺で二人
Just the two of us by the school window
ねぇ、早く言わなくちゃ
Hey, I have to say it soon
照れちゃうけど 好きです！
It's embarrassing, but I love you!
スペシャル！この想い
Special! These feelings...
君まで届け
...reach out to you!
Whip it! Bang-bang!
Woo! Hey!
Say Wow!
Yay!
Yay yay yay! That was Heart Challenger! Woo!
Remember, a while ago at Dokomi...
...where I had backup dancers who were doing the dancing for me?
And now I learned it myself and performed it myself. Yay!
That was fun. Hope you enjoyed that.
Well, you know, if you look at the time, you might think, "Oh, it's gonna be over soon."
And yeah, there is one more song.
But before that, let me say a few words to you guys.
So, yeah, we're getting close to the end...
...and I wanted to do something like this for a long time, as you probably know.
And I wanted to show off my dance moves for so long...
...which is, it's one of my, I guess, most prominent skills.
And it has been my dream since the start to show it off...
...to get into this 3D body, finally be free to do whatever I want.
Yeah, and today has finally come.
I hope you guys enjoyed it so far. Yeah.
I want to definitely say a big thanks to Ame and Ina and Gura for helping so much...
...with the recording and the setup.
You know, Ame basically built a whole studio...
...for me to record this in...
...and I really, really, really appreciate that.
And without her, it wouldn't have been possible at all.
And also big thanks to Kanauru for putting together all of this into a proper concert...
...and even creating this beautiful stage here.
Wow! Look, isn't it nice? Yeah.
Thank you so much!
In the future, I really hope that I can do more like this, more often...
...and get more members to join me in 3D...
...if possible, to dance together. Yeah.
Especially, you know, Myth and Holotori and EN as a whole...
...with all of them I want to dance and, yeah, have fun together.
And I think we're getting there, slowly but surely.
By the way, if you missed it, the birthday merchandise was announced...
...it was announced in the previous stream...
...before this one, the countdown stream...
...and it's linked in the description.
So please go check it out if you're interested.
And yeah, last but not least, I want to thank KFP.
You know how much I appreciate your support...
...and you believing in me and trusting in me means the world to me.
So thank you for giving me the strength...
...in a very, very, very stressful period leading up to this day.
Yeah, I think it was worth it. Yeah.
So thank you for waiting for me.
And I will continue working hard...
...to give back to you as much as I can.
Please continue supporting me...
...and watch me grow into a bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger Phoenix!
And I want to thank,
but I will do that with a song.
So please listen to that.
Last song.
どうぞ!
Please enjoy!
Black★Rock Shooter / supercell
Black Rock Shooter
どこへ行ったの?
Where did you go?
聞こえますか?
Can you hear me?
OK, KFP! 回せ!
OK, KFP! Spin them!
見てるか?
Are you watching?
あとどれだけ叫べばいいんだろう
How much more do I have to shout?
あとどれだけ泣けばいいんだろう
How much more do I have to cry?
もうやめて 私はもう走れない
Stop it already, I can't run anymore
いつか夢見た世界が閉じる
The world I once dreamed of is closing
真っ暗で明かりもない
It's pitch black, without a single light
崩れかけたこの道で
On this path that's starting to crumble
あるはずもないあの時の希望が見えた気がした
I felt like I saw the hope from that time that shouldn't even exist
どうして Black Rock Shooter 懐かしい記憶
Why, Black Rock Shooter, those nostalgic memories?
ただ楽しかったあの頃を
Of those times when it was just fun
Black Rock Shooter でも動けないよ
Black Rock Shooter, but I can't move
闇を駆ける星に願いを
A wish upon a star racing through the darkness
もう一度だけ走るから
Because I'll run just one more time
怖くて震える声で呟く
Muttering with a voice trembling with fear
私の名前を呼んで
Call out my name
夜明けを抱く空 境界線までの距離
The sky embracing the dawn, the distance to the boundary
あと一歩届かない
Still one step away
堪えた涙があふれそうなの
The tears I've held back are about to overflow
今下を向かないで 止まってしまう
Don't look down now, or you'll come to a stop
未来を生きていたいんだ わかったの
I want to live for the future, I've realized it
思い出して 強く 強く 信じるの
Remembering it, strongly, strongly believing in it
そうよ Black Rock Shooter 優しい匂い
That's right, Black Rock Shooter, a gentle scent
いたいよ つらいよ 飲み込む言葉
It hurts, it's painful, words I swallow back
Black Rock Shooter 動いてこの足!
Black Rock Shooter, move, these feet of mine!
世界を越えて
Crossing over the world
最初から分かっていた
I knew it from the start
ここにいることを
That I'd be here
私の中の全ての勇気が
All the courage inside of me
火を灯して
Lights a fire
もう逃げないよ
I won't run away anymore
Black Rock Shooter ひとりじゃないよ
Black Rock Shooter, you're not alone
声をあげて泣いたって構わない
It's okay to cry out loud
Black Rock Shooter 見ていてくれる
Black Rock Shooter, you're watching over me
今から始まるの
It's starting from now
私の物語
My story
忘れそうになったら この歌を
If you're about to forget, sing this song
うたおう〜
Let's sing~
Special Thanks to
all of KFP
Huke papa
Jenma, best Manager
Kanauru
Gojo
KIRA
Astrophysics
Myth Members
Nenechi
Reine
Subaru
Fauna
Henry (Ame's cat)
but especially, particularly,
the one and only
the wonderful and incredible
AMELIA WATSON
thank you for making this possible,
you are so selfless and supportive
you made my dream come true
and my hard work and suffering worth it!
thank you for all that you do for us.
Love,
Kiara