(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
hololive English 1st Concert Merch
Embroidery Keychain & Acrylic Stand
Tapestry, Shoulder Bag & Snapback Cap
Penlight Colors
Connect the World - Fan Messages
Mori Calliope Bundle - PREORDER NOW
hololive English x OMOCAT
Figures from hololive production
#holoENConnect
T-shirt Remix ver.
Essentials Pack
Random Button Badges
Embroidery Keychain & Acrylic Stand
Tapestry, Shoulder Bag & Snapback Cap
Penlight Colors
HYTE - MORI CALLIOPE BUNDLE PREORDER NOW
hololive x OMOCAT - Shop AX Booth #1100
FIGURES FROM hololive production SHOP NOW ON GOODSMILEUS.COM
The concert will be starting soon. Thank you for your patience!
NEW Merch - T-shirt Remix ver.
NEW Merch - Essentials Pack
NEW Merch - Random Button Badges
NEW Merch - Embroidery Keychain & Acrylic Stand
NEW Merch - Tapestry, Shoulder Bag, Snapback Cap
NEW Merch - Penlight Colors
Mori Calliope Bundle PREORDER NOW
OMOCAT × hololive English
FIGURES FROM hololive production
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while until the performance begins.
NEW Merch: T-shirt Remix Ver.
Essentials Pack
Random Button Badges
Merch: Embroidery Keychain & Acrylic Stand
Tapestry / Shoulder Bag / Snapback Cap
Penlight Colors
Connect the World
hololive English 1st Concert
#hololiveENConnect
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までもうしばらくお待ちください。
#hololiveENConnect
Please wait a little longer for the show to start.
NEW Merch
Weiβ Schwarz
hololive production is back with another big round of...
...expanding Weiβ Schwarz.
hololive production Volume 2 Booster Pack, coming soon!
Bushiroad
I know, I know. You guys have been dying for one of these, right?
HYTE. Experience play.
hololive Meet
Connect the World hololive English 1st Concert
Available on the OMOCAT Shop! omocat-shop.com
KIKKERIKI
TAKANASHI KIARA 小鳥遊キアラ
TAKANASHI KIARA
POP UP PARADE TAKANASHI KIARA 5,500JPY / 39.99USD
MORI CALLIOPE BUNDLE PREORDER NOW
Available on the OMOCAT Shop! omocat-shop.com
FIGURES FROM hololive production Shop Now on goodsmileus.com
#holoENConnect The concert will be starting soon.
NEW Merch T-shirt Remix Ver.
Essentials Pack
Random Button Badges
Merch: Embroidery Keychain & Acrylic Stand
Merch: Tapestry, Shoulder Bag, Snapback Cap
Penlight Colors
HYTE Mori Calliope Bundle PREORDER NOW
hololive x OMOCAT
FIGURES FROM hololive production SHOP NOW ON GOODSMILEUS.COM
hololive English 1st Concert -Connect the World-
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a while until the start of the performance.
NEW Merch T-shirt Remix Ver.
Essentials Pack [L, XL, XXL]
Random Button Badges
Merch: Embroidery Keychain / Acrylic Stand
Tapestry / Shoulder Bag / Snapback Cap
Penlight Colors
Connect the World
hololive English 1st Concert
MORI CALLIOPE BUNDLE
PREORDER NOW
www.amocat-shop.com
FIGURES FROM hololive production
SHOP NOW ON GOODSMILEUS.COM
Connect the World
The concert will be starting soon
NEW Merch
T-shirt Remix ver.
Essentials Pack
Random Button Badges
Embroidery Keychain & Acrylic Stand
Tapestry, Shoulder Bag & Snapback Cap
Penlight Colors
HYTE MORI CALLIOPE BUNDLE PREORDER NOW
hololive x OMOCAT
FIGURES FROM hololive production
Connect the World hololive English 1st Concert
公式ハッシュタグ #holoENConnect
Official Hashtag #holoENConnect
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
NEW Merch T-shirt Remix ver.
Essentials Pack
Penlight Colors
MORI CALLIOPE BUNDLE PREORDER NOW
FIGURES FROM hololive production
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while.
hololive 1st Concert NEW Merch
Penlight Colors
公式ハッシュタグ / #holoENConnect
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Official Hashtag / #holoENConnect
The concert will be starting soon.
公式ハッシュタグ / #holoENConnect
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Official Hashtag / #holoENConnect
The concert will be starting soon.
Weiss Schwarz
Hololive Production is back with another big round up!
Expanding Weiss Schwarz...
Hololive Production Volume 2 booster pack coming soon!
Pre-sales at Anime Expo.
Bushiroad.
I know, I know.
You guys have been dying for one of these, right?
KIKKERIKI
The concert will be starting soon.
Welcome.
Welcome to YouTube Theater.
Your safety is our number one priority.
In the event that it becomes necessary
to evacuate YouTube Theater,
please follow these guidelines to walk calmly
out and away from the facility.
Those exiting the floor seats
proceed to the nearest safe stairwell
on either side of the stage.
Continue up the stairs
until you get to an exterior exit.
Once outside, please continue
to walk away from the facility.
...facility.
Those seated in orchestra sections 101 through 105,
walk up the aisles and out onto the concourse.
Those in the box and club areas,
exit out of your box or the club onto the concourse.
Follow directions of YouTube Theater staff,
who will be available to guide you to the nearest safe exit.
If you're seated on the plaza level sections, walk up the aisles,
turn left or right, and proceed out the door.
Those on the balcony level, walk up the aisles onto the concourse,
turn left or right, and continue down the nearest safe stairway
to the ground-level concourse and out the door.
Once outside, please continue to walk away from the facility.
Elevators will not be in service during an emergency evacuation.
YouTube Theater staff will be available to guide and assist you.
For those who are unable to use stairs, YouTube Theater staff
will be available to assist you via an evacuation chair.
This has been the evacuation plan for YouTube Theater.
Thank you for being prepared ahead of time
to respond calmly in an emergency.
Enjoy the event.
Thank you for coming to hololive English 1st Concert -Connect the World-
Supported by Bushiroad at the YouTube Theater
here in Inglewood, California today!
This is Friend-A, also known as A-chan!
The time has finally come.
Today we celebrate the accomplishment of the girls of hololive English
and take another step towards their bright future.
Are you ready to become part of hololive English history?
Alright! Let's go!
Connect the World!
Let's Connect our worlds and have a blast, y'all! HoloEN has been working so hard to make you Smile, now we wanna Connect them all! 大好き!!
Let's Connect our worlds and have a blast, y'all! HoloEN has been working so hard to make you Smile, now we wanna Connect them all! I love you!!
Kikkeriki-! Finally the long awaited day has come! I'm so happy to perform for everyone! Let's make this day the most special one! I want to hear and see you cheer! ENに会いにきてくれてありがとう♡ KFP♡LOVE
Kikkeriki-! Finally the long awaited day has come! I'm so happy to perform for everyone! Let's make this day the most special one! I want to hear and see you cheer! Thanks for coming to see EN ♡ KFP ♡ LOVE
WAH!! It's finally happening!! EN Concert!!! Thank you so much everyone who supported us to make this happen!! I can't wait to see everyone from the stage again! We Are Hype!! See you soon!! Inanis.
Makin' Hololive history! ナイス! Gawr Gura
Makin' Hololive history! Nice! Gawr Gura
We made it! Our First EN Concert & I wanna See you Guys MOVE! Hope you all have light sticks! Can't wait to see every one on stage! Thank you for making this Possible - AME
HiRyS! I am so excited for our FIRST EN Concert! Let's make it an unforgettable memory! たのしみましょう! IRyS
HiRyS! I am so excited for our FIRST EN Concert! Let's make it an unforgettable memory! Let's have fun! IRyS
Kirin LOVE. Oh, hello there. I'm so happy to see everyone. Thank you for listening to my voice today! 大好き♡
Kirin LOVE. Oh, hello there. I'm so happy to see everyone. Thank you for listening to my voice today! I love you ♡
Thank you, everyone! Please look forward to the concert.
Oh hi! :D I'm so happy we can all be here today! I never imagined I'd be able to perform like this for so many people around the world! Thank you for making this possible! いつもありがとうございます!
Oh hi! :D I'm so happy we can all be here today! I never imagined I'd be able to perform like this for so many people around the world! Thank you for making this possible! Thank you as always!
* CONCERT DAY IS HERE!! * Ugi Wogi... am spaghetti... BUT! WE READY TO PUT ON THE BEST SHOW POSSIBLE!! IDOL RAT IS MAKING A COMEBACK! Thank you for all the support, love and support <3 いつも応援してくれてありがとう!! 最強のライブにするぞ!! HOLO EN FOREVER Hakos Baelz
* CONCERT DAY IS HERE!! * Ugi Wogi... am spaghetti... BUT! WE READY TO PUT ON THE BEST SHOW POSSIBLE!! IDOL RAT IS MAKING A COMEBACK! Thank you for all the support, love and support <3 Thank you for always supporting me!! I'm gonna make this the best live ever!! HOLO EN FOREVER Hakos Baelz
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to look toward the same future
あの夢手にしてみたい
I want to try reaching for that dream
それぞれ違った心で走れもっと
With our own distinct hearts, let's run further
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
Sprouting in a place where everything seemed dark
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳(め)奪われた
This tiny hope stole my gaze
不安で揺れる心をうまくチューニングして
Tuning my heart, which was shaking with anxiety
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I was squeezing out every bit of my small courage
あきらめの文字デリートして進む
Deleting the word "give up" and moving forward
苦しい時ももう私は一人じゃないから
Even in painful times, I'm not alone anymore
だからももっと夢追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dreams even more
ワクワク止まらない
This excitement won't stop
想像超えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try accessing it
後悔なんてさせない
I won't let you have any regrets
それぞれ違った心で走れもっと
With our own distinct hearts, let's run further
夜の空に輝く眩しい想いは
These dazzling feelings shining in the night sky
見たことのない光をリアルに届けるよ
Will deliver a light never seen before, for real
いつも聞こえるエールをここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
It makes me want to search for a new light again
君の笑顔を保存して進む
Saving your smile and moving forward
悲しい時に見返すよ力が湧くから
I'll look back at it when I'm sad, it gives me strength
胸を張って夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams with pride
奇跡のストーリー
A story of miracles
一緒に作ろう終わらない夢を
Let's create an endless dream together
愛が待ってたこの世界
This world where love was waiting
それぞれ違った心で彩れ
Color it with our own distinct hearts
悲しい時も寂しい時も信じ合えるものがある
Even in sad or lonely times, there's something we can believe in together
忘れずにこの鼓動鳴らし続けたい
I want to keep this heartbeat going without forgetting
終わらない世界に溢れ出すよ
It'll overflow into this endless world
笑顔　私
Smiles, and me
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my dreams
自分らしく輝きたい
I want to shine in my own way
時に涙して　また笑い合いたい
Sometimes I'll cry, but I want to laugh together again
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
踏み出そう　奇跡の一歩を
Let's take that miraculous first step
いきいきと夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams with vitality
わくわく止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像超えてく　世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination
アクセルふんでみたい
I want to try stepping on the gas
後悔なんてここにはない
There are no regrets here
空超えて誓った心で
With a heart that made a vow across the sky
作ろう
Let's build it
Kikkeriki! Hello everyone!
Hey, hey, hey! What's up everyone, what's up Los Angeles!
We're finally here, Kiara.
Yes! Yes!
Hug me, sister!
Alright!
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing! It's beautiful! So cool!
Everybody, calm down, calm down.
Chill, chill, chill.
Hololive English First Concert Ever...
...'Connect the World' has finally begun!
It's begun everybody!
Let me hear you cheer! Come on, let me hear your voices!
How you doing, how you doing?
The first MC part, the first MC is us...
...Takanashi Kiara, Mori Calliope, from Myth! Hello!
Hey guys! Thank you, thank you!
So the first song was the fan favorite...
...Shiny Smily Story!
SSS! SSS! SSS! SSS!
Alright, calm down, Kiara. Chill, chill.
Sorry, sorry, I'm excited!
She's excited! We started off with a banger though, right everyone?
そうですね！
That's right!
Chill, chill, chill. Everyone's really hyped today. I'm happy.
Yeah, yeah! Well, this is also the first time...
...we've ever had so many Hololive English fans...
...here together in one place.
Yeah, yeah. And also on the stream, too, yeah!
Are you guys watching? Stream camera doko?
Are you guys watching? Where is the stream camera?
Very nice. Alright, I already asked them to do this before...
...but I want them to do it again.
Everyone at the venue, raise your voice, shout as hard as you can!
Second floor, second floor!
I want to hear second floor! Third floor!
First floor! Go, first floor! Come on, use your voice!
So loud, so loud! Wow! Thank you!
Yeah, I think that that is sufficient. Alright, chill, chill, chill.
Oh but can I do one more thing?
What? What do you want to do?
I always do this like everywhere. You guys know what I want to do.
Do you guys know what I want to do?
Oh God, I know what she wants to do.
Yes! I want to do the wave! Can we do the wave?
Don't you think we already hyped them up enough?
No! This is exciting! Gotta use our time! Gotta do the wave!
I don't know why I asked. Alright, fine, let's do it. Come here, come here.
Let's do it! Okay, get ready! I'll go over here...
...and when we reach your point, you raise your arms!
You can even stand up if you want! Yeah!
Okay, are you ready? Here we go! Get ready!
Three, two, one, come on!
Raise 'em up, raise 'em up! Let's go, let's go!
Keep it going, keep it going! Very nice!
And back! Oh God, we're bringing it back!
Go, go, go! We'll bring it back!
Bring it back, bring it back! Motto motto!
Bring it back, bring it back! More, more!
Keep it going, keep it going!
Wonderful, wonderful! Okay, no more, no more wave!
Applause! It's done, it's done.
Thank you! Thanks guys!
I think that they're sufficiently hyped up.
Everybody's real excited, yeah. Don't answer that...
...you don't need to scream anymore.
You don't, you don't. You're gonna lose your voices...
...by the end of the concert.
You're right. We should refrain from hyping them up anymore.
Well, yeah. So we're gonna kick off the solo songs actually from now on.
Gonna hear a lot of EN members' solos.
And we'll give it our best, so please cheer for us!
Alright, very nice. Thank you. And...
It's only just begun!
We ain't gonna stop either...
...and I have confidence that you guys won't either.
You guys will keep the energy going all the way to the end, okay?
Don't stop!
All right, very nice.
So, together...
Three, two, one, let's go!
Connect the World!
Los Angeles!
Are you ready?!
Hey unhappy world ようこそ楽園へ",
Hey unhappy world, welcome to paradise
Into this chaos 吸い込まれて行く",
Into this chaos, getting sucked in
地球もそろそろ回り疲れて飽きちゃう",
The Earth is about to get tired of spinning and get bored
いつまで転がる？",
How long will it roll?
輪廻転生 繰り返される営み",
Samsara, the repeating business of life
邪魔ない正答と道程",
Clear answers and the journey
気取った世をぐちゃ混ぜ混同 召し上がれ",
Mix and confuse this pretentious world, help yourself
悪意が僕をさ 魅了して止まない",
Malice never ceases to fascinate me
硝子の靴を履いたら綺麗ね",
If you wear glass slippers, you're beautiful
罪の重さで木っ端微塵",
Shattered by the weight of sin
愛したいの 害したいの 壊したいの",
I want to love, I want to harm, I want to break
辞めたい世界が僕らを嫌うなら",
If the world we want to leave behind hates us
左胸で踊り狂う嘘つき",
The liar dancing wildly in the left chest
今は亡きしがみついてた被り物",
The now-lost mask I was clinging to
赤い目して おどけ騒ごう",
With red eyes, let's frolic and make a fuss
残酷は天使の面して",
Cruelty wears an angel's mask
震えながら弄んで",
Toying while trembling
弱者の這いじゃ 踏みつけて",
If it's just the crawling of the weak, trample it
サイコ サイコ！",
Psycho, psycho!
治療してよ 加害者はめちゃくちゃ",
Treat me, the perpetrator is a mess
刺してほら その細い針",
Look, prick me with that thin needle
不可解な快楽は 卑でも純真無垢でしょう？",
Mysterious pleasure is pure even if it's base, right?
これが お好きでしょう？",
You like this, don't you?
毒に染まるワイド 独創的な声",
Poisoned wide, original voice
僕はどこまで行けるのかな",
How far can I go?
醜いの 汚いの 美しいの",
Is it ugly? Is it dirty? Is it beautiful?
素晴らしいね 時代よ僕を受け止めて",
It's wonderful, world, accept me
Let me hear you scream!
ほらサイコサイコ 気が利いたよ 愚か者",
Look, psycho psycho, I was thoughtful, you fool
ストレス社会 遊んで",
Play in the stressful society
僕はひたすら この楽園を生き抜いてやる",
I'll just survive in this paradise
左胸で踊り狂う嘘つき",
The liar dancing wildly in the left chest
今は亡きしがみついてた被り物",
The now-lost mask I was clinging to
赤い目して 地を這い踊れ",
With red eyes, crawl on the ground and dance
残酷は天使の面して",
Cruelty wears an angel's mask
震えながら弄んで",
Toying while trembling
僕がいつか飽きるまで",
Until I eventually get bored
ただ 遊べ",
Just play
Look at me, this is my paradise.
Ah, come on, sing it!
弱者の這いじゃ 踏みつけて",
If it's just the crawling of the weak, trample it
サイコ サイコ！",
Psycho, psycho!
That's right, I'm not just a streamer...
...I'm an idol! Let's go L.A.!
A-M-E! Check it out, check it out!
When we first met...
...I wonder what you think of me.
The image was set...
...it was a perfect narrative.
But as time went by, I forgot to hide...
...the laughs that came so naturally.
Through lows and highs...
...I wonder why I ever thought you would leave.
Now no matter where or when we are...
I know it's you I can count on.
Magical, mythical...
...nothing can stop us now. Let's go!
Chiku Taku, where does time go?
Fuwa fuwa, how should I go?
Why it seems when you're here with me...
...the clock won't stop spinning. Fuwa fuwa fuwa!
Doki doki, heart beat faster...
...tomodachi, and forever...
...it's clear to see that...
...mystery was solved immediately, 地球の歪み。
...mystery was solved immediately, the distortion of the Earth.
It's been so long since I laughed so hard I cried.
Now you came along, it happens almost every time.
And then I hear your voice,
I'm left no choice,
but to let you know what you mean to me.
Finally, time to speak,
through treasured memories.
Now no matter where or when we're from,
our friendship's elementary.
Case closed,
now you know,
nothing can stop us now!
Let's go!
Tick-tock, where does the time go?
Wapu-wapu, how should I know?
Why it seems when you're here with me,
the clock won't stop spinning...
Wapu-wapu-wapu-wapu!
ドキドキ、heartbeat faster,
Doki-doki, heartbeat faster,
友達、friends forever,
Tomodachi, friends forever,
here to see that this mystery
was solved immediately,
地球の歪み。
The distortion of the Earth.
Though they say we're older,
what the future holds is not, not, not for us to know yet.
Gone, gone, gone before we know it,
so let's solve the question,
we can make each second
tick-tock, last forever,
wapu-wapu, now or never!
Tick-tock, where does the time go?
Wapu-wapu, how should I know?
Why it seems when you're here with me,
the clock won't stop spinning...
Wapu-wapu-wapu-wapu!
ドキドキ、heartbeat faster,
Doki-doki, heartbeat faster,
友達、friends forever,
Tomodachi, friends forever,
here to see that this mystery
was solved immediately,
地球の歪み！
The distortion of the Earth!
That's right! I'm not just a detective! I'm a time traveler!
Look at this! Rrrrrah!
We're here! Hello! Hi! Yay!
Hi Ame! Hi Ina! Hi everyone!
I'm so excited!
I'm so excited too!
Whoa, Ame. Yeah. Your Chiku-Taku.
Yeah! How'd you like my Chiku-Taku?
Ame, your Chiku-Taku was so...
Stop it!
Stay over there.
Stay on that side.
Oh no! I'm sorry.
The solo parts have begun!
Yeah, and Ina's dancing... it was so good.
Oh my goodness, she's always so good at dancing.
She's such a good dancer! Ah!
Right, it's thanks to all of you guys that support us
that we can perform live here!
So thank you! Thank you!
YouTube Theater!
I know! Can you... I've never been here before.
I know! It's so fun!
Hi everyone! Way out there!
Hi! You, you, I see you!
I see you, you and you! Tomodachi right there!
I see you, you and you! Friends right there!
I know there's one right there!
I know, can you... it's almost three years since we debuted,
guys! Like, did you ever imagine?
Standing in YouTube Theater, like, performing live?
I couldn't imagine it being like this, no.
It's crazy! It's so cool!
This place is huge!
I know.
Okay, there's one thing I really, really wanted to try.
One thing?
Are you guys ready?
I say wah, you say wah!
Wah!
WAH!
Wah-hoo! That was pretty good!
Yeah! That was pretty loud!
It's like, I don't know, it's so unreal hearing you guys.
I don't know, it kind of sounded like
one side was louder than the other.
Oh, you sure?
Yeah, I think we have to test it.
We have to test it! Yeah.
You guys can cheer or say wah, whatever you want.
Yeah, no cursing!
Which side did you choose?
This side? That side?
I picked this side!
That side?
Okay, I got this side!
All right! You want to go first?
I'll go first!
All right, my side, Ame Team, Team Ame!
Okay, I'm counting to three, okay?
One, two, three!
Yeah! Let's go!
Ame, that seemed a little quiet.
No, no, no!
All right, this side!
You guys know what's up, right?
You guys are ready?
せーの、Cheer!
One, two, cheer!
I can't hear you!
All right, we'll just say it was a tie.
Okay, it was a tie, you know?
I'm all for peace.
Yeah.
Well, we do have an important announcement...
...for those of you watching the live stream.
Hello, live viewers on YouTube!
Well, unfortunately the YouTube sneak peek ends here!
Guys, get out of here!
Uh, the solo parts will continue...
...and who do you guys think is next?
Who's next?
Who's that? Who's that?
Who? Who?
Blue? Someone blue?
Is that...
...stinky? Stinky fish?
Goob? Gooba?
Who's next?
So, if you'd like to continue watching...
...please buy the streaming ticket...
...on one of the available streaming platforms.
Ina...
I'm sure there are some Japanese fans watching too...
...so could you please explain to them in Japanese? お願いします。
...so could you please explain to them in Japanese? Please.
あ、ちょっと待って。日本語上手カード出してくるわ。
Ah, hold on. Let me pull out my Nihongo Jouzu card.
えー、この放送を見てる日本の皆さん！
To all the Japanese fans watching this broadcast!
えーと、残念ですが...
Um, unfortunately...
...YouTubeのチラ見せは、あー、ここで終了になります。
...the YouTube sneak peek will end here.
ソロパートは、あー、これからも続きますので...
The solo parts will continue from here on out...
ぜひぜひ、あの、ストリームサイトで見てください。
...so please, please watch on the streaming site.
次はぐらちゃんです！ういー！
Next up is Gura-chan! Wee!
Yeah, Gura-chan!
じゃ、あの、各プラットフォームの、あの、有料視聴チケット買って...
So, please buy the paid streaming ticket on each platform...
...見てくださいね！
...and watch, okay?
いやー、日本語難しいね。
Man, Japanese is hard.
Oh, thank you, Ina!
It's an ancient language.
We hope you all continue to enjoy...
Connect the World!
Okay, since we're here live, we can do this.
You guys can join us in saying this.
If we say 'Se-no'...
...you're going to say 'Connect the World' with us, okay?
Okay!
You want to say 'Se-no'? Should I say 'Se-no'?
You say 'Se-no'.
Okay, okay.
Se-no!
Connect the World!
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！