(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
supported by Pocky ACL
Ayunda Risu
Kureiji Ollie
Vestia Zeta
Moona Hoshinova
Anya Melfissa
Kaela Kovalskia
Airani Iofifteen
Pavolia Reine
Kobo Kanaeru
TERIMA KASIH!
THANK YOU!
BERKAT KALIAN, KAMI BISA BERSINAR. BERIBU-RIBU TERIMA KASIH
THANKS TO YOU ALL, WE CAN SHINE. THOUSANDS OF THANK YOUS.
TERIMA KASIH UDAH BIKIN STAGE INI & HIDUP KAMI LEBIH BERWARNA!
THANK YOU FOR MAKING THIS STAGE AND OUR LIVES MORE COLORFUL!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank You!!
TERIMA KASIH BANYAK!!!!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!!!!
Terima Kasih!! Kalian Semua Keren BGT!!
Thank You!! You All Are So Cool!!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank You!!
Makasih ya!!
Thanks!!
terima kasih
thank you
Ayo mulai!!
Let's start!!
CHROMATIC FUTURE hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も
Body and soul
この手で make you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine
Oh baby I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby I need you, I need you forever
君を見るたび 上書きされてく欲望に
Every time I look at you, my desires are overwritten
重なる Eyes, Eyes, Eyes
Our Eyes, Eyes, Eyes meet
胸を刺す Smile, Smile, Smile
That Smile, Smile, Smile pierces my heart
ねぇ その姿形 全てが拍車かけてく
Hey, your figure and form, everything just spurs me on
恋より 愛, 愛, 愛
More than a crush, it's Love, Love, Love
毎秒可笑しくなってく
Every second, I'm losing my mind
手を伸ばせばもう届く距離 至近距離で試したい
If I reach out, you're within reach; I want to test it at close range
穏やかに恋したい どんなシーンも私に見せて
I want to love peacefully; show me every single scene of you
このまま Stay by my side どこにも行かないで
Just like this, Stay by my side; don't go anywhere
早く奪い去って 純粋な愛だから
Hurry and snatch me away, because it's pure love
止められない感情 その腕で抱きしめてよ
This unstoppable emotion, hold me in those arms of yours
ずっとここからじゃ ずっともっと近くで
From this distance, always; forever even closer
見つめ合いたい
I want our eyes to meet
狂おしいほど
So much it's maddening
持て余すだけなら Fly
If it's too much to handle, then Fly
Tell me what's wrong with me
名も無き空想だし
It's just a nameless fantasy
君の全部知りたい I do need you 今すぐ
I want to know everything about you, I do need you right now
最初は声を聞く それだけでよかった
At first, just hearing your voice was enough for me
だけど次第に Why 我がままになった
But gradually, Why... I became selfish
誰かに微笑みかける その仕草に苛立ち
Seeing you smile at someone else, that gesture makes me irritated
隠せない自分に気づいた 独り占めしたい
I realized I can't hide my feelings, I want you all to myself
一層鎖に繋いで
Chain me up even tighter
二人きりの部屋 至近距離
Alone in a room, at close range
強引な発言制したい 想い捨てて眠りたい
I want to silence your forced words, I want to discard my thoughts and sleep
君の吐息感じさせて
Let me feel your breath
Stay by your side
どこにも行かせない
I won't let you go anywhere
早く奪い去って 私だけに依存してね
Hurry and snatch me away, just be dependent on me
色づく愛 全てを受け止めてよ
My love taking color, take it all in
ああ私たち だとしても息ができない
Oh, the two of us, even so I can't breathe
行かないで
Don't leave
狂おしいほど
So much it's maddening
止めきかせない絶対
I can't stop it, definitely
Tell me what's wrong with me
名も無き空想だし
It's just a nameless fantasy
君の全部知りたい I do need you 今すぐ
I want to know everything about you, I do need you right now
目を閉じたら 止めどない愛が 溢れたい
When I close my eyes, an endless love wants to overflow
Love you...
私の愛だけ
Only my love...
Stay by my side
二度と離れないで 早く奪い去って
Never leave me again, hurry and snatch me away
純粋な愛だから
Because it's pure love
奪い去ってゆくから
Because I'll snatch it away
酩酊で
In a state of intoxication
止められない感情
Unstoppable emotions
そう、もっと抱きしめてよ
Yes, hold me tighter
遠くから通う ずっともっと近くで
Coming from afar, always much closer
認め合いたい
I want us to acknowledge each other
はだける衝動 持て余した心なら Rust
If it's a bursting impulse, a heart I can't handle, Rust
Tell me what's wrong with me
何者でもない僕たち
We are nobodies
意味の全部知りたい
I want to know all the meanings
I need you 今すぐ
I need you right now
Oh baby I need you I need you ずっと
Oh baby I need you I need you forever
逃げるなら今だしよ 勝利を願っちゃって！
If you're gonna run, now's the time, pray for victory!
Happy Birthday!
This is HoloID!
Let's go party together! OK!
Are you a winner? ほら明日へ向かって
Are you a winner? Look, towards tomorrow
夢見なさい every 15 minutes
Dream every 15 minutes
眠り覚めて反芻して ほら
Wake up and ruminate, look
誰か純正スキャニング
Someone is pure scanning
A and B ではスタンバイナウ
On A and B, standby now
もう正直飽き飽きなんですよ
Honestly, I'm already tired of it
彷徨う残酷 私には知の味ね
Wandering cruelty, it's the taste of knowledge to me
爛漫 罪と選択 目を晦ます山と B-20
Fate, sin, and choice, the mountain that dazes my eyes and B-20
お行儀良くなる子なんかより 出したい忠実度
Rather than a well-behaved child, I want to show my fidelity
Day by day 正体 あらあら
Day by day, true identity, oh my
言ったこと全部ピンを刺した
Pinned down everything you said
笑ってくれたっていいさ トラップは乱れ狂うのさ
It's okay to laugh, the traps are going wild
Victory to the World end!
手に入れた場所の感動は きっとかけがえのないはずよ
The emotion of the place we attained must surely be irreplaceable
見て 見てよこの今日に いらっしゃって！
Look, look at this today, and join us!
断固たるメロディを吸い込みたい
I want to inhale the determined melody
段階並べた御作法
Manners arranged in stages
高過ぎる境界線の上 ここはどうしようかな
Above the border that's too high, what should I do here?
拾い上げたワン切り
The one-call I picked up
葛藤は私を強くしていくわ
The conflict will make me stronger
ポジショニング 高所から覗かれるのは尺で
Being peeked at from a high place, it's annoying
お仕置き会 1, 2, 3
Punishment session 1, 2, 3
死ぬのは嫌で Trip to Trip
I hate dying, trip to trip
気が付いたらロンリーデイ
Before I knew it, it's a lonely day
あれれ 隠れていたっけ
Oh my, I was just hiding
ないでないで 煩いで 鐘が鳴るなら
Don't cry, it's annoying, if the bell rings
邪魔な奴全部はキャンセル
Cancel all the annoying ones
ナイセー やめないさ これが 私の原動力になるとも知らずにね
Nice, I won't stop, without knowing this will be my driving force
Victory to the World end!
共に作る歓喜の詩 圧倒的にたまらないわ
The song of joy we make together is overwhelmingly irresistible
心地よいこの今日に 君染まっちゃって！
In this pleasant today, get dyed in it!
Comifuro!
Ayo nyanyi bareng!
Let's sing together!
Ayo nyanyi juga!
Let's sing too!
Ayo mana suaranya!
Come on, where's your voice!
BPM 走っちゃって
Running with the BPM
Hey I am ぶれないで
Hey I am, don't waver
Day by day 潜って まだまだ 降り立つ真理へ 乾杯とって
Day by day diving, let's keep going towards the truth that descends, take a toast
笑ってくれたっていいさ トラップはみんないつか チャンピオンを這い出すだけ
It's okay to laugh, everyone will crawl out as champions from the traps someday, as long as you wish
Victory to the World end!
絶対追い抜く あの光で 雪辱を
I'll definitely overtake you, revenge with that light
忘れられないほどの 勝利を願っちゃって！
Pray for a victory that is unforgettable!
境界を行こう GG
Let's go to the border, GG!
（ため息）
(Sigh)
Siapa di sini yang lelah dengan kehidupan?
Who here is tired of life?
Aku! Aku!
Me! Me!
Kalau capek enaknya gimana nih, Holohiro?
If you're tired, what's a good way to relax, Holohiro?
Malas saja! Cakep!
Just be lazy! Nice!
Bukannya sudah biasa...
Isn't it already common...
...ditikam oleh kecewa?
...to be stabbed by disappointment?
Aduh...
Ouch...
Saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya
When the world doesn't go the way it should
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya kau coba lepaskan saja
Maybe it's time you tried to let it go
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
No need to ask why anymore
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If you can't find the answer
Jangan tangisi coba lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry, try to go through the puzzles
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You're stronger than you think
Dah lah saja oh dah lah saja, jalani saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be, just live it
Mau di mana lagi
Where else could it be?
Walau kadang mati rasa
Even if it's sometimes numb
Bahkan hingga tak berdaya
Even to the point of helplessness
Dan usahamu terasa sia-sia
And your efforts feel in vain
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If you can't find the answer
Jangan tangisi coba lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry, try to go through the puzzles
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You're stronger than you think
Dah lah saja oh dah lah saja, jalani saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be, just live it
Lepas semua kendali
Let go of all control
Tancap gas dan berlari
Hit the gas and run
Terima dan sudahi
Accept it and end it
Comic Frontier! Konbanwa!
Comic Frontier! Good evening!
Konbanwa! Comic Frontier! Konbanwa!
Good evening! Comic Frontier! Good evening!
Welcome to Hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future!
Wah, gila gila gila. Makasih banyak semuanya udah pada datang ke konser 5 tahun kita ya!
Wow, this is crazy. Thank you so much for coming to our 5th anniversary concert!
Wah, nggak berasa nggak sih udah 5 tahun aja?
Wow, doesn't it feel like it's been 5 years already?
Kalau gitu, kita mulai dari perkenalan diri dulu nggak sih? Mulai dari aku-aku!
So, shall we start with introductions? Starting with me!
Aaa, mission start!
Aku Vestia Zeta dari Hololive Indonesia Gen 3. Nice to meet you!
I'm Vestia Zeta from Hololive Indonesia Gen 3. Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you, Zeta!
Kaelo, grinding every time, the blacksmith from Hololive ID Gen 3!
I'm Kaela Kovalskia. Nice to meet you all!
Nice to meet you, Kaelo!
Hoi, Boke-boke-boke! Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
Kobokers, mana suaranya?!
Kobokers, let me hear you!
Nah bertiga, kami dari Hololive Indonesia Gen 3, holoh3ro!
The three of us, we are Hololive Indonesia Gen 3, holoh3ro!
Wah, nggak nyangka juga deh konser 5th anniversary Hololive ID ini akhirnya ada juga.
Wow, I didn't expect the Hololive ID 5th anniversary concert would finally happen.
Dari lagu pertama aja udah keren banget, guys. Kerasa nggak sih semangatnya?
Even from the first song it's been so cool, guys. Can you feel the passion?
Seru banget ya? Iya nggak sih? Iya nggak sih?
So much fun, right? Isn't it? Isn't it?
Banget! Parah sih.
Definitely! It's crazy.
Ada adrenalin rush kan ya?
There's an adrenaline rush, right?
Pengen lari aku rasanya nih.
I feel like running right now.
Woi, woi, woi, woi! Mau ke mana?!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Where are you going?!
Mau ke mana? Mau ke mana?!
Where are you going? Where are you going?!
Yah, yah, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Hey, hey, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Nanti keringetan lho! Nanti keringetan.
You'll get all sweaty! You'll get sweaty.
Aduh. Kalo Kaela gimana?
Phew. How about you, Kaela?
Aduh, seru banget.
Man, it's so much fun.
Aku nggak nyangka sih sampe aku bisa ada di sini ya.
I never thought I'd be able to be here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong konsernya masih panjang banget.
But by the way, this concert is still very long.
Jadi kalian tetep semangat ya sampe akhir!
So stay enthusiastic until the end!
張り切ろう！
Let's stay fired up!
Semangat, semangat, semangat, semangat!
Stay fired up, go, go, go!
Eh, tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi...
But we've been talking about the concert...
...emang pada tahu judul konsernya apa?
...but do you guys know the title?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah "Chromatic Future"!
Our concert title this time is "Chromatic Future"!
Ada yang tahu nggak artinya apa? Ayo absen!
Does anyone know what it means? Sound off!
Nah, ini... Kobo paling tahu.
Now, this... Kobo knows best.
Nih, ah... yang jelasin yang paling tinggi.
Well... the tallest one should explain.
Yuk, let's go!
Come on, let's go!
Segitu ya? Ya udahlah, ya udahlah.
Is that how it is? Fine then, fine.
Nih ya, guys ya, buat kalian yang belum tahu...
Alright, guys, for those of you who don't know...
"Chromatic Future" itu artinya tuh...
"Chromatic Future" means...
...masa depan yang berwarna-warni.
...a colorful future.
Jadi karena Hololive Indonesia kan udah lima tahun nih.
So, since Hololive Indonesia is already five years old.
Kita sama-sama dari hari satu sampe sekarang.
We've been together from day one until now.
Nah, jadi itu untuk ke depannya kita tuh harapannya...
So, for the future, our hope is...
...kita bisa nyiptain waktu dan memori yang berwarna-warni...
...we can create colorful times and memories...
...sama seluruh fans dari Hololive Indonesia!
...with all the Hololive Indonesia fans!
Ya gitu! Betul Kaela Kovalskia! Catat, catat!
That's right! Correct, Kaela Kovalskia! Note it down!
Iya, iya, iya, iya!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Nah, kalian sekarang udah pada tahu 'kan?
So, you all know now, right?
Karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
Because Kaela explained it earlier.
Kalo gitu, konsernya 'kan udah mulai nih.
In that case, the concert has already started.
Kalian mau nge-post soal konser ini di medsos...
If you want to post about this concert on social media...
jangan lupa hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture ya!
don't forget the hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture!
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh...
Because we really want to see your...
apa sih? Pengen lihat semangat kalian!
what's it called? We want to see your passion!
Ya, itu! Betul banget, iya nggak?
Yes, that! Absolutely right, isn't it?
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
Don't make typos, don't make typos!
Asyik! Share ke semua, oke?
Awesome! Share it with everyone, okay?
Tapi, jujur deh. Kalian tuh pas dibilang...
But, honestly. When you were told...
kita bakal konser lho di Indonesia,
we were going to have a concert in Indonesia,
kalian pada kaget nggak sih?
were you guys surprised?
Halo? Ada yang dengerin?
Hello? Is anyone listening?
Oh, iya, iya! Betul! Aku setuju juga.
Oh, yes, yes! Right! I agree too.
Aku merasakan empati terhadap...
I felt empathy for...
...ini, adik saya Zeta.
...well, my little sister Zeta.
Iya empati, iya, iya.
Yeah, empathy, sure, sure.
Kalo Kaela gimana, Kaela Kovalskia?
How about you, Kaela Kovalskia?
Aku juga waktu itu nggak nyangka banget kayak...
I also didn't expect it at all, like...
"Hah? Beneran? Ini riil nih?" gitu 'kan?
"Huh? Really? Is this real?" right?
Kayak "Lho, bisa gitu? Akhirnya!"
Like "Wait, how? Finally!"
Mana udah bersembilan di Indonesia pula, 'kan?
Especially since all nine of us are in Indonesia, right?
Keren banget!
So cool!
Keren banget, iya!
So cool, yes!
Ini 'kan konser pertama Hololive Indonesia yang bersembilan.
This is Hololive Indonesia's first concert with all nine.
Sebenernya tuh nggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar
Actually, this is not only the biggest
dan terpenting juga untuk fans
and most important moment for fans
Hololive Indonesia...
of Hololive Indonesia...
tapi seluruh dunia juga pasti bakal nonton, nggak sih?
but the whole world will surely watch it too, right?
Iya nggak? Jawab!
Don't you think? Answer me!
Iya, iya! Makasih, makasih semuanya.
Yes, yes! Thank you, thank you everyone.
Eit, tapi tentu aja ini pencapaiannya
Wait, but of course this achievement
nggak bakal cuma sampe di sini aja 'kan?
won't just stop here, right?
Jadi next-nya mungkin kita bisa apa ya?
So next, maybe we can... what?
Dominating the world, gitu!
Dominate the world!
We are ready! Ready, ready, ready, ready!
Betul banget, Kaela, Zeta!
Absolutely right, Kaela, Zeta!
Selain dari dukungan fans in this opportunity...
In addition to the fan support on this occasion,
kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih
we also want to say thank you
untuk semua sponsor yang mendukung
to all the sponsors who supported
terjadinya konser ini!
the realization of this concert!
Terima kasih!
Thank you!
Terima kasih! Makasih! Makasih semuanya! Uh!
Thank you! Thanks! Thanks everyone! Whoo!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Eh, tapi ngomong-ngomong di konser ini...
But by the way, in this concert...
kayaknya ada yang beda nggak sih?
doesn't something seem different?
Ela, kamu nyadar nggak? Soalnya kamu paling peka 'kan?
Ela, did you notice? Since you're the most attentive.
Eits... ya sadarlah.
Wait... of course I noticed.
Kalo Kobo mah nggak bakalan sadar.
Kobo wouldn't have noticed, though.
Nih, nih, nih, nih. Yang beda tuh kali ini tuh model kita.
Here, look. What's different is our models.
Ini model baru nih!
These are new models!
Ooooh! Kawaii! Gemas banget!
Ooooh! So cute! So adorable!
Kamera, kamera! Kameranya deketin ke aku!
Camera, camera! Bring the camera closer to me!
Nah, mulai, mulai...
There she goes...
Iya, nih, nih. Kalian mau lihat keimutan Kobo nih, nih...
Yes, look. You guys want to see Kobo's cuteness...
Oshiri? Eh? Oh... eh, eh, eh!
Butt? Eh? Oh... wait, wait, wait!
Woi, woi, woi, woi!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Ini kamera diambil Kobo semua nggak sih?
Is the camera being taken over by Kobo completely?
Ini ke aku juga, aku juga, aku juga!
Look at me too, me too, me too!
Jangan cuma Kobo!
Not just Kobo!
Ichi, ni, san... Hai, owari! Kobo no ban desu!
One, two, three... Okay, finished! It's Kobo's turn!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Mulai, mulai... semua kamera diambil!
Starting again... taking all the cameras!
Oke, oke, oke.
Okay, okay, okay.
Kalo gitu...
In that case...
Sampai kehabisan napas!
I'm out of breath!
Jangan rebutan di depan konser!
Don't fight in the middle of the concert!
Haaai...
Okaaaay...
Iya, iya, iya, iya!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Hayo, Zeta kalo udah marah galak lho.
Watch out, Zeta is scary when she's angry.
はいよ ゼータが怒ると怖いからね
Alright, because Zeta's scary when she's angry.
Enggak, bukan.
No, it's not.
Tapi kalau Zeta udah ngomong...
But if Zeta has already spoken...
Takut kan?
Scary, right?
もういいや ゼータがカメラを独り占めしちゃダメっていうのは…うーん、しょうがない
Fine, Zeta said I can't hog the camera... well, it can't be helped.
Iya, iya, udah deh.
Yeah, yeah, fine.
Kalau enggak boleh rebutan kamera sama Zeta,
If I'm not allowed to fight for the camera with Zeta,
mmm... shoganai.
mmm... it can't be helped.
ファンのみんなと遊ぼう！さっきみんなからも大きな声もらってたわけだし、今度はこっちがみんなに大きな声をだしたいっす！
Let's play with the fans! Since we got a lot of loud cheers from everyone earlier, now I want us to shout back at everyone!
Kita main aja deh sama penonton-chan.
Let's just play with Penonton-chan.
Kobo pengen deh coba kita teriakin penonton, karena kan tadi mereka sudah teriakin kita.
Kobo wants us to try shouting at the audience, because they already shouted at us earlier.
はいはいはい！ そうっすよ、カエラの配信時間ほど長くはならないから安心して
Yeah yeah yeah! That's right, don't worry, it won't be as long as Kaela's streaming hours.
Iya, iya, iya.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maksudnya, kita teriakin intro kita bareng penonton-tachi.
I mean, let's shout our intro together with the audience.
Betul!
Exactly!
そう！みんなにじゃなく、みんなとね
そうそう！そういうことっす！
Yeah! Not 'at' everyone, but 'with' everyone.
Yeah yeah! That's it!
Teriaknya bareng penonton, jangan teriakin penontonnya.
Shout with the audience, don't shout at the audience.
Iya, gitu maksudnya.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
だってこれから歌わなきゃいけないからまず声を温存しなきゃでしょ？
Because we have to sing after this, so we should save our voices first, right?
Soalnya kan habis ini kita harus nyanyi,
Because we have to sing after this,
jadi kita harus simpen suara dulu enggak sih?
so shouldn't we save our voices first?
そうっすよ、カエラの配信時間ほど長くはならないから安心して
That's right, don't worry, it won't be as long as Kaela's streaming hours.
Betul ya. Enggak bakal sama itu, tenang aja
That's right. It won't be that long, don't worry,
enggak bakal selama durasi stream Kaela gitu ya guys ya.
it won't be as long as Kaela's stream duration, okay guys?
まあいい 大声出していいから好きにして
Well fine, you can shout as much as you want, so go ahead.
Ya udahlah, mau teriak-teriak, ya udah.
Well whatever, if you want to shout, fine.
Aku enggak masalah lah, aku ikut.
I don't mind, I'm in.
みんな準備はいいかな？
Is everyone ready?
Gimana nih semuanya, udah siap belum?
How about it everyone, are you ready yet?
Siap enggak?
Are you ready?
もう出来てるのかよ！っね！じゃあここから！
Are you already ready?! Right! Then from here!
Siap nih kayaknya. Oke, Kobo dulu ya.
Seems like they're ready. Okay, Kobo's turn first.
一緒に「BOKOBOKOBOKO!」って叫ぼう！よろしくよ！
Let's shout "BOKOBOKOBOKO!" together! Let's go!
Aku mau kita sama-sama teriak: 'BOKOBOKOBOKO!'.
I want us to shout together: "BOKOBOKOBOKO!".
Oke? Siap ya?
Okay? Ready?
いち、に、さん！
One, two, three!
BOKOBOKOBOKO!
いいわねいいわね！次はゼータ！
Nice, nice! Next is Zeta!
Seka-seka! Giliran Zeta,
Nice, nice! Zeta's turn,
giliran Zeta.
Zeta's turn.
「ミッションスタート！」って言ったら一緒に「スタート！」って言うわね！
When I say "Mission Start!", you all shout "Start!" together, okay?
Pas aku bilang 'Mission Start-o',
When I say "Mission Start-o",
kalian bareng-bareng teriak 'Start-o' ya.
you all shout "Start-o" together, okay?
いい？アアア！ミッション...
Ready? Ahh! Mission...
スタート！
START!
次はカエラ！
Next is Kaela!
Oke, habis ini Kaela.
Okay, next is Kaela.
よしよし！きてみんは、そしてholoh3roも
「holoh3ro!」って言ったら「HU-HA!」で返してね！簡単でしょ？
Alright! Kitemin, and holoh3ro too.
When I say "holoh3ro!", respond with "HU-HA!" Easy, right?
Nih ya buat semua penonton sama Holohiro juga,
Alright, for all the audience and Holohiro too,
kalau misalnya aku bilang 'Holohiro!',
if I say "Holohiro!",
kalian bilang 'Hu-Ha!'. Gampang kan?
you say "Hu-Ha!". Easy, right?
さあさあさあ！準備はいい？ holoh3ro!
Come on, come on! Are you ready? holoh3ro!
Langsung, langsung, langsung.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oke ya, siap ya. Holohiro!
Okay, ready. Holohiro!
HU-HA!
いいわねいいわね！
Nice, nice!
Mantap, mantap!
Great, great!
いいわ、ついに3期生は息ぴったり
そうね、まだまだ元気が余りそうだわ
Nice, Gen 3 is finally in sync.
Yeah, looks like there's still plenty of energy left.
Keren-keren-keren.
Cool, cool, cool.
Akhirnya Gen 3 kompak juga.
Finally, Gen 3 is in sync.
Iya kompak kelihatannya, masih pada semangat nih ya.
Yeah, looks in sync, everyone's still energetic.
だって、今日の一曲目だよ。でももうすごく伝わってくるんだもん
みんなまさか私たちの1曲目が「100%」だなんて思ってた？
Because it was our first song today. But it already resonates so much.
Did everyone expect our first song to be "100%"?
Soalnya dari lagu pertama kita hari ini aja udah kerasa banget.
Because from our first song today, it already felt so strong.
Kalian tuh pada nyangka enggak sih
Did you guys expect
kalau lagu pertama kita tuh bakal '100%'?
that our first song would be "100%"?
思うわけないよな。私もびっくりした
ホシノヴァ気分でライブ開始だなんて！すごいいよね？
No way. I was surprised too.
Starting the live with a Hoshinova vibe! Amazing, right?
Mana ada yang nyangka,
No one would have expected that,
aku aja sendiri enggak nyangka juga.
even I didn't expect it.
Langsung dibuka dengan 'Hoshinova mode' gitu,
Starting right off with "Hoshinova mode" like that,
keren banget kan.
it was so cool, right?
やばい！
Crazy!
Asik, asik.
Nice, nice.
かっこいいっすね。しかもさっきゼータと…いや違う
ゼータとカエラが歌った時はもう本家の「100%」みたいっす
It was so cool. Especially when Zeta and... wait no.
When Zeta and Kaela sang, it was just like the original "100%".
Keren banget sih, apalagi tadi
It was really cool, especially earlier
Zeta sama nyanyi... Zeta sama nyanyi.
when Zeta sang... Zeta sang.
Zeta sama Kaela nyanyi '100%'
Zeta and Kaela singing "100%"
tuh udah kayak real '100%' ya.
was like the real "100%".
マジかっこよすぎなんだけど、なんか, うーっ！ってなってっさ！
あんんなにかっこいい歌を歌ったことあるのかな？
It was seriously too cool, I was like "Uhh!"!
I wonder if they've ever sung such a cool song before?
Itu tuh bisa enggak sih, enggak sekeren tadi?
Could you not be that cool?
Aku tuh jadi pengen kayak... 'Uh! Uh!' gitu kan.
I felt like... "Uh! Uh!" like that.
Kalian pernah enggak sih nyanyi lagu sekeren tadi?
Have you guys ever sung a song as cool as that?
かっこつけてんの？
Are you acting cool?
Aura farming ya.
Aura farming, huh.
そう、かっこつけてる。本物のかっこつけ
だってムーナの曲かっこいいもん
Yeah, acting cool. Real cool guys.
Because Moona's song is so cool.
Aura farming sesungguhnya.
Real aura farming.
Keren banget emang lagunya Moona.
Moona's song is indeed very cool.
だってゼータがいつもスタイリッシュとかジャズっぽい曲ばっかだしよ？
だからさっき「100%」を歌った時、めっちゃ雰囲気が違う
Because Zeta usually does stylish or jazz-like songs?
So when you sang "100%" earlier, the vibe was totally different.
Emang, kan Zeta kan soalnya biasanya lagu-lagu
Indeed, because Zeta usually does songs
yang stylish, yang jazzy-jazzy gitu.
that are stylish, jazzy.
Jadi tadi pas dinyanyiin tuh ya '100%',
So when you sang "100%" earlier,
rasanya jadi beda banget vibe-nya.
the vibe felt totally different.
しかもカエラのラップも！
And Kaela's rap too!
Terus Kaela juga tadi ngerap ya.
And then Kaela was rapping too.
Tadatadatada... kayak apa itu?
Kobo imitating the rap sounds.
とにかくかっこよかった！すごいわ！
でも、それだけじゃないよ！次の曲が「NEWzOMBIE!!」でした！
Anyway, it was cool! Amazing!
But that's not all! The next song was "NEWzOMBIE!!".
Iya, pokoknya keren banget,
Yeah, anyway it was so cool,
keren banget ya tadi.
really cool earlier.
Tapi habis ini tuh masih ada lagi, 'NEWzOMBIE!!'.
But after this, there's still more, "NEWzOMBIE!!".
これだれの曲かわかるよね？
もちろんっだよ、うちの先輩だ
You know whose song this is, right?
Of course, it's our senior's.
Ayo, pada tahu dong ini lagu siapa.
Come on, you guys should know whose song this is.
Tahu lah, tahu lah, senpai kita, senpai kita.
Of course, of course, our senior, our senior.
holoroのパフォーマンスもめっちゃかっこよかったよ。まるでゲームの中にいるみたいだった
そうっわ！しかもバックダンサーもいたし
holoro's performance was also really cool. It felt like being in a game.
Right! And there were back dancers too.
Tadi tuh itu ya, Holoro tuh perform-nya
Earlier, Holoro's performance
juga keren banget kayak lagi di game gitu.
was also really cool, like being in a game.
Betul, setuju. Terus tadi ada back dancer-nya men.
Exactly, I agree. And there were back dancers, man.
かっこよかったっすね！
It was cool, right!
Keren ya guys, keren enggak?
It was cool, right guys? Wasn't it cool?
かっこいい！他になんかあったかな？レーザーも花火も…と
Cool! What else was there? Lasers, fireworks... and so on.
Keren! Ada apa lagi tuh tadi? Lampu laser,
Cool! What else was there? Laser lights,
terus ada efek kembang api segala.
and then firework effects and everything.
すごいギミックがたくさんあったっすわ！
There were a lot of amazing gimmicks!
Terus banyak lah ya gimmick-gimmick yang wow.
And there were a lot of wow gimmicks.
あのバックダンサーたちあたしのソロライブに雇うっす
I'm gonna hire those back dancers for my solo live.
Itu back dancer nanti aku hire semua ya buat solo konser aku.
I'm gonna hire those back dancers for my solo concert.
おっと、もうソロライブの話？
Whoa, talking about solo lives already?
Wah, udah ngomong solo konser aja.
Whoa, talking about a solo concert already.
まあ言葉も祈りってやつ
Well, words are like prayers.
Ya omongan adalah doa ya.
Well, words are prayers.
でもこのライブはまだ終わらないよ！まだあと！
But this live isn't over yet! There's still more!
Tapi konser yang ini belum selesai.
But this concert isn't over yet.
Belum, belum, belum.
Not yet, not yet.
でも…さっき何の歌を歌ったか知ってる？
But... do you know what song we sang just now?
Eh tapi, kalian tahu enggak sih
But wait, do you guys know
sebelum ini tuh nyanyinya lagu apa?
what song was sung before this?
もちろんっだよ。私の新しい曲だから
Of course. Because it's my new song.
Ets, aku mah tahu banget lah,
Heh, I definitely know,
itu lagu terbaru aku. Dahlah.
it's my newest song. "Dahlah".
そうっすね。まあいいや。まあいい
Right. Well anyway. Fine.
Iya, udah, enggak usah dibahas.
Yeah, fine, no need to discuss it.
Dahlah.
Whatever.
いやいや！タイトルは「dahlah.」だよ！「dahlah.」！
No no! The title is "dahlah."! "dahlah."!
Lho kok gitu? Itu tuh maksudnya judulnya Dahlah,
Hey, why like that? I meant the title is "Dahlah",
lagunya judulnya Dahlah.
the song title is "Dahlah".
おおなるほど
「dahlah.」だったか…まあわざとだったけど
「dahlah.」だったか。先に言ってよ！
Oh, I see.
It was "dahlah."... well, it was on purpose.
It was "dahlah.". You should've said so first!
Ooh, dahlah... ya dahlah.
Ooh, dahlah... yeah, dahlah.
Bilang dong. Sengaja sih.
You should've said so. I was doing it on purpose.
だっていつもそれ言ってるじゃん。本当に「まあいいや」って思ってた
Because you're always saying that. I thought it really meant "whatever".
Habisnya kamu kan sering 'dahlah, dahlah' gitu, jadi dikira emang beneran dahlah.
Because you often say "dahlah, dahlah" like that, so I thought it was really just "dahlah" [whatever].
それ言って帰ると思ってた。いやいや、かわいそうだから
I thought you'd say that and go home. No no, that's sad.
Entar dahlah, dahlah, pulang dia.
Next thing you know, she says "dahlah, dahlah" and goes home.
Jangan nanti, kasihan nanti dia.
Don't, poor her.
じゃあ「dahlah.」ってどういう意味？
So what does "dahlah." mean?
Kalau gitu, dahlah tuh maksudnya apa sih?
So what does "dahlah" mean anyway?
人生はしょうがないって意味
人生は重いから「まあいいや」って言えばいいだけ
そのあと人生を続けようって意味
It means life is what it is.
Life is heavy, so you just say "whatever".
And then it means to keep going with life.
Dahlah sama kehidupan. Hidup tuh berat ya guys ya.
Done with life. Life is heavy, guys.
Kalau hidup berat ya udah dahlah aja, habis itu lanjutkan hidupmu.
If life is heavy, just say "dahlah", and then continue your life.
そうっすね。大人になったらね
Right. Once you've grown up.
Iya betul teman-teman di kehidupan yang dewasa ini ya.
Yeah, that's right friends, in this adult life.
Untuk lagu-lagunya santai, easy listening, jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan nyapa fans gitu ya?
The songs are chill and easy listening, so we can walk around and greet the fans, right?
Asyik banget ya tadi ya? Aku juga suka banget tadi dance bagian reff-nya ya.
It was really fun, wasn't it? I also really liked the dance for the chorus part.
Dala dala dala dala dala...
Itu... itu beda lagu gak sih?
Wait... isn't that a different song?
Dala dala dala dala...
Enggak gitu deh... gitu kayaknya...
It's not like that... it's like this, I think...
Ya, tapi pokoknya asyik lah ya kalau nyanyi lagu chill santai-santai kayak gini.
Yeah, but anyway, it's fun to sing chill, relaxed songs like this.
Iya, santai dong!
Yeah, chill!
Tapi ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu. Hei, santai!
But speaking of chill, we actually can't relax just yet. Hey, relax!
Karena katanya enggak boleh santai terus.
Because they said we shouldn't keep relaxing.
Iya iya iya, jangan santai-santai. Jangan terlalu santai.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, don't relax. Don't be too relaxed.
Karena konsernya tuh masih panjang!
Because the concert is still long!
Jadi sebelum itu, kalian ada gak yang mau kalian sampaikan dulu?
So before that, do you guys have anything you want to say first?
Mulai dari ini nih, gak bisa diam.
Starting from this one who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja. I love you.
Just three words. I love you.
Keren. The best. Sangat jelas ya.
Cool. The best. Very clear.
Tetap semangat, tetap semangat menjalani hidup ya. Udah gitu aja. Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang. Semangat!
Stay spirited, stay spirited in living life. That's all. Anyway, it's still long until the end. Spirit!
사랑해요! 고마워요!
I love you! Thank you!
Oke kalau aku... ya, semangat selalu! Semangat santai! Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
As for me... yeah, always be spirited! Spirited chill! Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai ya.
Spirited chill.
Semangat santai apa semangat santai?
Spirited chill or spirited chill?
Semangat santai.
Spirited chill.
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjutkan...
Okay then, let's continue...
Eits eits eits tunggu dulu! Sebelum selesai-selesai ini ya, kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu gak sih?
Wait, wait, wait, hold on! Before we wrap this up, how about we shout together with the audience?
Iya dong! Ayo ayo ayo!
Yeah! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Oke oke.
Okay, okay.
Jadi kita teriak bareng ya. Dalam hitungan tiga, kita sama-sama teriak Chromatic Future. Oke ya?
So let's shout together. On the count of three, we'll shout "Chromatic Future" together. Okay?
Chromatic Future! Chromatic Future gitu kan?
Chromatic Future! Shout "Chromatic Future", right?
Iya iya kayak gitu kayak gitu. Oke langsung ya, sambil lihat sini sini sini sambil lihat.
Yeah, yeah, just like that. Okay, let's do it, while looking here, here, here...
Aku ya, aku yang penonton ini nih, penonton sini nih!
I'll take this audience here, the audience over here!
Aku ini nih, yang tengah yang tengah. Halo!
I'll take the ones in the middle. Hello!
Oke bareng-bareng ya. Satu... dua... tiga!
Okay, together now. One... two... three!
CHROMATIC FUTURE!
Everything was easy, I did it all alone
So effortlessly, I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Got all problems solved without any setbacks, there is nothing uncontrolled
There's no way I can begin, dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta soar a little higher, hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Just like a peacock with spreading wings
Kan kutaklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With the magic of the wind, I will invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit melawan dunia
All those who sleep to rise against the world
We'll never give up, as long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain, be stronger than that
Walking step by step, trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have. Let's go!
Just believe me
Let it go, they'll never bring me down
Let it go, they'll never bring us down
Just believe me, I'm not their cruel tease, still am I royalty
And when the universe works against me I will just
Let it go! If it's spicy just sip something let it go
I've been living carefree, there's no bitter words in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold, not letting it show
Things but I'm bigger than my feelings, so that will be enough
There's no way I can begin, dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta be better than ever, hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap, kan kutaklukkan gelap
Just like a peacock with spreading wings, I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit...
With the magic of the wind, I invite all who are asleep to rise...
melawan dunia
against the world
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in our cell
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than them
Walking step by step, trusting by our pace
Giving me what I deserve to have. Let's go!
Believe me, let it go. They'll never bring me down, just believe me.
Let it go. It'll never bring us down, just believe me.
Won't let their cruelty steal my royalty
And when the universe was against me, I will just...
Let it go!
Come on guys, let's do this!
One, two, three, let it go!
hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future
Supported by: Pocky, ACL