(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Hey DJ カマせ
Hey DJ, bring it on!
yeah yeah yeah 気分上々↑↑の
yeah yeah yeah, feeling great!
針落とせ 音鳴らせパーリナイ
Drop the needle, let the music play, it's a party night!
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai!
みんなで踊れ!
Everyone, dance!
ヒッポー ビーポー
Hip-hop, bee-pop!
かけてよミラクルNumber
Play that miracle number!
Yo! こんな時代に分かち合うMUSIC
Yo! MUSIC we share in times like these,
探したくて回す地球儀
Spinning the globe, wanting to search.
グラつく不安定生活
A shaky, unstable life,
それだからバランス重視
That's why I prioritize balance.
良いことばかりじゃないから
Since it's not always good things,
最悪な日にキック
Give the worst days a kick!
再起動のボタンクリック!
Click the reboot button!
DJ かけて!! 今TRIP
DJ, play it!! TRIP now!
シャレてるビートに乗って
Riding on a stylish beat,
感じる体 揺らそうよ
Let's shake our bodies, feeling it.
Hey DJ カマせ
Hey DJ, bring it on!
yeah yeah yeah 気分上々↑↑の
yeah yeah yeah, feeling great!
針落とせ 音鳴らせパーリナイ
Drop the needle, let the music play, it's a party night!
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai!
みんなで踊れ!
Everyone, dance!
ヒッポー ビーポー
Hip-hop, bee-pop!
かけてよミラクルNumber
Play that miracle number!
Hip Hop, R&B, Pops, Techno, House, Rock... Hip-Hop!!
オリジナル探すキーボーイ
Key boy searching for the original,
それぞれの色 重ね合わすレインボー
a rainbow of overlapping colors.
君に聴かせたいが為 苦しむあげくの果て
Just to let you hear it, after much suffering,
十字架背負い 今を楽しみたいんだ今
bearing the cross, I want to enjoy the now, the now!
Let's Hip-Pop!! Here we, Here we Go!!
はしゃぐフロアの上
Above the rowdy floor,
頭ん中 ゆさゆさぶる
it's shaking things up in my head.
Hey DJ シャシャれ
Hey DJ, show off!
yeah yeah yeah 気分上々↑↑の
yeah yeah yeah, feeling great!
波に乗って 弾け飛べファンキーナイ
Ride the wave and burst forth, funky night!
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai!
みんなで踊れ!
Everyone, dance!
ヒッポー ビーポー
Hip-hop, bee-pop!
朝までミラクルNumber
Miracle number until the morning!
ミラーボール
Mirror ball
スモークのにおい
The smell of smoke
溶けるようなハーモニー
A melting harmony
身にまとって踊り明かす
Wrap it around and dance the night away
がむしゃらなままで
Just being reckless
Hey DJ カマせ
Hey DJ, bring it on!
yeah yeah yeah 気分上々↑↑の
yeah yeah yeah, feeling great!
針落とせ 音鳴らせパーリナイ
Drop the needle, let the music play, it's a party night!
飲もう ライ ライ ライ
Let's drink, lai lai lai!
みんなで踊れ!
Everyone, dance!
ヒッポー ビーポー
Hip-hop, bee-pop!
かけてよミラクルNumber
Play that miracle number!
Hey DJ シャシャれ
Hey DJ, show off!
yeah yeah yeah 気分上々↑↑の
yeah yeah yeah, feeling great!
波に乗って 弾け飛べファンキーナイ
Ride the wave and burst forth, funky night!
飲もう
Let's drink
ライ ライ ライ
Rai rai rai
みんなで踊れ！
Everyone dance!
Hip-Hop
朝までミラクルNumber
A miracle number until morning
Hey DJ
カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Bring it on, yeah yeah yeah
飲もう
Let's drink
ライ ライ ライ
Rai rai rai
カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Bring it on, yeah yeah yeah
飲もう
Let's drink
ライ ライ ライ
Rai rai rai
カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Bring it on, yeah yeah yeah
飲もう
Let's drink
ライ ライ ライ
Rai rai rai
カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Bring it on, yeah yeah yeah
飲もう
Let's drink
ライ ライ ライ
Rai rai rai
Hey DJ
カマセ yeah yeah yeah
Bring it on, yeah yeah yeah
Bersama-sama!
All together now!
Kibun jojo!
Feeling great!
Aduh, cape jadi pengen sexy stretching.
Man, I'm tired. I feel like doing some sexy stretching.
Jadi, hari ini kita di sini mau ngapain?
So, what are we all doing here today?
Hari ini kita akan...
Today, we're going to have...
MINI LIVE!
A MINI LIVE!
Holoro semuanya udah berkumpul ya teman-teman.
All of Holoro has gathered here, everyone.
Habis ini kita akan nyanyi lebih banyak lagi.
After this, we'll be singing even more.
Terus masih ada banyak lagi yang pengen kita perlihatkan.
And there's still so much more we want to show you.
Pokoknya bukan cuma lagu doang, nggak sih? Ada banyak deh.
It's not just songs, you know? There's a lot.
Oke kalau gitu, perkenalkan diri dulu nggak sih?
Okay then, shouldn't we introduce ourselves first?
Ooh iya, bener bener bener.
Oh right, true, true, true.
Oke dari aku kalau gitu.
Okay, I'll go first then.
Halo semuanya, aku Anya Melfissa...
Hello everyone, I'm Anya Melfissa...
...dari hololive ID Generasi 2, Holoro!
...from hololive ID 2nd Generation, Holoro!
Dan guys, jangan lupa ya pakai hashtagnya.
And guys, don't forget to use the hashtag.
Hashtag Holoroshow dan dipost ke social media.
#holoroshow, and post it to social media.
Kita tunggu loh pesan-pesannya.
We'll be waiting for your messages!
Oke kalau gitu, dari Reine perkenalkan diri.
Okay then, Reine, please introduce yourself.
Oke, aku Reine, Resident bagian...
Okay, I'm Reine, the Resident...
...Tante Sexy Stretching dari hololive ID Generasi 2, Holoro!
...'Auntie' of Sexy Stretching from hololive ID Gen 2, Holoro!
Aduh Ibu... Ibu aku pulang!
Oh, Mother... Mother, I'm home!
Aduh! Suaranya mirip kayak ibu kos yang aku tempatin dulu.
Man! Her voice sounds like my old landlady's.
Oke next nggak sih? Ollie? Terakhir aku.
Okay, next? Ollie? Lastly, me.
Zombalas! Hebat Kawaii Zombie Idol!
Zombalas! The Great Kawaii Zombie Idol!
K-K-K-K-K-K-Crazy Ollie desu!
C-C-C-C-C-C-Crazy Ollie!
Btw, kalian tahu nggak ini kita sekarang lagi di mana?
Btw, do you guys know where we are right now?
Kayaknya familiar nggak sih?
It looks familiar, doesn't it?
Masa nggak tahu? Kalau lihat 3D showcase yang lain...
How could you not know? If you've seen other 3D showcases...
...masa nggak tahu ini kita di mana sekarang?
...how could you not know where we are now?
Jawabannya adalah...
The answer is...
HOLO ID STAGE!
THE HOLO ID STAGE!
Seperti kalian bisa lihat, ini adalah Holo ID Stage.
As you can see, this is the Holo ID Stage.
Ini sempat direnovasi kan ya biar kayak tema kita gitu.
It was renovated to match our theme.
Oke stagenya Anya diapain?
Okay, what happened to Anya's stage?
Ooh ya, di stage aku, ini lantainya pasir guys.
Oh right, for my stage, the floor is sand, guys.
Terus banyak pedang, banyak tembakan...
And there are lots of swords, lots of guns...
...pokoknya agak berbahaya untuk ngedance di sana.
...basically, it's a bit dangerous to dance there.
Kemarin aku juga sebenarnya agak berbahaya.
Yesterday was actually a bit dangerous for me too.
Tapi nggak ada yang bahaya untukku karena aku Keris Sakti!
But nothing is dangerous for me because I'm a Magic Keris!
Kalau punya kamu gimana?
What about yours?
Kalau di tempatnya Ollie ada banyak pudding gitu loh.
At Ollie's place, there's a lot of pudding.
Kalau di Reine ada apa deh?
What about Reine's place?
Aku banyak burung merak, terus ada gedung-gedung.
I have lots of peacocks and buildings.
Di bawah lantainya ini juga lantai merak.
And the floor here is also a peacock floor.
Hebat ya stage bisa langsung ganti-ganti.
It's amazing how the stage can change instantly.
Tapi ya udah kalau gitu sekarang kita ada yang lain dong.
But anyway, we have something else now.
Makanya tonton sampai akhir ya!
So make sure to watch until the end!
Saatnya kita ke live show! Live-nya berlanjut!
Time to go to the live show! The live continues!
Mari kita switch stage!
Let's switch stages!
ツギハギスタッカート
Tsugihagi Staccato
ツギハギだらけの君との時間もそろそろ
Our time together, full of patches, will soon be over
さあ、終わりにしよう
Now, let's end this.
この糸　ちぎるの色とりどり
Tearing these threads, in various colors...
散らばるでしょ
They'll scatter, won't they?
ねえ　ほら　あの時の言葉
Hey, look, the words from back then...
重ねた　無駄な時間
And the useless time we spent together.
この糸　ちぎるだけ
Just tearing this thread...
不相応だね　笑えるでしょ
It's unsuitable, laughable, isn't it?
チクタク　チクタク
Tick-tack, tick-tack
円を描いて
Drawing a circle.
ディンドン　ディンドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
遊びましょう
Let's play.
チクタク　チクタク
Tick-tack, tick-tack
結んで開いて
Tying and opening.
ディンドン　ディンドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
じゃあまたね
See you later.
ほつれた糸がささやく
The frayed thread whispers.
君よ　いっそ　いっそ　いなくなれ
I wish you'd just, just disappear.
変わらないこと　回ってるだけ
Things don't change, they're just spinning.
きっと　きっと　なんてことない
Surely, surely it's no big deal.
少し　軽くなるだけ
It'll just get a little lighter.
ねえ　いっそ　いっそ　捨てちゃえば
Hey, if I just, just throw it away...
気づかないまま　いられたらだけど
If only I could have remained unaware.
ずっと　ずっと　好きかもな
I might love you forever and ever.
少しだけ　痛いかな
It might hurt just a little.
気づけば　気にしてる画面を
Before I know it, I'm checking the screen.
そろそろ　見飽きた
I'm getting tired of looking at it.
アレ　抜き　コレ　抜き
Without this, without that.
それじゃつまんないんでしょ　退屈でしょ
That's boring, isn't it? Tedious, right?
フリック　フリック
Flick, flick
指を滑って
Sliding my finger.
スワイプ　スワイプ
Swipe, swipe
遠ざけて
Pushing it away.
フリック　フリック
Flick, flick
開いて　閉じて
Opening and closing.
スワイプ　スワイプ
Swipe, swipe
もう嫌だな
I've had enough.
スルスル糸がささやく
The sliding thread whispers.
君よ　いっそ　いっそ　いなくなれ
I wish you'd just, just disappear.
変わらないこのまま　だよ　だから
It's the same as always, that's why...
きっと　きっと　なんてことない
Surely, surely it's no big deal.
少し　寂しくなるだけ
It'll just get a little lonely.
ねえ　いっそ　いっそ　捨てちゃおう
Hey, let's just, just throw it away.
気づかないまま　過ごした分だけ
For all the time I spent unaware.
ずっと　ずっと　好きだけど
I'll love you forever and ever, but...
少しだけ　痛いけど
It hurts just a little, though.
だから
That's why...
だから　いっそ　いっそ　いなくなれ
That's why I wish you'd just, just disappear.
変わらないこと　回ってるだけ
Things don't change, they're just spinning.
きっと　きっと　なんてことない
Surely, surely it's no big deal.
少し　寂しくなるけど
It'll get a little lonely, though.
ねえ　いっそ　いっそ　捨てちゃうよ
Hey, I'm just, just going to throw it away.
気づかないまま　気づかないなら
Remaining unaware, if you won't notice...
ずっと　ずっと　好きなのは
The one who will love you forever and ever...
最初から　僕だけ
From the start, was just me.
チクタク　チクタク
Tick-tack, tick-tack
ディンドン　ディンドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
ツギハギだらけの　君との時間を
This time with you, full of patches...
そろそろ　終わりにしよう
It's about time to end this.
この糸　ちぎるだけ　簡単でしょ
Just tearing this thread, it's easy, right?
笑えるよね
It's laughable, isn't it?
（歓声）
(Cheering)
Wah, keren banget enggak sih kita tadi? Kita nyanyiin apa tadi?
Wow, weren't we so cool just now? What did we sing?
Tsugihagi Staccato!
Patchwork Staccato!
（歓声）
(Cheering)
Wah keren keren keren.
Wow, cool cool cool.
Keren, bagaimana menurutmu?
Cool, what do you think?
Ya pokoknya, pokoknya lagunya kayaknya ini ya, kombi kita punya potensi ya.
Well anyway, anyway, the song seems to show that our duo has potential, right?
Anomaly?
Anomaly. Yeah, that's our name.
That's our name!
Kita entah kenapa jarang kumpul ya guys dua ini.
For some reason, these two rarely hang out together, guys.
Kapan lagi kita nyanyi di stage bareng kayak gini dan dance di stage bareng kayak gini, iya enggak sih?
When else will we sing on stage together like this and dance on stage together like this, right?
Stagenya ini keren lho, by the way.
This stage is cool, by the way.
Wah stagenya, ya ini stage-ku. Hehehe. Sisisisi.
Wow, the stage, yeah this is my stage. Hehehe. Sisisisi.
Hati-hati ya, di bawah banyak senjata. Ada pistol di situ, serem sih.
Be careful, there are many weapons below. There's a pistol there, it's scary.
Tadi enggak ketusuk kan? Ada pedang, ada pistol dan lain-lain.
You didn't get poked earlier, right? There were swords, pistols, and so on.
Untungnya kaki masih aman.
Luckily my legs are still safe.
Kaki masih aman, enggak putus?
Legs are still safe, not severed?
Enggak putus.
Not severed.
Enggak putus. Oke, takut... takutnya aku itu doang sih, guys.
Not severed. Okay, I was just... just afraid of that, guys.
Wah, nahan-nahan nge-dance di sini agak bahaya ya kawan-kawan, jangan ditiru.
Wow, holding back on dancing here is a bit dangerous friends, don't copy this.
Benar, bahaya dan sulit lho. Ini soalnya pasir semua.
True, it's dangerous and difficult. It's because of all this sand.
Iya, ini pasir dan banyak senjata juga. Hayo gimana tuh nge-dance-nya?
Yeah, it's sand and many weapons too. So how was the dancing?
Ya kita latihan dan lain-lainnya guys, pokoknya...
Well we practiced and all that guys, anyway...
...kita berjuang dengan sangat keras. Itu tadi koreografi ada yang Anya buat...
...we fought very hard. That choreography earlier, some were made by Anya...
...ada Ollie yang buat juga. Ya kita berkolaborasi.
...some were made by Ollie too. Yeah we collaborated.
Ya ini nyanyi bareng, ya berkolaborasi.
Yeah this singing together, yeah collaborating.
Hmm... Oke, setelah ini masih ada banyak lho kolaborasinya, bukan cuma ini aja.
Hmm... Okay, after this there's still a lot of collaborations, not just this one.
Yes! Setelah ini akan ada stage selanjutnya!
Yes! After this there will be the next stage!
Wah, stage apa itu? Stage apa?
Wow, what stage is that? What stage?
Makanya nonton sampai habis ya guys!
That's why watch until the end guys!
Yay! Kalau gitu langsung ke lagu selanjutnya!
Yay! If so, straight to the next song!
アリンコシックな日常に　付き合う朝
An ant-chic morning I deal with daily
八百万の嘘を　笑うベッド
A bed that laughs at eight million lies
どうしようもないけど　気が狂う人の
It can't be helped, but as someone who's going mad
振りをしている　君を見ている
I'm watching you, pretending
安寧放蕩だから　切り捨てた
Because of peaceful profligacy, I cut it off
八畳サイズを　さらうドクト
A "docto" that sweeps away an eight-tatami size
申し訳ないけど　すれ違う度に
I'm sorry, but every time we pass each other
無意識に愛を　強いているわ
I'm unconsciously forcing love on you
饒舌な暴走　手入力の独創
A talkative rampage, a manually input creation
モラトリアム的　人間最下位
A moratorium-like bottom-tier human
根っからの鑑賞材
A decoration to the core
食べてすぐ寝て牛になる
Eat and then sleep immediately, becoming a cow
起きてまた寝て人非人
Wake up and sleep again, a heartless beast
マーシャル・マキシマイザー　マキシマイザー
Marshall Maximizer, Maximizer
求愛待って焦がした　フィルムの今日を
Waiting for courtship, burning today's film
なんてことない生きて　しまうのだが
I end up living a meaningless life, however
怨みも回る　元自堕落ね
Grudges also revolve, originally self-indulgent, right?
錯誤さ錯誤さ　ステイ
It's a mistake, a mistake, stay
傲慢な振る舞い　取り戻したい
Arrogant behavior, I want to take it back
でも演技が降る　落ちる落ちる
But the acting falls, falling, falling
払くらえアンバランス回　ファーラウェイ
Eat this unbalanced round, far away
安静放蕩に　狂い出す
Starting to go mad in quiet profligacy
八百万の嘘を　笑うベッド
A bed that laughs at eight million lies
どうしようもないから　気が狂う人の
It can't be helped, so to someone who's going mad
真似をしている　君へ
I'm imitating you
簡単な言葉　信じていたいなら
If you want to believe simple words
足りないよ
They're not enough
申し訳ないなら　擦れ合う通りに
If you're sorry, as we rub against each other
無意識に愛を　求めなさいよ
Go on and seek love unconsciously
公開はない暴走　手入力の乱暴
A rampage with no regrets, a manually input violence
モラトリアム的人間最小公倍数
A moratorium-like human least common multiple
アンド・トライ
And try
食べてすぐ寝て牛になる
Eat and then sleep immediately, becoming a cow
起きてまた寝て人非人
Wake up and sleep again, a heartless beast
マーシャル・マキシマイザー　マキシマイザー
Marshall Maximizer, Maximizer
求愛待って焦がした　フィルムの強行
Waiting for courtship, burning the film's forced action
なんてことら生きて　しまうのだが
I end up living a meaningless life, however
裏みも回る　惨事待てゲー
Grudges also revolve, a disaster-waiting game
マーシャル・マキシマイザー　マキシマイザー
Marshall Maximizer, Maximizer
求愛待って焦がした　フィルムの強行
Waiting for courtship, burning the film's forced action
なんてことら生きて　しまうのだが
I end up living a meaningless life, however
怨みも回る　元自堕落ね
Grudges also revolve, originally self-indulgent, right?
錯誤さ錯誤さ　ステイ
It's a mistake, a mistake, stay
傲慢な振る舞い　取り戻したい
Arrogant behavior, I want to take it back
でも演技が降る　落ちる落ちる
But the acting falls, falling, falling
払くらえアンバランス回　ファーラウェイ
Eat this unbalanced round, far away
マキシマイザー　マキシマイザー
Maximizer, Maximizer
Wah! Akhirnya!
Wow! Finally!
Akhirnya!
Finally!
Marshall Maximizer bareng Anya Melfissa!
Marshall Maximizer with Anya Melfissa!
Aku kan ya pernah cover ini ya...
I covered this before...
...terus aku agak kaget Reine milih lagu ini. Wah senang banget.
...and I was a bit surprised Reine chose this song. Wow, so happy.
Aku tuh, aku tuh senang banget sama cover-nya Anya. Jadi tuh mumpung ada kesempatan...
I really, I really like Anya's cover. So while there's an opportunity...
...akhirnya aku tuh harus kayak, "Aku harus nyanyi Marshall Maximizer sama Anya di stage!"
...finally I was like, "I must sing Marshall Maximizer with Anya on stage!"
Iya, tadi... tadi itu keren banget pokoknya kita.
Yeah, earlier... earlier it was so cool.
Iya, spicy gila sih.
Yeah, crazy spicy.
Gila! Dan ini stage-nya keren banget guys.
Crazy! And this stage is really cool, guys.
Iya dong, ini adalah stage-nya aku kali ini.
Of course, this is my stage this time.
Meraknya lucu!
The peacock is cute!
Ada burung merak di sininya, terus di bawahnya juga ada lho sebenarnya.
There's a peacock here, and below it there's one too actually.
Iya di bawahnya, ini... ini kaca ya? Aku sebenarnya agak takut ya soalnya aku kan keris ya...
Yeah below it, is this... is this glass? I'm actually a bit afraid because I'm a kris...
...jadi kalau nge-dance kan deg-degan gitu. Pecah nggak ya?
...so when dancing I'm nervous. Will it break?
Tenang, tenang, nggak pecah. Sebelumnya udah dipesenin pokoknya harus tahan, tahan keris pokoknya.
Calm down, it won't break. It's been ordered beforehand that it must withstand daggers.
Aduh makasih banget, soalnya kalau pecah bisa aku disuruh ganti.
Oh thank you so much, because if it breaks I might be asked to replace it.
Nggak dong, nggak dong.
No, no.
Gantinya dalam bentuk nyanyi sama Reine.
The replacement is in the form of singing with Reine.
Yeay!
Tapi gitu nih, ini tuh bukan semua, ini masih ada lagi sebenarnya ya.
But wait, this isn't all, there's actually more to come.
Iya masih ada lagi guys. Jadi tonton sampai akhir!
Yeah, there's more, guys. So watch until the end!
Yeay!
Eh bentar bentar bentar, sebelum itu aku mau mutusin nama duet kita dong.
Wait, wait, wait, before that, I want to decide our duet name.
Apa? Oh iya!
What? Oh yeah!
Oh iya kita belum ada nama kombo gitu kan ya?
Oh yeah, we don't have a combo name yet, right?
RENYA gimana? Kayaknya lucu banget.
How about RENYA? It seems really cute.
RENYA? RENYA lucu banget! Aku suka.
RENYA? RENYA is really cute! I like it.
Kalau gitu mulai sekarang nama duetnya Reine dan Anya adalah RENYA!
In that case, from now on the duet name for Reine and Anya is RENYA!
Kalo gitu kita ulang lagi, masih ada lagu selanjutnya!
Then let's do it again, there's still the next song!
Masih ada lagu selanjutnya, guys!
There's still the next song, guys!
Jadi tonton sampai akhir! Tonton sampai akhir, oke?
So watch until the end! Watch until the end, okay?
Dan mari kita pergi ke lagu...
And let's go to the...
...selanjutnya!
...next song!
嗚呼、素晴らしきニャン生
Ah, Subarashiki Nyansei
Lyrics・Composition: Nem
これは可愛いお嬢さん
Hey there, cute little miss,
真っ白な毛がとても素敵ね
Your pure white fur is so lovely.
こんな月が綺麗な夜は
On a night with a moon as beautiful as this,
僕と一緒に遊びませんか
Won't you come out and play with me?
ニャン生は一度きり
A cat's life is only once,
楽しむが勝ちなのです
So having fun is how you win.
あなたを縛る首輪
That collar that binds you...
噛みちぎってあげましょう
I'll bite it right off for you.
野良は最高ニャニャニャ
Being a stray is the best, nya nya nya!
魚盗んで、鳩追いかけて
Stealing fish, chasing pigeons,
昼は働く人間を
In the daytime, I watch humans working
尻目に屋根の上でフンス
Out of the corner of my eye, napping on the roof.
あなたも自由にニャニャニャ
You can be free too, nya nya nya!
素敵な仲間も紹介しましょう
I'll introduce you to some wonderful friends.
さっさの窓を開いて
Open up that window quickly
飛び出すのです
And leap out!
これは気ままな野良猫さん
Hey there, carefree Mr. Stray,
闇の中目だけが光ってる
Only your eyes are shining in the dark.
随分口が上手だけど
You're quite a smooth talker,
私は馬鹿な女じゃないわ
But I'm not a foolish girl.
ニャン生は一度きり
A cat's life is only once,
だからこそ飼われるのよ
And that's exactly why I'm kept.
ブランド首輪の価値が
The value of this brand-name collar...
あなたには分かるかしら？
Could you possibly understand it?
私は優雅よニャニャニャ
I'm elegant, nya nya nya!
美味しい食事にふかふかベッド
Delicious meals and a fluffy bed.
水はちょっぴり苦手だけど
I'm a little bit afraid of water,
毎日シャワーで洗えるの
But I can wash in the shower every day.
それに比べてニャニャニャ
Compared to that, nya nya nya,
身体を誰に守ってもらうの？
Who's there to protect you?
明日車に轢かれちゃうかも
Tomorrow you might get hit by a car,
知れないじゃない
You never know.
そんな強がりもニャニャニャ
Even that show of strength, nya nya nya,
とっても素敵です
Is very wonderful.
いっそあなたを
I've actually gone and...
好きになりました
...fallen for you.
あら正直ねだけど
Oh, how honest. However,
そんなに簡単じゃ
it's not quite that simple,
心揺らがないわ
my heart won't be swayed.
僕の夢はニャニャニャ
My dream is, nya nya nya,
いつかは黒い街を飛び出して
to one day leap out of this dark city,
はるか北の国に旅して
travel to a far-off northern country,
オーロラをこの目で見ることです
and see the aurora with my own eyes.
そこにあなたがニャニャニャ
If you were there with me, nya nya nya,
いてくれたらなんて素敵でしょう
how wonderful would that be?
だけどそれは叶わないらしい
But it seems that won't come true.
生き方はニャニャニャ
A way of life, nya nya nya,
そう簡単には変えられないの
can't be changed so easily.
それに私を飼っている
Besides, I can't leave
女の子を一人にできないわ
the girl who keeps me all alone.
話の途中よニャニャニャ
I'm still talking, nya nya nya!
あらもう行っちゃうのねちょっと
Oh, you're leaving already? Hey!
明日もここに来ていいのよ
You can come here tomorrow too, you know.
待ってるからね
I'll be waiting.
ニャー！
Nyaa!
ニャニャニャニャニャ...
Nya nya nya nya nya...
Kucing garong!
Garong cat!
Kucing garong? Aku kucing rumahan.
Garong cat? I'm a house cat.
Aku kucing garong!
I'm a garong cat!
Yang barusan adalah Ah, Subarashiki ニャン生！
That was 'Ah, Subarashiki Nyansei'!
Yeay!
Keren ya? Keren keren keren keren.
Cool, right? Cool cool cool cool.
Ini tuh sebenarnya siapa sih yang kayak pertama kali menyarankan lagu ini tuh siapa sih Kak Kubo?
Who was it that first suggested this song, Kak Kubo?
Aku lupa deh, kayaknya kita udah kesepakatan bersama gitu deh.
I forgot, I think we reached a mutual agreement.
Soalnya gimana ya? Kayaknya tuh kalau ngomongin Pafo-Ri tuh kayak lagu ini tuh Pafo-Ri banget nggak sih?
Because, you know? It feels like when talking about Pafo-Ri, this song is very Pafo-Ri, isn't it?
Ho-oh. Kayak rules-nya itu udah pittari gitu lho.
Yeah. It's like the rules are a perfect fit.
Iya, kayak nggak usah kayak siapa yang jadi ini siapa yang jadi itu kayak...
Yeah, like no need to decide who's who, like...
...Ollie tuh udah pasti jadi kucing garongnya...
...Ollie is definitely the alley cat...
...aku udah pasti jadi kucing rumahannya.
...and I'm definitely the house cat.
Iya, terus kebetulan tadi di liriknya itu "Mashiro no ke".
Yeah, and coincidentally in the lyrics earlier, it was "Mashiro no ke".
Ooh... ngeprossei!
Ooh... so impressive!
Gak, gak, maksudnya rambut kamu, rambut kamu putih.
No, no, I mean your hair, your hair is white.
Ah, oke. Ah, oke. Bener juga ya, bener juga.
Ah, okay. Ah, okay. That's true, that's true.
Betul betul betul. Terus kenapa posenya harus begini gitu lho?
True true true. And why did the pose have to be like this?
Gak kepikiran. Improv, improv, improv ya guys.
Didn't think about it. Improv, improv, improv, guys.
Terus tadi kan kita sempat di stage-nya Anya.
And earlier we were on Anya's stage.
Betul. Stage-nya Reine.
True. Reine's stage.
Hmm, kali ini...
Hmm, this time...
...di stage-nya Ollie!
...on Ollie's stage!
Wah! Banyak Udin ya?
Wow! So many Udins?
Iya dong! Di sini Udin, di sana Udin, di mana-mana Udin!
Of course! Udin here, Udin there, Udin everywhere!
Pitanya juga lucu-lucu banget yang di belakang.
The ribbons in the back are also very cute.
Rame banget, cocok banget tau lagu ini di sini tuh.
It's so crowded, this song fits so well here.
Iya kan ya? Kayak teater gitu.
Right? It's like a theater.
Aku seneng, aku seneng sekali bisa perform sama Ollie.
I'm happy, I'm very happy to be able to perform with Ollie.
Aku juga!
Me too!
Waduh... Eh, ngomong-ngomong ya, habis ini tuh ada sesuatu yang spesial banget buat kalian.
Wow... Anyway, after this, there's something very special for all of you.
Pokoknya ada ini kalian tuh pasti udah nanti-nantiin banget ini.
Anyway, there's this thing you've all been waiting for.
Jadi pokoknya ini kejutan ya, jadi kalian duduk manis...
So anyway, it's a surprise, so you sit tight...
...dan nantikan acara selanjutnya. Oke!
...and look forward to the next part. Okay!
Serta kita saatnya pindah!
And it's time for us to move!
Yeeeee!
Huh... sepertinya dengan ini...
Alright I think...
...sudah bersih semua ya.
...the sweeping is all done now!
Ollie!
Iya?
Yes?
Rak yang di sana sama kasurnya udah aku bersihkan ya.
I'm done dusting the shelf & the bed!
Terima kasih banyak Anya!
Thank you so much, Anya!
Aku senang bisa dibantu.
I'm so happy you're willing to help me!
Iya, sama-sama ya Ollie.
You're welcome, Ollie!
Memang ibu kita itu entah kenapa suka jahatin Ollie ya.
For some reason, our mother is always mean to you, Ollie.
Iya ya...
Yeah.
aku kasihan sama kamu Ollie.
I feel bad for you, Ollie.
Entah kenapa kadang kamarku suka diberantakin...
I don't know why, but she always messes up my room...
...suka diisengin pula. Parah banget.
...and she's always picking on me! She's awful!!
Tapi aku bersyukur...
But I'm grateful
...karena berkatnya aku jadi punya keluarga.
thanks to her I can have a family.
Yah, gak bisa minta banyak sih...
I can't ask much though
...karena aku bukan anak sebenarnya, seorang zombie pula.
since I'm not an actual part of the family, plus I'm a zombie...
Ollie...
gak usah pikirin ada hubungan darah atau tidak...
it doesn't matter if we're not blood-related!
...kita semua itu tetap keluarga.
We're all still family!
Anya!!
Heh! Ngapain, ngapain, ngapain?
Hey!! What are you doing??
Kerja tuh yang bener! Udah bersih belum?
Do your work properly!! Is it clean yet?
Maaf ibu!
I'm sorry, mother!
Ibu...
Mom...
udah kita bersihin kok, Bu.
We did clean it, mom!
Apaan?
What is this??
Masih kotor!
It's still dirty!
Ngapain aja sih dari tadi?
What were you doing all this time??
Bersih-bersih kok, Bu.
I am cleaning, ma'am!
Ibu, Ollie tuh bener kok kerjanya, Ibu.
Ollie has been working hard, mom!
Dia bersih-bersih tadi.
She did do the cleaning
Kamu belain dia?
Are you taking her side?
Aduh pasti kamu bantuin dia.
You must be helping her out
Aduh memang deh anak aku tuh pinter bersih-bersih...
My daughter is truly talented with cleaning
...gak kayak...
Unlike...
...ini nih orang yang udah disuruh...
this kid right here! Who's been tasked to clean...
...tapi gak becus!
but can't even do it properly!
Maaf, Bu.
I'm sorry, ma'am!
Udah! Saya, saya gak mau denger lagi.
Enough! No more excuses!
Pokoknya tuh gini ya, omong-omong tadi tuh si Udin ya...
By the way... Earlier, Udin...
...si Udin itu aku suruh ngebikin teh.
I had him make me some tea
Tapi sendoknya gak ada.
but I forgot my spoon
Jadi sekarang kamu tolong ya ambilin saya sendok. Oke?
Now I want you to bring it at once! Okay?
Udah gak usah bersih-bersih, saya udah gak mau lihat lagi.
Stop cleaning, I don't want to see it anymore.
Baik, Ibu.
Of course, ma'am!
Ollie... gak apa-apa aku bantu bersih-bersih ya...
Ollie... It's okay, I'll handle the rest of the cleaning
...kamu ke dapur aja gak apa-apa.
You just go ahead to the kitchen now
Makasih Anya!
Thank you, Anya!
Kalau begitu aku akan mengambil sendok dulu ya.
Then, I'll go bring the spoon now!
Semangat ya Ollie!
Do your best, Ollie!
Terima kasih!!
Thank you!!
Iuh! Iuh!
Eww!! Eww!!
Jijik banget sih teh buatannya si Udin!
This tea that Udin brewed is truly disgusting
Ibu!
Mother!!
Sudah saya bawakan sendoknya, Bu.
Here is your spoon, ma'am!
Goblok!
You imbecile!!
Cangkul dibilangin sendok!
That's a hoe! Not a spoon!
Tapi Ibu...
But mother...
Aww! Sakit, Bu!
It hurts, mother!!
Dasar anak tidak berguna!
You are such a useless girl!
Bikin teh buat saya aja gak becus!
Why can't I just get a nice cup of tea?
Gak kamu...
Whether it's you...
...gak beruang yang sama kamu terus tuh!
...or that bear that's always with you
Aww!
Ibu!
Mother!
Ibu jahat sekali!
How could you, mother
Tega-teganya Ibu kepada Udin pula!
You are so mean even to Udin!
Udin...?
Udin di mana ya?
Where did he go?
Hah, mana saya tahu?
Heck if I know
Kayaknya sih tadi habis bikinin teh, dia tuh ke dapur deh.
He went to the kitchen after he made the tea
Dapur??
Kitchen??
Udin!
UDIN!!!
Udin?
Enggak...
No...
ASTAGA UDIN!!
OH MY GOD!!!
UDIIIIINNNN!!!!!
O- Ollie??
Ollie??
Ollie, kenapa Ollie??
Ollie, what happened??
Kenapa?
What happened?
ASTAGA!!!
OH GOODNESS!!!
Udin...
Sabar ya Ollie.
You must be strong, Ollie!
Ibu mana ibu?
Where did mom go?
Gimana ini Udin??
What should we do about Udin??
Ya ampun!
My word!
Jangan-jangan, karena dia ceroboh habis bikinin teh,
Perhaps he slipped and fell in while brewing the tea!
dia kepleset masuk ke dalam panci.
Tapi nggak papa sih kecemplung.
But it's good that he fell in
Sekalian dicuci.
He's finally cleaned now
Habisnya jorok sih!
That filthy thing needed a cleaning anyway
Makanya jadi anak tuh jangan bandel!
That's why you should be obedient to me!
Ibu tega...
How could you, mother...
Ibu...
Mother...
Ibu kenapa tega banget sih ibu!
I can't believe how cruel you are!
Ibu-ibu harus merasakan balasan
You shall get what you deserve, mother!
dari perbuatan ibu selama ini!
Makanlah...
TAKE THIS...
Azab ini!!!
PUNISHMENT!!!
Maafkan aku ibu.
I'm sorry mother
Tapi ini jalan yang ada...
But this is the only way...
Ollie...?
Ollie?
Kamu nggak papa Li?
Are you okay?
Bangun Li!
Wake up!!
Bangun!
Sakit kepalaku...
Ouch my head...
Ollie, kamu nggak papa?
Ollie, are you okay?
Anya?
Iya!
Yes!
Kamu pingsan Ollie!
You passed out, Ollie!
Aku pingsan...?
I passed out...?
Iya kamu pingsan!
You passed out!
Itukah...
I see...
Ollie...
Maaf ya Ollie, selama ini kamu sengsara.
I'm so sorry! I put you through so much!
Tidak apa-apa.
Don't mind it!
Kita tetap keluarga kan?
We're still family, right?
Iya Ollie!
Yes Ollie!
Kita keluarga!
We're family!!
Terima kasih Anya!
Thank you, Anya!!
Ibu...
Mom...
Ibu?
Mom?
Anya...?
Ollie...?
Ibu, kok auranya beda ya Bu?
Mom, your aura feels different now
Ya ampun...
Oh my...
Selama ini aku ngapain aja?
What have I been doing all this time??
Anya!
Khususnya Ollie!
Especially Ollie!!
Maafkan ibu ya nak.
Please forgive me
Ibu kesamber apa ibu?
What struck you, mother?
Petir nak.
Lightning, my daughter
Ibu sekarang sudah sadar.
My eyes are open now
Maafkan aku ya semua, maafkan ibu.
Please forgive your mother
Kalian berdua...
You two...
Anya!
Ollie!
Kalian berdua...
You both...
adalah anakku!!
are my daughters!!
Ibu!!!
Mother!!!
Kita keluarga!
We're all family!!
Kita maafkan ibu!
We accept your apology, mom!
Ibu!!!
Mother!!!
Aku sayang ibu!
I love you!!
Directed by Pavolia Reine
Production: COVER
Kureiji Ollie as stepdaughter/housemaid
Anya Melfissa as biological daughter/fairy godmother
Pavolia Reine as evil stepmother
YEY!!!
Keren-keren! Yang barusan adalah
Cool, cool! That was the Holoro Soap Opera!
Sinetron Holoro!
Bagaimana teman-teman?
How was it, friends?
Gila! Tapi Reine tadi serem banget ya guys.
Crazy! But Reine was really scary earlier, guys.
Tapi kamu paling cocok sih sama yang gituan,
But you're most suitable for that kind of thing, antagonist auntie.
tante antagonis.
Kurang ajar!
How rude!
Apalagi pas bagian akhirnya itu,
Especially that ending part where you finally repented.
kamu akhirnya tobat gitu kan.
Keren!
Cool!
Berasa ikatan Holoro.
It felt like the Holoro bond.
Ikatan Holoro!
Holoro bond!
えーと、今のところ、いくつかのお知らせがありますが...
Um... So for now, we have some announcements, but...
おおっ！お知らせの時間だ！
Ooh! Announcement time!
ちょっと待って、ここどこ？
Wait, where are we?
そうだね、ここどこだろう？お知らせの場所じゃなさそう...
Oh yeah, where is this? This doesn't look like an announce...
ここどこ？
Where are we?
あれも何？
What's that over there?
AとBがある。パネルみたいだね。
There's an A and a B, like a panel.
本当だ。え？
Oh yeah. Eh?
これ何？日本のゲーム番組みたい。
What is this? It's like those Japanese game shows.
中には何があるの？
What's inside?
それで、お知らせはどうなるの？
Yeah, and what about the announcements?
クイズみたいな感じだね。
Like a quiz or something.
えっ、待って待って待って。
Eh, wait wait wait wait.
はいはい、ええ。スタッフさんによると...
Yes yes, mm-hmm mm-hmm. The staff said...
テストがあるって！
...we're having a test!
はあ？テスト？
Huh? A test?
ホロローの絆を試したいんだって。
They want to test the Holoro bond, they said.
ホロロークイズ！〜友情の絆テスト〜
Holoro Quiz! ~Friendship bond test~
ほらね！ホロロークイズってどういうこと？
See! What does Holoro Quiz mean?
ホロロークイズ？
Holoro Quiz?
いつからホロロークイズなんて？
Holoro Quiz? Since when?
ホロロークイズ！
Holoro Quiz!
ホロロークイズ！友情の絆テスト！
Holoro Quiz! Friendship bond test!
たぶん、わざわざ私たちのためにクイズを作ったんだよ、それで...
I think they deliberately made a quiz for us so that...
私たちがどれだけ仲が良いか試したいんだね。
...they can test just how close we are.
日本のクイズ番組みたいにAとBがあるのも納得だね。
No wonder there's an A and B like in Japanese quizzes.
おお〜。おお〜。
Ohhh... Ohhh...
他には何があるの？それだけ？
Then what else? Is that it?
まあ、いいか。それから...
Well, that's fine. And...
あっ、あれ何？あそこにあるやつ。
Oh that, what's that over there?
これ何？急に出てきた。
What's this? It suddenly appeared.
私の隣にあるの何？
What is this next to me?
正解してテストに合格すれば...
So they said if we get it right and pass the test...
これが一番上まで上がって、それからやっとお知らせができるんだって。
...this will go all the way up, and only then can we make the announcements.
おお〜、なるほどね。
Oh... I see...
まあ、いいか。でもホロローなら簡単だよね？
Oh, that's fine then. But it's easy for Holoro, right?
もちろん！当たり前だよ、簡単、簡単。
Hell yeah... Of course, easy peasy.
私たちはもう、私たちがどれだけ...
We've shown just how much we...
どれだけ...
...just how much...
どれだけお... どれだけ大きい何？
...how bi... How big what?
言い間違えた、ごめん。
Wrong word, sorry.
どれだけフレンドリーで、家族同然か見せてきたでしょ？
Just how friendly and like a family we are, right?
そうだね、私の髪より... 大きくて濃い絆だよね。
Yeah, more... bigger and thicker than my hair.
おお、その通りだね。本当にそう。
Oh, absolutely. That's so true.
じゃあ、早速始めちゃおうか？
Well then, shall we just get started?
オッケー！オッケー！第一問だ！
Okay! Okay! First question!
レイネは何のマッサージが好き？ A: 足、B: タイマッサージ
What kind of massage does Reine like? A: Foot, B: Thai Massage
第一問！
First!
わあ、第一問は...
Whoa... The first question is...
第一問。
The first question.
レイネは...
Reine...
何のマッサージが好き？
...likes what kind of massage?
Aは足...
A, Foot...
そしてBはタイマッサージ。
...and B, Thai Massage.
おお〜。タイマッサージって何か知ってる？
Ooh... Do you know what Thai Massage is?
えっと、あれ... あの、ほら...
Uh, that's... That's... the...
不健全なやつ？
Dirty?
違うよ！体を伸ばすやつでしょ？
No! The one where you get stretched, right?
ああ、そういう意味ね、そうそう。
Oh, that's what you mean, yeah yeah.
オリー...
Ollie...
そうそう。
Yeah yeah.
じゃあ、誰が答える？
Well then, who's going to answer?
誰が答えるの？誰が知ってそうかな？
Who's answering? Who might know the answer?
うーん... アーニャが答えたいけど...
Um... Anya wants to answer, but...
うわあ、初めてだね、でも...
Whoa... The first time, but...
うーん、どうだろう？
...hmm, I wonder.
できるよ、できるよ。
You can do it, you can do it.
よし、レイネはよくマッサージに行ってるみたいだし...
Okay, Reine seems to get massaged often...
よくわからないけど、とにかく激しい感じのが好きみたいだから。
...and the massages she likes are, I don't know, ones that feel extreme.
だから、アーニャはBのタイマッサージにします。
So Anya wants to answer B, Thai Massage.
おお〜。
Ooo...
アーニャの答えが合っているか見てみよう！
Let's see if Anya's answer is correct or not!
よし！分かった、Bに走るよ。
Right! Okay, I'm going to run to B.
オッケー！
Okay!
三、二、一、走れ！
Three... two... one... Run!
お、おわっ！
O-owh!
アーニャ！どこに行ったの？
Anya! Where did you go?
ああああああ！
Aaaaaaa!
アーニャ！
Anyaaa!
落ちちゃったよ！
She fell, man!
えっ、落ちた... 落ちた！
Hey, she fell... She fell!
アーニャが落ちた！
Anya fell!
アーニャ... おかえり。
Anya... Oh, welcome back.
落ちちゃったよ。どうだった？
I fell, hello. How did that feel?
落ちる感じだよ、気持ちよくなかったよ、オリー！下にクッションがあったよ。
It felt like falling, it wasn't nice, Ollie! We have cushions down there.
そうだよね、レイネはタイマッサージが好きだもんね。
Yeah, you like Thai Massage, Reine.
それも好きだけど、本当は、足で踏まれるマッサージはまた別物なんだよね。
I like it too, but honestly, getting massaged with feet is different.
だから答えは「足」でした！
So the answer is foot!
おお〜、正解はAでした、みんな。
Oh... Turns out it's A, everyone.
イェーイ...
Yay...
オッケー、足だったんだね。
Okay, it was foot.
でもそれだと、あーあ、ゲージが溜まらないね。
But if that's the case, well, the gauge won't fill up.
そうだね。
You're right.
まだ空っぽだ。
It's still empty.
でも、でも、まだチャンスはあるよ、まだできる。
But but but, we still can, we still can.
私に問題があるみたい。
I think I have a question.
おお〜、どんな？
Ooh... What is it?
そう、問題があるよ！
Yeah, I have a question!
アーニャがMinistry Host Clubで貢いだホストは誰で、いくら？ A: Hayko 500万、B: Faun 700万
Who is the host at Ministry Host Club that Anya spent money on, and how much? A: Hayko 5M yen, B: Faun 7M yen
それで... おお... アーニャがMinistry Host Clubで貢いだホストは誰で、いくら？
So... Ooh... Who is the host at Ministry Host Club that Anya spent money on, and how much?
ちなみに、そんなに貢いでないからね。失礼な。
I didn't spend that much, by the way. Don't be ridiculous.
おお！
Oh!
困ったな... 答えは...
Oh boy... The answer is...
わからないよ... わからない。AはHayko、500万円...
I don't know... I don't know. A, Hayko 5 million yen...
...それともB、Faun、700万円。
...or B, Faun 7 million yen.
アーニャがそんな人だったなんて知らなかったよ。
I didn't know you were that kind of person, Anya.
違うよ！これ書いたの誰、Mちゃん？貢いでないってば！
Wrong! Who wrote this, M-chan? I didn't tip them!
そんなに貢いだことないもん。で、誰が答える？
I never tipped that much, so who wants to answer?
貢いでなくても、ホストクラブには行ってたんでしょ。何してたの？
Even if you didn't spend much, what were you doing at a Host Club anyway?
ホストクラブで何してたの？じゃあ、こうしようか...
What were you doing at a Host Club? If that's the case...
アーニャは良い子だし、そんなに貢ぐわけないって信じてるから...
Because I believe Anya is a good person and wouldn't tip that much...
いわゆる「大人の事情」ってやつがあるんだよ。
...there's something called 'adult circumstances'.
ああ... 大人の事情ね。
Oh... Adult circumstances.
じゃあ、まだマシな方を選ぼうか。
Alright then, let's just pick the better one.
私はAにするよ。
I'm answering A.
Siapa kah host di ministry host club yang diporotin Anya dan berapa banyak?
Who is the host at the ministry host club that Anya fleeced, and for how much?
Hayko, 5 juta yen.
Hayko, 5 million yen.
Oke, jadi jawabanmu...
Okay, so your answer is...
A, kalau begitu aku akan pergi ke A ya.
A, in that case, I'll go to A.
Oke. Oh, ternyata B aku akan sangat syok.
Okay. Oh, if it's B, I'll be very shocked.
Oke? Aku mau pergi sekarang.
Okay? I'm going now.
Tiga...
Three...
Dua...
Two...
Satu!
One!
Selamat!
Congratulations!
Aku tahu aku bisa percaya kepadamu Anya!
I knew I could trust you, Anya!
Wah, kamu pertama! Selamat!
Wow, you're the first one! Congratulations!
Berarti beneran morotin orang 5 juta yen?
So you really fleeced someone for 5 million yen?
I mean untuk gacha-ku apa sih yang...
I mean, for my gacha, what is it that...
...apa sih yang enggak boleh?
...what isn't allowed?
Boleh kan ya sekali-kali.
It's okay once in a while, right.
Aku percaya kepada Anya. Dia hanya morotin 5 juta.
I believe in Anya. She only fleeced 5 million.
Hanya? Hanya? Hanya?
Only? Only? Only?
Hanya. Next time aku porotin lebih banyak deh.
Only. Next time I'll fleece even more.
Eh bukan porotin, salah, salah.
Eh, not fleecing, wrong, wrong.
Berarti ini akan... gacha naik dong!
So this means... the gacha will go up!
Naik dong kalau gitu!
It'll go up then!
Naik, naik, naik, naik, naik, naik, naik!
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up!
Bisa dong, yoi. Bisa, bisa, bisa, bisa.
Of course, yeah. We can, we can, we can, we can.
Gampang menurut aku ya.
It was easy, in my opinion.
Mudah sekali. Mudah sekali.
So easy. So easy.
Kalau begitu... kita ke pertanyaan ketiga!
In that case... let's go to the third question!
Kalau gitu pertanyaan berikutnya, kan tadi udah Reine, udah Anya...
Then for the next question, since we've had Reine and Anya...
Berarti berikutnya Ollie dong!
Then next is Ollie!
Kalau gitu... pertanyaan Ollie!
In that case... Ollie's question!
Dadang!
Ta-da!
Sebelum debut, Ollie pernah latihan satu skill yang akhirnya tidak pernah dipakai sampai sekarang.
Before debuting, Ollie practiced a skill that ended up never being used until now.
Sebelum debut, Ollie pernah... melatih satu skill yang akhirnya tidak pernah dipakai sampai sekarang.
Before debuting, Ollie once... practiced a skill that ended up never being used until now.
Apakah itu? Apakah A, standup comedy?
What is it? Is it A, standup comedy?
Atau B, beatbox?
Or B, beatbox?
Aku tahu, aku tahu! Aku tahu!
I know, I know! I know!
Kayaknya sih aku biarin Anya aja yang ngejawab kayaknya.
I think I'll just let Anya answer.
Oh ya? Begitu kah? Kalau gitu, Anya...
Oh? Is that so? In that case, Anya...
Anya, jawaban kamu adalah...
Anya, your answer is...
Aku samar-samar ingat ya... Boleh ka aku jawab, Ollie?
I vaguely remember... May I answer, Ollie?
Silakan dijawab.
Please, answer.
Oke aku jawab, jawabanku adalah... B! Beatbox!
Okay, I'll answer, my answer is... B! Beatbox!
Oh, beatbox! Beatbox.
Kalau gitu siap lari? Oke.
In that case, are you ready to run? Okay.
Aku akan lari ke B. Eh, B.
I'll run to B. Uh, B.
Tiga...
Three...
Dua...
Two...
Satu!
One!
Wah, benar! Ya benar, yey!
Wow, correct! It's correct, yay!
Ya benar! Kamu tahu sih!
Yes, it's correct! You knew it!
Keren, keren, keren, keren, keren!
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool!
Apa sih yang aku nggak ingat tentang kalian?
What don't I remember about you guys?
Ayo, mana katanya gacha-nya naik? Gacha, gacha!
Come on, where's the gacha increase? Gacha, gacha!
Naik, naik, naik, naik, naik, naik, naik!
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up!
Cuma segitu aja? Kok nggak langsung mentok?
Just that much? Why didn't it max out?
Pelit ya? Pelit ya?
Stingy, huh? Stingy, huh?
Kalau begitu pertanyaan selanjutnya, gas!
In that case, the next question, let's go!
Oke kalau gitu pertanyaan selanjutnya!
Okay, then the next question!
Keren banget. Kalau begitu lanjut nggak sih? Lanjut!
So cool. In that case, are we continuing? Yes!
Pertanyaan keempat!
Question number four!
Reine kalau malam-malam paling sering delivery apa?
What does Reine most often have delivered at night?
Apa ini? Pertanyaan Reine!
What's this? Reine's question!
Pertanyaannya adalah... Reine kalau malam-malam sering delivery apa?
The question is... what does Reine most often have delivered at night?
A, Sushi.
B, Ayam Geprek.
Siapa nih yang mau jawab? Aku, aku! Aku dari tadi belum jawab.
Who wants to answer? Me, me! I haven't answered yet.
Aku tahu sih jawabannya.
I know the answer.
Jadi jawabannya itu adalah B! Karena Reine suka makanan yang pedas.
So the answer is B! Because Reine likes spicy food.
Oke. Langsung saja... mari kita lihat.
Okay. Let's get right into it... let's see.
Apakah sudah siap? Siap!
Are you ready? Ready!
Tiga...
Three...
Dua...
Two...
Satu!
One!
Jatuh dia! Wah!
She fell! Whoa!
Jatuh! Jatuh dia!
Fell! She fell!
Wah, kasihan sekali. Di sana seperti apa, Ollie?
Wow, how pitiful. What's it like down there, Ollie?
Serasa balik ke kuburan, woi!
It feels like I'm back in the grave, hey!
Serem. Akhirnya ada yang tahu perasaanku untuk jatuh ke sana.
Scary. Finally someone knows my feeling of falling down there.
Tinggal Reine nih belum jatuh.
Only Reine hasn't fallen yet.
Eh, jangan dong. Itu ayam geprek gitu...
Hey, don't say that. About the ayam geprek...
...karena nggak tahu kalau malam-malam makan ayam geprek itu...
...because I don't know if eating ayam geprek at night...
...nggak tahu sih nggak pernah.
...I don't know, never did.
Udah tutup kali, jadi nggak pernah mesen. Biasanya siang.
It's probably closed, so I never order it. Usually at noon.
Iya, kalau misalnya ini...
Yeah, if for example this...
Pokoknya gitu deh. BTW, apakah dia akan naik menurut kalian?
Anyway, that's it. BTW, do you think it'll go up?
Lho! Kok turun! Kok turun!
Wait! Why is it going down! It's going down!
Yah, Ollie salah!
Aw, Ollie was wrong!
Ollie salah!
Ollie was wrong!
Wah, Ollie salah! Parah banget, aku kira dia bener.
Whoa, Ollie was wrong! That's too bad, I thought she was right.
Gimana sih? Yah!
What happened? Aw!
Wah, dia jatuh! Dia jatuh!
Whoa, she's falling! She's falling!
Oke, aduh maaf, maaf gelut.
Okay, sorry, sorry for the fight.
Belum selesai! Nanti, nanti, nanti.
It's not over yet! Later, later, later.
Gelutnya di belakang parkiran saja kalau sudah selesai.
Just fight behind the parking lot once we're done.
Di belakang parkiran? Tidak ramah bintang satu.
Behind the parking lot? One star review, not friendly.
Serem banget tante. Tapi kita masih bisa nggak sih?
That's scary, auntie. But can we still do it?
Masih bisa lah menurutku. Bisa, bisa, bisa lah.
I think we still can. We can, we can, for sure.
Oke. Sampai penuh.
Okay. Until it's full.
Sampai penuh. Sampai ke pertanyaan...
Until it's full. Until the next...
...berikutnya!
...question!
Wah, kalau gitu waktunya untuk pertanyaan selanjutnya nggak sih?
Whoa, then isn't it time for the next question?
Waktunya untuk pertanyaan selanjutnya!
Time for the next question!
Aku deh! Aku deh!
Me! Let me do it!
Aku! Aku mau nanya! Aku mau nanya!
Me! I want to ask! I want to ask!
Silakan Ollie. Silakan Ollie.
Go ahead, Ollie. Go ahead, Ollie.
Kalau begitu kita langsung masuk saja, pertanyaan...
Then let's just jump right in, the next...
...berikutnya!
...question!
Binatang apa yang menyerang Ollie saat stream?
What animal attacked Ollie during a stream?
Apakah laba-laba, A, atau B, kecoak?
Is it a spider, A, or B, a cockroach?
Siapa nih mau jawab? Reine mau jawab?
Who wants to answer? Does Reine want to?
Aku! Gantian kamu yang jatuh!
Me! It's your turn to fall!
Gantian kamu yang jatuh! Aduh.
It's your turn to fall! Oh boy.
Binatang yang menyerang Ollie saat stream...
The animal that attacked Ollie during a stream...
Kayaknya... aku tahu nih, aku tahu.
I think... I know this, I know.
Laba-laba itu serem, tapi dia nggak loncat. Biasanya pelan.
Spiders are scary, but they don't jump. Usually they're slow.
Jadi kalau kecoak itu kan biasanya kayak "werrr" gitu.
But cockroaches usually go "werrr" like that.
Iya, soalnya wording-nya "menyerang".
Yeah, because the wording is "attacked".
Jadi instingku, aku akan menjawab B, kecoak. B!
So my instinct says I'll answer B, cockroach. B!
Wah, kayaknya percaya diri.
Whoa, someone's confident.
Kalau begitu, B mulu ya dari tadi kayaknya.
It seems like it's been B every time.
Oke, kalau begitu aku akan maju ke B, oke?
Okay, then I'll head for B, okay?
Oke! Ayo bersiap!
Okay! Get ready!
Tiga, dua, satu!
Three, two, one!
Wah! Yeay!
Whoa! Yay!
Wah, selamat! Bagus sekali!
Wow, congrats! That was great!
Okaeri! Yeay!
Welcome back! Yay!
Ayo, ayo! Naik, naik, naik!
Come on, come on! Go up, go up, go up!
Naik, naik, naik!
Go up, go up, go up!
Naik! Kamu kapan diserang kecoak?
Go up! When did you get attacked by a cockroach?
Pernah waktu itu, awal-awal debut, tiba-tiba ada kecoak melayang gitu.
It happened once, during early debut, suddenly a cockroach was flying around.
Pancuran Ollie kali itu.
That was Ollie's "pancuran".
Zom-ray! Zom-ray! Ternyata...
Zom-ray! Zom-ray! Turns out...
...zom-ray pun ini ya, cross species juga.
...the zom-ray is cross-species too.
Cross species, betul! Halus sekali!
Cross-species, exactly! Very smooth!
Wah keren! Masih belum, masih aman.
Whoa, cool! Not yet, still safe.
Masih belum jatuh, guys. Kita harus memenuhi gauge ini sampai maks.
Still haven't fallen, guys. We need to fill this gauge to the max.
Mentok! Kalau begitu langsung saja kita ke pertanyaan...
To the limit! Then let's head straight to the next...
...selanjutnya!
...question!
Wah sip! Ini sudah berapa? Keenam ya?
Alright! How many is this? The sixth?
Pertanyaan keenam! Wah, cepat sekali ya.
The sixth question! Wow, that was fast.
Cepat sekali. Kalau gitu siapa yang mau nanya?
Very fast. Then who wants to ask?
Kalau gitu aku deh! Giliran aku yang nanya ya guys.
Then let it be me! It's my turn to ask, guys.
Oke, oke. Oke, pertanyaan keenam!
Okay, okay. Okay, the sixth question!
Apa judul lagu yang dinyanyikan Anya pada hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade?
What is the title of the song Anya sang at hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade?
Apa judul lagu yang dinyanyikan aku pada hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade?
What's the title of the song I sang at hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade?
Masa nggak nonton? A, Phony, B, cutlery?
Don't tell me you didn't watch? A, Phony, B, cutlery?
Wah! Aku tahu! Aku tahu! Aku tahu!
Whoa! I know! I know! I know!
Jawab! Jawab!
Answer! Answer!
Jawab B, cutlery!
Answer B, cutlery!
Apakah sudah yakin? Saya yakin!
Are you sure? I'm sure!
Oke Kureiji Ollie, silakan kamu lari.
Okay Kureiji Ollie, please run.
Oke! Huisha!
Okay! Huisha!
Wah! Posisi siap! Siap!
Whoa! Ready position! Ready!
Tiga, dua, satu, go!
Three, two, one, go!
Wah! Yeay!
Whoa! Yay!
Keren kan? Sudah saya hafal semua.
Cool, right? I've memorized them all.
Keren banget! Semua yang tampil di fes aku hafal semua.
So cool! I've memorized everyone who performed at the fes.
Iya, dia paling sering nonton ya konser-konser Hololive dan lain-lain.
Yeah, she watches Hololive concerts and stuff the most.
Kalian semua juga nonton kan? Iya!
You all watch them too, right? Yeah!
Berarti gauge-nya naik dong! Naik lagi, naik lagi!
That means the gauge goes up! Up again, up again!
Naik lagi! Wah, dikit lagi!
Up again! Whoa, just a bit more!
Gampang banget ya dari tadi? Kecurang! Kecurang!
It's been so easy, right? Cheating! Cheating!
Naik lagi dong, please! Kok cuma segitu? Ya sudahlah.
Go up more, please! Why only that much? Oh well.
Ya sudah, kita tinggal berusaha...
Alright, we just need to try...
Lho, lho, lho! Berhenti! Naik atau turun?
Wait, wait, wait! It stopped! Up or down?
Naik lagi dikit, dikit lagi, dikit lagi.
Up a bit more, just a bit more, just a bit more.
Bisa dinaikin nggak sampai mentok?
Can we push it to the limit?
Dikit lagi! Ya ampun! Yah! Yah! Yah!
Just a bit more! My gosh! Aw! Aw! Aw!
Mohon maaf, maaf.
Sorry, sorry.
Oke kalau gitu, kita pengen memenuhi ini kan?
Okay then, we want to fill this up, right?
Kalau begitu langsung aja nggak sih ke pertanyaan berikutnya!
Then let's just go straight to the next question!
Dikit lagi nih guys. Udah ke berapa? Ketujuh?
Just a bit more, guys. Which one is it? The seventh?
Pertanyaan ketujuh? Wah!
The seventh question? Wow!
Cepat sekali!
So fast!
Duh ya, tadi kan pertanyaan ke-7...
Gosh, that was the 7th question...
Gimana kalau Anya tanya lagi deh?
How about Anya asks again?
Anya tanya lagi deh.
Let Anya ask again.
Kalau gitu Anya tanya lagi deh.
In that case, let Anya ask again.
Oke, aku lagi? Aku lagi?
Okay, me again? Me again?
Soalnya tadi kita bener kan?
Because we were right, wasn't it?
Boleh nih, boleh nih. Oke.
This is fine, this is fine. Okay.
Kayaknya pertanyaanku gampang-gampang ya?
Seems like my questions are pretty easy, right?
Gak! Susah!
No! It's hard!
Susah? Tapi kalian semua benar.
Hard? But you were all correct.
Itu sih skill issue aja sih menurutku.
That's just a skill issue, in my opinion.
Oke, pertanyaan ke-7.
Okay, question number 7.
Apa kepanjangan dari Omet?
What does Omet stand for?
Apa kepanjangan dari Omet? Hah?
What does Omet stand for? Huh?
A. Om dan Jamet.
A. Om and Jamet.
B. Organisasi Masyarakat Telat Tidur.
B. Late Sleeper Community Organization.
Ini... ini... aku... aku...
This... this... I... I...
Siapa yang mau jawab?
Who wants to answer?
Aku! Eh, tadi kan udah, tadi kan udah.
Me! Oh, but you already did earlier.
Jadi ini... Reine mau jawab.
So this... Reine wants to answer.
Oke, sesungguhnya... sesungguhnya...
Okay, actually... actually...
Aku kalau boleh jujur ya, aku gak pernah denger tuh B,
To be honest, I've never heard of B,
Organisasi Masyarakat Telat Tidur, gak pernah denger.
Late Sleeper Community Organization, never heard of it.
Tapi aku yakin dengan pilihanku yaitu, Om dan Jamet.
But I'm sure of my choice, which is Om and Jamet.
Kenapa milih Om dan Jamet?
Why choose Om and Jamet?
Karena gak pernah denger B itu apa.
Because I've never heard what B is.
Tapi aku kan sempat tidur, jadi bisa aja dong, kan telat tidur.
But I did sleep, so it could be, since it's "late sleeper".
Kalau telat tidur sih itu si Omet yang satu lagi.
If it's about being a late sleeper, that's the other Omet.
Iya, kamu emang telat tidur? Kamu kayaknya tidur terus deh.
Yeah, you stay up late? You seem to sleep all the time.
Iya sih, iya sih, bener sih. Ada... ya... gitu deh.
Well, yeah, that's true. There's... yeah... something like that.
Dukung aku semuanya!
Support me, everyone!
Kambis tipis bisa!
Kambis can do it!
Oke! Oke!
Okay! Okay!
Kita lihat, apa kali ini Reine akan jatuh?
Let's see, will Reine fall this time?
Eh, jangan dong!
Hey, don't say that!
Tiga, dua, satu!
Three, two, one!
Yukkuri, yukkuri!
Slowly, slowly!
Lari, lari, lari!
Run, run, run!
Eh, bener lagi loh!
Eh, it's correct again!
Bener lagi! Berarti gatcha!
Correct again! That means gacha!
Naik, naik, naik!
Up, up, up!
Anya-la naik! Reine-la naik!
Anya-la up! Reine-la up!
Tapi ya, berarti ini sudah menunjukkan kalau holoro ikatannya...
But yeah, this shows that holoro's bond is...
...begini banget ya, erat ya. Erat!
...like this, very tight. Tight!
Yeay!
Berarti kita boleh pengumuman dong?
Does that mean we can make an announcement?
Boleh, boleh! Yes!
You can, you can! Yes!
Kalau gitu, pengumumannya mana?
In that case, where is the announcement?
Ini dia! Jajang!
Here it is! Ta-da!
Pertama-tama, mari kita lihat merch ini!
First of all, let's look at this merch!
hololive Indonesia Second Generation 3D Acrylic Stand!
Lucu banget kita!
We look so cute!
Posenya itu loh, aku suka.
That pose, I like it.
Iya, posenya keren banget. Keren banget!
Yeah, the pose is really cool. Really cool!
Pose Reine beneran tante antagonis banget.
Reine's pose is really like an antagonist auntie.
Dia kayak ojou-sama gitu.
She's like an ojou-sama.
Eh, diam.
Hey, shut it.
Tapi masih ada lagi loh, kan ini collab merch kita kan ya?
But there's more, this is our collab merch, right?
Kita juga ada merch-merch kita sendiri kan ya?
We also have our own individual merch, right?
Betul sekali! Yang kemarin diumumkan ya.
Exactly! The ones announced yesterday.
Ini dia! 3D-Debut Celebration!
Here it is! 3D-Debut Celebration!
Ada apa aja?
What do we have?
Foto dari... ada Ollie, ada Coach Jacket.
A photo of... there's Ollie, there's a Coach Jacket.
Terus aku, Anya Melfissa Special Cushion.
Then me, Anya Melfissa Special Cushion.
Dan aku, Sweet Tonjok Hoodie dari Reine!
And me, Sweet Tonjok Hoodie from Reine!
Cute kan? Cute kan? Goodbye wallet ya dong.
Cute, right? Cute, right? Goodbye wallet, indeed.
Gak apa-apa, aku juga kok.
It's okay, me too.
Ayo kita lihat lebih dekat lagi, tapi sebelum itu, kalian udah siap?
Let's take a closer look, but before that, are you guys ready?
Eh, bentar-bentar, tunggu-tunggu.
Wait a minute, wait, wait.
Pitanya ya?
The ribbon?
Eh, aku kayaknya udah deh.
Eh, I think I'm ready.
Udah? Eh tunggu sepatunya.
Already? Oh wait, the shoes.
Oh iya sepatu, sepatu. Soalnya maaf, biasanya nyeker soalnya.
Oh right, shoes, shoes. Because sorry, I'm usually barefoot.
Oke, ayo kita ganti ke sexy pose.
Okay, let's change to a sexy pose.
Dengan begitu, mari kita open!
With that, let's open!
Kita balik lagi ke stage, apa udah ganti ke bright outfit?
We're back on stage, have we changed to the bright outfits?
Oh my god, so sexy!
Ya, jadi kita akan announce merch dengan outfit ini.
Yes, so we will announce the merch with these outfits.
Kalau gitu kita lihat acrylic stand-nya dulu kali ya.
Then let's look at the acrylic stand first.
Acrylic Stand!
Mana acrylic-nya? Mana? Mana?
Where's the acrylic? Where? Where?
Kocira de! Di sini! Di sini!
Over here! Here! Here!
Acrylic Stand!
Pokoknya acrylic stands kita... mm-hm...
Anyway, our acrylic stands... mm-hm...
Jadi ada 3D Acrylic Stand yang tadi pose tadi itu.
So there's the 3D Acrylic Stand with that pose earlier.
Mmm, tadi gimana sih posenya? Aku lupa.
Mmm, how was the pose again? I forgot.
Oke, kayak gini.
Okay, like this.
Kurang lebih lah. Kurang lebih.
Close enough. Close enough.
Ayo pokoknya kumpulin semuanya ya teman-teman.
Anyway, make sure to collect them all, friends.
So cute kan? So cute. Terus...
They're so cute, right? So cute. Also...
Lucu banget! Wah!
So cute! Wow!
Pokoknya tuh paling seru tuh kalau bertiga dijejerin, nggak sih menurut aku?
I think it's most fun if the three of them are lined up together, don't you?
Iya, satu paket teman-teman.
Yes, as a set, friends.
Ber-tiga-tiganya guys, sini sini sini.
All three of them, guys, come here, come here.
Satu paket teman-teman. Ber-tiga-tiganya guys.
As a set, friends. All three of them, guys.
Set, tiga-tiganya dong seperti kita.
There, all three of them just like us.
Habis itu kita mau lihat nggak sih merch kita yang individu juga?
After that, don't we want to see our individual merch as well?
Yes yes yes! Kita lihat dari yang pertama kali debut dulu kali ya 3D-nya.
Yes yes yes! Let's look at the one that debuted in 3D first.
Apa ya? Apa ya?
What could it be? What could it be?
Dari... dari Tante, silakan.
From... from Auntie, please go ahead.
First is mine, Reine! Sweet Tonjok Hoodie!
Ilustrasinya dibuat oleh Yomozaka-sensei.
The illustration was made by Yomozaka-sensei.
Terus di tangannya tuh ada itu lho, ada "Salam MERAKyats".
And on the sleeve, there's the "Salam MERAKyats" message.
Jadi kalau misalkan kalian ketemu Merakyats tuh kayak...
So if you meet other Merakyats, it's like...
"Salam Merakyats! Salam Merakyats! Salam Merakyats!"
"Greetings Merakyats! Greetings Merakyats! Greetings Merakyats!"
Banyak katun gitu, sangat... ooh seru pokoknya.
It's made of lots of cotton, it's really... ooh, it's fun.
Oke, selanjutnya... Ollie?
Okay, next is... Ollie?
Oh, aku! Kalau gitu, eto... here's mine! Ini dia punya Ollie!
Oh, me! In that case, here's mine! This is Ollie's!
Wuih lucu banget!
Wow, so cute!
Super Kawaii Zombie Coach-Jacket, teman-teman!
Super Kawaii Zombie Coach-Jacket, friends!
Ini tuh kayak lucu tapi cool gitu.
It's like, cute but cool at the same time.
Iya kan ya? Kayak double color gitu...
Right? With those double colors...
...kayak rambutnya Ollie gitu ceritanya. Warnanya bom banget sih.
...just like Ollie's hair. The colors are really the bomb.
Terbuat dari poliester dan all size lho teman-teman. Jadi kalian nggak usah khawatir.
It's made of polyester and it's one-size-fits-all, friends. So you don't have to worry.
Sama, aku juga all size.
Same here, mine is also one-size-fits-all.
Iya, dua-duanya kalian itunya all size ya.
Yes, both of yours are one-size-fits-all.
Kamu apa?
What about yours?
Oh, kalau punya aku... cushion! Ini dia Anya Melfissa Special Cushion!
Oh, as for mine... a cushion! Here's the Anya Melfissa Special Cushion!
Bentar guys, aku ada bawa lho guys sebenarnya.
Wait guys, I actually brought it with me.
Dia ngiler dong itu. Ngiler kayak Udin.
It's drooling. Drooling like Udin.
Enak aja kayak Udin. Ngiler.
Don't say it's like Udin. It's drooling.
Tadaa! Lucu banget!
Tada! So cute!
Boleh pegang nggak? Depan belakang beda guys.
Can I hold it? The front and back are different, guys.
Ooh... ngiler. Mumumu... pegang.
Ooh... drool. Mumu... let me hold it.
Ih lucu banget!
It's so cute!
Oh my god, Anyanya ada dua!
Oh my god, there are two Anyas!
Halo guys, aku Anya Melfissa dari Hololive ID.
Hello guys, I'm Anya Melfissa from Hololive ID.
Eh Holo JP desu.
Uh, Holo JP desu.
Ber-beda ya.
It's different.
Keren, lucu banget! Ini... ini fluffy banget gila.
Cool, so cute! This... this is crazy fluffy.
Ngiler. Kalian juga bisa memegang iler Anya kalau kalian beli ini.
Drool. You can also hold Anya's drool if you buy this.
Gimana ya? Gimana ya teman-teman?
How about it? How about it, friends?
Aduh jualnya di mana sih?
Where is it being sold?
Ini semuanya akan on sale hari ini ya guys pada jam sembilan malam waktu Indonesia Barat.
All of these will go on sale today at 9 PM Western Indonesia Time.
Atau jam 11 JST!
Or at 11 PM JST!
Kuji-ji kara hatsubai de gozaimasu!
It will be on sale starting from 9 o'clock!
Di mana sale-nya? Di Hololive Production Shop, Tokopedia, dan Geek Jack.
Where's the sale? At the Hololive Production Shop, Tokopedia, and Geek Jack.
In stock ya guys, in stock ya guys. Bukan PO.
It's in stock, guys. Not a pre-order.
Limited quality.
Limited quantity.
Dah... tunggu tunggu tunggu dia... dia belum balik.
Wait... wait, wait, it... it hasn't come back yet.
To iu wake de... Oke teman-teman, bagaimana tadi?
So... Okay friends, how was it?
Buruan beli iler Anya, kapan lagi iler Anya!
Hurry up and buy Anya's drool, when else could you get Anya's drool!
Gitu gitu, lima menit lagi ya, betul lima menit lagi.
Right, five more minutes, that's right, five more minutes.
Jadi tolong dibeli ya teman-teman.
So please buy them, friends.
Info jual ginjal? Jangan! Jangan!
Info on selling kidneys? Don't do it! Don't!
Oke, kalau begitu... sudah nggak sih? Eh? Segitu aja?
Okay, then... is that it? Eh? Is that all?
Nggak! Nggak gitu! Masih ada lagi guys!
No! That's not it! There's more, guys!
Jangan pergi dulu! Tonton sampai habis pokoknya.
Don't leave yet! Watch until the end.
Karena ada apa ya? Ada apa Ollie? Ada apa kita?
Because what's coming up? What is it, Ollie? What do we have?
Ada surprise buat kalian.
There's a surprise for you all.
Surprise after surprise yang sudah ditunggu-tunggu.
Surprise after surprise that you've been waiting for.
Apa itu? Apa itu?
What is it? What is it?
Yaitu... Satu, dua, tiga... Lagu Baru Holoro! Wah!
It's... One, two, three... A new Holoro song! Whoa!
Lagu baru Holoro! Apa? Lagu baru!
A new Holoro song! What? A new song!
Lagu baru! Lagu baru! Yes, there's more!
A new song! A new song! Yes, there's more!
Nah ini tuh seru deh pokoknya. Jadi apa namanya kita harus bernyanyi...
Anyway, this is going to be exciting. So, we're going to sing...
...dengerin kita ya guys menyanyikan lagu...
...listen to us sing a song, guys...
...sebagai unit.
...as a unit.
Yes! Kita hari ini showcase-nya yang lagu apa ya?
Yes! Which song are we showcasing today?
Lagu... lagu versi Jepang kan?
The... the Japanese version, right?
Iya. Oke.
Yes. Okay.
Oke guys, eto... tolong dengarkan...
Okay guys, so... please listen...
...please listen... kiite kudasai... Slap by Step!
...please listen... please listen... Slap by Step!
Holoro! Are you ready?
Who do you think we are? We are always ready.
Stop chatting, the show needs us.
単純なphraseでcatchして
Catch it with a simple phrase
困難だらけの...
Even in the midst of many hardships...
困難だらけの人生だけど
Life is full of difficulties, but...
自由奔放に slap して楽しんじゃおう
Let's slap freely and enjoy ourselves!
Ah Oh Ah Oh
Fly like a feather soaring high!
立ちはだかる壁なんて
Any wall standing in the way...
3秒で knock out
...is a knock out in 3 seconds!
Fly like a feather soaring high!
止まらないんじゃなくて
It's not that I won't stop...
止まれないんだ！
...I can't stop!
Slap by Step で空中散歩 私なりで
Walking in the air with Slap by Step, in my own way
隙あらば その瞬間に完全掌握
If there's an opening, I'll take complete control
沼にハマっちゃうぞ！
You're going to fall for us!
One Two Three で深層心理 crash して
Crash into the deep psyche with One Two Three
ツマラない
This boring...
現実を常識外れの
...reality, with an unconventional...
rifle で撃ち抜いて！
...rifle, shoot it through!
Ah 極彩色の dance floor
Ah, a multicolored dance floor
とんだ無礼ね 平手打ちよ
What an insult, here's a slap across the face
子供扱いしないでね
Don't treat me like a child
ニヤついた顔に slash it!
Slash that grinning face!
Clap your hands and stand up, please!
首飛んじゃっても為せば成る
Even if your head flies off, where there's a will there's a way
それが theory さ
That's the theory
Clap your hands and stand up, please!
つべこべ言わず 着いてきな
Follow me without complaining
Ready? It's time for the show!
We're ignited,
and have no fear,
ready to break through.
姿
Appearance,
形は
Shapes,
違っても同じ想いだ
Though different, the feelings are the same
そうだから...！
That's why...!
Slap by Step で空中散歩 私なりで
Walking in the air with Slap by Step, in my own way
隙あらば その瞬間に完全掌握
If there's an opening, I'll take complete control
沼にハマっちゃうぞ！
You're going to fall for us!
One Two Three で深層心理 crash して
Crash into the deep psyche with One Two Three
今すぐね 私たちの色に
Right now, I'll show you the world...
染め上げた世界を見せる！
...dyed in our colors!
How was it everybody?
You've had enough? I know you're all hyped!
With #holoroshow and #holoro3D, we can hear your voices clearly!
But louder for everyone in the back!
Cape... Balik lagi!
I'm tired... We're back!
Jadi gimana tadi adalah original song kita,
So, how was that? That was our original song,
Slap by Step!
Coba-coba gimana, gimana?
Tell me, how was it, how was it?
Saya mau mendengar opini kalian!
I want to hear your opinions!
Gimana opini netizen?
How are the netizens' opinions?
よかった！
Great!
Jadi untuk release-nya,
So for the release,
tolong dinanti-nantikan!
please look forward to it!
Akan ada digital release-nya juga kan ya pastinya.
There'll surely be a digital release too.
Betul sekali!
Exactly!
Pokoknya sampai waktu release mohon dinanti-nantikan ya.
Anyway, please keep looking forward to the release.
Kalau perlu PV-nya dimainin, dihafalin lagunya.
Play the MV and memorize the song if you have to!
Jadi pas release dah kayak, udah hafal!
So that when it releases, you'll already know it by heart!
Gila gila gila. Capek, capek.
Crazy, crazy, crazy. I'm exhausted.
Kalau begitu, itu saja dari kita Holoro!
In that case, that's all from us, Holoro!
Kita ngomong yang biasa nggak sih?
Should we say our usual sign-off?
Otsu Holoro?
Okay, satu, dua, tiga...
Okay, one, two, three...
おつほろろ〜！
Otsu Holoro~!
Bye-bye!
July 29 22:00 (JST)