(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
I'm Gigi Murin!
I used to be 14 years old in 8th grade, but now I'm not!
I'm a bit clumsy, crazy and silly, and I may not look it,
but actually, I'm a member of Hololive English Justice.
That's true.
I literally call myself the Fister because I fister people with my big big power glyph,
and the citizens don't really like that I call myself the Fister,
and I don't really know why.
TWO GREMS AND A SHOEBOX
Literally called the Fister because I fister people, you know?
You know what I mean?
Today's the day of a very important Justice meeting,
but I- I accidentally overslept!
So I have to hurry up and...
make sure to look both ways before crossing the road!
And go!
Ah!
Gigi goes bye-bye!
Ah! Ouch!
Who is that? That was so weird.
Wow! Where am I?
Beautiful 2D fantasy world!
I'm so efficient at doing things in my car...
Hit them with a car and it'd be really cool... what the...?
A horse? That's not a truck.
That's dangerous! I could have died!
But phew! That Grem sure knows how to drive.
Gremlin Justi-
Ah!
Ugh... my body hurts.
I feel like I got run over by something, but I don't know what.
Oh! Is that a statue of a Grem? Looks cool.
Wait a second... I know this!
I've been Isekai'd!
What the freak! Gigi, you're here too?
This Justice cardboard...
Gigi, what's going on? Where are we?
What are you guys doing? Why are you cardboard?
Why does Cece look so sad?
You f***ing h**! How dare you do this to me!
You b***h! This is your fault somehow!
I don't know how you did this, you absolute little d***head! Oh, you look terrible!
Well, let's go investigate around here!
Let's go! Okay! I'm on my way!
Wait, guys! Wait for me!
We can have an adventure together! It'll be so fun and...
Wait, wait! What's going on?
Ahhhhh!
Horses!
Two of them!
Ahhhhh!
Goodbye,
leaving heartbreak of the past behind
Looking back
it's time
Moving down our own path
Evermore voyaging forward
To make this journey last
GIGI MURIN
In a sparkle within the light
Like a promise found riding the wind
Where a myth begins spiraling outward and up
An inspiring tale begins
We who dared defy changing of times
As we follow unreachable dreams
Know it's here and right now
That we're drawn to somehow
Deep inside a will to live believe
Wandering near and far
Touching lives just like ours
Finding fires
Till they've wasted away
One day
I'll recall this night
Our relentless odyssey
Pressing onward
We never surrender
Toward the skies we can rise
Again
ううう... ああ...
Uuuh... Aah...
これ以上何かにぶつかったら
If anything else hits me,
もう長くは持たないと思う...
I don't think I'll survive much longer...
本当にもっと気をつけないと
I really need to be more careful.
生きててよかった
Thank goodness I'm still alive.
風がお前の訪れを囁いていた...
The winds whispered of your coming...
そして今、お前はここにいる
And now, here you are.
あんた誰！？
Who are you!?
ワシはグレム王国で最も偉大な魔法使い
I am the greatest wizard in all of Grem Kingdom.
魔法使いおじいちゃんだ
Wizard Oji-chan.
魔法使いおじいちゃん？
Wizard Oji-chan?
魔法使いなの、おじいちゃんなの？
Are you a wizard or Oji-chan?
名前はあるの？何て呼べばいい？
Do you have a name? What should I call you?
多くのグレムの戦士たちが一人、また一人と倒れていった
So many of Grem's warriors have fallen, one by one,
お前の到着を待つ間に...
while we waited for your arrival...
オッケー
Okay.
待った甲斐があった！
The wait was worth it!!!
ジジ！
Gigi!
お前はワシが想像したどんな英雄よりもはるかに強力だ！
You are far more powerful than I ever imagined a hero could be!
返事してくれないな。たぶんNPCだ
He's not responding to me. He's probably an NPC.
これってゲーム？ゲームみたいな感じ？
It's like this is a game? Like a game?
NPC！？
NPC!?
NPCだと！？
わあ、ごめんなさい！ごめんなさい！
Oh, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
ワシは高貴な魔法使いだぞ！
I am the noble wizard!
おじいちゃんだぞ！
Oji-chan!
ごめんなさい！喋れるなんて知らなかったの！
Oh, I'm sorry! I didn't know you could talk!
お前が鍵なのだ
You're the key.
お前がいなければ、お前の友もこの世界も
Without you, your friend and this world
失われてしまう...
are lost...
えっ？失われる？何の話？
What? Lost? What are you talking about?
ジジよ
Gigi,
世界が待っている...
the world is waiting...
私の名前を知ってるの？
He knows my name.
それ、私。私がヒーローなんだ
That's me. I'm the hero.
世界を... 段ボールになることから救うんだ！
I'm going to save the world from... from being cardboard!
ハズァーーーーッ！！
HAZZAAHH!!
うわああ、私に何をしたの！？
Aaah, what did you do to me!?
痛い！痛いよ！
It hurts! It hurts!
おかしいな...
That's strange...
何て言ってるの？何で痛いの？
What are you saying? Why does it hurt?
ハズァッ！！
HAZZAA!!
わあ！私、すごく可愛くて柔らかくてふわふわになった！
Wow! I'm so cute and soft and fluffy now!
お友達になりましょう！在庫がある時に買ってね！
Friends with you! Purchase next time they're in stock!
ごめん、もう一回やらせて！
Sorry, let me try again!
今度はちゃんとやるから！
I'll do it right this time!
よくわからないけど...
I don't understand...
オッケー、オッケー！
Okay, okay!
ハズァーーーーッ！！
HAZZAAHH!!
スクイーク！スクイークスクイーク！
Squeak! Squeak squeak!
どうした、もっと強くなりたいか！？
What's wrong, you want to be more powerful!?
よーし、いいぞ！準備はいいか！？
Okay, okay! I'm ready!
ジジ！行くぞ、ボディー！
Gigi! Here we go, body!
パアアアア！！
PAAAAHH!!
ううう... ああ...
Uuuh... Aah...
あ、待って！動けるようになった！
Oh wait! I can move now!
What's this?
Hands!
You did it! You've done it!
Oh my god, look how... how cute I am.
Aww, I've always been cute, but now...
now it's even cute... now everyone can see how cute I am.
Look at that fat tail. Look at that fat tail.
I can do everything!
I can't do that.
Watch this, guys. You've never seen this before.
Okay, okay. Whee! Whee! I can do everything.
Two in a row? Just kidding.
I have a world to save.
Look at that! Everyone loves me!
Gigi Murin! Hahaha!
Oh, dizzy.
Wizard: Oh, I'm so dizzy.
Wizard: Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
What... what should I do to save everyone?
Oh, the world is spinning. Owie.
Wizard: Before saving everyone...
let's see if you can survive basic chores.
Basic? I can do basic chores.
Wizard: Let's start with...
Start with what? Start with what?
What? What are we starting with?
What? What? A wing?
Wait! Wait! What did you do? What did you do?
Oh, did you do something? Wait! Ah!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
No! No!
The birds took him.
I knew I could never trust a bird.
Sewer Grem: Hey you. Come here! Follow me!
A Grem?
Um... but I have to help my... friend.
Sewer Grem: You're scared and lost... Not knowing what to do, right?
Sewer Grem: I'll show you how to save your friends. Follow me!
Oh, okay.
So small.
This is weird.
This place is dark and it smells bad.
Sewer Grem: Hey it smells good!!!!
Do exactly as I say if you want to save your friends!
Sewer Grem: Go to the Grem Kingdom and return with the One Ping, a Honkshoe, and a Straw Hat.
Why do you need them?
Sewer Grem: YOU DON'T GET TO ASK ME ANY QUESTIONS!!! NOW GO GIGI, GOOOOOOO!!
Okay.
Whoa!
So this is the Grem Kingdom?
It's so cool. There's so many Grems!
Does this mean this entire kingdom is mine if I save it?
Whoa, there's so many of you.
What? No, not all at once. No, no, no.
What? Oh, I can't hear you.
Let's... let's try this Grem. Lucky little Grem, what's on your mind?
Grem NPC: Things aren't going well with my partner... I need your help to fix our relationship.
Aww... that is not my problem.
Ah, okay. How about this Grem? Do you have anything interesting to say to me?
Grem NPC: My tummy is getting very large and I don't know why.
Please come with me to the doctor.
(Whispering) Okay, a little secret... pregnant.
Okay, how about this one?
Grem NPC: Make a contract with me, and become a magical girl!
Oh, that is not my problem either. Oh no, no, no, no.
I will not be doing that. I know what happens when you sign a contract.
You should never put your name down on things.
Well, these Grems were useless.
I think if I use my RPG knowledge, you're supposed to get information from NPCs...
at a store!
And there's so many stalls near me. Ah, I'll go to this one.
Aww, so cute.
Aww, are you a little worker Grem? Aww.
How much do you make an hour? Do you even make enough to survive?
Aww. Oh, what is this?
Ooh, for me?
General Store Grem: Uh, that's decorative hay, not edible...
Could I ask you something?
Oh, what is this? Dialogue!
Um...
Where can I get The One Ping?
Oh you are looking for the One Ping?
Then, here is the Quest for you!
Take this ring and throw it
into a volcano to destroy it.
This cursed ring holds centuries of anger.
To purify it, it must be thrown into a volcano...
...but we fear fire and can't go near it.
Okay, yeah,
I can do that quest for you.
Don't worry, I am the chosen one.
A ring!
Wow!
I don't know what a volcano is.
How is this supposed to help me save Justice?
They're gonna die!
They're gonna die if a volcano erupts!
Oh wait, I don't know what a volcano is.
Let's just try to find The One Ping myself.
Wait, this box looks a little suspicious.
Hmm.
Deliver to weapon shop.
Oh, cool!
It's for a quest.
Okay!
Hey, I got a package!
I got you guys a package!
It's a gift from me!
I bought this!
I'll just leave it right here.
Iya!
It looks just like the box of the BL novel set I lost!
Thank you!
Your BL novels?
No... no...
No...
Don't lose sight of the quest, Gigi.
Whoa, this is a really cool sword!
I bet I could save Justice with this!
Why is this so heavy for cardboard?
Oh my god.
I'm gonna put it back.
This is why Liz has so much arm strength.
Oh my god.
Hahaha! That sword is pretty useless.
It can undo cardboardification or something...
This sword's really cool.
How much is it?
What's that?
Five dollars?
I can't afford that.
But how about I save them through the power of friendship?
Oh, another textbox.
Is The One Ping even real?
I present a quest to you!
Conquer it, and The One Ping shall be yours!
Would you craft 10 iron bars?
Okay,
sounds easy. I can do that.
To craft 10 iron bars,
you need to perform a freestyle dance and rap.
Gather 10 Grems with your performance
to craft 10 iron bars.
What?
I don't think that's how you craft an iron bar.
Ayo, you set, bro?
Show us what you've got!
Where'd I get over here?
Why do I have sunglasses?
Grems, this place is kinda nasty.
Who let you live in a shoe box?
Oh, okay.
I'm getting it.
Oh okay, I guess we're really doing this.
Okay.
Set on a quest to save my friends
I don't really know what rhymes with friends
Old man wizard, take it from me
Evil flying birds looking for a treat
Don't even know if he's alive or not
But who really cares what the poems that I got
Horse girls racing, my heart pacing
Grab ya money, big skill activation
Then a bunch of Grems surrounded me
Asked me to forge some iron bars, you see
Wait a second
Starting to realize what you meant by bars
But my rap game is fire
And my dance is not desired
But if there's one thing that I'm not,
it's definitely not a liar
So I hope you don't mind
if I twerk up on ya, you see
There's a promise that I made to Father
Yeah,
oh, I'm twerking
Oh, I don't know how to twerk
I don't want to put in the work
You see, twerking is a skill
you have to train up for everyone
And I ran out of rhymes 30 seconds ago
Alright, um...
I got dance moves
And then...
Okay, I can't do that.
Mic drop.
Yo! Yo! That was amazing!
Really?
You liked it?
You successfully crafted 10 iron bars!
Yippee!
I got that iron bar!
Take this as a reward.
Is that what I think it is?
THE ONE PING IS REAAAL!
Oh, what's my gauntlet?
Oh, is this yours? I found it down in the sewer.
Can I have it?
If you want it back, throw the ring into the volcano.
Oh cool, thanks. I'm gonna go now.
If you dare throw it away,
a ferocious monster will awaken...
Meat... I'm so hungry. I can't save justice like this.
Meat!
For me?
For free?
Hey! Who told you you could eat that?!
Woah, big ass hat.
You... You don't like my hat?
No, no. I think your hat is lovely.
I love it.
Lovely? Really? You can eat as much meat as you want!
Oh, thank you...
By the way, I'm looking for a straw hat.
Any idea where I can find one?
I'll trade it if you complete my quest.
Oh, here we go again.
I want 26 pictures of giant rats.
Giant rats?
Where do I find one of those?
Oh! Here they are!
Take your camera and capture
family photos of all 26 of them!
Whoa! So this is a family of 26 rats?
I guess I can see why you want pictures of them.
Okay! It's picture time!
I'll get pictures of all 26 of them!
Hell yeah!
Get in the frame! Let me get a picture of you!
One of them doesn't even look like a rat.
That's a really big person.
What about down here?
One more! One more!
That's a Grem!
What are you doing? You're not even a rat!
Okay, what about down here?
And look at those! They look just like Justice!
If Justice were a rat...
but they're cardboard.
Whoa!
Don't worry, I got you!
I got every angle imaginable!
That's a computer mouse.
And look at this photo I took! And this one! And this one!
They're so cute! All these rats are so cute!
And this is awesome!
And this is a yummy looking rat! Yay!
How cute!! I love them!!
Please accept this straw hat!
A hat! For me?
Yay! Now I have two items!
The stables are over there.
Maybe I can get the Honkshoe from the stables.
You scared me!
How are you doing?
Is everything going well?
Bad! I'm doing bad!
A few more quests might cheer you up!
You should take the ring to...
It's like no one cares about me.
This cruel evil world... The stables!
Aww, horses!
Oh hello! Hi! Hi there!
Hey!
Oh, you... I can share.
Here you go, eat up.
Is this horse okay?
Oh no, I think he's sleeping.
Okay, I think I can just... Don't mind if I...
I'll just take this.
You don't need this, do you?
I've done it! I've gathered all three items!
By myself! Yay!
I am the hero of this kingdom!
Sewer Grem!
You probably didn't think I'd get them all, but I did.
I got everything because I am the hero!
Those... are for you.
Oh wow, you really managed to
get everything I asked for!
Hold on, wait here.
There's something special just for you!
Ah man, can't believe I got everything.
Does that mean I saved Justice?
Oh they're gonna be so proud of me!
え？
Eh?
Is there something...
No, no, please, no! Not to her! No!
Help me!
Why does this keep happening to me?
Where am I?
What is this?
This isn't my Fantasy Life.
A house?
Where am I going? What is... Ah!
How was it, how's it going, guys!
Hello everyone! My name is Bae!
And my name is Biboo!
And together we are...
BAE-BOO!
Welcome, welcome to our Let's Play!
Today we are playing a new game called...
GIMS or JIMS!
I don't know how to pronounce it.
It's a fresh new game from the Rat.
And the Alpha!
We are the first ones to touch it!
We've got exclusive footage here for you today!
Let's get started!
The premise of this game is we have our character...
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi!
It's kind of like a real-life simulator game.
If I push this button right here,
she should be able to sit down.
Let's see. Oh, there we go!
Whoa! I didn't do that!
The controls... let's test them out some more.
Can I make her sit on the sofa?
Let's see if she can act like a dog.
You got that dog in you!
Of course, of course!
Biboo would make me act like a dog.
Woof woof woof woof woof!
LOUDER!
WOOF WOOF WOOF WOOF WOOF!
Look at the physics!
So this is just the base game, right?
Something weird is going on with the room.
We've got the main living room, the bedroom and the bathroom.
Should we go check out the kitchen?
Yes, let's go see the kitchen!
Move our character into the kitchen!
Come on, Gigi! I don't want to!
Anything we can interact with in the kitchen?
Oh look, a knife!
Pick up the knife! Pick it up right now!
What does she have? A knife!
Why is there so much input lag?
Maybe the connection's just a little bit slow.
Okay, now what? Face into the stove!
Yes, into the burning hot stove!
I don't wanna stab myself!
Oh my god! Look at her physics!
Maybe that's something they can add in the next update.
Pick up the knife again! Always carry a knife!
What are you guys doing to me?
Shall we move into another room?
Yeah, let's go into door number one!
Walk! Walk forwards! Go!
There she goes! What is in that door?
Oh, she clipped through the wall!
Oh, there's a bathtub and there's a toilet!
I know, I know! Have you heard of Skibidi Toilet?
Oh gosh, what is Skibidi Toilet?
I'm gonna make the character phase into the toilet.
Her head's gonna stick out to become Skibidi Toilet!
Become one with the toilet! NOW!
Skibidi Toilet! I learn something new every day!
Skibidi dop dop dop yes yes yes!
Spin her around! Spin your head around!
Spin my head right round, right round!
If you guys liked what you saw, make sure you press like and subscribe!
SKIBIDI TOILET!
Wow! Okay!
Wow! Subscribe and hit the notification bell...
...so you don't miss the next episode!
Yeah!
And PEEPO! Thank you for watching!
Bye!!!
Are they gone?
I don't hear their voices anymore.
Oh thank God.
Oh get me out of this toilet!
Out of that Skibidi toilet!
First you take over my body...
...then you make me Skibidi toilet!
How do I get out of here?
How could they torture me like this?
Why did they make me do all those things?
They didn't even feed me!
They didn't even say that I was a good girl...
...after they made me do all those things!
And now I'm poor!
I have to take it out on this canvas.
Ooh, if I just paint what I want...
...then maybe I'll be rewarded for it.
Because karma comes to good people.
So... beautiful woman... boobs...
Yes! YES! HAHAHA!
I've done it! My greatest work yet! My painting!
Hello?
Gigi?
Hello? Knock knock.
Are you in there?
Okay, I'm gonna come in.
Oh my goodness! This absolute masterpiece!
One of the lost works of Picasso? Or no...
...it has to be Leonardo da Vinci!
It's so incredible, I've never seen anything like it.
I can't believe something like this is before my eyes.
Gigi!
Gigi, wake up!
Gigi, WAKE UP!
Gigi, are you alright?
Something attacked me...
Oh, I don't know what kind of...
Why are you screaming?
Oh, beautiful woman...
Oh, yes! It's me. I came over just like you invited me.
Nerissa Ravencroft? Is that you?
And not the painting?
No, but did you make this, Gigi?
I made this.
It's incredible.
You like it?
I do. I thought of you while making it. Can you tell?
I can.
If it's so, I am your muse. Maybe we could be together?
Really?
Yes, no one's ever said that to me.
I... I've...
I've never wanted anything quite as much after seeing this.
The fire of my heart has been inflamed...
...and I feel like I cannot live without you, Gigi Murin.
Tickle tickle tickle! Don't scream now.
Gigi, are you okay?
You're tickling me.
You know what? I've thought a lot of thinking.
Thought, thought about thinking. I've thought of it.
And I've come up with a thing.
We should get married.
Oh, I thought you'd never ask!
Really? Really?
Why would you think that?
Do you want me?
I want you so bad!
You have no idea how bad I want you.
Let's go! Let's go home...
...and consummate our marriage!
What?
What? I don't know if I'm ready for that!
I don't either! I don't know!
そう簡単な祈りだった
It was such a simple prayer.
端から段々と消える簡単
The simplicity that gradually fades from the edge.
今から緞帳が下がるから
Since the curtain is about to fall,
静かな会場を後にさよなら
I bid farewell to the quiet venue.
言いかけてた言葉 ひとつ消えて
A single word I was about to say vanishes.
そう簡単な祈りだった 端から
It was a simple prayer after all, from the start
段々と消える感嘆 今から
Admiration gradually disappearing now
緞帳が上がるから 静かな
As the curtain is raising up, in this quiet...
会場を後にさよなら
...meeting place, we bid farewell
言いかけていたことが 一つ消えてまた増えて
Words I was about to say disappear and increase again
背中に後ろめたさが残る
Guilt remains on my back
従いたい心根を 吐き出さぬように込めて
Trying not to spit out the heart I want to follow
胸の中が檻のように濁る
My heart is getting cloudy like a cage
受け止めたいことが 自分さえ抱えられず
I want to accept it, but I cannot even hold onto myself
持て余したそれを守っている
I am guarding that which I have leftover
霞んだ声はからからに 喉を焼いて埋め尽くす
The blurred voice is parched and burns my throat
何を言うべきか分からなくて
I don't know what I should say
感じてたものが今 凝縮花放たれていた
What I felt was condensed and released like a flower
同じように同じように違うんだ 価値が
In the same way, it's different. The value is...
いつまで行くか どこまで行けるのか
How long will it go? How far can we go?
定かじゃないなら何を思うの
If it's not certain, what do you think?
僕らが離れるなら 僕らが迷うのなら
If we separate, if we lose our way,
その度に何回も繋がれるように
so that we can be connected again and again...
ここへ引き込まれるなら 放さずいられたなら
...if we're drawn in here, if we could stay held,
まだ誰も知らない感覚です
it's a sensation no one knows yet
変わっていって
It keeps changing
ASDTIE
平穏とは程遠く 代わりに成って
Far from peaceful, it takes its place
実態はとも代わりもなく
The reality remains unchanged
享楽とは嘘で成る 誇りの前に
Pleasure consists of lies, before pride
凍り付いたどこかへと 誇りの前に 凍り付いたどこかへと
Before pride, to somewhere frozen over
健気な願いを 同じように同じように つぶやく
Muttering a brave wish in the same way...
どこから聞こうか 何を見失うか
Where shall we start? What will we lose?
定かじゃないから言葉を置けない
Since it's not certain, I can't find the words
僕らが去りゆくなら これで最後なら
If we leave, if this is the end,
その度に何回も逃げ出せるように
so that we can escape again and again...
心が震えるように 奪われないように
...so our hearts tremble, so we aren't robbed,
互いを探してから 預けてよ
find each other and then entrust it all
ナル ナル ノ... ラル ラル タ...
Naru naru no... raru raru ta...
ラル ラル タ...
Raru raru ta...
ナル ナル ノ...
Naru naru no...
ラル ラル タ... ラル ラル タ...
Raru raru ta... raru raru ta...
君と泣く
Crying with you
君と笑う
Laughing with you
君と行く
Going with you
君と歌う
Singing with you
君と飛ぶ
Flying with you
君とダンス
Dancing with you
いつまで続くだろうと 同じように同じように つぶやく
Muttering 'how long will it last?' in the same way
今は忘れないように 刻まれた空気を
Now, so I don't forget the atmosphere carved in
これから何度思い出すのだろう
I wonder how many times I'll remember this
僕らだけだ
It's just us
僕らが離れるなら 僕らが迷うのなら
If we separate, if we lose our way,
その度に何回も繋がれるように
so that we can be connected again and again...
ここへ引き込まれるなら 放さずいられたなら
...if we're drawn in here, if we could stay held,
まだ誰も知らない感覚
it's a sensation no one knows yet
僕の生きる姿を 確かめて正しくして
Confirm my existence and make it right
ASDTIE
Oh husband, I'm so happy to be living a domestic life with you, Gigi Murin.
Well, in your awesome house, with your awesome kitchen,
and your awesome floor, and this awesome couch.
Wife.
Husband.
I've never been married before.
Me neither.
What am I supposed to do? How am I supposed to take care of you?
Take care of me? You're so sweet, no one's ever wanted to do that.
I want to take care of you.
I've dreamed of this...
...forever.
And ever.
Oh, Gigi Murin, please!
Not in front of... not in front of the studio audience!
Whoa.
Oh my beautiful, beautiful wife.
How far does your leg go up?
As far as you want it to.
I see. That's enough.
Not in front of the studio audience.
I can't believe you did that.
Me?
If you say so, husband.
I can't believe I'm such a dirty, dirty girl.
In front of this audience and everything.
And that's only for me, my dirty, dirty girl.
Yes!
I wouldn't want anyone else to see me like that but you.
I should do something for you.
That is what a Gigi Murin should do.
Yes, I would love that.
I should make you some toast.
Some toast for me?
Yes, for you.
You're so sweet.
Have you ever cooked before?
No, never.
Never. Never.
I don't even know how to use a microwave.
Really?
Yes, really.
Well, I only have one thing here and it's toast.
Wow, you're so amazing!
Did you make the bread yourself too?
I made it.
Whoa!
Oh, it's been on the floor! That's even better!
You stepped there!
Watch me... watch me flip it, okay?
Yes, I'm watching.
Oh! Oh!
Wait, wait!
Here, wait! I have a solution.
Okay, flip it!
Yes! You're amazing!
Ah, that made me really hungry.
Do you mind if I eat this toast first?
Of course you can!
Really?
Anything for you! You're such a sweetheart!
That looks tasty.
I have to use the bathroom, my sweet.
Oh, of course.
By all means.
Anything you need.
If I look through the doorknob hole...
I can see Gigi on the toilet.
I've never done such a thing before! Who's going to teach me?
We're going to learn together.
You can just learn from nothing?
Of course.
That's dope, you can just do that?
We'll find it out.
How do you think the first humans learned things, Gigi?
I don't know! Why are you asking me that?
Philosophical... it's pillow talk.
Anyway... Oh, oh, okay.
Well, shall we?
Well, now that you've brought it up...
The first humans probably learned things
by doing them.
Yes!
So let's just do it then.
Okay.
I can't wait another moment.
That was enough.
That's too much.
That was way too much.
Gigi Murin, you monster!
I'm sorry!
I was trying to be really gentle.
You did great.
Really?
Yes, it was amazing.
Well, I'm glad that we could spend our first day
in the bedroom together as a married couple.
Yes, but Gigi, there's something strange going on.
Did you transfer your stomachache to me?
I don't think so.
You can't just give a tummy ache to someone.
But it really, it really hurts.
Maybe you need to use the bathroom?
I don't think so, but oh...
Gigi! Wait a moment!
Gigi, your fingers! No! No!
No, I'm not ready! I'm not ready!
You know! You forgot to wear both gloves!
No! How is it? I can't! We can't!
We don't have the money!
Gigi, I'm sorry! We can't tell you to get this...
This house is barely holding together!
Doctor! Doctor! Ahhh!
Doctor! Gigi! Doctor!
Doctor!
Doctor, please! My wife, she's in pain!
Can you please help? Please, doctor!
Please help me!
What? Hello? Are you going to help her?
Hello? Why are you laughing? I'm giving birth here!
She's literally...
She is literally giving birth and you are just laughing at her!
Yeah, what kind of doctor...
I'm gonna go on the internet and leave bad reviews about you!
Your days are numbered, you're going out of business,
and you're going to go bankrupt!
Gigi! Gigi! The baby! Oh no!
It won't wait another minute!
Gigi! I got it!
She's safe! Our child! It's our baby!
It's a... it's a beautiful egg.
It is such a beautiful egg. Wow.
We didn't need a doctor after all.
You're a pro... you're a natural.
It seems like we're both a natural at a lot of things.
Yes. Wow. You know, I'm a little impatient.
I kind of wonder, what are you?
What are you in there? Hello?
Hey! Are you... hello?
Are you going to just shake the baby? Yeah! Wake up!
Oh goodness! Oh my god! It's our son!
Our son! Oh he's so cute!
Let's, let's let them hold the baby.
Yes. Should we name him?
Should we name him?
You're not gonna hold it like a mommy?
Should we name him? Yeah, we should name him.
Maybe we should let them name him.
Them? Them? Them out there?
Yeah, they've been watching us this whole time, you know.
What? Do you guys have an idea to name our baby?
They've been watching... give birth!
They're giving name suggestions. They've been what?
Yeah! Those are some great suggestions.
What do you think? They're all terrible.
Oh. I'm gonna name it Nerigi.
Nerigi. Yeah, cause it's like your name and then my name...
and together and now... It's perfect!
It's just a happy family. Just you, me, Nerigi.
And then now you're a beautiful mother. Yes.
And now I'm also a beautiful father. What else can we do?
I don't know, maybe you should go somewhere else
while I take care of the baby.
Okay.
Yoshi yoshi yoshi yoshi...
Why are you still watching me? Go away!
Go away.
I better get the mail for my wife.
I think giving birth is really expensive.
Whatever to pay the bills.
I don't have any money though.
God, I hope these aren't bills.
Help!
I don't...
Hey! Wait, did you leave your controller on?
Oh maybe I dropped it on the floor and the controller...
Wait I'm not touching the controller wait...
Wait she's going for the ladder!
Take it out! Take it out!
Yeah, take the ladder!
Leave the ladder!
The liquid of water is filling your lungs.
The air is slowly moving out of your body.
You are drowning.
Wait she's kind of cute though.
Oh my god wait what's happening?
Oh my god did you see that?
Is the house on fire?
My house might be on fire.
Inhaling... filling your lungs with water.
You are slowly suffocating from the inside. Haha.
Bae help me!
I think there is a quiz function.
I think if this character can answer the quiz correctly,
the ladder will come back as a prize.
I have too much water!
I'm gonna throw up!
Are you ready for the quiz?
Are you ready?
Let me out!
What is the name of the hypothetical particle
that mediates the force of gravity in quantum field theory,
and has not yet been observed experimentally?
A. Photon.
B. Gluon.
C. Graviton.
Or D. Neutrino.
Please answer correctly or else you will die.
Why are you doing this to me? It's C!
I don't care, it's C! I need to be C!
A! It's C! It's C!
The answer was C, Graviton.
Bye-bye.
What do you mean?
Maybe the next character will know.
Try harder next time.
Oh well.
I'm bored now.
Shucks. Oh well.
Oh she did.
Took my ladder away!
Someone help me!
Work-wife!
Give me a hand!
Work-wife, I'm drowning!
Get your... Work-wife!
She's flashing me while I'm dying!
Work, there's a better time for that! I'm... Stop!
Stop! I can't look! Work-wife!
Put that away! Put...
Hey! Hey! Listen to me!
I'm drowning! Listen to me! I'm okay.
You made me watch dancing fruits on TV.
You liked it.
You made me dance next to horses.
I liked that.
Fuck you.
Wait, we can talk about it! Work-wife, wait!
Die, idiot!
Work-wife!
Someone help me, I'm drowning!
Bae, people are killing me!
They're literally drowning me! Work-wife!
She's killing me!
I'm alive!
I'm not drowning! But my wife!
My child! My beautiful wife and child,
where are they? Why am I in the Grimm Kingdom?
What about Nerissa? My beautiful wife!
Nooo!
Nerissa, where did you go? I love you!
Why is everything on fire?
What?
There's a dragon here!
My friends are made out of cardboard!
They are not fire resistant! Oh no!
Okay, I see the Grems are doing their best to save them.
Okay, Grems.
What's this one doing? What are you up to?
Oh, you are not helping at all.
It's okay, little Grem.
Your arms will reach one day.
These Grems on the other hand...
You have magic! Wow!
Where'd you learn this?
Grems are so talented.
Not you though.
It's okay. Well, one day.
Oh, Grems... Grems are working really hard so...
I, me, Gigi Murin the hero...
is here to save the day!
Oh!
This must be my hero weapon,
as all heroes have a hero weapon.
Okay.
Ooh!
Oh!
One million dollars?
What?
Oh, kingdom can save itself.
I am not... (laughs)
Oh wait, a catapult!
Of course! Of course, obviously. Okay.
I'll help with this. Don't worry, Grems.
Let me... what ammo is here?
Okay, let's...
let's just pick this up.
(making vrooming noises)
Yay! Let's go Grem!
Let's save the kingdom!
Let's save the kingdom together! Yah!
Huh.
We're barely scratching it!
I don't know what to do.
There's... there's just no other choice.
I'm gonna have to pull out...
that move.
Yeah, yeah, that move. My ultimate move.
Alright everyone, are you ready to see my ultimate move?
Okay.
IKUZOOOOO!
LET'S GOOOOO!
Stop!
Oh, you guys scared me! Oh wait...
No! You took...
you took the fire breath, Gigi-chan!
Stop it! Stop! You're gonna die!
No! No! No, you're getting hurt!
Please, I need you!
If you're not here, who's gonna tell me how to defeat the dragon?
No! No! Please! Please!
You're getting hurt! Don't! Don't!
Are you okay?
おじいちゃん？大丈夫？
Grandpa? Are you okay?
Are you... are you okay?
Gigi-sama... oh no...
Lady Gigi... oh no...
You saved me!
You must save...
What... what is it?
this kingdom.
The kingdom?
How am I supposed to save it without you?
おじいちゃん！だめ！
Grandpa! No!
I don't know how else to save the kingdom
and destroy the dragon!
It's not taking any damage!
Help! Call the guard
wizard graveyard
Grems come and pray, Gremdal the Grey
Danger is here, a dragons appear
What the... what the hell?
Come seize the day, Fight and we slay
Gi gi Mu rin
Here at the scene
Look and behold, Legends Foretold
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
Where did you come from?
From near and far, hit by a car
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh
So many of you! Like... like 15 of you!
Gremurin, gremurin
Wait, what are you singing about? About me?
Help! Call the guard
Gigi Murin?
Grems come and pray
That... wait...
Danger is here, a dragons appear
That's right! I am a hero!
Come seize the day, Fight and we slay
I can save the day! Through the power
Gi gi Mu rin
Here at the scene
of these children singing for me!
Look and behold, Legends Foretold
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
I can do anything! Yeah!
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
Yeah, I can do it all!
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
From near and far, hit by a car
Okay, okay, what should I do? What should I do, Grems?
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
I don't know! I know!
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Through the power of interpretive dance!
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh
That's the only way we can destroy a dragon!
Because it has not been taking
any physical damage! So...
The best way to defeat this dragon
Gremurin, gremurin
is through mental damage!
Alright! I've never done a worm before.
I'm about to do a worm!
Gremurin, gremurin
Help! Call the guard
Is it working?
Grems come and pray
Danger is here, a dragons appear
Oh, sorry Grems! I'm sorry!
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
I'm not an interpretive dancer!
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Gigi is here!
Don't worry!
Help! Call the guard
Grems come and pray
Danger is here, a dragons appear
And then a worm?
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
Is it working?
Is the dragon being cringed out by me?
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
Oh no, I cannot do this.
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
From near and far, hit by a car
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Murin
My name! They're saying my name!
Gigi Murin Acrylic Stand
We'll win somehow, Purchase it now
What is this?
This power I'm feeling...
Oh no, it's surging in...
...in my veins!
Oh man... I feel it!
Help! Call the guard
They don't call me "The Fister" for nothing!
gremurin, gremurin
Gi gi Mu rin
That's me, The Fister.
Here at the scene
Gigi Murin, Hololive English Justice.
I've done it!
Gigi Murin has done it!
I defeated the dragon!
I did it!
Oji-chan, it was all thanks to you...
...and the fifteen children!
But it was all thanks to you...
...and the fifteen children that I did it!
Yay!
Oji-chan? Wait, you're still dead!?
No! No!
I thought my power of dance could save you!
Oji-chan!
You're okay!
The power of dance does save everyone!
You're okay, right?
You're not possessed, are you?
Oh, what is this?
Oh, what are you doing?
Oh, what is happening?
Oh god, what's... what's happening?
What the... what the heck is happening?
Oji-chan?
Uh! Oh! Oji-chan!
You're okay!
I've done it!
Yay!
Behold! The darkness has lifted from the dragon's soul.
My final desperate strike has shattered its cruel memories.
No longer a beast of fury,
it has been reborn as an innocent baby dragon!
にっこり調査隊！
Nikkori Survey Team!
おはこんばんちわ！
Good morning, evening, and hello!
How are you?
今日も今日とて最高ぜ！
Today's the best as always!
Oh, wonderful!
はい！笑う門には福来たる
Yes! Fortune comes to those who smile.
笑顔は貯設物
Smiles are savings.
はい！隊長、俺に名案が！
Yes! Captain, I have a great idea!
あーあー！
Ah, ah!
でもまだ何も言ってないんだが！
But you haven't said anything yet!
ま、とにかく、アレだほら。亀の甲より年の功！
Well, anyway, look. Experience comes with age!
はい！百聞は一見に如かずだね
Yes! Seeing is believing, right?
おっ、それだ！
Oh, that's it!
つまり、虫取り！？
So, bug catching!?
違ーう！
Wrong!
隊長、何事も経験が大事なはずっ！
Captain, experience should be important in everything!
何はともあれ、出発しましょう！
Anyway, let's set off!
とりあえず、出発進行！
For now, departure!
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
えっ！？出発進行！
Eh!? Departure!
ちょっと待ってって！旅支度くらいさせてよ！
Wait! Let me at least prepare for the trip!
落ち着いて！　では持ち物チェック始めまーす！
Calm down! Now, let's start the baggage check!
まずは基本のパスポート持った？
First, do you have your basic passport?
はい！
Yes!
チケット忘れた！
I forgot the ticket!
でもモバイルバッテリー持った？
But do you have a mobile battery?
はい！
Yes!
志は持った！
I have the ambition!
バッチリ！
Perfect!
おたま抱いて！
Hold the ladle!
私が行く！
I'm going!
しかも普通じゃない！？
And it's not normal!?
誰の事かな？
Who could it be?
「にっこり」には不可能を可能に
"Nikkori" has something that turns...
変えちゃう何かが…ある！！
...the impossible into the possible!!
にっこりこりこりこりあんな！
Nikkori kori kori kori Anna!
あっちもこっちも千客万来！
Customers flooding in from everywhere!
君の笑顔もコレクション、させて！
Let me collect your smile too!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
大人も子供も関係ねぇぜ！
Adults and children don't matter!
これぞ一流のエンターテイメント！
This is first-class entertainment!
私のっていつか夢を叶えてやるって
Saying that my dream will come true someday
We can do it!
このにっこりに触れてもっと胸深い波の光ったさ
Touching this Nikkori, a light shone in the depths of my heart
Gu!
にっこり調査隊 おはこんばんちわ (how are you?)
Niccori Survey Team! Good morn-evenin-n (how are you?)
今日も今日とて 最高です おぉ～わんだほーい！
Today is also the best, as usual. Oh~ Wonderhoi!
探索！コレクション！探求！ E・G・A・O
Search! Collection! Investigation! E-G-A-O
諸君！
Everyone!
（はい！）
(Yes!)
我々は世界の笑顔を調査する！
We are investigating the world's smiles!
はい隊長 俺に名案が
Yes, Captain! I have a great idea!
却下
Rejected!
ってまだなにもいってないんだが？
Wait, you haven't even heard it yet!
もー とーにーかーく あれだほら
Geez, anyway... that, look...
カナブンは一見にしかず？
Is 'kanabun' seeing is believing?
あぁ 百聞は一見に如かずだねぇ
Ah, you mean 'seeing is believing', right?
（それそれ！）
(That's it, that's it!)
つまり虫取り？！
So, bug catching?!
違うって 隊長！
That's not it, Captain!
（なになに～）
(What is it~?)
提案があります
I have a proposal!
ぜひ聞かせてほしいものだな
I'd love to hear it!
とりあえず
For now...
とりあえず？
For now?
とりあえず出発しよう ノープランで
For now, let's set off! No plan!
うん！
Yeah!
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute!
え？
Eh?
出発進行！
Departure proceed!
ちょっとまってって！ 旅支度くらいさせろ～！
Wait, I said wait! Let me at least pack!
数・日・後
A few days later...
じゃあ持ち物チェックをはじめまーす
Now, let's start the item check!
まずは基本の！
First, the basic one!
ぱ！ ぱぱ パスポート持った？
Pa! Pa-Pa, did you pack your passport?
はーい！
Yes!
き！きき
Ki! Ki-Ki!
着替え
Clothes!
わすれた！
I forgot!
え～
Eh~
も！ モバイルバッテリー 持った？
Mo! Did you pack your mobile battery?
はーい
Yes!
こ！
Ko!
志はもった？
Did you bring your ambition?
もちろん！
Of course!
仲間がいて 私がいる
There are companions, and I am here too!
しかもフツー
And it's not just usual...
にっこりこりこりこりお利口ちゃん
Niccori-kori-kori-kori, you good children
陰キャも陽キャも ウェルカム ウェルカム
Welcome, welcome, whether you're an introvert or an extrovert
君の笑顔が調査対象さ
Your smile is the subject of our investigation
いいぇーいいぇいいぇい いぇ～
Yeah-yeah-yeah, yeah~
フィジカル メンタル トータルOK
Physical, Mental, Total OK!
ききめ抜群の エンタ～↓テイメ～ン↑
Effectiveness is outstanding, Entertainment!
私だって いつか夢を叶えてやるって
Even I will make my dreams come true someday!
(We can do!)
ほら にっこり笑って
Look, give us a nice smile!
もっと胸膨らましましたとさ
And our hearts swelled even more!
そのしょんぼり にっこりに変換
Change that sadness into a smile!
うちらに任せろ You're my smile!
Leave it to us! You're my smile!
晴れの時だって 雨の時だって かきまぜちゃって
In sunny times, in rainy times, mix it all up,
スパイスだって 完璧だ！
even the spices! It's perfect!
That's not all! That's right!
You didn't expect this, oh you didn't expect this!
There's 3D merch! Yay!
You too, you watching at home, can own your very own...
Grem Hand In Cushion!
What does that mean? You can put your hands in the Grem!
You can remember all the good times that we had in the Grem Kingdom with Oji-chan! Yay!
And you can do so many things with this Grem, like stick your hands in it, which I said.
You can stick your hands in the Grem, and you can sleep on it...
...and you can squish it, and you can cherish it, and you can love it!
And it's very soft, and very squishy.
Just watch Oji-chan play with it. Doesn't it look so cool?
3Dお披露目グッズの登場じゃー！
3D debut goods are here!
ヒャッハー！
Hyah-ha!
見よ！このグレムのもちもちのハンドインクッションじゃよー
Look! This is Grem's squishy hand-in cushion.
超キュート！
So cute!
いっぱい可愛がっておくれよ
Please love it a lot.
頼んだぞー！
I'm counting on you!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Thank you everyone for coming to my 3D live today!
I worked really, really hard on it.
And thank you to the staff who is, who is overseeing me.
And thank you for Oji-chan for being here.
And thank you for the Grems, and thank you for Mocha-pi, and Nerissa...
Bae, Biboo, and Justice for being here, a part of my 3D live.
This was so much fun!
Oh, it was so awesome!
Oh, thank you!
And I'm looking forward to doing more 3D things for you guys!
Yay! Yippee-ki-yay!
And don't forget, there is more 3D debuts next week!
So make sure you tune in, because all of Justice has been working so hard!
Okay? Okay!
Bye everyone!
I'll see you later!
Bye-bye!