(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
RISU'S ISEKAI EXPRESS SPECIAL PERFORMANCE DELIVERY
Telole, telole, telole, telolet!
Honk, honk, honk, honk!
Hello, everyone!
Selamat datang di birthday show Ayunda Risu!
Welcome to Ayunda Risu's Birthday Show!
Gimana? Keren nggak, guys? Cia, cia, cia, yak!
How is it? Cool, right, guys? Cia, cia, cia, yeah!
Malam ini, guys, kalian diundang untuk ikut dalam pernyanyian sambil naik Risu Isekai Express.
Tonight, guys, you're invited to join a 'sing-trip' while riding the Risu Isekai Express.
Kenapa sebutnya pernyanyian?
Why do I call it a 'sing-trip'?
Karena kalian akan diajak pergi ke berbagai macam tempat bersama Risu sambil bernyanyi.
Because you'll be taken to various places with Risu while singing.
Jadi kita akan berjalan-jalan, mendaki gunung, melewati pantai, sambil bernyanyi bersama.
So we'll be traveling around, climbing mountains, passing through beaches, while singing together.
Terus dapat dilihat juga nih di pojok layar kalian ada hashtag #RiSekaiExpress3D,
Also, you can see in the corner of your screen there's the hashtag #RiSekaiExpress3D,
yang bisa kalian pakai untuk membagikan pengalaman perjalanan kalian bersama Risu Isekai Express.
which you can use to share your travel experience with Risu Isekai Express.
Tunggu apa lagi?
What are you waiting for?
Apalagi?
What else?
Ayo kirimkan review kalian guys
Come on, send your reviews, guys,
selama perjalanan dengan hashtag di atas.
during the journey with the hashtag above.
Dan post di sosial media kalian ya.
And post on your social media, okay?
Lihat nih, nih, nih.
Look at this, this, this.
Di sini Risu sudah siap untuk mengajak kalian
Here, Risu is ready to take you
berkeliling dengan truk kesayangan Risu.
around with Risu's favorite truck.
Siapa yang sudah nggak sabar
Who's already impatient
untuk pergi naik Risu Isekai Express?
to go ride Risu Isekai Express?
Ayo teman-teman, kita let's go!
Come on, friends, let's go!
Telolet telolet telolet telolet!
Langsung aja ke lagu pertama nggak sih?
Should we just go straight to the first song?
Eh, bentar guys, bentar.
Eh, wait guys, wait.
Kok ada suara telepon?
Why is there a phone sound?
Risu angkat dulu bentar ya guys.
Risu will pick it up for a moment, guys.
Hari itu kulihat langit sore
That day I saw the evening sky
Berandai jika aku seorang peri
Wondering if I were a fairy
Kan ku terbang langsung kunjungi mu
I would fly straight to visit you
Lewat lembah gurun bersahdu
Through valleys and serene deserts
Meskipun raporku selalu merah
Even though my report card is always red
Aku mau jadi fisikawan
I want to be a physicist
Kan ku hilangkan jarak dan waktu
I will eliminate distance and time
Agar aku selalu bersamamu
So that I can always be with you
Walau hanya sebatas video call saja
Even if it's just a video call
Sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Just sending cat photos
Sebatas ucapan pagi, oh senangnya
Just a morning greeting, oh how happy
Lama-lama memupuk jadi cinta
Gradually nurturing into love
Malam itu kau ajakku berkencan
That night you asked me on a date
Di atas perahu Venesia
Aboard a boat in Venice
Tak sengaja tangan kita berdua bertemu
Accidentally, both our hands met
Rasaku menggebu di dada
My feelings surge in my chest
Doki-doki
Kuingat ku akan mimpi malam tadi
I remember I would dream of last night
Namun hari kini sudah pagi
But now it's already morning
Mungkin tak lama lagi kita berjumpa
Maybe soon we will meet
Arungi angan ku bersamamu
Navigating my dreams with you
Walau hanya sebatas video call saja
Even if it's just a video call
Sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Just sending cat photos
Sebatas ucapan pagi, oh senangnya
Just a morning greeting, oh how happy
Lama-lama memupuk jadi cinta
Gradually nurturing into love
Walau hanya sebatas video call saja
Even if it's just a video call
Sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Just sending cat photos
Sebatas ucapan pagi, oh senangnya
Just a morning greeting, oh how happy
Lama-lama memupuk jadi cinta
Gradually nurturing into love
Walau hanya sebatas video call saja
Even if it's just a video call
Sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Just sending cat photos
Sebatas ucapan pagi, oh senangnya
Just a morning greeting, oh how happy
Lama-lama memupuk jadi cinta
Gradually nurturing into love
Walau hanya...
Even if only...
...sebatas video call saja
...just a video call
Sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Just sending cat photos
忘れられぬものだけが美しくはないのでしょう
It's not just the things we can't forget that are beautiful, is it?
忘れることばかりが美しくはないでしょう
It's not just the act of forgetting that is beautiful, is it?
哀しいことばかりが人生ではないのでしょう
It's not just the sad things that make a life, is it?
二人で得た喜びとは比べゆくでしょう
They will be compared to the joy we found together
船よ船よ　荒海の中で
Oh boat, oh boat, in the midst of the rough seas
流されず居られたでしょうか
Were you able to stay without being swept away?
皆そこに座す　あなたと尖った衝動自在
Everyone sitting there, with you and sharp, free impulses
サヨナラするこの知られとは
What is known of this farewell...
万象
The universe
痛みの数数えて
Counting the number of pains
傷の数指を折る
Counting the wounds on my fingers
一つ余り小指は愛しさだなんて
One left over, the pinky finger is for 'beloved'...
辛いこともありましょう
There will be hardships
あなたのせいもありましょう
And it might be your fault too
それでも赤い糸
Even so, the red thread of fate
繋いでいるのでしょう
...must be tying us together.
底知れぬものだけに 怯えるのではないでしょう
One shouldn't fear things just because they are bottomless, right?
届かぬものばかりが 妬ましくはないでしょう
It's not as if only the unreachable things are enviable.
優しいことばかりが 優しさではないのでしょう
Gentleness is not just about being kind, is it?
さりとて赤裸々では こそばゆいのでしょう
Yet, being completely naked is a bit ticklish, isn't it?
跳ねよ跳ねよ 人波を望み
Leap, leap, longing for the crowd of people.
人波に拒まれては
And being rejected by the crowd...
皆そこ目指す 未だ勝手な場所
Everyone aims for that place, a place that's still selfish.
傍若無人であいた頃を
Back when we were insolent and arrogant.
遠吠えとわ Let's go
What is called a howl? Let's go!
髪の長さ揃えて 爪の先を塗り直す
Trimming my hair and repainting my nails.
あどけない唇も 色めき立つその目
My innocent lips and those eyes that light up.
語らうこともありましょう 語らぬ人もおりましょう
There will be times when we talk, and there will be those who don't.
それゆえ慰めなど もう要られないのでしょう
That's why comforts are probably no longer needed.
跳ねよ跳ねよ 皆共に散って
Leap, leap, let us all scatter together.
既知の数数えて 痛みの数指折る
Counting the known things, counting the pains on my fingers.
一つ余り小指は 愛おしさらばね
The one left over pinky finger is for love.
悔やむこともありましょう 私の所為もありましょう
There will be regrets, and some will be my fault.
いつかは赤い糸 断ち切るのでしょう
One day, the red thread will probably be cut.
花びらに囁きを 憐れみから口づけを
Whispers to the petals, a kiss out of pity.
懐かしくて初めて 咲き退けるのでしょう
It's nostalgic, and for the first time, it will bloom and fall.
迷うこともありましょう 誰かの所為じゃないでしょう
There will be times of doubt, and it won't be anyone's fault.
難しいものですね 愛するということは
It's a difficult thing, isn't it? This thing called loving.
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I become captivated by you, I'm sure...
この夏は充実するのもっと
...this summer will be much more fulfilling.
噂のドリーミンガール忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored "Dreamin' Girl".
summertime
Lyrics: 原田夏樹, 鈴木まりこ Music: 原田夏樹
Lyrics: Natsuki Harada, Mariko Suzuki Music: Natsuki Harada
何年経っても言えない
Even after years pass, I can't say it.
後悔したって構わない
I don't mind even if I regret it.
でも言葉はここまで出てるの
But the words are right on the tip of my tongue.
ねえ サマータイム
Hey, summertime.
海岸通りを歩きたい
I want to walk along the coastal road.
ドライブだってしてみたい
I even want to go for a drive.
ただ視線を合わせてほしいの
I just want our eyes to meet.
ねえ サマータイム
Hey, summertime.
夜明けまで海辺走って
Running along the beach until dawn.
潮騒に包まれたいね
I want to be enveloped by the sound of the tide.
彼女の仕草が
Her gestures...
甘いね
...are sweet, aren't they?
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I become captivated by you, I'm sure...
この夏は充実するのもっと
...this summer will be much more fulfilling.
噂のドリーミンガール忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored "Dreamin' Girl".
でも気持ちを伝えてしまえばいつか
But if I tell you how I feel, then one day...
この夢は覚めてしまうだろうな
...this dream will probably come to an end.
青い影が揺れる街角
At the street corner where blue shadows sway.
占いなんて信じない
I don't believe in things like fortune-telling.
運命なんてあるわけない
There's no way things like "fate" exist.
ただ本当のことを知りたいの
I just want to know the truth.
ねえ サマータイム
Hey, summertime.
近づく距離にも気づかない
Not even noticing the distance getting shorter.
胸の高鳴り誤魔化せない
I can't hide the throbbing of my heart.
でも昔と変わらず鈍いの
But you're just as slow as you used to be.
ねえ サマータイム
Hey, summertime.
思い出は色褪せたって
Even if memories have faded...
惚れた腫れたの中がいいね
...being head over heels is good, isn't it?
彼女の笑顔が
Her smile...
憎いね
...is frustrating, isn't it?
君の虜に...
Captivated by you...
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I were to become your prisoner, surely...
この夏は充実するもおっと
...this summer would be even more fulfilling.
噂のドリーミンガール忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored Dreamin' Girl.
でも気持ちを伝えてしまえばいつか
But if I convey my feelings, someday...
この夢は覚めてしまうだろうな
...this dream will probably wake up.
青い影が揺れる
A blue shadow sways.
Ah!
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I were to become your prisoner, surely...
この夏は充実するもおっと
...this summer would be even more fulfilling.
噂のドリーミンガール忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored Dreamin' Girl.
でも気持ちを伝えてしまえばいつか
But if I convey my feelings, someday...
この夢は覚めてしまうだろうな
...this dream will probably wake up.
青い影が揺れる街角
A blue shadow sways on the street corner.
Summertime...
Wah!
Whoa!
Telolet telolet telolet telolet telolet!
Gimana lagunya barusan guys?
How was the song just now, guys?
Seru gak?
Was it fun?
Serulah!
Of course it was!
Jadi, tadi Risu sudah menyanyikan lagu dengan judul "Batsubyo" dan juga "Summertime".
So, Risu has just sung the songs titled "Setting Sail" and "Summertime".
Kalian pasti udah pernah denger lagu "Summertime" kan?
You've definitely heard the song "Summertime" before, right?
Yap, pasti udah pernahlah ya. Hehe.
Yep, I'm sure you have. Hehe.
Dua lagu barusan tuh, kalau kata Risu sih, cocok banget dengan tempat yang kita kunjungi sekarang, guys.
Those two songs, in Risu's opinion, really suit the place we're visiting now, guys.
Kan kalau di pantai kayak gini nih, lagunya kan juga harus yang bersemangat, terus juga fresh gitu nggak sih?
When you're at a beach like this, the songs should be energetic and fresh, shouldn't they?
Terus guys, gimana tadi penampilan truknya Risu?
And guys, how was Risu's truck performance?
Selain bisa dipakai buat bepergian, truknya juga bisa berubah jadi panggung gitu, guys.
Besides being used for travel, the truck can also transform into a stage, guys.
Wow, keren banget nggak sih kalau kata Risu sih ya, keren banget, guys.
Wow, isn't it super cool? In Risu's opinion, it's super cool, guys.
Oh, spoiler dikit ya.
Oh, a little spoiler.
Truknya nanti nggak cuma bisa satu mode lho, guys.
The truck will have more than one mode, guys.
Jadi jangan pergi dulu dan tonton acaranya sampai habis ya!
So don't go anywhere and watch the show until the end, okay!
Eits, jangan lupa buat screenshot yang banyak...
Hey, don't forget to take lots of screenshots...
...dan post di sosial media dengan hashtag di atas.
...and post them on social media with the hashtag above.
Kalau nggak, nanti truknya nggak lanjut jalan lho.
If you don't, the truck won't keep going.
Hmm hmm hmm.
Wih, udah pada banyak aja nih yang nge-post.
Whoa, there are already a lot of people posting.
Ya udah kalau gitu, kita let's go ke tempat selanjutnya.
Alright then, let's head to the next location.
Telolet telolet telolet telolet telolet!
Weight of the World / English Version
I feel like I'm losing hope
In my body and my soul
And the sky, it looks so ominous
And as time comes to a halt
Silence starts to overflow
My cries are inconspicuous
Tell me, God, are You punishing me?
Is this the price I'm paying for my past mistakes?
This is my redemption song
I need you more...
I need you more than ever right now
Can you hear me now?
'Cause we're gonna shout it loud
Even if our words seem meaningless
It's like I'm carrying the weight of the world
I wish that some way, somehow
That I can save every one of us
But the truth is that I'm only one girl
Maybe if I keep believing, my dreams will come to life
Come to life...
After all the laughter fades
Signs of life all washed away
I can still, still feel a gentle breeze
No matter how hard I pray
Signs of warning still remain
And life has become my enemy
Tell me God, are you punishing me?
Is this the price I'm paying for my past mistakes?
This is my redemption song
I need you more than ever right now
Can you hear me now?
'Cause we're gonna shout it loud
Even if our words seem meaningless
It's like I'm carrying the weight of the world
I wish that some way, somehow
That I can save every one of us
But the truth is that I'm only one girl
'Cause we're gonna shout it loud
Even if our words seem meaningless
It's like I'm carrying the weight of the world
I wish that some way, somehow
That I can save every one of us
But the truth is that I'm only one girl
Still we're gonna shout it loud
Even if our words seem meaningless
It's like I'm carrying the weight of the world
I hope that some way, somehow
That I can save every one of us
But the truth is that I'm only one girl
Maybe if I keep believing, my dreams will come to life
Come to life...
カイネ / 救済
Kaine / Salvation
カイネ／救済
Shol bar a wiim
Ar djad na wisiil
Da gala dofor
Malik fueder as lader shpor
Yo ta tere adre kuharem folle ya poi
Yo mika dayo kura mohe kaine rikoro
Yo mika dayo kura mohe
Ya da korer dore pa yu ra chu
Shol bar a wiim
Ar djad na wisiil
Da gala dofor
Malik fueder as lader shpor
Yo ta tere adre kuharem folle ya poi
Yo mika dayo kura mohe kaine rikoro
Yo mika dayo kura mohe
Ya da korer dore pa yu ra chu
Departures 〜あなたにおくるアイの歌〜
Lyrics, Music: ryo
Departures ~A Song of Love for You~
もうあなたから愛されることも
Being loved by you no longer...
必要とされることもない
...nor being needed by you exists anymore.
そして私はこうして一人ぼっちで
And so, I am here all alone like this.
あの時あなたは何て言ったの?
What did you say back then?
届かない言葉は宙を舞う
The words that cannot reach dance in the air.
わかってるのに今日もしてしまう
Even though I know, I do it again today.
叶わぬ願いごとを
Making a wish that won't come true.
離さないで ぎゅっと 手を握ってて
Don't let go, hold my hand tightly.
あなたと二人 続くと言って
Tell me that the two of us will continue.
繋いだその手は温かくて
The hand I held was so warm...
優しかった
...it was so kind.
あなたはいつもそうやって私を
You always do that to me...
怒らせて最後には泣かすんだ
...making me angry and making me cry in the end.
だけど後になって「ごめんね」と言う
But then later you would say "I'm sorry".
その顔 好きだった
I loved that face of yours.
離さないで ぎゅっと 思い切り
Don't let go, hold me tight with all your might.
あなたの腕の中にいたい
I want to be in your arms.
二人で...
Together we...
...おでこを合わせながら
...while touching our foreheads together.
ねえ、
Hey,
ありがとう
thank you.
会えないってこと、知ってたの
I knew that we couldn't meet.
離さないで
Don't let go.
ぎゅっと、あなたが好き
Hold me tight, I love you.
もう一度だって 笑ってくれないの
Won't you smile for me even just once more?
あなたの温もりが消えちゃう前に
Before your warmth fades away,
抱きしめたい
I want to hold you.
Telolet telolet telolet telolet!
Honk honk honk honk!
Hehe!
Siapa yang suka driving sambil lihat pemandangan...
Who likes driving while looking at the scenery...
...dan sing along sama lagu yang lagi diputar di musik player?
...and singing along to the song playing on the music player?
Aku aku aku aku!
Me, me, me, me!
Barusan juga kalian kan udah dengar lagu-lagu yang menyentuh hati...
Just now, you also heard songs that touch the heart...
...sambil ditemani pemandangan alami gitu.
...accompanied by a natural view like that.
Ya, nggak?
Right?
Lagu-lagu sebelumnya tuh lagu favorit Risu semua, Guys.
The previous songs were all Risu's favorites, guys.
Pasti kalian udah pada tahu judulnya, kan ya?
I'm sure you already know the titles, right?
Wih, pasti kalian terharu banget sih dengernya tadi. Hehe.
Whoa, I'm sure you were really moved hearing them earlier. Hehe.
Terus, setelah melewati pemandangan yang asri...
Then, after passing through the lush scenery...
...kita masuk ke daerah perkotaan nih, Guys.
...we're entering the urban area, guys.
Enak banget sih kayaknya nyetir di perkotaan sambil nyanyi-nyanyi gitu.
It feels really nice driving in the city while singing along like that.
Apalagi kalau lagunya yang syahdu gitu, Guys.
Especially if the song is serene like that, guys.
Ayo, lanjut nyanyi bareng Risu sambil lihat pemandangan kota.
Come on, let's continue singing with Risu while looking at the city view.
Ayo, Guys! Let's go!
Come on, guys! Let's go!
Telolet telolet telolet telolet! Hehe.
Honk honk honk honk! Hehe.
急に不機嫌な音 消えた
Suddenly, the sullen sound vanished.
部屋に残った缶ビール
A beer can left in the room.
押し殺した息が 喘いだ私に
My stifled breath gasped as I...
見えた
...saw.
めちゃくちゃになった部屋
A room in a total mess,
死体みたいなぬいぐるみ
a stuffed toy like a corpse.
今夜はパレード
Tonight is a parade.
弱めの冷房に揺れた前髪が
My bangs swayed in the weak air conditioning,
あの夏を
making me remember
何度も思い出させる
that summer over and over.
眠る街に行こう
Let's go to the sleeping city,
眠る街に行こうよ
let's go to the sleeping city.
今夜も街とは
Tonight, too, the city
耐え切れずに目をつぶるんだ
can't take it anymore and closes its eyes.
砕けて散った落とし物
Lost things shattered and scattered,
ドラマで見たんだ
I saw it in a drama.
正義は必ず勝つって
That justice always wins...
正義って何なの
...but what is justice?
わかんないことはわかんないよ
I don't understand what I don't understand,
まだ子供だし 大人じゃないし
I'm still a child, not an adult yet.
今日も天井を見ていた
Today, too, I was looking at the ceiling,
変わらない風景だ
it's an unchanging scenery.
眠る街に行こう
Let's go to the sleeping city,
眠る街に行こうよ
let's go to the sleeping city.
今夜向かいのビルも
Tonight, even the building opposite
布団に潜るんだ
crawls under its duvet.
眠る街に夜行
Night travel through the sleeping city
もうすぐ終点だよ
It's almost the last stop.
さよなら
Goodbye
なんてことない気がしたんだ
I felt like it was nothing special
あの日の私と変わらない私に
To the me who hasn't changed since that day
もういいよ
It's enough already
許してそれから
Forgive me, and then...
眠る街に夜行
Night travel through the sleeping city
眠る街に夜行をーよ
もういいよ
It's enough already
疲れたよ
I'm tired
じゃあまたね
Well then, see you later
またね
See you
HIKARU SSS
ピアノ×フォルテ×スキャンダル
Piano x Forte x Scandal
Lyrics, Music: OSTER project
ありふれた私というコンチェルトなぞれる日々
Days where I can trace the concerto of my mundane self
それとなくタクトに合わせれば保証されるハーモニー
Harmony is guaranteed if I casually follow the baton
ダウンビート割とストイックでクラシカルな誘惑せいでーも
Even if the downbeat is somewhat stoic
and caused by classical temptation
アップビートはアドリブで行かなきゃ退屈でしょ
The upbeat must be an ad-lib, otherwise it's boring, right?
あぁスコア通りの日常に枯れゆくこの命ならば
Ah, if this life of mine is to wither away
in a routine following the score
いっそ背徳の渦に溺れてしまいたい
I'd rather drown in a whirlpool of immorality
その指に光る愛の証さえ消えそうなほど優しく
So gently that even the proof of love
shining on that finger seems to fade
ささやいた言葉は禁断のセレナーデ
The words whispered were a forbidden serenade
24時瞳を閉じれば想うのはあなたのことばかり
At midnight, when I close my eyes,
I think only of you
そんなの良くないよなんて友達は言うけれど
Friends say that's not good, but...
あぁそんな言葉じゃ私の乾きが潤うことなどない
Ah, words like that will never quench my thirst
可愛げないセリフでプライドが乱れ出す
My pride begins to unravel with uncute lines
散らばったスコアの上ひび割れた愛が溶け散るその前に
Before the cracked love melts and
scatters on the scattered scores
キスで繋ぎ止めて回り始めたラプソディ
Hold it together with a kiss,
the rhapsody has begun to turn
加速するアイドリズム突き詰めて確かめ合うように永久
Accelerating idolism, pushing it to the limit
to confirm each other forever
フォルテッシモでもう強く強く抱きしめて
Hold me tighter and tighter in fortissimo
重なり合うこの声は闇に溶けて消えてゆくから
Because these overlapping voices will
melt into the darkness and vanish
きっと大丈夫よ何も悪いことじゃない
I'm sure it'll be okay, it's nothing bad
「メトロポリス (metropolis)」
"Metropolis"
Lyrics, Music: Shishishishi
Arrangement: Shunsuke Tsuri
どうだった？
How was it?
言い換えれば灰色だったんだ
In other words, it was gray
夜から　帰らなきゃって言って
Saying I have to go home from the night
どれほどたちのさじを払った
How much fate did I pay for?
退屈な原っぱ
In this boring field
抜け出せるなら　明日は明日の花
If I can escape, tomorrow's flower is for tomorrow
痛いけど　同期はよりによって
It hurts, but of all things, the sync...
と言われるがままだ
...is just as they say
ビロードの目に映る都のネイビー
The city's navy reflected in velvet eyes
頭上だ　トドの如く居座れたら
Above my head, if I could sit there like a sea lion
枯れるまで煽る
Stoking it until it withers
パッと眼舞う　キリのない
Flashing before my eyes, endless
眠らない　街びる
The city that doesn't sleep
憧れに千切れるまで　Low
Until torn by longing, Low
行ったり来たりのパンチ
Back and forth punches
頭振りゆくジャンキー
A junkie shaking their head
あんな間に散りゆく満点　灯
Perfect lights scattered in an instant
踏んだり蹴ったりのダーリン
Misfortunes never come singly, darling
その先は甘美
Beyond that is sweet
巡り巡るメトロ
The spinning metro
いちばんの夢見たこの迷路
This maze where I had the greatest dream
この夜 Make it out
This night, Make it out
これは運命と
This is fate, I say
解く解くよ
Explaining it, explaining it
止まることのない通りは
The street that never stops
Walk walk walk around
寝れない夜明かそうよ
Let's stay up all night
ステップ　タタタ
Step, ta-ta-ta
踊れる　大人ら
Dancing adults
重なる心臓　地団駄踏んでも
Overlapping hearts, even if I stamp my feet
期待とか見栄とかわからない
I don't understand expectations or vanity
ただ夢を見続けた
I just kept on dreaming
虹色グラフィティ
Rainbow-colored graffiti
離れないよね　オングラビティ
You won't leave, will you? On gravity
このフラットな夜　変えるから
I'll change this flat night
雑踏の渦のシルクハット
The top hat in the whirlpool of the crowd
頭上だ　トドの如く居座れたら
Above my head, if I could sit there like a sea lion
枯れるまで煽る
Stoking it until it withers
パッと眼舞う　キリのない
Flashing before my eyes, endless
眠らない
Doesn't sleep
憧れに千切れるまで　Low
Until torn by longing, Low
行ったり来たりのパンチ
Back and forth punches
頭振りゆくジャンキー
A junkie shaking their head
歩みに散りゆく満点　灯
Perfect lights scattered as I walk
右も左もダーリン
Right or left, darling
いつの日か甘美
One day, it will be sweet
Wow! Lagu apa itu, guys?
Wow! What song was that, guys?
Lagu siapa itu? Apa? Ayunda Risu? Wow, keren banget nggak sih lagunya?
Whose song was that? What? Ayunda Risu? Wow, isn't the song really cool?
Oh my God, Ayunda Risu rilis lagu baru!
Oh my God, Ayunda Risu released a new song!
Hehe, eh sabar. Risu mau bagiin info lagunya, guys, ke kalian dulu nih di sosial media.
Hehe, wait. Risu wants to share the song info with you guys first on social media.
Hah, agak susah sih posting sambil nyupir, guys.
Hah, it's a bit hard to post while driving, guys.
Tapi tenang, Risu kan supir truk profesional. Jadi aman.
But don't worry, Risu is a professional truck driver. So it's safe.
Hup!
Tada! Sudah deh.
Tada! Done.
Kalian bisa cek info tentang lagunya di sosial media sekarang ya, guys.
You guys can check the info about the song on social media now, guys.
Apa? Kalian belum bisa lihat? Hah, nggak mau beranjak dari layar?
What? You can't see it yet? Huh, don't want to move from the screen?
Nih, nih, nih, Risu kasih lihat ya nih, guys.
Here, here, here, Risu will show you, guys.
Ini dia, guys, lagu baru Risu yang berjudul 「メトロポリス (metropolis)」.
This is it, guys, Risu's new song titled "Metropolis".
メトロポリス。Dari judulnya aja udah kelihatan sih kalau lagunya tuh...
Metropolis. Just from the title, you can tell that the song is...
Ayunda Risu 2nd ORIGINAL SONG
「メトロポリス (metropolis)」
January 15th 2026 00:00 RELEASE!
Ayunda Risu 2nd ORIGINAL SONG
"Metropolis"
January 15th 2026 00:00 RELEASE!
Cocok banget sama vibe perkotaan gitu, guys.
It fits the city vibe perfectly, guys.
Terus, kalian nyadar nggak sih?
Also, did you guys notice?
Judulnya kalau dibaca pakai logat Jepang, guys,
If you read the title with a Japanese accent, guys,
cara bacanya tuh jadi "Metroporisu".
the way to say it is "Metroporisu".
Metroporisu.
Jadi di judulnya ada nama Risu-nya gitu, guys.
So, there's Risu's name in the title, guys.
Keren, kan? Weh, keren lah.
Cool, right? Of course it is.
Terus lagunya sengaja dibuat upbeat
Also, the song was intentionally made upbeat
biar bisa bikin kalian semangat gitu, guys,
to get you guys hyped up,
pas berangkat atau pulang sekolah, kerja,
when going to or coming home from school, work,
dll gitu lah.
and things like that.
Abis itu lagunya juga cocok banget buat
Besides that, the song is also very suitable
nemenin kalian jalan-jalan di malam hari gitu, guys.
to accompany you on a night stroll, guys.
Nah, lagu sekeren ini tuh dibuat oleh
Now, a song this cool was made by
produser musik yang bernama Shishi-Shishi-san.
a music producer named Shishi-Shishi-san.
Bukan sishishishi ya, guys.
Not "sishishishi," guys.
Bukan sishishishi ketawa bapak-bapak, guys.
Not that old man's "sishishishi" laugh, guys.
Buat yang udah nggak sabar pengen dengerin lagunya lagi, guys,
For those who can't wait to hear the song again,
lagunya akan rilis di platform musik digital favorit kalian masing-masing
the song will be released on your favorite digital music platforms
di jam 00:00 waktu setempat.
at 00:00 local time.
Nanti waktu kalian sudah denger lagunya di jam 00:00,
Later when you've heard the song at 00:00,
langsung share yang banyak
immediately share it a lot
di grup WA keluarga, sekolah, kantor,
in your family, school, office WA groups,
terus apa ya, grup sosmed, forum sosmed,
then, let's see, social media groups, social media forums,
pokoknya semuanya lah.
basically everywhere.
Biar makin banyak yang dengerin, guys.
So that more people listen to it, guys.
Terus buat yang sudah denger,
Also, for those who have already heard it,
jangan lupa looping terus lagunya ya, guys.
don't forget to keep looping the song, guys.
Et, tunggu dulu.
Wait a second.
Perjalanan kita masih belum selesai ya, guys.
Our journey isn't over yet, guys.
Masih ada satu tempat lagi yang belum kita kunjungi.
There's still one more place we haven't visited.
Risu juga masih mau nyanyi-nyanyi bareng kalian nih, guys.
Risu still wants to sing together with you all, guys.
Jadi kita lanjut yuk!
So, let's keep going!
3, 2, 1...
ケロッ！とマーチ　いざ進め
Kero! to March, let's advance
地球しんりゃくせよ
Invade the Earth
ケケケロッ　傘持って
Ke-ke-kero, holding umbrellas
出かけた日にはいつも晴れ
Whenever we head out, it's always sunny
気をつけ！
Attention!
目をくいしばれ！
Grit your eyes!
カレーのライスを炊き忘れ
Forgot to cook the rice for the curry
閉まるドア小指はさんだ
Pinky finger caught in the closing door
飛び乗ったら行き先ちがう
Jumped on, but it's the wrong destination
社員旅行はケロン
The company trip is to Keron
あ、買ったほうが安いね晩御飯のおかず
Ah, it's cheaper to just buy side dishes for dinner
ピロッ！と突撃　動く歩道
Piro! to charge, moving walkway
いてゆけ
Go forth
ピッピロッピロ　早寝して
Pi-piropiro, sleep early
目覚まし待たずに二度寝する
Sleep in twice without waiting for the alarm
全体！
Everyone!
止まれ！回れ！お手！
Halt! About face! Shake hands!
嫌われたいのに愛される
Wanted to be hated, but ended up being loved
いらないもの片付けバイバゲン
Cleaning up unneeded things, buy-bargain
欲しいものあるとお金がない
When there's something I want, I have no money
四の五の言えよケロン
Complain all you want, Keron
あ、雷鳴っても隠すヘソがない
Ah, even if it thunders, I have no belly button to hide
熱きこの血潮と
With this hot blood
胸に刻まれし闘魂
The fighting spirit carved in my chest
永遠に勝ち誇れ
Be proud in victory forever
我らがケロン
Our Keron
熱きこの血潮と
With this hot blood
胸に刻まれし闘魂
The fighting spirit carved in my chest
永遠に勝ち誇れ
Be proud in victory forever
愛しき星よ
Oh, beloved planet
我らがケロン
Our Keron
全体！
Everyone!
止まっちゃダメ！
Don't stop!
勝ったら いちごの かおり
If you win, it smells like strawberries
ケロンマーチは 宇宙 飛ぶ
The Keron March flies through space
アッ 駅から 徒歩 五分
Ah, it's a 5-minute walk from the station
それじゃあ それじゃあ どっと お疲れさん！
Well then, well then, thanks for all the hard work!
ケロッ ケロッ
Kero kero
ケロッ！
Kero!
Gifted, talented, I was wanted
中学、2年で、アキラめかけた
In my second year of middle school, I almost gave up
反則、異次元、この世のものではないです
Foul, another dimension, it's not of this world
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないって
Impossible game, I didn't hear about that
Ay, ライバル、口を揃えて
Ay, rivals, all saying in unison
Whoa, ライバル、口を揃えて
Whoa, rivals, all saying in unison
バグで、マグネ、認めん、絶てえ
Bug, magnet, won't admit it, absolutely
マジで、これおま、全部生身で？
Seriously, you, all with your physical body?
It's namami, it's namami, yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah
It's raw, it's raw, yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born
実力を発揮しまーい
Gonna show off my skills
相手の方がバクれて悔しい
Frustrating that the opponent is bugged out
上がりきるハードル、ベリーハッピー
Raised hurdles, very happy
明らかにダントツでいかちい
Obviously the toughest by far
相変わらずスタンプしてるマイネーム
Stamping my name as usual
Bling, bling, bling
誰の、何、光もいらねえ、俺のあいつより愛しい
Don't need anyone's light, more dear than my eyes
俺パッと見できないことばっかりだけど、ベリーハッピー
At first glance, I can't do anything, but I'm very happy
呆れてる、呆れてる周り。恵まれてる家族友達
People are exasperated. Blessed with family and friends
反則的な立ち位置、皆俺に任せておけばいい
An unfair position, just leave it all to me
教科書にない、歴史にない、超バッドなまじない
Not in textbooks or history, a super bad spell
鏡よ、鏡、答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror, just answer me
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh, yeah!
生身のまま行ける、とこまで
Going as far as I can with just my physical body
To the next, to the ichiban ue
To the next, to the very top
Now singin' bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born
To the next, to the ichiban ue
To the next, to the very top
Ey-day, 俺のままでいるだけで超フレックス
Ey-day, just being myself is a super flex
Ey-day, 誰も口を挟ませない
Ey-day, won't let anyone butt in
Ey-day, 俺のままでいるだけで超フレックス
Ey-day, just being myself is a super flex
Ey-day, 誰も口を挟ませない
Ey-day, won't let anyone butt in
学歴もない、前科もない、余裕で
No academic background, no criminal record, with ease
この存在自体が、文化財な脳みそ
This existence itself, a brain that's a cultural asset
高級車は買えん、免許はない、愛車
Can't buy luxury cars, don't have a license, my favorite car
全国各地揺らす、エピック、このベロが
Shaking the whole country, epic, this tongue
関西なまり、生身の言葉まんま
Kansai accent, raw words as they are
漫画みたいな輩と、まんまで張り合ってしまってる漫画
Competing with guys like in a manga, it's just like a manga
圧倒的力、この頭と口から
Overwhelming power, from this head and mouth
この体、ドーピングは入ってない
This body, no doping involved
この面に、傷もついてない
On this face, not a single scratch
繰り返し、貸してきた貸し
Repeatedly, the favors I've lent
俺のままで、ブリストバース、飛ばすための、ポン！過ぎた日本
Being myself, Bling and birth, to blow it away, Pon! Past Japan
鏡よ、鏡、答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror, just answer me
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh, yeah!
生身のまま行ける、とこまで
Going as far as I can with just my physical body
To the next, to the ichiban ue
To the next, to the very top
Now singin' bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born
To the next, to the ichiban ue
To the next, to the very top
Ey-day, 俺のままでいるだけで超フレックス
Ey-day, just being myself is a super flex
Ey-day, 誰も口を挟ませない
Ey-day, won't let anyone butt in
Ey-day, 俺のままでいるだけで超フレックス
Ey-day, just being myself is a super flex
Ey-day, 誰も口を挟ませない
Ey-day, won't let anyone butt in
Membuka mata dan bangkitkan diri",
Opening eyes and waking up
Tiada waktu untuk bermimpi",
No time to dream
Dunia pun akan jadi saksi",
The world will also be a witness
Menyambut bangkitnya kami",
Welcoming our revival
Aduhai cermin-cerminan menyinari sanubari",
Moved, and mirrors illuminate the heart
Yang terbengkalai",
That is neglected
Sekarang dapat kurasa panggilan yang t'rus menggema",
Now I can feel the call that keeps echoing
Di dalam dada",
Inside the chest
Seakan terangkat lagi semua memori",
As if all memories are lifted again
…di sela kelembutan
...amidst the softness
menjadi raga yang tertakdir…
becoming a body that is destined...
…dalam labirin yang tiada akhir…
...in a labyrinth that has no end...
…ke mana pun ku pergi
...wherever I go
hanya senja hari yang menanti…
only the sunset awaits...
Rantai-rantai mengikat diri ini
Chains bind this self
membisikkan jangan pergi…
whispering don't go...
…kejauhan pun menghampiri
...remoteness approaches
memadam suara hati…
extinguishing the inner voice...
…di balik esok hari ini
...behind tomorrow today
area tak terjelajahi…
unexplored area...
…suatu saat kau lewati garis tepi…
...one day you'll cross the boundary line...
tuk bangkitkan kami…
to awaken us...
…layang dalam gelas
...drifting in a glass
tanpa sadarkan betapa…
without realizing how...
…lama waktu yang…
...long the time that...
…lah berlalu mengalir
...has passed flowing
semuanya tersingkap…
everything is revealed...
…tentang jarum jam
...about the clock hands
seakan teringat lagi…
as if remembering again...
…tepi laut sepi…
...the quiet seaside...
…dan hari-hari di hutan tak diketahui…
...and days in the unknown forest...
…jatuh dari langit untuk ku jauhi…
...falling from the sky for me to distance...
…masa lalu yang masih kini juga menghantui diri…
...the past that even now still haunts me...
Rantai-rantai menahan diri ini
Chains hold back this self
meskipun lanjut mencari…
even though I continue searching...
…asal usul kejadian diri yang tak akan terganti…
...the origin of this self that won't be replaced...
…di 51 misteri yang tak dapat terjahit…
...in 51 mysteries that cannot be sewn...
…seperti bangunnya diri yang lain ini…
...like the awakening of this other self...
…tersatukan lagi…
...reunited again...
…kartu-kartu takdir
...destiny cards
menunjukkan masa depan…
showing the future...
…hilangkan bimbang…
...remove hesitation...
Rantai-rantai yang membebani hati…
Chains that weigh down the heart...
…takkan lagi menghalangi diri
...will no longer stop me
beralih menanti…
switching to wait...
…sorot matahari
...the spotlight of the sun
melangkah maju memasuki…
stepping forward to enter...
…area tak terjelajahi
...unexplored area
saatnya datang tuk lewati garis tepi…
the time has come to cross the boundary line...
…dan sambut matahari…
...and welcome the sun...
Telolet telolet telolet telolet...
Wih! Gimana perjalanan kalian sejauh ini teman-teman?
Wow! How has your journey been so far, friends?
Tadi kita sudah melewati tempat yang hijau...
Earlier, we passed through a green place...
...melewati pantai, perkotaan...
...passed the beach, the city...
...lalu ke taman bermain sambil bernyanyi bersama.
...then to the amusement park while singing together.
Huh! Seru banget sih kalau kata Risu.
Whew! It was really fun, if you ask Risu.
Terus tadi Risu juga ada pengumuman lagu baru.
And then, Risu also had a new song announcement.
Nah, jangan lupa dicek nanti rilisan digitalnya ya guys.
So, don't forget to check out the digital release later, guys.
Terus kalau kalian gimana nih guys?
So, how about you guys?
Kira-kira nih bagian mana yang jadi favorit kalian...
About which part was your favorite...
...dari perjalanan Risu Isekai Express hari ini guys?
...of Risu's Isekai Express journey today, guys?
Nah, jangan lupa share juga momen favorit kalian di sosial media...
Now, don't forget to also share your favorite moments on social media...
...dengan hashtag nih yang sudah ada nih...
...with this hashtag that's already here...
...yaitu #RiSekaiExpress3D.
...which is #RiSekaiExpress3D.
Itu hashtagnya guys.
That's the hashtag, guys.
Terus... tetetete...
And then... *drumroll*...
Acara spesial kayak gini guys, apalagi birthday show...
A special event like this, guys, especially a birthday show...
...kayaknya sih belum lengkap ya kalau belum jualan gitu.
...doesn't feel complete without some merch sales.
Hehehe. Buat kalian yang sudah nggak sabar...
Hehehe. For those of you who can't wait...
...nih Risu akan ngiklan dulu ya guys.
...Risu is going to do some advertising now, guys.
Kalian...
You guys...
...gak bisa skip ads kali ini, guys.
...can't skip ads this time, guys.
Jadi kalian harus pantengin sampai selesai.
So you have to watch until the end.
Merch untuk birthday tahun ini adalah...
The merch for this year's birthday is...
Kita punya jaket super keren, diorama stand,
We have a super cool jacket, diorama stand,
dan juga handuk! Wow, lengkap banget sih.
and also a towel! Wow, it's really complete.
Kalau kata Risu ya, set ini tuh buat kalian para bapak-bapak
In Risu's opinion, this set is for you fathers
dan juga umm para supir truk di luar sana.
and also umm truck drivers out there.
Kalau kalian lihat, jaketnya ini keren banget, guys.
If you look at it, this jacket is really cool, guys.
Oh jaketnya ini cocok banget buat dipakai jalan-jalan kasual.
Oh this jacket is really suitable for casual outings.
Jadi ya bisa lah dipakai buat hangout atau jalan-jalan sama teman gitu, guys.
So yeah, it can be used for hanging out or going out with friends, guys.
Kalau kata Risu sih, kalian wajib banget, guys, beli jaket ini
In Risu's opinion, you guys really must buy this jacket
biar koleksi Risudrip kalian tuh lengkap.
so your Risudrip collection is complete.
Terus, terus... minimal sih kalau kata Risu... beli tiga ya, guys.
Next, next... at least in Risu's opinion... buy three, guys.
Habis ini tuh ada buat kalian yang suka pergi ke anime event gitu, guys.
After this, there's something for those of you who like going to anime events, guys.
Nah, bisa banget pakai face towel ini.
Well, you can really use this face towel.
Gunanya sih, selain untuk ngelap keringat ya,
The purpose, besides wiping sweat,
bisa banget buat kalian bawa terus pajang gitu, guys, waktu lagi ada event, panel, konser gitu, guys.
it can really be brought and displayed, guys, when there's an event, panel, or concert.
Kalian angkat di atas gitu lho. Terus sekalian bisa apa ya...
You lift it up like that. Then at the same time you can what is it...
...kayak pamer oshi gitu. Hehehe.
...like showing off your oshi. Hehehe.
Terus, terakhir nih ada diorama stand yang lucu, guys.
Next, lastly there's a cute diorama stand, guys.
Iya, lucu banget. Cocok banget buat dipajang di meja, di kamar...
Yes, very cute. Very suitable to be displayed on a table, in a room...
...terus bisa juga di dalam mobil, guys.
...then it can also be in a car, guys.
Terus, terus, buat kalian yang beli full set, kalian akan dapat bonus
Next, next, for those of you who buy the full set, you will get a bonus
postcard yang ditandatangani langsung oleh Risu.
postcard signed directly by Risu.
Asli, guys! Ditandatangani oleh Ayunda Risu. Wow!
Genuine, guys! Signed by Ayunda Risu. Wow!
Tunggu apa lagi, guys? Langsung aja borong dan check out.
What are you waiting for, guys? Go ahead and buy it all and check out.
Terutama yang full set ya.
Especially the full set.
Nah, kalian bisa check out di link yang ada di deskripsi
Well, you can check out at the link in the description
atau bisa langsung gas ke website Hololive Official Store.
or you can go straight to the Hololive Official Store website.
Oh! Jangan lupa kalau kalian beli full set,
Oh! Don't forget if you buy the full set,
nanti akan dapat bonus kartu yang bisa kalian pakai di Hololive Production Official Card Game.
you'll get a bonus card that you can use in the Hololive Production Official Card Game.
Terus kartunya hanya ada dalam bahasa Jepang ya, guys.
And the card is only available in Japanese, guys.
Nah, terus berhubung kita udah sampai di penghujung acara...
Well, and since we've reached the end of the show...
Risu mau bilang terima kasih untuk semua yang sudah ikut di perjalanan Risu Isekai Express.
Risu wants to say thank you to everyone who joined Risu's Isekai Express journey.
Terima kasih juga untuk semua ucapan selamat ulang tahun yang kalian berikan untuk Risu.
Thank you also for all the birthday wishes you gave to Risu.
Risu sih senang banget ya bisa merayakan ulang tahun Risu dengan kalian semua.
Risu is very happy to be able to celebrate Risu's birthday with you all.
Jadi semoga kalian semua juga ya, guys, enjoy perjalanan dan nyanyiannya dari awal sampai akhir.
So I hope you all too, guys, enjoy the journey and the singing from beginning to end.
Terima kasih semuanya!
Thank you everyone!
Puru-puru...
...otsu Risu Isekai Express!
Wae! Bye-bye!