(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Seems time's a-wastin'
Show me what you really wanna do
Tonight's my turn to show ya
how obvious I can be
Sometimes it feels like you're playing
a game of me and only me
Looks so, so predictable,
they can see what I can see, go, go, go!
Get back! Just crash!
吐き溜めた希望を...
The hope I've vomited out...
Let's just crash!
飛び火していくんだ...
It's spreading like wildfire...
不鮮明な情けない世界で
空白重ねた光
In a blurred and pathetic world,
light layered upon emptiness
脈打つ鼓動 誰にもなれない
言葉を紡いでる
A pulsing heartbeat, spinning words
that no one else can become
Under the black / We fall, we break
We drown in fire / Lost inside this dark desire
去ろう、焦がす、未来の Mercy / Mercy
Let's leave, scorching the future's Mercy / Mercy
見ろ 何もしない 最高潮の愛に
Look, at a love that does nothing
and reaches its peak
雲立って / Tell me what I'm not to say
What's your problem?
Clouds rise / Tell me what I'm not to say
夜をひとり あたしが迷う
Alone in the night, I wander
When the thunder crashes down / When the world
caves under my pressure, there'll be no one to save
巡る巡る 運命に逆らって
出会い 思いを通わせた
Going 'round and 'round, defying fate,
we met and shared our feelings
These strangers I followed
with stars in their eyes
Don't keep on waiting, wanting, faking
You're someone you're not reaching, longing, changing
I can't be someone else / Despite it all
my mind has become my hell / With no escape or hope
くらくらしちゃうでしょ
It'll make you dizzy, right?
ほらほら遠くそう
そうでしょ Flash bang!
Look, look, it's far away
That's right, Flash bang!
In this moment / Maybe I jumped the map
Not knowing if I never try
昨日の夢を見るたびに
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
Every time I dream of yesterday,
I end up thinking about the meaning of my birth
ああ 美しい 青い...
Ah, beautiful, blue...
We fall, we break / We drown in fire
Lost inside this dark desire / No love, no fate
What's up all you deadbeats!
Welcome to Disasterpiece Release...!
ようこそ！
Welcome!
たくさん楽しもうね！
Let's have a lot of fun!
Let's go! Come on!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Ha! You got eyes but you don't look or listen.
In other words, you're useless every last one of you.
And that's why I'm gonna send you all to Hell!
All of humanity!
全容 察した 閉じ全容 善兵 投げて
I sensed the whole picture, closed it,
threw all my pieces in
I'm just the type you forget,
so don't waste your time, yeah
契り 崩れ 賭けのチェイン 狂いそう
Somebody's gotta pay
Bonds crumble, a chain of bets,
I'm going crazy, somebody's gotta pay
Everybody's got 'em and they can't be satisfied
Until somebody's at the bottom
So what you think you're special
Cause you got some greed and hunger?
We ain't getting any younger
Let's just crash!
お前が募る場所に花は咲く
Flowers bloom where you gather
かな...
I wonder...
Let's try it!
吐き溜めた希望
Hopes spat out
積み上げた苦悩
Piled up suffering
いただきケガラレたキャラコンボイ
A defiled character convoy from the top
美しき理想
Beautiful ideal
汚してく野郎
A bastard who defiles it
誰が言いたい？ 誰が言いたい？ 誰が熱唱しても
Who wants to say it? Who wants to say it? No matter who sings passionately
この理想は無理だろうぜ
This ideal is impossible
誰が言いたいとしても 限界だってことさ
No matter who wants to say it, it's at its limit
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Come on!
世界は世界を背負ったって
Even if the world carries the world
そんなところまで出して見せろよだって
Because show me to that point
Yo, everyone's got problems
Everybody's got 'em and they can't be satisfied
Until somebody's at the bottom
So what you think you're special
Cause you got some greed and hunger?
We ain't getting any younger
Let's just crash!
心が通う時たましいが
When hearts connect, the soul...
叫ぶ
...shouts
どぶねずみのように
Like a sewer rat
気高く生きるんだ
Living with pride
俺が通る今すぐに どけ
I'm passing through, get out of my way right now
Let's try it!
吐き溜めた希望
Hopes spat out
積み上げた苦悩
Piled up suffering
いただきケガラレたキャラコンボイ
A defiled character convoy from the top
美しき理想
Beautiful ideal
汚してく野郎
A bastard who defiles it
誰が言いたい？ 誰が言いたい？ 誰が熱唱しても
Who wants to say it? Who wants to say it? No matter who sings passionately
この理想は無理だろうぜ
This ideal is impossible
誰が言いたいとしても 限界だってことさ
No matter who wants to say it, it's at its limit
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
限界だってことさ
It's at its limit
皆さん！
Everyone!
We're just getting started!
始まったね！
It's started!
When thunder crashes down
When the world gives under pressure
there'll be no one left to save
Where is your pride, you human will to survive?
Was it just empty words for your grave?
I'll reach inside this sound
now all that remains is illusion, now decay
Because of you, I lived this way
We're not rivals
We're not equals
You're just confused
Lightning never strikes twice in the same spot
so go ahead and run up on me 'til you get shot
I see the weapon that you're hiding
come on, ready or not
Another life and you would never get a second thought
DISASTER SHOW Mori Calliope
Thinking your pride's different than mine
Thinking I've had a sudden change of heart
But we still gotta pretend to our friends from our enemies
Wouldn't you agree?
Forged in fires of hell, I can't betray you
If I'm a fallen angel, what does that make you?
I'm not debasing myself to see the same view
When it's your pride on the line
no one can save you from mine
We're not rivals
We're not equals
Thank you for coming today everyone, it's over!
It's okay, no, no, no, we're back, we're back.
Just some technical difficulties.
Staff-san, the beats!
Everyone calm down, it's fine, it's fine, we're okay.
Welcome, welcome!
Hey, you know what? It fits in the theme of the show
that there'd be some technical issues.
So it can't be perfect, right?
But I'm looking at your comments right now
and thank you by the way to Shiori for the raid as well.
Hope the outfit reveal went super good.
Hi Dead Beats! Hello!
We're here, we're here!
We're finally at the Disasterpiece venue.
And I'm reading your comments, but there might be a little bit of lag,
so sorry about that.
Anyway, check it out. I've got a special,
I've got my own special mic
that is definitely what I'm using to talk and not the headset.
But check it out!
Oh, I'll show it to you closer later.
I've got... oh, hello! Liz is here too!
Amazing Senpai, woo! Thank you.
Welcome to Disaster Show everyone.
Disasterpiece is out at long last!
Hooray! We did it! We finally got here.
And now, I'm gonna do some songs for you guys.
Whoa, Akaspa... I can't read it right now,
but I'll have to read them later. Thank you so much.
The new art style is so nice?
This is some unreal power, Dead Beats, unreal power.
It's stunning, isn't it?
I bet you want to get a closer look
and maybe get some screenshots of Mori Calliope's face.
So let me show you, Staff-san is holding a special camera.
よろしくお願いします！ うおっ！
Please look after me! Woah!
Hey hey! Hold on, I think this is my normal hand. Oh!
Alright, I'm gonna get some good reactions for you guys.
Hold on a sec.
Here I go. Check this shit out.
Hah!
I'm being silly.
I'm being silly 'cause I need time to chill right now.
You sound amazing, Calli! I'm doing my best, whew!
And the outfit, too!
Look how shiny! Shiny!
It just... it looks so good.
And my face... my face looks good too.
Oh gosh, I'm still not used to holding the camera though,
so I'm trying to make it perfect,
but you might have to edit it later.
Hold on, no, I got this. Okay.
RTX on.
Very realistic.
I can wink. Hold on, here I go.
Here... wait, hold on, I got...
I suck at this.
That's okay, though. It's fine if it's not perfect.
I think I can wink. Check this out.
頑張れ！
Do your best!
Close enough!
It looks good. And look, behind us, we've got the track
from the "Let's Get It Crashed" MV.
And we've got Challenger's car behind me.
And we've also got King's car as well.
Um, and then, well, you Deadbeats,
you're all on your way to the next stage, so you're not there yet.
Um, but let me show you my mic...
マイク見せたいから。ありがとうございます。
Because I want to show the mic. Thank you very much.
Okay. Check it... check out the mic.
This is the special Mori Calliope mic
that was made special for me. Isn't it cool?
Look how sick!
The red and the roses... I'm obsessed.
I'm obsessed with it.
So, anyway, that's what's going on, Deadbeats.
I wanted to show you the actual future of Hololive.
Well, I mean, the technology will only get better and better.
So, um, anyway, this is exciting.
You guys want to see some more songs?
Oh, also, buy the album!
I'm all bent out of shape. I feel like MCs...
I'm like good when it's an actual live, like in a venue,
but then if it's like this, I screw up a lot, so... oh well.
New merch? Um, not... well, I mean, this!
Oh, you're talking about the mic?
You want the mic as merchandise?
I'll think about it.
Not a bad idea. I think P-san's listening to that,
so I'll have to talk to her about it later. Welcome to the future!
Anyway, Deadbeats... I gotta do a quick costume change and scene change.
So, let's get out of here and I'll sing some more songs
and... be up with you hither and thither...
that's probably the wrong word to use in that situation.
But thank you, Saps-san!
Alright, I'll catch you guys there.
Time for a... 変身！ 行くぞ！
Time for a... Transformation! Let's go!
Golden Buddy / アンバランスを解いた
Golden Buddy / Unbalanced Resolved
確かな物語に
In a certain story,
勝ち獲るアイデンティティ
identity is won.
荒れ狂った手応え
The raging feedback,
自信を変え
transforming confidence,
時に伴う さあ 激昂
accompanying the times, come on, fury!
感情はノンフィクションで喜怒哀楽
Emotions are non-fiction, joy, anger, grief, and pleasure.
一心同体 災禍さの勝負
Two bodies, one soul, a battle in the calamity.
失敗も 正解も 味わえ
Savor both failure and the right answer.
One and only Golden Buddy
意味なんてないような世界で
In a world that seems to have no meaning,
偶然重なった光
light that happened to overlap.
脈打つ鼓動
Pulsing heartbeat,
誰にもなれない
becoming someone no one else can be,
言葉を紡いでゆく
continuing to spin words.
運命じゃないよ
It's not destiny,
小さな勇気と辿り着く
I'll arrive with a little courage.
強気に解き合み行く
Strongly unraveling and moving forward,
ハートをセッション
heart session,
2人ならやれるさ
if it's the two of us, we can do it!
Back to back no matter what
ぶちまけるスペルで飛ばす Spark
Sending out sparks with spells to be poured out.
段違いで研ぎ澄ませた Pass
A pass sharpened to a different level.
誰も邪魔できないこの Route
No one can interfere with this route.
サン・ニ・イチ・ゼロ
Three, two, one, zero.
2人でお宝攫うさ
The two of us will snatch the treasure.
ウザいくらい遠くに放とう
Let's release it as far as it can be annoying.
地獄から奏でるぜ Loop
Playing from hell, a loop.
イメージの合図 どこまでも
The signal of an image, anywhere.
無限に 荒れ果て道じゃない
It's not a path that's infinitely desolate.
言葉の道を突き進む クラウド
Pushing through the path of words, cloud.
才能を産む ロケーション
A location that gives birth to talent.
どうせなら ぐちゃぐちゃにしてやれ
If anything, make it a mess.
始めてのなら やりきる覚悟を
If it's the first time, have the resolve to see it through.
敗者と勝者のデュエット
A duet of the loser and the winner.
弾き出した不条理のクズ
Scum of the absurdity that was flipped out.
振り払え Don't stop me
Shake it off, don't stop me.
心の死は 消えない
The death of the heart won't vanish.
2人ならやれるさ
If it's the two of us, we can do it!
Heart set!
生きるってなんだ　すっぽかした文句チックショーの物
What is living? Just ditched complaints, dammit.
逃げればせっせ
If you run, do it diligently.
奪い去られない　縁冷めないぜ
It won't be stolen, the connection won't cool.
人生キャッキャッキャッキャッキャッキャッ
Life's just laughing and having fun.
絶望もう行こうもねえ飯はファイター
Despair or moving on, eat like a fighter.
どんなたちにでも　凝らないんだって
No matter what kind of person, I won't get stuck.
見せられた現実に囚われ
Trapped in the reality I was shown.
This life where we're stuck taking chances
飽き飽きしたんでしょ
You're tired of it, right?
We're living in a world with no direction
Reach out with our hearts till we make a connection
Tearing the walls apart, facing it out side by side
Once again it's us against the world
ナンバーワンのよう　本当を見つけさせて
Like being number one, let me find the truth.
本物を見せつけて
Show me the real thing.
ハートセット　World Unbalance
Heart set, World Unbalance
踊れ
Dance
Adrenaline! Hey!
踊れ
Dance
So just how far can I go?
I think I already know
That view that I want to see
A place in history that's mine, I
I don't know why we're always side-by-side worlds apart
It's trial by fire, I'm fighting for a place where we can breathe
When spite takes over, I might just take it out on you
Cause you're too good to be true
Struggling but carrying on, I'll go where nobody has gone
I'm searching again and again and again for something only I can do
Asking why I can't be someone else
Despite it all my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark
But still in my heart your words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go but I can't erase you
I'm following behind but I won't chase you
I'm swallowing my pride until the time that I can face you
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
It's never been enough but I'll keep on writing a story
That's evolving from the day that I decided I'm alone
I don't belong anywhere anymore, it was my decision
I'm gonna break down the door to your heart without your permission
There was nothing that could make me stay
Remember it like it was yesterday, hanging on every word you'd say
What if I'd walked away?
How can I still carry on, someday when you're finally gone
I'm searching again and again and again for something only I can do
The truth is I can't be someone else
Despite it all my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark
But still in my heart my words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go and you can't erase me
Cause I'm the only one that could ever replace me
Igniting every line until the time that I can face you
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
It's never been enough but I'll keep on writing a story
That evolved me, it's the day that I'm deciding I'm alright
So just how far can I go?
I think I already know
That view that I want to see
I still could make it in time
みなさん、welcome to the next stage!
Everyone, welcome to the next stage!
ぱちぱち、thank you for the ぱちぱちぱち。
Clap clap, thank you for the claps.
Thank you so much! What did you guys think?
And check it out, we got this... and now I'm being goofy, I'm sorry.
ぱちぱちぱち... thank you so much! Oh, is Oda-san here?
Clap clap clap... thank you so much! Oh, is Oda-san here?
Sorry if there's like, again, just lag.
...is very high quality machine we're using
...is a very high quality machine we're using
to broadcast to all of you, so
there might be a bit of lag.
But I'm happy that I can read some of your
comments in real time.
Thank you so much, you guys.
Makes me very happy. パチパチパチ！
Makes me very happy. *Clap clap clap!*
Thank you! Oh, but we might...
we might need to refresh the chat,
because now it has stopped moving.
Anyway, in the mean— Oh!
There it goes, there it goes. Oh wow,
I think it just exploded when Raora
entered the chat. Anyway.
Thank you so much, you guys.
I hope you guys have been liking the new songs.
Memento was one of the new songs
that I wrote. I wish I could go
into it in a longer MC
or talk more about it,
'cause there's so much I want to say about that song.
But it's... it's... Oh!
Oh! Oh! Hold on, hold on!
I'm frozen in... I'm frozen in place!
Okay... alright. We're good, we're good.
大丈夫。Sorry.
Everything's okay. Sorry.
ザ・ワールド。No problem, no problem.
The World. No problem, no problem.
Here, for now though, instead of going
into talking about the lyrics,
which I'll probably do during the next...
during the next stream,
we'll find some time before or after
I play a game, and then I'll talk about the songs.
Until then... Hang on, hold on a second.
ケンティーさんは Gold Ambivalence には
Kenty-san couldn't be here
来られなかったけど、
for Gold Ambivalence...
でもケンティーさんから学んだのは、
but you know what I've learned from Kenty-san
ファンサービスがすごく大事だってこと。
is that fan service is very important.
昔はファンサとかするの、
I used to be really like nervous
すごく緊張してたんだよね、
about doing some fan sa and stuff like that...
だって恥ずかしがり屋だからさ。
...'cause like I'm... I'm an embarrassed person.
でもケンティーさんはあんなに軽々と、
But, but Kenty so easily is just like...
「チュッチュ」ってファンにしたり、
Oh, like... "Chu chu" to like the fans...
ウィンクしたり、ファンサがすごく上手で、
...like wink, and like, I don't know, he's so good at the fan sa...
しかも全然恥ずかしがらずに。
...and like, with no shame whatsoever.
私もあんな風にやってみなきゃって思ったんだ。
I thought to myself, I need to try and do some of that too.
だから... やってみるよ。
So... I'm gonna do that.
チュ！
*Kiss!*
あまり上手くないかもだけど。チュ！
Probably not very good at it, but anyway. *Kiss!*
待って、始め— ああ、完璧じゃん！
Hold on, I'll start— Oh no, it's perfect!
ザ・ワールドが君たちのために止めてくれたから、
Because The World... The World! It stopped it for you
写真が撮れるよ。
so that you could get a little picture.
そのカメラどこ向けてんの！
Watch where you're pointing that camera!
ちょっと待って、怪しいとこなんか
Hold on a second, I'm not pointing it
向けてないよ。何言ってんの。
anywhere suspicious. What are you talking about?
変顔していい？
Can I do... Can I do a funny face?
ワアアアア！
Bwaaaah!
ハアアアア！
Hwaaaah!
あちゃー。
Oh no...
とにかく... この衣装、見て。
Anyway... so here's this outfit.
これもまたすごくクオリティ高いよね。
And it looks so high quality again.
ねえ、ステージに何か気づいた？
Hey, you notice something about the stage?
これ、Gold Ambivalence の冒頭のコインなんだ。
This is the coin from the beginning of Gold Ambivalence.
デッドビーツ、見て！
Dead Beats, look!
意味なんてないような世界で...
Imi nante nai yo na sekai de...
It's the... 不確かな物語に...
It's the... futashika na monogatari ni...
とにかく... 見てみて。ちょっと待って。
Anyway... so check it out. Hang on.
ところで、このステージめちゃくちゃかっこよくない？
Look at how cool the stage is, by the way.
ステージチェックしてる？
Are you checking out the stage?
あのバラ... それから月！
Look at those... the roses... the moon!
ユニバーサルミュージックジャパンから
It reminds me of when I debuted
デビューした時を思い出すなあ。
from Universal Music Japan...
背景に月があったんだ。あれは何だったっけ？
and I had the moon in the background of what was it?
デビューアルバムのどれかだったと思う。
I think it was one of my debut albums.
超クール。すごく立派に見えるね。ああ、わかってる。
So cool. Looking very respectable. Oh, I know.
言われなくても、もうわかってるよ。
You don't need to tell me. I already know.
もちろん。いつものようにね。できるだけ高くしてみる？
Of course. As always. Should I put it as high as possible?
わあ！暗闇の中で目が光ってる。
Whoa! My eyes are glowing in the darkness.
エフェクトはどう？
What about the effects?
このショーのエフェクトもすごくクールだよね。
The effects are also so cool for this show.
信じられない。もっとすごいステージが控えてるよ。
I can't believe it. We have some even more amazing stages coming up.
まだアルバムをチェックしてない人は、新曲がいっぱいだよ！
But if you guys haven't checked out the album yet, it's full of brand new songs!
そのうちの一曲は自分で作曲したんだ。それから全曲...
One of them I composed myself. And then all the songs...
私の曲の英語の歌詞は全部私が書いてる。
all the English in my songs is written by me.
「Cult Following」以外は、それだけかな。
Except for maybe "Cult Following", and that's it.
でもあれは別のアルバムだから。だから間違いなく、
But that's in a different album. So it's safe to say...
英語の歌詞は全部私自身のものだよ。
all the English lyrics are my own.
日本語の歌詞については、作詞家の方に
And then for Japanese lyrics, I basically tell
どんな内容にしたいか伝えて、
the lyricists what I want it to be about...
自分の歌詞を渡して何を書いてほしいか伝えてるんだ。
and give them like my lyrics so they know what to write about.
そう、だから私の考えと気持ちが詰まってる。
But yeah, so it's full of my thoughts and my feelings.
これ置いとこう。ずっと持ってる必要ないもんね。
I'm gonna put this away. I really don't need to keep holding this.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
そう、世界や自分の周りの世界に対する
But yeah, it's full of my thoughts and my feelings
考えや気持ちが詰まってる。
about the world and the world around me.
今回は少しダークで、少しエモーショナルかな。
And this time it's just a bit darker, a bit more emotional.
でも皆、私の中にたくさんの感情があるのは知ってるよね。
But you guys know that I have a lot of emotions inside of me...
それらに対処する最善の方法は、
and I feel like the best way to deal with those
世界に向けて生産的な形で出すことだと思うんだ。
is to put them out in the world in like a productive way.
「終電」が大好き。「終電」は、
I love "Shuuden". "Shuuden"...
英語で「Last Train」って意味なんだ。
"Last Train", that's what it means in Japanese.
あの曲についてももっと話すのが待ちきれないよ。
I can't wait to talk more about that song too.
あの曲もすごく思い入れがあるんだ。
That's also very close to my heart, that song.
もっとたくさん話したいけど、もうまとめなきゃね。
I want to say so much more but I probably need to wrap it up.
相変わらず最高。ありがとう、気に入ったよ。
Amazing as usual. Thank you, I dig it.
本当にありがとう。
Thank you so much.
歌詞が全部素晴らしいね。ありがとう、デッドビーツ。
The lyrics are all amazing. Thank you, Dead Beats.
みんなに... みんなに感謝してるよ。ありがとう。
I appreciate... I appreciate all of you. Thank you.
さて、ここでもっとやることがあるから、
Well we have... we have some more to do here,
いつまでも続けてられないね。
so I can't go on forever.
すごく長い MC になっちゃった。だから...
This is a very long MC. So...
また別の変身をしよう。
let's do another Henshin.
それから... 行くぞ！
And... Let's go!
そば立った僕は零した 消して不確かな...
Sobatta boku wa koboshita / keshite futashika na...
...something you can move to,
don't look back,
look forward,
don't look back.
I slipped in the foam and kept on looking
for something to bring me up,
asking myself, no such thing as hope,
holding down a what?
What the thing I seen in shattered pieces
more than a reach,
it seems so much chances decreases.
It's the winter of cynical as I just might be,
a random still and unwritten,
I think I'm about to break free.
My limits closing around me
they're sounding less and less real,
because my heart is beating louder
than the fear that I feel.
My mind's already made,
not afraid of unrealistic dream,
looking for most pristine so I can walk on water.
Used to look for perfection, now it's progress,
every tooth paid part of progress.
And this moment,
maybe it's all glass,
now knowing if I never try.
Changing faces,
enveloped in moonlight,
I can see stars now,
running through an endless sky.
Don't look back,
look forward,
find something you can move to,
don't look back,
look forward,
don't look back.
I fight another day, these battles inside and outside,
have all that I wanted, why am I still not satisfied?
Lost taxis and street signs,
the city mirroring my mind,
countless ways to level took forever to find.
Yeah, the world declined me,
I was always dope but they were like "nah",
now it's up to me to rise, take them by surprise.
My mind never slides, always riding high, thrive,
on this lovely hate, my future's in sky.
Running all my shadows, still in worn out shoes,
with everything to gain,
even more to give up and lose.
This time you gotta choose,
no excuse tired of sleeping,
gotta move and envision tomorrows
that are too good to refuse.
Red skies waiting,
but I'd lost my aim,
more things change,
the more they stay the same.
Burning strife and shame,
this pain will be my strength.
And this moment,
maybe it's all glass,
not knowing if I never try.
Changing faces,
enveloped in moonlight,
I can see stars now,
guiding me to find for this moment,
we're no longer broken,
never leaving us behind.
This morning,
I wake up to soundness,
living with resolve now,
running with a fearless stride.
Don't look back,
look forward,
don't look back,
find something you can move to,
don't look back.
Hello、謳った。君がダメ。
Hello, I sang. You are no good.
花咲いた、明日は雨。
Flowers bloomed, tomorrow it'll rain.
為せば成るんだわ、惜しみない pain
Where there's a will there's a way,
unsparing pain
Falling on and on、惜しまれど sell.
Falling on and on, though regretted, sell.
メッセンジャーと grab hand、よもや千年前よ惚れ。
Grab hand with the messenger,
falling in love as if a thousand years ago.
今世中、脱する砂時計 travel、trouble、capsize.
Escaping the hourglass in this life,
travel, trouble, capsize.
喜怒哀楽、経た達成感、不変 infinity、
気にしてんだ、本当に本当に。
Emotions, the sense of achievement gained,
unchanging infinity, I'm thinking about it, truly, truly.
上昇し、雲の上、昇天し。
Rising above the clouds, ascending.
Underneath the blue sky,
still choosing to sing 'cause I refuse to die.
Breathe deep and try to look past the pain,
but these flowers are watered with acid rain.
I can't change belief that I tried and tried,
and I grieve for the scene that I left behind.
If I could find a place to rest as of mine,
that I could live with a lifetime.
Someday I'll have sung all I'm meant to say.
Got a feeling that I'll still sing anyway.
Sorrow、焦がする未来の mercy
Sorrow, the mercy of the burning future
Fade out、仇に死んで、再の愛に。
Fade out, dying in vain, to a second love.
焦げ付くほどの hold you are God.
To the point of scorching, hold you are God.
Hello、Hello、今宵の daydream
Hello, Hello, tonight's daydream
Let's maintain.
Messenger to grab hell, you’re both so Nen you’re yo-play
Konsechu-dasei suru na togo to travel, trouble cap the life
Sacrifice the false cards, bloodying the cat’s out the claws
Nobody’s ever truly what they seem
With the limelight gleaming to conceal the flaws
Can’t escape the scrolling, it takes a toll of me
Dead and lost still looping, holding me
Didn’t even matter in the end that I held out
Sorry I could never be the god I was sought to be
So to speak, annihilate fools gold
Living out the role I was told to be
I’ll be old and free in a matter of centuries
Wondered if there was a point to me
Was thinking for sure I’d belong on my own
But I found a place to belong
People I can't live without
FOLLOW ME PLEASE! DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO OKAY!
暗闇　奏でるMy Soul nowhere
Playing in the darkness, my soul's nowhere
溶け連ね　駆けてただ　惹き合う
Melting together, just running and attracting each other
Hello, Hello, 今宵のEnsomnia
Hello, Hello, tonight's Ensomnia
Let's maintain
In a world where nothing is certain
Except that someday we will say goodbye
I want to keep my eyes on the sky
砂漠みたいな街 Disaster!
This desert-like city is a Disaster!
双六　加速する未来のMercy
Sugoroku, the mercy of the accelerating future
否ならぬ　信じたい再会に
Not a no, to the reunion I want to believe in
焦げ付くほどの　Hold you all day long
Burning so hot, I'll hold you all day long
Hello, Hello, 今宵のDaydreamer
Hello, Hello, tonight's Daydreamer
Let's maintain!
SHOUT! We're changing the game
Masquerading the chains, what gives you the say?
S-O-S THE FIRE!
SHOUT! We're changing the game
Masquerading the chains, what gives you the say?
S-O-S THE FIRE!
Hey, yeah, hey, hey, everyone! Whoo!
How was that? Tenshu and Mercy.
You know, writing that song reminded me, yes, I still can write songs...
...that are extremely difficult to perform live. Let's go!
Some things never change, it feels.
But hey, how about the tech for this concert?
Hold on, are you guys seeing this Sakura behind me? Like, the detail?
Oh, hold on. Sorry.
Again, the Sakura tree is very powerful.
It's such a big item and so detailed.
Sometimes I stop moving.
That's okay, doesn't matter. Whoo!
パチパチパチ！
Batchi batchi batchi!
That was a thousand out of ten. Nailed it. Let's go!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
It is clean. Drink water.
That's a really good idea.
水、水、水。
Water, water, water.
The invisible water.
But I mean, if you guys think back to Phantomime...
I see a lot of you guys talking about, like, "Oh, the production, the quality is so crazy!"
It's very powerful stuff going on around here...
...and they really knocked it out of the park with this.
I just have so much thanks to give to my staff.
Um, be sure, we have a little credit roll at the end that will play...
...and, you know, that's my staff and big ups to them.
But remember the Phantomime concert, you guys...
...that we did, the little mini live for the release of Phantomime, which was really cool?
That already had like the echoes of the beginning of even better quality for these shows, right?
Well, can you imagine what the next is gonna look like?
I mean, if this, if this looks like this right now...
I mean, can you imagine where we go from here?
I mean, it's just really exciting to think about.
20 years from now, Dead Beats, 20 years from now, who knows?
I probably will be as detailed as that Sakura tree...
...but don't worry, it won't be too much, it'll still feel like me.
I'll make sure about that.
This is already kind of toeing the line, I think...
...but I'd love to, like, move my face a little bit more and stuff like that.
It would be more dramatic if leaves were scattering around?
That's a good point.
However, Dead Beat, you say that, if Sakura was falling right now...
...I think that every PC in this studio would catch on fire.
Great idea though.
自撮りタイム！
Selfie time!
Okay, here we go.
Now I'm using this camera again.
Whoa, okay.
You guys can get... I'm backing up, I'm backing up.
A bit of a closer look...
...that Sakura tree behind, that is 3D.
They're laughing, they're laughing.
You're laughing at me! Stop it!
Stop!
Someday I'll be able to make an angry face at you, so get ready for that.
That's another thing to look forward to, Dead Beats. Bye!
W-wait... making an angry face?
Fuck you!
Ooh! Check out my nails!
Even cats hide their claws.
Hey! This is a cute little screenshot too.
I heard from my P-san, my P-san showed a little piece of paper to me...
...that said that #disastershow entered the trends in USA.
Thank you so much for that!
Dead Beats, keep it coming, and some folks are like...
"Mori, I can't believe this is free!"
Of course it's free, 'cause I know that the majority of you guys bought the album...
...so it might as well be free.
Um, and if you didn't buy it, you at least have been streaming it.
So it just, it just feels right, I guess...
...to do what I can to make it worth it to you guys, even more so.
Hi! You guys remember this outfit?
It's a little on the older side, but check it out, you guys remember, right?
From my very first solo show, "New Underworld Order".
It's looking good, right? I'm looking good.
Hi! Hi!
Trying to get as much camera screen time as I can.
Buy the album! Buy the album! Say the Dead Beats.
お願いします！ If you could, I'd be very happy.
Please! If you could, I'd be very happy.
Whoa, this is kind of a cool shot with the Sakura.
My eyes are glowing in the darkness. Hey there. Hi.
I'll keep trying to make silly faces though.
That's something that'll never change about me.
This is a screenshot moment.
Whenever it stops, it means it's a screenshot moment. Maybe.
Anyway, it's time to move on because I still have a couple songs to sing for you guys.
I think this one will end up being longer than "Dance Past Midnight", which is a good thing.
I get to sing even more for you!
What songs will they be? I wonder.
ありがとう、スタッフさん！
Thank you, staff!
And, uh, yeah. So, I guess it's about time that we move on to the next spot.
Looking good.
Thanks Dead Beats. You want to see my high kicks I've been working on?
おいしょ！ And...
Hup! And...
おいしょ！ My high kicks.
Hup! My high kicks.
おいしょ！ Next year I'm going to kick even higher, you'll see.
Hup! Next year I'm going to kick even higher, you'll see.
Anyway, that's some randomness right there.
Let's go. Next... 変身！
Let's go. Next... Transformation!
行くぞ！
Here we go!
I put my last illusions behind...
Still you're creeping through my thoughts tonight.
Now I know it's so mis-skin deep...
Drawn like moths to flames inside your heat.
Heat, heat.
Consider myself fine, but I'm christening every line...
...drunk on love that's not mine.
Heaven sent you way too late, kiss of death and take the fate...
...past lives and loaded dice, white lies and alibis.
Fingers tracing edges of the medicine I never swallow...
...rights don't know the enemy to fight, not in this life.
Stolen whispers, don't ask and don't tell...
...step into my world, welcome to hell.
Sinking down in your deep black...
We fall, we break...
...we drown in fire.
Lost inside this dark desire.
No love, no faith...
...just you and I...
...dancing to the end of time.
Ba la la la la la la la...
...end of time, end of time, end of time. Ba la la la la la la la...
I still blame myself for this haze...
...shame that overflows, it never dissipates.
I let words unsaid rot slowly, tainted and unholy...
...no don't say...
Watch, wait, cold steel pressed against your neck.
Ba la la la la la la la...
...end of time, end of time, end of time.
One last breath before we die...
...the sight of you intoxicates...
Say a prayer, pass the time to confess...
...us, it's a game we never plan to win
and take us to rest, six feet under side by side
We fall,
we break,
we drown in fire
lost inside this dark desire
No love,
no fear,
just you and I
dancing till the end of time
La la la la la la...
Ashes fall from blackened skies
all that's left is you and I
drunk inside this love tonight
La la la la la la...
End of time, end of time
End of time, end of time...
I ain't tryna stress you, I must confess though
my heart's beating to your song
(Oh yeah!) Thinking hurry up
Orpheus, time's a-wastin'
Tell me what you really wanna do!
Another late night aimless dreaming
The bitter taste starts to call
Still got like a million deadlines, beating red wine
my back up against the wall
I got my headphones on, walk home alone
dragging feet like I'm born to lose
Till somehow they're tapping along
to you-know-whose song, a melody I can't refuse
Cause when my heart beats fast
when you look this way
Can you see us on the stage
when you feel the same, okay?
I know I get a little carried away, but we got
music when there aren't any words to say
Cause when my heart beats fast when you look this way
can you see us on the stage when you feel the same?
Now I'm in distress, you got me possessed, I might be
obsessed, so let me get a little something off my chest, look
I ain't tryna stress you, I must confess though
my heart's beating to your song
(Oh yeah!) Thinking hurry up
Orpheus, time's a-wastin'
Tell me what you really wanna do!
Tonight it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
Sometimes it feels like you're playing guitar
for me and only me
Critics so loud, so predictable
they can't see what I can see
Gonna wind up a star, got me dancing in the dark!
This-this-this got me feeling fond
and I wonder if it's enough
Cause I'm not lying when I'm implying
you're all that I've been thinking of
Maybe they'll call me delusional
maybe this could be real love
Give me one chance and I'll take, dance the night away!
Now it's a game that I played before
But with the way the scene changed
there is nothing you can blame me for
I'm talking TV screens, magazines, seen you in a
couple dreams, pictures up on every patio wall in floor
Always talking bout no time to desire a love
so why'd you paint your nails up in my favorite color?
I got an attitude just when it comes to you
see reality is kind of slipping out of view
Never lost in the groove of somebody new
if it's devotion you're after I'm staying true
So are you noticing me noticing you noticing me?
No disillusion but there's not a lot of guarantee
Cause when my heart beats fast when you look this way
can you see us on the stage when you feel the same?
You're strumming next to me and I'm in ecstasy
and for the rest of the week I'm depression free
I ain't tryna stress you, I must confess though
my heart's beating to your song
(Oh yeah!) Thinking hurry up
Orpheus, time's a-wastin'
Tell me what you really wanna do!
Tonight it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
So just as long as you keep playing that guitar!
Critics so loud, so predictable
they can't see what I can see
Gonna wind up a star, got me dancing in the dark!
This-this-this got me feeling fond
and I wonder if it's enough
Cause I'm not lying when I'm implying
you're all that I've been thinking of
Maybe they'll call me delusional
maybe this could be real love
Give me one chance and I'll take, dance the night away!
Hey, hey, come on!
So let's blow this joint and if the feeling's right
then we can make a little music of our own tonight!
Come on! Hey, hey! Why you walking away? I got a lot
to say, guess I'll save it for the next one!
I ain't tryna stress you, I must confess though
my heart's beating to our song
So hear me out Orpheus, thinking next time
I'll show you what I really wanna do!
I'm back Dead Beats! Where'd the cats go? (laugh)
Hey wait a minute, where'd the weird cats at?
They were just here a second ago.
Dead Beats, check out what I can do. Hold on.
Get ready. Are you ready? Check it out.
I'm obsessed with how this dress moves. Dead Beats!
I mean, look at this. Let me... let me... let me just...
Maybe I should back up a little bit.
Look at how it moves.
Ooo, so scandalous. Ah, don't look!
The physics are crazy.
How about those weird cats though? Doing the dance.
It was so cute. The creature, nice moves, thank you.
Thank you, Dead Beats.
Oh, that was fun. That was fun, Dead Beats.
I had such a good time with you guys today.
Actually, I mentioned to you guys my family?
My family came to glorious Nippon and actually...
My family came to glorious Japan and actually...
...we kind of celebrated the release together.
I was like, you know, sneaking around some places
that were selling the album...
...and then hearing my own music
blasting on the speakers.
They were playing Orpheus,
they were playing Golden Balance,
they were playing Let's Just Crash.
And for the first time ever, Dead Beats,
walking around the store, I didn't feel like...
embarrassed.
Which is a step in the right direction.
I feel like I've been getting better, Dead Beats.
I hope it was fun. It was so fun.
Dead Beats, I can't even explain...
...being able to be so proud and say,
"Look, that's my thing.
They're playing my song on the speaker."
It's so cool.
I mean, I went to karaoke with my little sister.
She told me that "Die for You"
was her favorite song of mine
and "MERA MERA", which made me very happy.
Those are little sister Reaper's favorites
and I sang it for her and her friends
because they really wanted to hear
and they're like, "Whoa, free concert!"
It was really cool.
Um, so yeah, there was that.
What else did I want to talk about?
I don't know, I feel like even today
with today's show,
I feel like I'm getting more confident
to do more things with my voice.
And I can do more things with my voice.
It's still a little rough and unpolished,
but like, that's the point of Disasterpiece in general, right?
I'm working towards my masterpiece and maybe...
...it will take some time to get things exactly
the way that I want, maybe I'll never get there, you know?
But I'm doing more with my voice
and even though it's new stuff and it needs polishing,
I'm really happy with it.
What's my favorite song, asks the Dead Beats?
Oh, I don't know, I like them for different reasons.
The one that maybe I'm proudest of
is maybe "Rivals and Equals"
because I still listen to that and I'm like,
"Yeah, that's really good."
But then I also really like "SHU-EN"
for the lyrics as well,
probably my favorite lyrics
I've written in a long time.
So, yeah. That's right,
that Dead Beat says it's about the journey. Exactly.
I'm running out of time here so let me get this
jidori camera real quick. Hold up.
selfie camera real quick. Hold up.
Ah, yes. My eyes are glowing in the dark right now
because we're in a dark area.
But now I'm going to show you the skirt move,
let's get on the red.
Gotta get on the red.
Okay, I'm moving my chest piece,
which is myself, to the red. Look at the skirt.
It's kind of hard to see. Sorry.
Sorry. Doing my best over here.
Uh, maybe it's better to view from the other side.
So look, there's the—this is the stage
from "Die for You" MV.
And then you can see if we look this way,
it's darkness,
and then if we look this way, it's darkness.
But it's still really cool. Whoa, what's that?
It kind of looks like the wall
that maybe leads to the hospital?
I don't know.
Respectfully, of course. Peace.
Peace. Peace.
I'll make it work. Hi. Hello.
It is I, Mori Calliope, and I just released
a new album.
It's my best work so far. And in Japan,
we got number one album on iTunes ranking.
Yay! For alternative, for alternative music.
So let's see how much further we can push.
Last time I checked in US it was climbing,
it was getting high up, but you know
there's a lot of stiff competition there.
So it's all good, it's all good if we don't
reach number one that's fine.
But I'd love for you guys to keep pushing
for me if you would like to.
Spread the word and keep listening
in all your favorite places. Keep enjoying the album.
And I will keep making—I'll keep doing stuff
that only I can do.
Like writing Mori Calliope lyrics. So, yeah.
I guess that's about it. I want to give a
special thanks to Dead Beats
and to Staff-san.
いつもありがとうございます。
Always, thank you very much.
My staff is the best. Please look at the credits
so you know who to say thank you to.
Dead Beats, and yeah, post it everywhere.
Thank you, thank you Dead Beats.
I'm reading y'all's comments to eat the camera?
I think that's a bad idea.
I think they'll get mad at me if I do that.
I think it's going to break things.
Anyway, that's the end of the jidori camera.
Anyway, that's the end of the selfie camera.
Anyway, we are back here. So, I guess that's—
Oh, like I said, I'm using a headset.
No, no, no. Really, microphone. Trust, trust.
But you know, with the technical stuff,
there's always a little bit of magic involved, right?
In order to get the level of quality
that we've got. So...
...but thank you guys always for cheering
for me and being excited about my work.
Now there is no encore because life has
no encore. So sorry about that.
I think there are a lot of songs
you guys want to hear me sing.
...singing them soon for you, on my streams.
So tune into my streams...
...and my- my karaoke streams...
...and streams where I'm singing my stuff...
...and, uh, future shows.
If there's a song that you really want to hear,
like I know a lot of you probably want to hear
"SHŪTEN", for example.
So if you want to hear it,
you've got to stay tuned and come to the next one.
Like I said, life has no encore.
So, what I want you to do now is...
...just rewatch the live.
And then go listen to the music.
Links in the description.
Thank you Dead Beats always for cheering for me.
Thank you for supporting what I do.
I'm strange,
but you know, this is really fun.
I'm glad I get to do this every day.
And I put my whole heart into the new release.
So... I'll see you guys tomorrow.
We're playing a game.
There's- there's a game stream tomorrow.
See you guys around.
Thanks again everyone!
I'm your Mori, hope you'll remember me.
Peace!
DISASTERSHOW
Mori Calliope
M1: LET'S JUST CRASH
M2: Rivals and Equals
M3: Unbalance feat. 中島健人
M3: Unbalance feat. Kento Nakajima
M4: Memento
M5: Seeing Stars feat. Lotus Juice
M6: 天誅 & Mercy feat. 10-FEET
M6: TENCHŪ & Mercy feat. 10-FEET
M7: Die For You
M8: Orpheus
Dead Beats!! Much love to you.
Thank you for following your (at times) disaster
(affectionate) of an oshi.
Let's keep chasing our own masterpieces
even if we're imperfect,
even if we fail every time.
That is to live, I think.
Calliope Mori.
1. Orpheus
I feel so something so...
...predictable, wait till what I can see girl.
2. LET'S JUST CRASH
Let's ride!
Get back!
掻き乱して響き合う
Stir it up and resonate with each other
Let's just crash!
全て壊れて飛んだ
Everything broke and flew away
いたずらなキャラだけは此処に
Only the mischievous persona remains here
笑い
Smiling
Lose control!
美しき賛美
A beautiful praise
3. Gold Unbalance feat. 中島健人
3. Gold Unbalance feat. Kento Nakajima
何でもないような世界で
In a world that seems like nothing
不条理重ねた光
The light of piled-up absurdities
脈打つ鼓動
A pulsing heartbeat
誰にもなれない
I can't be anyone else
言葉を紡いで
Spinning words
4. Die For You
Insomniac Black.
We fall.
We break.
We're drown in fire.
Lost inside this dark desire.
5. 天誅 & Mercy feat. 10-FEET
5. Tenchuu & Mercy feat. 10-FEET
天誅 焦がす未来の Mercy
Divine punishment, Mercy for the scorching future
Mercy! Mercy!
未だ何もしない最小の愛に
To the smallest love that still does nothing
6. Ningen Dakara
Tell me what I'm not to say.
What's your problem?
夜更け一人 私が迷う
Alone late at night, I am lost
7. Rivals and Equals
When the world crashes down.
When the world keeps under pressure.
There'll be no more to say.
8. INSOMNIAC BLACK
巡る巡る運命に逆らって
Going against the circling destiny
出会い 想いを通わせた
An encounter, sharing our feelings
The strangers I followed with stars in...
9. Shuuden
I keep on waiting, wanting, faking you're someone...
...you're not reaching, longing, changing.
10. Memento
I can't be someone else.
Despite it all my mind has become my hell.
With no escape or hope in the dark.
But still...
初回限定盤 / Limited Edition
Limited Edition
Bonus Track
11. FLASH BANG feat. PES
クラクラするでしょ
You're feeling dizzy, aren't you?
ほらほら遠くそうそうそうでしょ
Look, look, far away, that's right, isn't it?
FLASH BANG!
12. Seeing Stars feat. Lotus Juice
In this moment maybe I'm not so bad...
...knowing if I never try... someday.
13. Sepia feat. TOOBOE
夢を見るたび
Every time I dream
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I end up thinking about the reason I was born
ああ美しき青い...
Ah, the beautiful blue...
14. Die For You feat. ARTMS
We fall.
We break.
We're drown in fire.
Lost inside this dark desire.
No love, no fate, just...