(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Ayunda Risu
Kureiji Ollie
Vestia Zeta
Moona Hoshinova
Anya Melfissa
Kaela Kovalskia
Airani Iofifteen
Pavolia Reine
Kobo Kanaeru
TERIMA KASIH!
THANK YOU!
BERKAT KALIAN, KAMI BISA BERSINAR
BERIBU-RIBU TERIMA KASIH
THANKS TO YOU ALL, WE CAN SHINE
THOUSANDS OF THANKS
TERIMA KASIH UDAH BIKIN STAGE INI
& HIDUP KAMI LEBIH BERWARNA!
THANK YOU FOR MAKING THIS STAGE
& OUR LIVES MORE COLORFUL!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank You!!
TERIMA KASIH BANYAK!!!!!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!!!!!
Terima Kasih!!
Kalian Semua Keren BGT!!
Thank You!!
You All Are So Cool!!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank You!!
Makasih ya!!
Thanks!!
terima kasih
thank you
Ayo mulai!!
Let's start!!
CHROMATIC FUTURE
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も
Body and soul
この手で Make you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine
君を見るたび
Every time I look at you
上書きされてく欲望に
With desires being overwritten
重なる Eyes, eyes, eyes
Overlapping eyes, eyes, eyes
目を伏せ Your smile, smile, smile
Casting eyes down at your smile, smile, smile
ねえ、その姿形
Hey, that figure and form
全てが拍車かけてく
Everything is spurring it on
恋から 愛、愛、愛
From falling in love to love, love, love
毎秒おかしくなってく
Going crazy every second
手を伸ばせば届く距離
Within reach if I extend my hand
危険なノイズ 試したい
Wanting to test the dangerous noise
穏やかに 恋したい
Wanting to fall in love peacefully
どんなシーンも私に見せて
Show me every scene
このまま Stay by my side
Just like this, stay by my side
どこにも行かないで
Don't go anywhere
愛 100パーセント
Love 100 percent
純粋な愛だから
Because it's pure love
止められない感情
Unstoppable emotions
その腕抱きしめてよ
Hold me in those arms
もっと奥から愛
Love from deeper within
ずっと もっと近くで
Always, much closer
見つめ合いたい
Wanting to gaze at each other
狂おしいほど
To the point of madness
持て余すだけなら Fly
If it's too much to handle, then fly
Hey, mean, what's wrong with me?
名もなき普通だし
I'm just a nameless ordinary person
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you, right now
最初は声を聞く
At first, just hearing your voice
それだけでよかった
That was enough
だけど次第に Why
But gradually, why
我がままになった
I became selfish
誰かに微笑みかけ
Smiling at someone
その仕草に苛立ち
Irritated by that gesture
隠せない自分に気づいた
I realized I couldn't hide it
独り占めしたい
I want you all to myself
いっそ鎖に繋いで
Might as well chain you up
二人きりの部屋
In a room with just the two of us
強引な発言 視したい
Wanting to ignore pushy remarks
思い捨て 眠りたい
Throwing away thoughts, wanting to sleep
鋭い吐息感じさせて
Let me feel your sharp breath
永久に Stay by your side
Forever stay by your side
誰にも貸さない
Won't let anyone else have you
愛 100パーセント
Love 100 percent
私だけに依存してね
Please depend only on me
色づく合図
The coloring sign
丸ごと受け止めてよ
Accept it all
もっと私を知ら
Knowing more about me
たとしても引き返せない
Even so, there's no turning back
行かせてよ
Let me go
抗い切れない絶対
Absolutely irresistible
Hey, mean, what's wrong with me?
名もなき普通だし
I'm just a nameless ordinary person
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you, right now
目を閉じたら
When I close my eyes
止めど流れない愛感
Endless feeling of love
触れたい
Wanting to touch
愛
Love
私の愛だけ
Only my love
このまま Stay by my side
Just like this, stay by my side
二度と離れないで
Never leave me again
愛 100パーセント
Love 100 percent
純粋な愛
Pure love
Lalala...
明いてよ
Shine on
止められない感情
Unstoppable emotions
その手で抱きしめてよ
Hold them in your hands
あとどこまで通う？
How much further to go?
ずっともっと近くで
Always much closer
認め合いたい
I want us to acknowledge each other
荒ぶる衝動
Wild impulses
持て余すだけなら Slash!
If you can't handle them, then Slash!
Tell me what's wrong with me
何もないない筆出し
Nothing, nothing, just starting to write
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I just need you 今すぐ
I just need you right now
Oh baby I miss you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby I miss you, I need you forever
逃げるなら今だ
If you're going to run, now's the time
比勝利を願っちゃって
Praying for incomparable victory
ハメッケチー!
HAMEKKECHII!
THIS IS HOLOBA!
LET'S GO SET THE WORLD ON FIRE!
Are you all ready? 模したってのさ
Are you all ready? Just as I imagined
油断ない去りに Fifteen minutes
Without a moment's neglect, it's over in fifteen minutes
目を覚ませ 半信半疑の先にほら
Wake up, look beyond the half-belief and half-doubt
誰か Just Scanning
Someone is Just Scanning
Ready では Standby now
Already on Standby now
今更 時空飽き飽きなのよ
By now, I'm bored with time and space
遠回りは残酷
Taking a detour is cruel
私には血の味ね
For me, it tastes like blood
舐めんな 罪と先手
Don't underestimate the sin and the first move
Medikitの山と B20
A mountain of Medikits and B20
Good luck 祈る幸運なんかより
Rather than praying for good luck
確かな実力
Certain ability
Day by day 初出し あらあら
Day by day, the first appearance is 'oh my'
やったこと全部 PINを刺した
Everything I've done, I've pinned it
笑ってくれたっていい
You can laugh if you want
鮫に割れるやら恋は遊び
Divided by sharks or love is just a game
VICTORY TO THE WORLD
ねえ 今こそ感じを
Hey, feel the vibe right now
ギュッと かけがえないはずよ
It should be tightly irreplaceable
見ていて見てよ この今日
Watch, look at this today
慈にいらっしゃって
Come and see with mercy
ランダムな未来労働
A random future labor
饐えた来ない欄階
A stale future stage that hasn't come
嘗めた 五三系
I've tasted the five systems
降雷すぎる外殻の上
Above the outer shell where thunder strikes too much
ここはどこ Over?
Where am I, Over?
拾い上げた ワンキレ
Picking up a worn-out slice
滑走 私を強くしてくわ
Gliding, it's making me stronger
Positioning 高所から
Positioning from a high place
覗かれるのは尺で
Being peeked at is annoying
押し返り 1, 2, 3
Pushing back, 1, 2, 3
死ぬのは嫌で Trip Trip Trip
I don't want to die, Trip Trip Trip
気が付いたらラウンジで
Before I knew it, I was at the lounge
あれれ? 隠れていただけ?
Wait? Was I just hiding?
Night and night Fighting
金たや ららん なのじゃ
Money and such is useless
全部は Cancel
Everything is Cancel
泣いたって やめないだって
Even if you cry, don't stop
これが私の憲法になる
This will be my constitution
共知らずにね
Without knowing together, right?
VICTORY TO THE WORLD
共に作り出したいんだ
I want to create it together
熱気でたまん中を
In the middle of the heat
心地いい この今日
This pleasant today
君 染まっちゃって
Get dyed in your colors
KOMICHI BLOOM!
AYO ANYA MANA?!
AYO ANYA WHERE ARE YOU?!
AYO ANYA MANA SUARANYA?!
AYO ANYA WHERE IS YOUR VOICE?!
BBM 走っちゃって
Running with BBM
Hey I am ブレないで
Hey I am, don't waver
Day by day 潜って
Day by day, diving
まだまだ降り立つ死に家
Still descending to the death scene
カウント取って
Take the count
笑ってくれたっていい
You can laugh if you want
さては みんなで
Well then, everyone together
VICTORY TO THE WORLD
絶対 抜くよ あの光で
I'll definitely pull through with that light
結び縄を
The destiny
忘れられないほどの
To an unforgettable extent
勝利を願っちゃって
Praying for victory
今日を行こう GG!
Let's go today GG!
Hah... Siapa di sini yang lelah dengan kehidupan?
Hah... Who here is tired of life?
AKU! AKU!
ME! ME!
Kalau capek enaknya gimana nih, El-Hero?
If you're tired, what's good to do, El-Hero?
Malas saja.
Just be lazy.
Cakep!
Nice!
Bukannya sudah biasa
Isn't it already normal
Ditikam oleh kecewa
To be stabbed by disappointment
Saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya
When the world doesn't go as it should
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya kau coba lepaskan saja
Maybe it's time you just try to let go
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
No need to ask why anymore
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If indeed you don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry, try to go through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Let it go
karena pada akhirnya kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
because in the end, you are stronger than you think
Dahlah saja
Just leave it
oh dahlah saja
oh just leave it
Jalani saja
Just live it
Dahlah saja
Just leave it
oh dahlah saja
oh just leave it
Jalani saja
Just live it
Mau gimana lagi
What can you do
Walau kadang mati rasa bahkan hingga tak berdaya
Even if sometimes numb, even to the point of helplessness
Dan usahamu terasa sia-sia
And your efforts feel in vain
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If indeed you don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry, try to go through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Let it go
karena pada akhirnya kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
because in the end, you are stronger than you think
Lepas semua kendali
Release all control
Tancap gas dan berlari
Step on the gas and run
Terima dan sudahi
Accept and finish it
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If indeed you don't get the answer
Jangan tangisi cobalah lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry, try to go through the puzzle
Relakanlah
Let it go
karena pada akhirnya kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
because in the end, you are stronger than you think
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Dahlah saja
Just leave it
oh dahlah saja
oh just leave it
Jalani saja
Just live it
Dahlah saja
Just leave it
oh dahlah saja
oh just leave it
Jalani saja
Just live it
まいっか
Oh well
Halo Comic Frontier!
Hello Comic Frontier!
Halo!
Hello!
Welcome to hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future!
Wah gila gila gila!
Wow, crazy crazy crazy!
Makasih banyak semuanya udah pada datang ke konser 5 tahun kita ya!
Thank you so much everyone for coming to our 5-year concert!
Wah nggak berasa nggak sih udah 5 tahun aja?
Wow, doesn't it feel like it's already been 5 years?
Kalau gitu kita mulai dari perkenalan diri dulu nggak sih?
If so, should we start with self-introductions?
Mulai dari aku, aku!
Starting from me, me!
Ah Mission Starto! Tatatata!
Ah Mission Start! Tatatata!
Aku Vestia Zeta dari hololive Indonesia Gen 3. Nice to meet you!
I'm Vestia Zeta from hololive Indonesia Gen 3. Nice to meet you!
Oke, next Kaela!
Okay, next Kaela!
Kaela grinding every time, the blacksmith from hololive ID Gen 3. I'm Kaela Kovalskia. Nice to meet you all!
Next next next, Kobo Kobo Kobo!
Bokobokobo Kobo Kanaeru at your service. Let me be your sun to shine your day. Ehe! Kobo-kan!
Mana suaranya?!
Where's the noise?!
Nah bertiga kami dari hololive Indonesia Gen 3! HoloH3roes!
So the three of us are from hololive Indonesia Gen 3! HoloH3roes!
Wah nggak nyangka juga deh konser 5th Anniversary hololive ID ini akhirnya ada juga.
Wow, I didn't expect that this hololive ID 5th Anniversary concert would finally happen.
Dari lagu pertama aja udah keren banget guys. Kerasa nggak?
The first song alone was so cool guys. Can you feel it?
Masih semangat ya? Iya nggak sih? Iya nggak sih?
Are you still energetic? Right? Isn't it? Isn't it?
Parah sih, ada adrenalin—rasakan ya?
It's crazy, there's adrenaline—can you feel it?
Pengen lari aku rasanya nih!
I feel like running right now!
Stop stop stop stop stop stop stop!
Mau ke mana? Stop stop stop!
Where are you going? Stop stop stop!
Nanti keringetan lho, nanti keringetan.
You'll get sweaty later, you'll get sweaty.
Kaela gimana?
How about Kaela?
Aduh, seru banget.
Man, it's so fun.
Aku nggak nyangka sih sampai aku bisa ada di sini ya.
I didn't expect that I could be here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong konser-nya masih panjang banget.
But by the way, the concert is still very long.
Jadi kalian tetap semangat ya sampai akhir!
So you guys keep up the spirit until the end!
Semangat semangat semangat semangat!
Spirit, spirit, spirit, spirit!
Eh tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi, emang pada tahu judul konser-nya apa?
Eh, but we've been talking about the concert, does everyone know the title?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah Chromatic Future!
Our concert title this time is Chromatic Future!
Ada yang tahu nggak artinya apa? Ayo absen!
Does anyone know what it means? Let's check!
Nah, ini, Kobo paling tahu.
Now, this, Kobo knows best.
Nih, ya...
Here, you see...
Ya, yang ngejelasin yang paling tinggi. Ayo let's go!
Yeah, the tallest one will explain. Come on, let's go!
Segitu ya... ya udahlah, ya udah nih.
Is it like that... alright then, alright here it is.
Nih ya guys ya buat kalian yang belum tahu, Chromatic Future itu artinya tuh...
Here it is guys, for those of you who don't know, Chromatic Future means...
...masa depan yang berwarna-warni.
...a colorful future.
Jadi karena hololive Indonesia kan udah lima tahun nih...
So since hololive Indonesia has been around for five years...
...kita sama-sama dari hari satu sampai sekarang.
...we've been together from day one until now.
Nah, jadi itu untuk ke depannya kita tuh juga harapannya tuh...
So for the future, our hope is also...
...kita bisa nyiptain waktu dan memori yang berwarna-warni sama seluruh fans dari hololive Indonesia!
...we can create colorful times and memories with all the fans of hololive Indonesia!
Ya gitu, betul Kaela Kovalskia! Cakep!
Yeah like that, you're right Kaela Kovalskia! Nice!
Nah, kalian sekarang udah pada tahu kan karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
Now, you all know now because it was explained by Kaela.
Kalau gitu, konser-nya kan udah mulai nih.
In that case, the concert has already started.
Kalian mau nge-post soal konser ini di medsos, jangan lupa...
If you want to post about this concert on social media, don't forget...
...hashtag holoIDChromaticFuture ya!
...hashtag holoIDChromaticFuture, okay!
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh apa sih, pengen lihat semangat kalian!
Because we really want to see... what is it, want to see your spirit!
Ya itu, betul banget, iya nggak?
Yeah that, very true, right?
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
No typos, no typos!
Asik, share ke semua, oke? Jadi tapi jujur deh...
Cool, share with everyone, okay? So, but honestly...
...kalian tuh pas dibilang kita bakal konser lho di Indonesia, kalian pada kaget nggak sih?
...when you were told we're going to have a concert in Indonesia, were you guys surprised?
Halo? Ada yang dengerin?
Hello? Is anyone listening?
Betul! Aku setuju juga.
Right! I agree too.
Aku merasakan empati terhadap... ini adik saya Zeta.
I feel empathy towards... this, my little sister Zeta.
Iya, empati, iya iya.
Yeah, empathy, yeah yeah.
Gimana Kaela Kovalskia?
How about Kaela Kovalskia?
Aku juga waktu itu nggak nyangka banget kayak 'Hah? Beneran? Ini riil nih?' gitu kan.
I also at that time didn't expect it at all, like 'Huh? Really? Is this real?' like that.
Kayak 'Loh? Bisa gitu? Akhirnya...'
Like 'Wait? Is that possible? Finally...'
...mana udah bersembilan di Indonesia pula ya kan. Keren banget!
...especially with all nine of us in Indonesia too, right. So cool!
Ini kan konser pertama hololive Indonesia yang bersembilan.
This is the first hololive Indonesia concert with all nine of us.
Sebenarnya tuh nggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar dan terpenting juga untuk fans hololive Indonesia...
Actually, not only is this the biggest and most important moment for hololive Indonesia fans...
...tapi seluruh dunia juga pasti bakal nonton nggak sih? Iya nggak?
...but the whole world will definitely watch too, right? Isn't it?
Iya iya makasih-makasih semuanya.
Yeah yeah thanks-thanks everyone.
Wait, tapi tentu saja ini pencapaiannya nggak bakal cuma sampai di sini aja kan.
Wait, but of course this achievement won't just stop here, right.
Jadi next-nya mungkin kita bisa apa ya, dominating the world gitu.
So next, maybe we can... what is it, dominating the world like that.
We are ready! Ready ready ready ready!
Betul banget Kaela, Zeta. Selain dari dukungan fans, in this opportunity...
Very true Kaela, Zeta. Besides the fans' support, in this opportunity...
...kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih untuk semua sponsor yang mendukung terjadinya konser ini!
...we also want to say thank you to all the sponsors who supported this concert!
Terima kasih! Thank you thank you!
Thank you! Thank you thank you!
Eh tapi ngomong-ngomong di konser ini kayaknya ada yang beda nggak sih?
Eh, but by the way, in this concert, it seems like there's something different, isn't there?
Ela kamu sadar nggak? Soalnya kamu paling peka nggak sih?
Ela, do you notice? Because you're the most sensitive, aren't you?
Wait, ya sadarlah. Kalau Kobo mah nggak bakal sadar.
Wait, of course I notice. As for Kobo, she won't notice.
Nih nih nih, yang beda tuh kali ini tuh model kita.
Here, look at this, what's different this time is our models.
Ini model baru nih!
This is a new model!
Kameranya dekatin ke aku! Kameranya dekatin ke aku!
Bring the camera closer to me! Bring the camera closer to me!
Nah mulai-mulai. Ka mau lihat keimutan Kobo nih.
Here we go. You want to see Kobo's cuteness.
Wait wait wait, sini sini sini... ini kamera diambil Kobo semua nggak sih?
Wait wait wait, over here... is this camera all taken by Kobo?
Ini ke aku juga, aku juga! Jangan Kobo doang!
To me too, me too! Not just Kobo!
Stop stop stop stop stop! Mulai mulai mulai... semua kamera diambil!
Stop stop stop stop stop! Here they go... taking all the camera!
Oke oke oke, kalau gitu... aduh sampai kehabisan napas.
Okay okay okay, in that case... man, I'm out of breath.
Jangan rebutan di depan konser!
Don't fight in front of the concert!
Kalau Zeta udah ngomong...
When Zeta has spoken...
Kalau enggak boleh...
If we're not allowed...
...rebutan komidi sama Zeta...
...to fight over comedy with Zeta...
...hmm, ya sudahlah.
...well, whatever.
Kita main aja deh sama penonton.
Let's just play with the audience.
Kobo pengin deh coba kita teriakin penonton...
Kobo wants to try shouting at the audience...
...karena kan tadi mereka sudah teriakin kita.
...because they shouted at us earlier.
Maksudnya kita teriakin intro kita bareng penonton-tachi!
I mean, let's shout our intro together with the audience!
Betul! Teriaknya bareng penonton, jangan teriakin penontonnya.
Right! Shout with the audience, not at them.
Iya gitu maksudnya.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
Soalnya kan habis ini kita harus nyanyi...
Because we have to sing after this...
...jadi kita harus simpan suara dulu enggak sih?
...so shouldn't we save our voices?
Betul, ya. Enggak bakal selama itu ternyata...
True. It won't be that long actually...
...tenang aja enggak bakal selama...
...don't worry, it won't be as long as...
...durasi stream Kaela gitu ya guys ya.
...my stream duration, guys.
Ya sudahlah mau teriak-teriak ya sudah, aku enggak masalah lah, aku ikut.
Fine, if you want to shout, I don't mind, I'm in.
Aku ikut! Gimana nih semuanya, sudah siap belum?
I'm in! How about it, everyone, are you ready?
Siap!
Ready!
Siap nih kayaknya, oke!
Seems they're ready, okay!
Kobo dulu ya.
Kobo first, okay?
Aku mau kita sama-sama teriak Baka-Baka-Baka!
I want us to all shout Baka-Baka-Baka together!
Oke, siap ya!
Okay, ready!
Satu, dua, tiga!
One, two, three!
BAKA-BAKA-BAKA!
Suka-suka! Giliran Zeta, giliran Zeta.
Suka-suka! Zeta's turn, Zeta's turn.
Pas aku bilang "Mission Starto",
When I say "Mission Starto",
kalian bareng-bareng teriak "Starto" ya.
you guys shout "Starto" together, okay.
Siap? Aaa... Mission...
Ready? Aaa... Mission...
...Starto!
STARTO!
Oke, habis ini Kaela.
Okay, next is Kaela.
Oke, oke, oke. Nah, nih ya
Okay, okay, okay. Now, for
buat semua penonton sama HoloHeros juga...
all the audience and HoloHeros too...
...kalau misalkan aku bilang "HoloHeros!", kalian bilang "Hu Ha!".
...if I say "HoloHeros!", you guys say "Hu Ha!".
Gampang kan?
Easy, right?
Langsung, langsung, langsung!
Let's go, let's go!
Oke ya, siap ya. HoloHeros!
Okay, ready. HoloHeros!
HU HA!
Mantap! Mantap, mantap, mantap!
Great! Awesome, awesome!
Keren, keren, keren. Akhirnya Gen 3 kompak juga.
Cool, cool, cool. Finally, Gen 3 is in sync.
Iya kompak.
Yeah, in sync.
Kelihatannya masih pada semangat nih ya.
Looks like everyone is still energetic.
Soalnya dari lagu pertama kita hari ini aja sudah kerasa banget.
Because it's already been so felt since our first song today.
Kalian tuh pada nyangka enggak sih kalau lagu pertama kita tuh bakal 100%?
Did you guys expect our first song would be 100%?
Beuh, mana ada yang nyangka.
Whoa, no one expected it.
Aku aja sendiri enggak nyangka juga.
Even I didn't expect it myself.
Langsung dibuka dengan Hoshinova mode gitu.
Opening straight with that Hoshinova mode.
Keren banget kan?
So cool, right?
Keren banget sih, apalagi tadi Zeta sama nyanyi...
It was so cool, especially earlier when Zeta sang...
Zeta sama nyanyi...
Zeta sang...
Zeta sama Kaela nyanyi 100% tuh sudah kayak real 100% ya.
Zeta and Kaela sang 100% and it was like real 100%.
Itu tuh bisa enggak sih enggak sekeren tadi? Aku tuh jadi ingin kayak...
How could it be that cool? It made me go like...
...ugh, ugh gitu kan. Kalian pernah enggak sih nyanyi lagu sekeren tadi?
...ugh, ugh. Have you guys ever sung a song as cool as that?
Aura farming ya?
Aura farming, huh?
Aura farming sesungguhnya keren banget emang lagunya Moona.
Aura farming indeed, Moona's song is really cool.
Emang kan Zeta kan soalnya biasanya lagu-lagu yang stylish...
Right, because Zeta usually does stylish songs...
...yang jazzy-jazzy gitu.
...jazzy-jazzy ones like that.
Jadi tadi pas dinyanyiin tuh ya, 100%, rasanya jadi beda banget vibes-nya.
So when she sang that, 100%, the vibes felt so different.
Terus Kaela juga...
Then Kaela too...
...tadi nerap ya, tadadadadada, kayak apa tuh?
...rapping earlier, tadadadadada, like what was that?
Pokoknya keren banget.
Anyway, it was so cool.
Keren banget ya tadi.
It was so cool earlier.
Tapi habis ini tuh masih ada lagi, New Zombie.
But after this, there's more, New Zombie.
Ayo pada tahu dong ini lagu siapa.
Come on, you guys must know whose song this is.
Tahulah, senpai kita, senpai kita.
Of course, our senior's, our senior's.
Tadi tuh itu ya, HoloRo tuh perform-nya juga
Earlier, HoloRo's performance was also
keren banget kayak lagi di game gitu.
so cool, like being in a game.
Betul, setuju. Terus tadi ada back dancer-nya men!
True, agreed. And there were back dancers, man!
Keren ya guys? Keren enggak?
Cool right, guys? Isn't it cool?
Keren!
Cool!
Ada apa lagi tuh tadi? Lampu laser...
What else was there earlier? Laser lights...
...terus ada efek kembang api segala.
...then there were firework effects and all.
Terus banyaklah ya gimmick-gimmick yang wow.
And lots of wow gimmicks.
Itu back dancer nanti aku hire semua ya buat solo konser aku.
I'll hire all those back dancers later for my solo concert.
Wah, sudah ngomong konser solo aja.
Whoa, already talking about a solo concert.
Ini omongan adalah doa ya.
This words are prayers.
Tapi konser yang ini belum selesai!
But this concert isn't over yet!
Eh, tapi kalian tahu enggak sih sebelum ini tuh nyanyiin lagu apa?
Wait, but do you guys know what song was sung before this?
Eh, aku mah tahu banget lah. Itu lagu terbaru aku, "Dalah".
Oh, I definitely know. That's my newest song, "Dalah".
Ya sudahlah.
Whatever.
Iya, "Dalah".
Yeah, "Dalah".
Enggak usah dibahas.
No need to discuss it.
Ya sudahlah.
Whatever.
Lho kok gitu?
Wait, why the reaction?
Itu tuh maksudnya judulnya "Dalah", lagunya judulnya "Dalah".
I mean the title is "Dalah", the song's title is "Dalah".
Oh, dalah. Iya, dalah. Bilang dong!
Oh, dalah. Yeah, dalah. Say so!
Habisnya kamu kan sering "dalah dalah" gitu.
Because you often say "dalah dalah".
Jadi dikira memang beneran "dalah".
So I thought you were really just done.
Entar dalah-dalah, pulang dia.
Later you'll "dalah" and just go home.
Pulang nanti, kasihan yang anda.
You'll go home, poor you.
Kalau gitu "Dalah" tuh maksudnya apa sih?
So what does "Dalah" mean then?
Dalah" sama kehidupan. Hidup tuh berat ya guys ya.
"Dalah" with life. Life is heavy, guys.
Kalau hidup berat ya sudah, dalah aja. Habis itu lanjutkan hidupmu, begitu.
If life is heavy, well, "dalah" it. After that, continue your life, like that.
Iya betul teman-teman, di kehidupan yang dewasa ini ya.
That's right friends, in this adult life.
Untung lagu nyasantai...
Good thing the song was chill...
...easy listening, jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan...
...easy listening, so we could walk around...
...nyapa fans gitu ya.
...greeting the fans like that.
Asyik banget ya tadi ya?
It was really fun earlier, wasn't it?
Aku juga suka banget tadi pas bagian reff-nya ya.
I also really liked the chorus part earlier.
Da la da la da la da la da la...
Itu... itu beda lagu nggak sih?
That... that's a different song, isn't it?
Da la da la da la da la da la...
Nggak gitu deh.
It's not like that.
Ya tapi pokoknya asyik lah ya kalau nyanyi lagu chill santai-santai kayak gini.
Yeah, but anyway, it's fun to sing a chill and relaxed song like this.
Iya, santai dong.
Yeah, chill of course.
Tapi ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu.
But speaking of chill, we actually can't chill just yet.
Hei, santai...
Hey, chill...
Karena kayaknya katanya nggak boleh santai-santai.
Because it seems like we're not allowed to be too chill.
Iya iya iya, jangan santai-santai. Jangan terlalu santai.
Yeah yeah yeah, don't be chill. Don't be too chill.
Karena konser nya tuh masih panjang.
Because the concert is still long.
Jadi sebelum itu, kalian ada nggak yang mau kalian sampaiin dulu?
So before that, do you guys have anything you want to say first?
Mulai dari ini nih, yang nggak bisa diem.
Starting from this one, who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja.
Just three words.
I love you.
Keren. The best.
Cool. The best.
Sangat jelas ya. Tetap semangat...
Very clear. Stay spirited...
Tetap semangat menjalani hidup ya. Udah gitu aja.
Stay spirited in living your life. That's it.
Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang. Semangat!
Anyway, it's still long until the end. Spirit!
Saranghaeyo!
I love you!
Gomawoyo!
Thank you!
Oke kalau aku, ya, semangat selalu.
Okay as for me, yeah, always stay spirited.
Semangat santai!
Spirited chill!
Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai ya! Semangat santai apa tuh?
Stay spirited chill! What's spirited chill?
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjutkan ke...
Okay then, let's continue to...
Wait wait wait tunggu dulu!
Wait wait wait hold on!
Sebelum selesai-selesai ini nih ya...
Before we finish this up...
...kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu nggak sih?
...shouldn't we shout together with the audience first?
Iya dong! Ayo ayo ayo!
Of course! Let's go let's go let's go!
Jadi kita teriak bareng ya.
So we'll shout together.
Dalam hitungan tiga, kita sama-sama teriak...
On the count of three, we'll all shout...
...'Chromatic Future'. Oke ya!
...'Chromatic Future'. Okay!
Oke oke. 'Chromatic Future' gitu kan ya?
Okay okay. 'Chromatic Future' like that, right?
Iya iya kayak gitu.
Yeah yeah, like that.
Oke langsung ya. Sambil lihat sini sini sini...
Okay, right now. While looking here here here...
Aku ya, aku yang penonton ini nih. Penonton sini nih.
Me, I'll take this audience. This audience here.
Aku ini deh, yang tengah yang tengah. Halo!
I'll take this one, the center one. Hello!
Oke bareng-bareng ya. Satu, dua, tiga!
Okay, together now. One, two, three!
CHROMATIC FUTURE!
Everything was easy
I did it all alone
So effortlessly
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Got all problems solved
Without any setbacks there is nothing uncontrolled
There's no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta soar a little higher
Hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a winged peacock
Kan kutaklukkan gelap dengan sihir angin
I will conquer the dark with wind magic
Kan kuajak semua yang terlelap untuk bangun melawan dunia
I will invite all who sleep to wake up and fight the world
We'll never give up
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain, be stronger than that
Walking step by step, trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have, let's go!
Just believe me, let it go, they'll never bring me down
Just believe me, let it go, they'll never bring us down
No matter the cruelty, still am I royalty
And when the universe works against me I would just let go
If it's spicy, just sip something, let it go
Let it go
I've been living carefree, there's no bitter words in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Not letting it show, things but I'm bigger than my feelings, so that'll be enough
There's no way I can begin
Dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta be better than ever
Hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a winged peacock
Kan kutaklukkan gelap dengan sihir angin kan kuajak...
I will conquer the dark with wind magic and I will invite...
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit...
All those who are asleep, wake up...
...melawan dunia
...and face the world
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than them
Walking step by step
Trusting by our pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Believe me, let it go
They'll never bring me down
Just believe me, let it go
It'll never bring us down
Just believe me
Won't let their cruelty steal my royalty
And when the universe was against me, I will just...
...let it go!
Let it go!
One life's not enough to do this
One, two, three, let it go!
hololive Indonesia CHROMATIC FUTURE
5th Anniversary LIVE
• Acrylic Panel • Acrylic Stand
• Holographic Button Badge
• Lanyard & Ticket Holder • T-shirt