(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
TAKANASHI KIARA 小鳥遊キアラ
3D Showcase
TAKANASHI KIARA
Kiara 3D Showcase
SPARKS
Lyrics: KIRA / Composer: KIRA
Lying down on the floor late night
and you don't know, don't know, don't know what to do
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right,
if yes or no, don't know, don't know what to do
The storm hits hard and you're losing the way,
just take a chance and dance in the rain
Cause you've got the key, never throw it away,
don't forget, don't forget what I said
Get out of your head,
life is only what you make it,
you're gonna be okay
So go ahead and do it, do it,
if you want it let's get to it,
everybody's gonna know your name
Cause sparks like the flame through the dark of the night,
until today, don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
So don't be afraid, trust your heart,
keep your head in the game, keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
Gotta make it hot like a volcano, set a match and burn it up,
kick your feet against the table to the beat of your own drum
Sparks like...
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait
start a fire today.
Just go your own way.
Ain't looking back, take the fast lane now,
the driver's seat's strapped and it's gas poured out.
Going so fast and it shouldn't be allowed,
that's how we like it.
You heard what I said.
Get out of your head,
life is only what you make it,
you're gonna be okay.
So take a step and move it, move it,
unless you try you won't get through it,
everybody's gonna know your name.
Cuz sparks light the flame,
turn the dark of the night into day.
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way.
Don't be afraid,
trust your heart, keep your head in the game.
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid.
Let go of the past tonight,
choose the future only you define.
Even when the flames burn too bright,
you're alive, from the ashes you rise!
Cuz sparks...
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way.
Don't be afraid,
trust your heart, keep your head in the game.
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid.
Gotta make it hot like a volcano,
strike a match and burn it!
Start a fire today.
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way,
higher!
Kikeriki!
Hi everybody!
My voice, it works! It's working! Ah!
Hi KFP! Oh wait, wait, wait.
You have so much to react to, you have me to react to,
but you have this place to react to, right?
Oh my god!
Yes, we started with a banger, we started with Sparks.
One of your favorites, I think, right?
Same for me!
Kikeriki! みなさん、おはようございます！
Kikeriki! Good morning, everyone!
Yay!
It's Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English 1st Generation Myth. Yeah!
It's real! Oh my god! Yes, this is KFP!
Whoa! So many details! We shall look around. Ooh!
Hi! Oh, what's your name?
Harry? Harry, oh, nice to meet you, Harry.
How you doing today? What are you eating?
Oh, he's eating the Yagoo Burger!
Which is also on the menu up there, yeah!
And also the chicken bucket. Oh my god!
How you eating so much alone?
I can't even relate. He's eating way too much.
Two pieces of fries, Yagoo Burger, a shake probably, Oreo shake...
and the chicken bucket! Damn!
Ooh, I'm also getting hungry, hungry!
Let's look around a bit more.
We have the menus up there.
Inspired by, of course, the real KFC menu,
cuz this is the real deal.
There's hot dogs, hamburgers, Smart...
What the hell is a Smart Burger? I don't know.
Who decided on that one? I don't know anything about the Smart Burger.
Do I get smart if I eat that?
And we have the Phoenix Burger, of course.
Yagoo Burger apparently is black, I didn't know about that.
So much good-looking stuff!
And we have a kitchen in the back. Everything! Yay!
It's so cheap! I think it's cheap.
Let's say hi to Jimmy who just hatched again.
Jimmy!
People always worry about you, Jimmy.
How you doing? You're alive again! Yay!
You know, I ate you recently, so I felt like
you deserved to be reborn. Jimmy!
Look at my sweet boy...
Yes, our too cute little boy.
Look at him! Look at him!
Look! Such a good boy. Oh!
He's in his uniform. He's ready to... uh...
...work right as he has been hatched immediately.
He wants to get to work. He's frightened?
He's not frightened.
怖くないよね？
You're not scared, are you?
You're not scared. Yes, yes.
Actually he can, I think he can walk a little bit.
動けるんだっけ？
Can he move?
I think he can walk.
Let's go! Let's go, Jimmy. Let's go to work.
Let's go to work, Jimmy. He's so cute!
Okay. I pick you up because you're so baby in your heart.
Blink twice if you need help.
No, he cannot blink.
He's incapable of blinking. Hmm.
Franzie, don't say that. Well, actually...
...he's not the only one, right? There's more people working here.
もっといるよね？
There are more, right?
店員さん！
Employees!
Where's all the others?
Where are you guys? どこ...？
Where are you guys? Where...?
Oh my god! So many! So many!
You're ready for your shift?
Hi! Hi! Oh! Hi, hi! Oh!
So many KFP, maybe some new ones, some old ones.
Wow!
わあ、いっぱい来てくれてる。
Wow, so many have come.
仕事が始まったからね。
Because work has started.
Yeah, you're ready. Me too!
Ha!
Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy, this is... imagine this is you guys.
It might be Jimmy but just imagine it's you.
Osho, osho, osho.
So proud of you, so proud. Ready for your shift?
Well, actually, I think there is more.
Okay, bye-bye, go get to work, go get to work.
Hush, go get to work.
I'm gonna go get to work too.
(Humming) Tututututu...
Hi!
And welcome to KFP!
いらっしゃいませ！
Welcome!
Uh, smiles are for free, I guess.
スマイルは無料です。
Smiles are for free.
Tehe, tehe. Hmm, so we have a register...
...so I can, you know, take your change... or not,
I take your money, I give you change.
Here, five cents, there you go. はい、どうぞ。
Here, five cents, there you go. Here you go.
Hmm, and then... (bell rings) Ding ding ding ding!
Don't do that on me, okay? Just don't do that.
Be quiet. Don't ding-ding-ding-ding me.
No Karens allowed either, no, no.
Only good customers and good employees.
Yeah, and then up here, I already showed you the menus,
in the back there's menus, the kitchen working hard.
Are you working hard or hardly working? What was that?
How do you say that? (Laughs)
I could also go back there, but not right now, not right now.
I think we should play a game, okay? Alright, alright.
We're gonna play the game.
Love is just a game, I can't complain, I do the same. Oh!
Well, actually, no, no, no, not a game.
It's real business. It's the real stuff.
I am Tenchou after all. So, I think we need to prove it,
'cause you guys sometimes doubt me, right? No doubting allowed.
I have only best ingredients prepared.
We have some chicken, the famous one! Ooh!
(Chomp noises)
Om-nom-nom-nom. Om-nom-nom-nom.
Oh, that's the good stuff. It's perfectly seasoned,
perfectly crispy, as it should be. We have the bucket!
Ooh! The KFP bucket! Which... is it still an emote?
If it's still an emote, you guys gotta post it,
but... did I take it down?
It at least used to be a chat emote for a long time.
Hmm, I'm not sure. Is it gone? It's not?
Ah! I had to get rid of it. Oopsie, well, imagine.
And then we have some ingredients. We have the tomatoes,
some salad, pickles, and we have cheese with... um... onions.
And we have several patties. And now this is the difficult part
because there's three pieces of bread. We have the top one,
the middle one, and the... the bottom one.
I've never had a burger before which has a middle part
because I know I can't eat it alone. Oh, well, well, well.
Before we play the game, can I drink some water?
水飲んでもいいかな？ちょっと待って。
Can I drink some water? Wait a moment.
Okay, okay, okay. I think, thank you, thank you.
I'm back. Okay. I'm ready to play the game.
Hydration, yay! So... ah, not, of course not a game...
This is real, real work.
It's called... uh, what's it called?
配膳ゲームもやりましょう。
Let's do the serving game too.
Serving game - 配膳ゲーム -
Serving game - Food Service Game -
Serving game!
Yay!
Okay, what does that entail? I think you can guess...
...by looking at the stuff.
I'm going to be looking at the screen to see...
...what I have to make for the customer.
And then I'll make it, and we'll see if it's right.
But I have to remember it.
Will my memory hold up?
さて、どうでしょう？
Well, how will it go?
All right, figure it out.
Bring it on, baby! Bring it on!
Bring it on! Bring it on!
かかってこい！
Bring it on!
スタート！
Start!
Bottom, patty, middle... No!
What? What? Okay, I think I have to...
...freestyle some of this.
I think it was another patty, maybe.
And then some... something green.
But not all of this.
I don't remember!
And then look at that.
I don't know.
I'm not sure about this one.
合ってるかな？
Is it correct?
え？
What?
It was almost right. It was just...
...this, this one.
こっちだった。
It was this one.
This would have been the right... yeah.
あー、やっちゃった！
Ah, I messed up!
But it's not fair! It's not fair!
One more, one more, one more.
Let's put it back.
And then we'll do the next one.
All right, this time, this time... This was warmup. Okay.
Round two! Go!
Can I already start? But I don't...
Eh? Oh, I really don't remember.
I'm so nervous. You can't do this to me.
I think there was like at least one chicken in there.
え？わかんない、わかんない。
What? I don't know, I don't know.
I think I chose the wrong one.
Cause that was not the top one.
I mean, who knows what they do to bamboozle me.
No way! No way, no way!
なんか違うような...
Something feels wrong...
I'm nervous!
Give me a break, please.
Well, I don't know, so let's just go with this.
違うだろう。
It's wrong, right?
I don't know! Okay.
Yeah, the real thing is... え？待って。
Yeah, the real thing is... What? Wait.
How was I even supposed to build that?
Like, it's impossible. 無理でしょ。
Like, it's impossible. It's impossible, right?
You're making me create things that are not even possible.
I'm so angry I have to go drink some tea.
ちょっと待って。
Wait a second.
And we have one more round, I think.
Okay, let me take this apart.
Angry tea. What the...
Okay, let's not swear in my big, big 3D stream.
Let's try.
It's probably just going to get more difficult from this on, right?
もっと難しくなるよね。
It'll get even more difficult, right?
Round three, please!
スタート！
Start!
Bread, salad, bread, meat...
...chicken, meat, bread. Okay.
Bread, if I say that out loud, I think I remember.
Bread, salad...
Which one?
Bread, salad... I'll just go with this one.
Because I think I would have said cheese if it was the other one, right?
Bread, salad, bread, meat...
...chicken, meat.
If I get this right, you guys invite me for a burger, right?
Ah, 順番が曖昧ですけど。
Ah, the order is a bit vague, but...
I think you're not, maybe not sure what order this is, but...
I'll go with this! これにします。
I'll go with this! I'll go with this one.
これにします。
I'll go with this one.
お願いします！
Please!
No! No!
No, what was it?
Ya ya ya ya ya! No, そもそも...
Ya ya ya ya ya! No, in the first place...
そもそも...
To begin with...
Not even cheese in the picture,
how am I supposed to remember that?
Cheese is ないぞ! 画像!
There's no cheese! In the picture!
What? But besides that I was right.
それ以外は合ってた?
So besides that, I was correct?
さすが。
As expected.
This is weak!
No, that's really weak though.
嘘でしょ!
No way!
Well, I mean... in the end, this is your job.
This is your job. Not my job.
I am just here to observe, that's my job. Okay?
Well... so, I think it's better
if I just do mostly idol work
and dancing and singing, right?
Mainly...
踊る方向でいきます。
I'll go in the direction of dancing.
And you guys do the work, okay?
Well then, with that... next song!
Let's turn this place into a disco!
I'm tired of the same song
every day like it's on repeat
I need a risky break down
oh honey the night is calling
Don't need a steady simple melody
can you make it a bit unnatural
Take me away like it's just the two of us
I'm ready
Do you feel the music baby?
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat get me dancing
feel it rush through me
Let this music take over me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
Lately I'm dancing alone
so robotic so emotionless
But then I see you across the dance floor
so now honey follow me
I need a brilliant red hot melody
something to keep me up all night
Don't look away now it's just the two of us
I'm ready
Do you feel the music baby?
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
moving my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat get me dancing
feel it rush through me
この心の音を　合わせてよ Follow my heartbeat
Sync with the sound of this heart, follow my heartbeat
バダバダバダバビバ　聴かせてあげる
Ba-da-ba-da-ba-da-ba-bi-ba, I'll let you hear it
心のバタバタバティ　合わせて Follow my heartbeat
The flutter in my heart, sync it up, follow my heartbeat
Crazy for your rhythm
I'm in a trance with the way that you're moving
You got me shining glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild
Don't care who's watching us so baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light come alive
moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat get me dancing
feel it rush through me
I don't need no drinks tonight
give me that beat get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
baby can we dance until the daylight
Crazy about this sound I'm making with you
Yay! I wasn't muted! That was on purpose.
That was a transition, guys!
Like a commercial, yeah!
Did you enjoy the night at my own personal disco, hmm?
Basically, it was like, as you guys were saying it in the chat, I think.
But basically you get food and you get a performance.
Is there something like this already existing?
If not, then absolute genius.
And even if, then still genius, right? Yeah.
Yeah, that was like a disco ball, and the floor was disco, everything was disco!
Ten out of ten establishment!
Thank you, thank you, please vote ten out of ten for KFP, and come back, okay?
And actually, you know what, that's not a choice anyway.
Hi, Callie! "Studio Movie Grill"? What?
What does that mean?
Anyway... Callie! Callie!
Speaking of Callie, I think I'm gonna maybe need to talk to her personally, and actually all of the Myth members.
Shall we talk to them? Yay!
Moshi moshi! Purupurupurupuru...
Gachan!
Hi!
Hey!
Hello!
O-denwa... Oh, I missed the chance!
Kiara!
I was gonna pull the voicemail prank.
Whu-? No! No voicemail! No!
You're really here right now, right?
Hi!
I'm for real.
For real!
Congratulations, Kiwawa!
Thank you!
Really quickly, let's do introduction here.
This one is?
Amelia!
And this one is?
Ina'nis!
Wah!
And this one is?
Gura!
Gubugubugubugubu...
And this one is?
Ina'nis!
Hum hum hum...
And this one is?
Mori!
Exactly!
Kiwawa! Hi! I love you!
Out of these ones, this one, this Tako, already had her reveal.
The rest are to come!
I did! I'm free!
I'm really nervous right now, but you girls being here helps me a little bit.
Hehe! Have fun! It only happens once!
It does only happen once, yeah.
Finally! You are amazing so far, Kiara!
Oh, thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
Well, um, there's actually a hashtag up there, right?
#Kiara3DParty! And with that, if you guys were wondering what should we tweet...
Well, how about some screenshots? And I'm gonna give you guys...
I already posted some!
Wait, you mean the hashtag is #Kiara3DParty?
Yes! You got it right!
Yes, yes, that's it, that's it, that's exactly it!
I should type it into Twitter sixty times to make sure it's right.
That's it, that's exactly it, yeah, you got it right! You heard exactly.
But in order to take some great screenshots, I think we need your help, my dear Myth members.
So, are you ready to, you know, do some stuff with me?
I've been waiting!
Ready, Kiara!
Okay, let's start with Ame! Ametori!
Kiara-Kiara... can I get a... Kiara-Kiara... can I get a...
Can I get the Smart Burger set and the large fries and...
No! No! Not now!
You gotta get it yourself! If you want some food, you gotta go yourself!
Oh, I can go back there? I have permission?
Hmm... yeah, if it's you, okay!
Okay, my- my pose is the... the fetal position.
Fetal?
Did I hear correctly? Fetal position?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You want me to become baboo baboo baboo...
...feet?
Baboo Kiara!
Wait, is it fetal or feet-us?
I said it's like a baby, right?
Is that what you meant?
Baboo baboo baboo baboo baboo...
That's just, that's just taking a nap.
Wait, that's not a fetal position.
I guess it's more like... more closer?
That's close enough.
Like rocking back and forth, like having an existential crisis.
Oh, it's also, you also get the snail.
It's a snail!
Snail!
We can redo it as snail!
Yeah, snail!
Snail! I do!
And snail!
Oh... oh... Oh, look at her!
Yeah! NG, NG!
I think that's it.
Oh, you know the Chikens want that. Just kidding.
I think Ame has too crazy ideas.
Gura, can you give me something that's more safe for Twitter, please?
Yo. Okay.
I would like you to...
give me a pose that would entice me to buy all of the chicken in your establishment.
Entice you?
Ooh, entice you to buy all of the chicken.
Oh, okay. I guess it's not that kind of chicken.
Okay, okay, let's bring out the chicken! Tada!
Ooh, yum yums! All right, all right.
Entice you... Entice you...
Ooh, mmm... yum yum yum...
Mmm, this looks so delicious.
Mmm, yum yum yum yum yum.
Come closer.
How is that?
Doesn't it smell nice?
Just for you, fresh chicken straight out of the kitchen.
Mmm. Mwah.
Maybe I should stand here.
On the Phoenix! Yum yum yum yum yum.
Beautiful.
How's that? Is that enticing?
You feel like buying some?
I'm drooling.
I'm just, I've just thought about it.
How about the bucket?
I've come broke.
Okay, I'll throw in the bucket too. Throw in the bucket!
Bucket, bucket! Throw in the bucket!
Shall we throw in the family pack? Let's throw it all in.
The family pack! Cute!
I'll take two.
Two? Ooh, but there's like... there's like 12 pieces in there.
Can I get the combo?
The combo! Co-co-co-combo! Yes, number 9, please.
You can have everything for free today! It's on me!
The extra bucket! For free! For free!
Free? What a deal!
What a deal!
Oh, speaking of Ina.
Ina, what do you want from me?
Oh, hmm... what do I want? What do I want?
Is it possible to maybe...
unleash the special thing on your belt to...
you know, maybe perhaps take out your weapon?
Okay! Let me just drink some water real quick.
We've got violence here.
Let's go violence.
What's she doing?
Ah, hitting the griddy.
I'll go get my sword and my shield!
We got biscuits here. Stab me!
Tada! Sword and shield! Some biscuits!
Whoa! Powerful!
Hyah! Hyah!
Okay, watch out for the camera!
Oh, cute! This is a familiar scene.
We saw it already today.
Hyah! Hyah! Cute!
Oh no! All right, Kiara.
She's so feisty.
Now I want you to take your sword and lick it.
Huh? No, actually... okay.
Licking is okay too, but I'll one-up you.
How about, you know, the sword-eating thing?
Surely I can do that! Do it, do it!
A trick! Yeah, let's go! She totally ate it!
Whoa! Let's go! For the clout!
For the clout! Ollie, is that you?
Oh my god! I thought I saw Ollie for a second.
Must have been my imagination.
Never mind. You know, I think that was already too...
...like, you know, the camera that went down my throat yesterday.
That's enough.
It's a bit sensitive right now, okay?
But for serious, for real, for real.
I would like you to make the letters K, F, and P...
...using a way with my stuff. Okay.
K-F-P? Yeah.
Okay. K...
K! Ah, wrong side.
K! F! and P!
Okay, I'll take it.
There it is! Okay, last but not least.
Calli, what do you got?
Yeah, I want to order some chicken, some chicken legs.
Um, I want to see those chicken legs...
...trying to balance in the cutest idle pose that you can for the longest time.
Balance? So one leg up?
One leg. Okay, on one chicken leg.
Here we go!
Ready, go!
Let's go. So, we gotta talk about something...
Kiara, idol pose!
There we go!
Can I do it while doing this?
Sure thing. Sure thing.
Have you ever been to Medieval Times before?
Medieval Times?
Yes!
Why do you ask that?
Yeah, that's what I was thinking when you said "dinner and a show" besides Studio Movie Grill. Yeah.
Wait, you don't mean the medieval times...
...like many thousand years ago?
You mean like there's a place like that?
No, there's a place called Medieval...
Oh, of course you've been to the Medieval...
No, we mean the medieval times, right? Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I can do this forever, Calli!
Oh my god. Well, stick your...
Okay, you need to put your other foot up higher.
Higher?
It's too close to the ground.
Higher!
Pull it up, pull it up.
Yes, pull it up.
It's higher! It's cuter!
I gotta do this with one foot...
Higher, higher, higher!
Higher, higher, higher! You're on fire!
Let's go! Yeah, let's go!
Can she stay on one foot?
Ladies and gentlemen, let's find out!
I can!
Oh yeah, really good balance.
さすがアイドル！
As expected of an idol!
Incredible.
Alright, alright. She's too good at this.
Okay, you want to go ahead and do the chicken dance real quick?
Chicken dance! Okay.
Ta-da-da-da, ta-da-da-da, ta-da-da-da, ta-da!
No DMCA. No DMCA.
Oh, is that maybe free? Who knows?
I don't know, maybe.
We just... we just have to add in "HoloLive" in the middle.
Ta-da-da-da HoloLive!
Let's not risk it.
It's pretty good though.
I really don't know how that one works though.
I don't know. You do something... it's not just this.
Yeah, you like turn, you like do the hokey pokey...
...and you shake it all about, or something like that.
I hope that was enough for the screenshot game.
Hope you guys got some good ones. Did you?
I forgot.
You forgot?
I was too happy watching you, you know?
I took them with my eyes.
Don't worry, there will be more opportunities.
I'm sure chat took some. Or like a thousand. Two thousand.
You better put them on the internet #Kiara3DParty.
You mean #Kiara3DParty?
Is that what you said? #Kiara3DParty?
Yeah, that's exactly what I said.
I'm typing it into Google to check it... once, fifty times.
Is it correct? #Kiara3DParty?
That's it, that's it! Kiara 3D Party!
Sounds right to me.
Thank you so much for coming, girls!
No problem! Have fun!
Alright.
Okay, so wow... there is still more to come though.
Because these were my gen mates, right?
But I feel like I need something that's not cardboard.
How about we bring in some 3D guests!
Alright, but for that we have to change location!
Let's change! Whoo!
The Usual Room
友達は友達なんだ！
Lyrics: つんく / Composer: つんく
Friends Are Just Friends!
Lyrics: Tsunku / Composer: Tsunku
ねえ　友情って
古くなって　いいんだよ　My friend
Hey, it's okay
for friendship to grow old, my friend
そんなの続かないから Oh, my friend
That won't last, so oh my friend
自慢の彼をみんなに一度会わせたら
Once you introduce your proud boyfriend to everyone
あとは彼に尽くしなよ
After that, just devote yourself to him
お家事情はみんなとつるんで楽しい
Home life is fun hanging out with everyone
朝まで友情語り合ったりした
Talking about friendship until morning
でも一人二人と彼氏ができ始めたら
But when one or two start getting boyfriends
彼氏優先！
Boyfriends come first!
友達は友達なんだ
Friends are friends
気を使うくらい距離のある友なら意味ないよ
Friends you have to be careful around are meaningless
またそのうち語り合おうぞ
Let's talk again sometime
そのうちにはワイワイとみんなで会えるだろう
Sometime soon, we'll all be able to meet and have fun
気なんか使わない
I won't be careful
このままでいたいな
I want to stay like this
告られそうになりゃすぐに教えなよ Oh my friend
If you think someone's gonna confess, tell me right away Oh my friend
愚痴くらい聞いてあげるよ Oh my friend
I'll at least listen to your complaints Oh my friend
でも中途半端にしゃしゃり出ないよ
But I won't interfere half-heartedly
もっと複雑になるし
It'll just get more complicated
もし終わった恋バナみんなでキチンと料理
If a romance ends, let's process it properly together
うまい笑い話に変えてあげるさ
And turn it into a good funny story
そのうちいつも以上にノリを掴みができるはずさ
Sometime soon, we should be able to get into the groove even more
友達は友達なんだ
Friends are friends
どんな時も元の位置に戻れる
We can return to our original positions anytime
それが友
That's what friends are
とは言え年一度くらい
Having said that, maybe about once a year
昼でもいいランチして情報交換したいな
Let's have lunch, even during the day, and exchange info
ドタキャンもありで
Last-minute cancellations are okay too
このままでいたいな
I want to stay like this
友達は友達なんだ
Friends are friends
気を使うくらい距離のある友なら意味ないよ
Friends you have to be careful around are meaningless
友達は友達なんだ
Friends are friends
どんな時も元の位置に戻れる
We can return to our original positions anytime
それが友
That's what friends are
とは言え年一度くらい
Having said that, maybe about once a year
昼でもいいランチして情報交換したいな
Let's have lunch, even during the day, and exchange info
ドタキャンもありで
Last-minute cancellations are okay too
このままでいたいな
I want to stay like this
よっしゃー！
All right!
キアラ！
Kiara!
セレブレート！セレブレート！
Celebrate! Celebrate!
スバル様、落ち着け、落ち着け。
Subaru-sama, calm down, calm down.
落ち着くんだ。
Calm down.
OK!
ヒカニキ！
Hikaniki!
紹介してください。
Please introduce yourself.
This is the legendary Subaru. どうぞ。
This is the legendary Subaru. Go ahead.
I introduce!
My name is Subaru!
Hololive Generation Second!
Whoa!
Nice to meet you! Yeah!
やっと、
Finally,
Finally, we're together!
Yeah!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
うん。
Yeah.
今日お披露目。
Today's the showcase.
パーフェクト 3D お披露目。
Perfect 3D Showcase.
Yeah!
Yes, today my ohirome,
my showcase.
どう？
How is it?
Showcase...
まあね。
Well.
Showcase...
Your body is perfect!
Oh!
Especially,
your hip!
I know my butt!
Oh!
Oh my God!
Look at that butt! Oh!
Yes, yes!
Yes-taro!
え、でも、あの、キアラのボディを例えるとどんな感じ？
Hey, but, how would you describe Kiara's body?
うーん...
Hmm...
例えると、
If I were to describe it,
Kiara body is like fruit!
Beautiful fruit!
Oh!
Which fruit?
どの果物？
デリシャスアップル！
Delicious Apple!
アップル！
Apple!
アップル！アップル！
Apple! Apple!
違う、違う、違う。
Wait, wait, wait.
え？ペア、ペアかな？ペア。
Huh? A pear, maybe? A pear.
あ、洋梨！洋梨！
Ah, European pear! European pear!
そうそうそうそう。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
洋梨！
European pear!
洋梨！洋梨！
European pear! European pear!
えっと、スバル先輩。
And then, Subaru-senpai.
何何？やりたい！
What, what? I want to do it!
I want to do something.
Okay!
あ、でも逆、逆、逆。
Ah, but reverse, reverse, reverse.
So, you probably have seen it before.
The famous Suba-dance!
しゅばだ！
Suba-dance!
しゅばダンス！
Okay!
So, "Hey Ya"っていう曲、今流せないけど。
So, the song "Hey Ya", we can't play it right now,
We can't play the song.
But!
I want to do it, and then you guys put it together, please.
You could just put the song on there, alright? Okay.
Okay, let's go! Suba-dance!
はい、せーの！
Alright, here we go!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
チャン、チャン、チャン、チャン、チャン、チャン！
Chan, chan, chan, chan, chan, chan!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
チャン、チャン、チャン、チャン、チャン、チャン！
Chan, chan, chan, chan, chan, chan!
1, 2... 違う、逆だ！
1, 2... wait, it's backwards!
逆だ！いつも逆だ！
It's backwards! It's always backwards!
でも間に1回できたから、OKかな？
But we got it right once in the middle, so it's fine?
Alright!
イェーイ！しゅばだ！
Yay! Suba-dance!
いいね、いいね。いいでしょう。
Nice, nice. Looking good.
あの曲、いっぱい聴いてほしい。スバル先輩にも一回歌ってほしい。
I want people to listen to that song a lot.
I want to sing it with Subaru-senpai once.
しゅばだ？しゅばダンスの歌？
Suba-dance? The Suba-dance song?
Hey Ya?
そう。
Yeah.
OK、あの…
OK, well...
歌ってほしい。
I want to sing it.
Next time, you must send my Discord.
Next time, you must send to my Discord.
OK, OK! I will send.
I will send after this, after.
OK, but after this...
After this...
実は、この後もゲストがいる！
Actually, there's another guest after this too!
おー、バッ！
Oh, but!
キアラ！
Kiara!
うん。
Yeah.
I have a question.
お、何何何？
Oh, what is it?
Why this song?
Why do you choose this song?
Why did you choose this song?
あ、そっか！
Oh, right!
Yes, I forgot!
忘れてた。ごめん、あーまち。
I forgot, sorry. Oh wait.
もう、先輩頼れる！
Man, senpai is so reliable!
Thank you, senpai.
まあ、そのソング、この曲…
Well, that song, this song...
そのソング？そのソング？
"Sono song"? "Sono song"?
まあ、友達は友達なんだ。
Well, friends are friends.
そう！
Yeah!
Why?
It's a song from my favorite idol group,
Berryz工房。私、ベリヲタなんで。
Berryz Kobo. I'm a "Berry-ota" (Berryz fan).
そう。
Yeah.
で、一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう。
So, thank you for singing it with me.
ベリヲタ、ベリヲタ。
Berry-ota, Berry-ota.
ベリヲタとして、めっちゃ嬉しかった！
As a Berry-ota, I'm so happy!
You are... because you are otaku.
Yes, yes, yes!
そういうことなの？
Is that how it is?
ね、まあ、あと歌詞も、めちゃくちゃ合うなと思ったし。
Well, also the lyrics, I thought they really fit us.
Yeah.
あと、曲のなんか元気さもスバル先輩には合うかなと思ったから、
And also, the energy of the song,
I thought it would suit Subaru-senpai well,
この曲選んだんです。
that's why I chose this song.
Powerful song!
Yeah!
元気ソング！
Energy song!
おおー！サンキュー！
Ohh! Thank you!
Thank you too!
じゃあ、友達だから友達っぽく帰りますか？
Well, we're friends, so shall we go back like friends?
ハハハ！
Hahaha!
今まで友達じゃないみたい… We are friends!
It's like we weren't friends until now... We are friends!
Okay!
ホロバード！ホロバード！
Holo-bird! Holo-bird!
ホロバード！
Holo-bird!
Okay!
じゃあ、別のとこに行くから。移動！
Well, we're going somewhere else now. Let's go!
Let's go!
Let's go!!!
流れ星...
A shooting star...
La la la...
流れ星 願い事込めれば君に伝わるの
A shooting star, if I put a wish in it, will it reach you?
この街は孤独なほど景色に溶け込んでく
This city melts into the scenery as it becomes lonelier
涙星 頬に流れてる 私の涙よ
Tear stars, they're flowing down my cheeks, these are my tears
悔しくて泣くんじゃない 生きてる証なんだよ
I'm not crying out of frustration, it's proof that I'm alive
胸を癒すような このメロディ
This melody that seems to heal my heart
ひとり...
Alone...
だけど...
But...
なぜか...
For some reason...
ひとり...
Alone...
…じゃないような気分になれる
...I can feel like I'm not...
悲しきヘブン 心が乾くけど
Sad Heaven, though my heart is dry
たった一つ 夢があるだけで
Just having one dream
私はそれで十分
is enough for me
セブンス・ヘブン いつかはたどりつく
Seventh Heaven, I'll reach it someday
この果てなき 空を行けば
Travelling through this endless sky
迷うこともあるだろう
I might get lost sometimes
流れ星 都会じゃ見えない
Shooting stars, unseen in the city
現実の中で
within this reality
今夜だけ 一人じゃない
Just for tonight, I feel like
そんな感じがしてる
I'm not alone
ため息で 言葉にならない
There are moments when sighs
瞬間もあるが
take the place of words
寂しくて 震えていた
I feel nostalgic for those days when
あの頃が懐かしいな
I was lonely and trembling
そうさ 過去なんて どうでもいい
That's right, the past doesn't matter
明日になれば きっと
When tomorrow comes, surely...
まぶしい光 この手に入る
...dazzling light will be in my hands
悲しきヘブン 傷んだ翼でも
Sad Heaven, even with damaged wings
それが叶うことを 信じなきゃ
It's meaningless if I don't believe
意味がない
it will come true
セブンス・ヘブン 碧いこの星から
Seventh Heaven, from this blue planet
遠きゴール 目指すだけさ
Just aiming for a distant goal
好きなことなら続く
I'll keep going if it's something I love
悲しきヘブン 心が乾くけど
Sad Heaven, though my heart is dry
たった一つ 夢があるだけで
Just having one dream
私はそれで十分
is enough for me
セブンス・ヘブン いつかはたどりつく
Seventh Heaven, I'll reach it someday
この果てなき 空を行けば
Travelling through this endless sky
迷うこともあるだろう
I might get lost sometimes
流れ星 願いを込めれば 君に伝わるの
If I wish upon a shooting star, will it reach you?
この街は 孤独だけど
This city is lonely, but it's the city
君と出会えた街だから
where I met you
（歓声と拍手）
(Cheering and applause)
キキキ！
Ki-ki-ki!
こんねね！こんねね！
Kon-nene! Kon-nene!
二人目のゲスト、ねねち！
My second guest, Nene-chi!
桃鈴ねねでーす！
I'm Momosuzu Nene!
踊ったな！
We danced!
できたね！
We did it!
いいよ！かっこいい！
Nice! So cool!
かっこいいでしょ！
We're cool, right?
英語自己紹介できる？
Can you introduce yourself in English?
ホロライブ五期生、
Hololive Fifth Generation,
ねね、桃鈴ねね！イェーイ！
Nene, Momosuzu Nene! Yay!
うちの自己紹介もいらないよね。
I don't need to introduce myself, right?
So actually, you guys probably know,
together, people call us a name, which is "Orenzu".
「おれんず」って呼ばれてるね、うちら。
We're called "Orenzu", right?
呼ばれてる。
We are.
呼ばれてるっていうか…
Well, "called" or...
うちらが先に名乗り出したから。
because we started calling ourselves that first.
そう、名乗り出したから。
Yeah, because we named ourselves.
So thank you for calling us "Orenzu".
I knew that if I had to call a guest for my show,
ゲスト呼ぶんだったら、うちの中で絶対的にねねち呼ぶしかないと思ってた。
I thought it absolutely had to be Nene-chi.
I had to call you!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
So this is basically the first time that Orenzu is dancing together in 3D.
初めてだね。
It's the first time.
初めて。
First time.
かわいいよ、キアラちゃん！かわいいよ！
You're so cute, Kiara-chan! So cute!
ねねちの方がかわいい！
Nene-chi is cuter!
あ、やだやだやだ！
Oh, stop it!
ま、ということで、初めての「おれんず」ということで…
So, since it's the first Orenzu collab...
やっぱりお互いどっちもアイドル大好きでしょ？
We both love idols, right?
I love idols. You love idols. We are idols.
So I want to create some kind of idol-poi greeting, 挨拶作りたい。
So I want to create some kind of idol-like greeting.
ありがとう！オレンジだよね？
Thanks! It's orange, right?
そうね、それをずっとやる。
That's right, we'll keep doing that.
やり続ける。オケ、オケ。わかった。
Keep doing it. Okay, okay. Got it.
ここ、じゃ大事だね、これ。オケ。
This part is important then. Okay.
まぁオレンジデイズということで、どうする？
Well, since we're Orange Days, what should we do?
うーん、なんかテーマみたいな。オレンジのテーマ。
Umm, like a theme. An orange theme.
オレンジでしょ？オレンジで！オレンジ、オレンジ！
Orange, right? With orange! Orange, orange!
うーん、なんかこうグローバルな感じがいいな。はい、はい。
Umm, I'd like a global feel. Yes, yes.
Global, international. Okay.
So, how about we make the whole world orange?
おぉ、いいね！世界を...
Oh, nice! The world...
オレンジ色に染め上げるとか、染めていくとかどう？
...how about "dye it all in orange" or "keep dyeing it"?
おんじゃ、染めちゃうにしよう。染めちゃうで。オケ、オケ。
Then, let's go with "sometchau". "Sometchau" it is. Okay, okay.
おんじゃ動きも。動き。We need some movement.
Then, the movement too. Movement. We need some movement.
え、え、世界観出して。世界... 世界を...
Um, um, give it a world-view. World... The world...
オレンジ色に...
...in orange color...
染めちゃう！で！
...sometchau! And!
オレンジデイズ！いいね！オレンジデイズ！
Orange Days! Nice! Orange Days!
あ、オケ。これでいく？決まった。もう一回やってみよう。ちゃんと。もう一回。正式に。はい。
Ah, okay. Shall we go with this? It's decided. Let's try it again. Properly. One more time. Officially. Yes.
世界を...
The world...
オレンジ色に...
...in orange color...
染めちゃう！
...sometchau!
オレンジデイズ！わっちまた染めちゃうと言ったよ。まぁいいよ、いいよ。
Orange Days! I said "sometchau" again. Well, it's fine, it's fine.
オケ。これずっとやるのか、今後。
Okay. Are we going to keep doing this from now on?
そうやる。忘れちゃいけない。Don't forget, this is our official greeting now.
We will. Mustn't forget. Don't forget, this is our official greeting now.
えー、じゃあもう一個。えー、let's talk about the song and our practice and all that.
Eh, then one more thing. Umm, let's talk about the song and our practice and all that.
この曲についてと練習について語ろう。まずね、Kanashiki Heaven is another Hello Project song.
Let's talk about this song and the practice. First of all, "Kanashiki Heaven" is another Hello Project song.
I love Hello Project. And this is from °C-ute, the idol group °C-uteね。
I love Hello Project. And this is from °C-ute, the idol group °C-ute.
あ、°C-uteね。好きだもんね。
Ah, °C-ute. You like them, don't you?
Yeah. And it's a very dramatic, sad song with a strong dance move, strong choreographyね。
Yeah. And it's a very dramatic, sad song with a strong dance move, strong choreography.
あの激しい振り付けだったね。そうなの。ヤバかったよ、もう。ただ、うちらは...
It was a really intense choreography, wasn't it? That's right. It was crazy. However, we...
二時間でできた。覚えました。Two hours. We had two hours of dance lessons together.
Finished in two hours. We learned it. Two hours. We had two hours of dance lessons together.
Yeah, the dance teacher was like, "Oh, you guys are learning it so quickly," she was happy.
ダンスの先生がね、早く覚えてと。ね、褒めてくれたんだ。すごい。
The dance teacher said we learned it quickly and... Right, she praised us. Amazing.
すごい早いって言われたよね。ね。うちもねっちとのダンス練習は楽だろうなと思って楽しみにした。
She said we were really fast, didn't she? I thought dance practice with Necchi would be easy and was looking forward to it.
え、本当？ね、うちもすごい楽しみにした。でもちょっと朝だったから...
Eh, really? Yeah, I was looking forward to it too. But it was a bit early in the morning, so...
朝じゃないから。Yeah, 昼過ぎてたよ。She's saying it was morning time so she was so tired...
It wasn't morning. Yeah, it was past noon. She's saying it was morning time so she was so tired...
...but it was way past morning, it was already noon time. ねねにとっては昼は朝。
...but it was way past morning, it was already noon time. For Nene, noon is morning.
なるほど。まぁうちもたまにそう。はい。え、苦労した振り付けとかある？
I see. Well, I'm like that sometimes too. Yes. Um, was there any choreography you struggled with?
この二番のこれね、この動きね。パンパンパン。
This part in the second verse, this movement. Bam-bam-bam.
それ難しいよね。タンタタン。早いから。で、ここが難しかった。タンタンタンタン。
That's difficult, isn't it? Tan-ta-tan. Because it's fast. And this part was difficult. Tan-tan-tan-tan.
早いから。ばぁ。できてるかな？あ、違う。早いからな。そう、ゆっくりやるとすごい綺麗にできるんだけど。
Because it's fast. Bam. I wonder if I'm doing it right? Ah, no. It's fast, you see. Yeah, if you do it slowly you can do it really beautifully.
大変だったけど、we did our best, it was fun, and I hope we can do more. 難しかったけど、もっとやりたい！
It was hard, but we did our best, it was fun, and I hope we can do more. It was difficult, but I want to do more!
やりたいやりたい！お願いしますお願いします！公式さんもお願いしますお願いします！オレンジをよろしく！
I want to, I want to! Please, please! Official staff, please, please! Please take care of Orange Days!
ということで、I'm gonna send off Nene-chi, so we're gonna change location. ねねちをとりあえず送り出す。
So, I'm gonna send off Nene-chi, so we're gonna change location. For now, I'll send Nene-chi off.
オケ。いってくるね！
Okay. I'm off!
バーン！Welcome back to KFP, guys!
Baan! Welcome back to KFP, guys!
I'm sorry, it's not over yet. I have something really important for you guys.
And that is... what could it be? What could it be? That's right, merchandise!
Okay. Let me introduce to you, I mean, you know there's burgers and all that...
...but this time, very special, time-limited offer for you guys. Tada!
It is the beautiful Hot Phoenix Thermo Bottle & Bottle Case Set.
Hot Phoenix Thermo Bottle & Bottle Case Set
That's right, it comes with like, kind of like a bag for the thermos bottle.
I already saw it in reality and it looks so good! Yay!
And of course, it's thermos, which means your hot drinks will stay hot and your cold drinks will stay cold!
Perfect! Genius! Oh my god.
...special 3D merchandise for this occasion.
And...
...there's something else that I want to tell you about.
Tomorrow!
Yes, tomorrow at 6 PM JST...
...my very first Hologra is coming out!
明日6時に出ます！
It's coming out at 6:00 tomorrow!
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
夜、夜の6時です。
In the evening, 6 PM.
Well, and of course tomorrow...
...is also the 3D debut of Calliope Mori.
So go check her out, okay?
It's TakaMori weekend! Yay!
So, besides that...
...I have one more song for you guys.
But we— I think we should change location.
Is that okay?
Change! Change!
Alright, there's one more stage I haven't shown you guys yet...
...which is the big Hololive English stage!
Let's go!
Ah, ah... That video!
I did not give the permission to show that video!
Why did you show that video?! Ahh!
I wasn't slacking, I was practicing!
Well, I am here on this beautiful EN stage right now...
...to perform one last song!
But before that, I want to say thank you guys so much...
...for waiting for such a long time.
Two and a half years, I think, roughly...
...until we got to this point, which is unusually long.
But yeah, we all were patient...
...and I think it was worth it.
I hope so! Was it worth it?
Well, I practiced really hard for this day.
And I tried really hard to fix my throat for this day.
So I hope you guys enjoyed it.
It was a very special day for me.
I was really nervous...
...but I hope I could show you all the beautiful parts...
...all the good things about Takanashi Kiara!
Yeah, let's do more in the future, okay?
Okay.
So with that, the last song...
DO U.
DO U
Produced by: KIRA / Written by: monii, Johnny / Lyrics by: monii, KIRA
I don't wanna stop it yet
Playin' Russian Roulette
Yeah boy as soon as I saw you I knew it
Baby it's you, oh ya, now / Got me love drunk I'm knocked...
...down
There's somethin' special about you
When I see you I know it's true
Oh ya now, gotta get ya, oh ya now
Now... now... now
If it ain't you baby then I'm done
(Yeah yeah oh girl, you know it!)
I just can't resist you
Your eyes are like a spell that I can't break through
You're captivating me
But I don't know baby
And in the end you'll let me go
That's just what we do...
Love, hate, all the same / If you know, play the game
I'm all locked up-up inside
No I can't fight the feeling and I won't try
All the same / If you know, play the game
Baby you decide
If you want me then shout it out right now!
Love is just a game / I can't complain...
...I do the same, oh!
DO U? DO U?
Say you do feel the same
Spark me like a flame
I know I'll never be the same, oh!
DO U? DO U?
In the end love's just all a game
Don't ever let yourself fall in, you got it?
'Cause love's just like a toxin
The way pain is so common
No problem, I can't solve it!
Save me, I'm just a fool in love
Know that this more than a crush
So you can't save me
I'm in too deep
And I love the rush, yeah
I just can't resist you
Your eyes are like a spell
that I can't break through
And that should scare me
But I don't know baby
You're captivating me
And in the end you'll let me down
Love, hate, all the same
If you know, play the game
Locked up deep inside
No I can't fight the feeling and I won't try
All the same
If you know, play the game
Baby you decide
If you want me then shout it out right now!
Love is just a game, I can't complain
I do the same, oh!
DO U? DO U?
Say you do feel the same
Spark me like a flame
I know I'll never be the same, oh!
DO U? DO U?
In the end love's just all a game
Got me breathless, oh yeah
I'm by you night and day
How can somethin' so wrong
Be making me feel so right
Breakin' me down, down
Pick me up just like you do
I'm always coming back to you, you, you...
Love is just a game, I can't complain
I do the same, oh!
DO U? DO U?
Say you do feel the same
Spark me like a flame
I know I'll never be the same, oh!
DO U? DO U?
In the end love's just all a game
Love is just a game we play
Love, hate, trust then betray
DO U? DO U?
You do feel the same
Love is just a game we play
Love, hate, trust then betray
DO U? DO U?
In the end love's just all a game...
Hey. Uh-huh. Uh-huh.