(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D Showcase
#Mori3D
Am frog.
ほっ！皆さん！調子どうですか？
Ho! Everyone! How are you doing?
How are you?!
It's time!
It's time, it's time, it's time, it's time, it's time!
Everybody, hello!
I'm Mori Calliope from hololive English -Myth-,
and welcome to the Underworld!
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
I have many things to show you!
Check it out!
Check out my stage!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
Check it out, look at the skulls with the wings in the background,
and oh man, this...
this is the best venue in the Underworld.
You know it.
You know that this is the place to be.
Check it out.
Hey, look at that!
Look at all the Dead Beats in the crowd swinging the lights.
They're like "woo-woo-woo-woo-woo"!
And it's on fire!
Wow! すごいな！ Check out the big speakers too.
Wow! It's amazing! Check out the big speakers too.
Yo, that's actually dope. Thanks, glad you think so.
That's me! Correct, that is you.
And you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you.
And you, and you. That's kind of hot, not gonna lie.
Correct, correct. It's a little hot in here, but we're about to make it hotter.
Because, guess what you guys, this, this before your eyes...
...is not just a regular place to chill. No, no, no, no, no.
We have performances. Performances, action, romance...
...maybe not romance, but lots of, lots of performances. So get ready.
And thank you for the many congratulations, you guys. All right.
Now, now, for the first performance I want to do...
...I have something special to show you.
Check it out. Oh, it's over here.
I gotta go grab... I gotta go grab it really quick. Hold on.
I'm getting it. It's now in my hand. Okay.
Just so you know, it's... it's in my hands now. Staff-san, staff-san, it's here.
The first song that we're singing today is Wanted, Wasted.
Let's go.
Wanted, Wasted
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh...
Lyrics by Takuya Yamanaka (THE ORAL CIGARETTES) / Yuki Tsujimura / Mori Calliope
Music/Arrangement by Takuya Yamanaka (THE ORAL CIGARETTES) / Yuki Tsujimura
Guess who's the reaper, turn it back around, going looking deep inside for the truth to exploit.
You know I smoke 'em, I smoke 'em, I smoke 'em, I dye 'em, I smoke 'em, drive me crazy, ah!
Wanted, Wasted, start looking twice, can't, can't stop falling down.
Tell me how mortals show you where the dirt is. One man's trash is another man's purpose.
Stay won't fly high, come tomorrow, fucking die. Stop trash, choking, why? Nothing I own's true mine.
I started... 愛の無い夢を見てるのは何故? Whoa-oh-oh...
I started... why am I having a dream without love? Whoa-oh-oh...
When I wanna be loved but I can't be seen.
変えたい現実も、泣き叫ぶ訳も、響き渡る...
Both the reality I want to change and the reason for crying out, they echo out...
やっちゃって、やっちゃって、やっちゃって、そのままずっと狂い咲いちゃって...
Do it, do it, do it, just like that, bloom madly forever...
聴いて売るギル、バッド・エンディング、縁から目出す悩み...
Hear and sell guilt, bad ending, worries emerging from the edge...
終わそう、そうあそ、そう、とっくに仕上げて頂戴。整合性、正々堂々、正義の名のもと...
Finish it, yeah, finish it already. Consistency, fair and square, in the name of justice...
下してやるも、ゲーム・メーカー、アンダーテイカー、脳天直下、喰らえ！
I'll strike it down, game maker, undertaker, straight to the brain, take this!
Oh-oh-oh, 響き、Mayday, Mayday...
Oh-oh-oh, echoing, Mayday, Mayday...
鳴らす...
Ring it...
聴こえないふりして逃げられると思ってんの？ クソ！
Do you think you can escape by pretending you can't hear? Shit!
Why am I having the dream? I started... 愛の無い夢を見てるのは何故? Whoa-oh-oh...
Why am I having the dream? I started... why am I having a dream without love? Whoa-oh-oh...
Where I wanna be loved but I can't be seen.
変えたい現実も、泣き叫ぶ訳も、響き渡る...
Both the reality I want to change and the reason for crying out, they echo out...
不埒な声で、喘ぐ声は、天国に近づく気がしてた。Alright.
With an outrageous voice, the gasping voice felt like it was approaching heaven. Alright.
本来の反逆、狂おしく舞い上がってしまえ！
Original rebellion, dance up madly!
Oh my God, Oh my God, Oh my God, Oh my God, Oh my God, Oh my God, Oh my God.
傷つけちゃって...
Getting hurt...
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh...
足りない、足りない、足りない、カルマ。
Not enough, not enough, not enough, karma.
Loading...
あぁ、もう絶対どうにかしておく魂。
Ah, the soul I'll definitely do something about.
I'm nothin' about this mess. I started... 愛の無い夢を見てるのは何故? Whoa-oh-oh...
I'm nothin' about this mess. I started... why am I having a dream without love? Whoa-oh-oh...
Where I wanna be loved but I can't be seen.
変えたい現実も、泣き叫ぶ訳も、響き渡る...
Both the reality I want to change and the reason for crying out, they echo out...
不埒な声で、喘ぐ声は、天国に近づく気がしてた。Alright.
With an outrageous voice, the gasping voice felt like it was approaching heaven. Alright.
本来の反逆、狂おしく舞い上がってしまえ！
Original rebellion, dance up madly!
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh...
足りない、足りない、足りない、足りない。
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough.
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh...
足りない、足りない、足りない、足りない。
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough.
Wanted, Wasted.
Thank you. Thank you so much everyone!
Whoo, look at them go. But it's not over yet.
Because now, I've got another song to sing.
This one's called NEZUMI Scheme.
Here we go.
NEZUMI Scheme
All right, all right! Hey! Hey!
English lyrics by Mori Calliope
Let's go! Come on everybody!
Music by FAKE TYPE.
Arranged by DYES IWASAKI / Japanese lyrics by TOPHAMHAT-KYO
Put your hands up! Yeah, yeah, hey!
That's my debt, came up the rat race, cat chasing dumb and fall, but the kingdom of swingdom is open to all.
Enter the game, it's a place to make a profit, rabbit swing is the thing now, more for you to scoff it.
Look, boys and girls...
Poison Hades, underrated girl born to hate it.
Shout out to any crazy people still in the empire.
Just wanna set fire, I'm wishing I went higher!
冷え切ったスピーカー
Chilled speakers
聞く耳なんてない奴ばかりだろ
Most people don't even listen
似て非なる自信、自惚れ
Confidence and hubris, similar but not the same
紙一重 恐れおののけ
The line is fine, be afraid of this
奢って、吹聴、自縛、困窮
Gilded, boastful, self-bound, destitute
逆に振って 張り倒して
Swing the other way, knock them down
ハロー Staff-san ok?
Hello staff-san? Step-up ok?
Step-up ok?
逆の目 逆の目
The other eye, the other eye
しゃらくせえ
Shut up your drivel.
所在無さそうね
Know your place.
ボロ儲けして 塗りがかった 綺麗なネズミ
You fake making cheddar, you rat!
香水 振りまいても 消えないわ その悪臭
No amount of perfume can kill the stench of your cheese.
What's it all for? You a skeptic?
Those opinions kind of septic.
You're my minions...
No, wait, my biggest fans! Internet business women drawing up ten plans.
Why you trying to pin me for a pyramid scheme?
I refuse to be a part of any derelict dreams.
Swipe over and hear the screams, and they say us...
...basically gotta get to saying those prayers.
転ばぬ先の杖
Better safe than sorry
持っちゃいない 向こう側のドア
I don't have it, the door on the other side
You've got nothing going for you!
似て非なる自信、自惚れ
Confidence and hubris, similar but not the same
紙一重 恐れおののけ
The line is fine, be afraid of this
奢って、吹聴、自縛、困窮
Gilded, boastful, self-bound, destitute
逆に振って 張り倒して
Swing the other way, knock them down
ハロー Staff-san ok? Step-up ok?
Hello staff-san? Step-up ok?
勘違いしてる奴らばかり うざい
Everyone's getting it wrong, it's annoying
決してあんたの方は向かない 秤
The scales will never tip in your direction
あんたの知らせは まだまだ臭い
Your information is still way too fishy
刈り取るまでもない 拙い話は Bye
Your petty stories aren't even worth reaping, bye
御山の天狗を 並べた鼻で笑お
Let's laugh at the 'Great Tengu of the Mountain' and their big noses
虎の威を借る 爆速できるならやってごらん
Borrowing the tiger's authority, try it if you can do it at top speed
全然足りない 其の走辞も頻くはならない
Not enough at all, even that rhetoric won't be frequent
驕るもの久しからず
Pride comes before a fall
似て非なる自信、自惚れ
Confidence and hubris, similar but not the same
紙一重 恐れおののけ
The line is fine, be afraid of this
Just a little cowardly, a girl alone
奢って、吹聴、自縛、困窮
Gilded, boastful, self-bound, destitute
逆に振って 張り倒して
Swing the other way, knock them down
ハロー Staff-san ok? Step-up ok?
Hello staff-san? Step-up ok?
逆の目 逆の目
The other eye, the other eye
しゃらくせえ
Shut up your drivel.
所在無さそうね
Know your place.
ボロ儲けして 塗りがかった 綺麗なネズミ
You fake making cheddar, you rat!
香水 振りまいても 消えないわ その悪臭
No amount of perfume can kill the stench of your cheese.
Thank you! Thank you very much everyone!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I take a bow. I take a bow.
Thanks so much! Go Calli, go!
Thank you very much!
Encore, encore, encore, right?
Encore, right? No encore right now.
I have something important to introduce to you.
My Dead Beat backup dancers, Gaikotsu-chan!
Hey, hey, Gaikotsu-chan!
めっちゃかわいい ガイコツちゃん
Super cute Gaikotsu-chan
so cute! Hey, hey!
Let's go, let's go, Dancer-san!
超かわいい、超かわいい！
Super cute, super cute!
めちゃめちゃいい感じ！
Feeling really, really good!
Look at Mr. and Mrs. Bones.
Wow, thank you so much for coming!
See you later! Bye-bye!
いいね！
Nice!
Man, I'm already worn out from that...
...but it was so cool to dance together with my skeletons.
Y'all look cute, thank you very much.
They did a great job.
I'm glad that you agree.
I'm glad that you're vibing.
No, Mr. Bones, oh it's okay, Mr. and Mrs. Bones...
...they may come back. I don't know.
But for now, I do know that I need to...
...I need to chill for a second.
You know, there's one thing that I always really kind of wanted to do.
And that was, drink a nice glass of wine during my 3D.
I don't really drink wine very much anymore...
...but I told myself that I would.
For this special momentous occasion, right?
So that's what I'm going to do!
And the team here at the Great Jigoku Theater...
...decided to set up something special for me.
My own little wine tasting corner.
Rise!
Very nice!
There it is, ladies and gentlemen, check it out!
My own little special corner for the tasting of the wine.
It's got a bunch of different types of wine...
...but I chose the most...
I found the cheapest one at the convenience store to try for today.
So, this is where we're going to be enjoying some time together.
よいしょ、よいしょ...
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
Are you guys ready?
Swank, very fancy.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Well, I guess it's time.
Oh, staff-san got the wine bottle ready for me.
Alright, well, let me go ahead and grab this and okay.
Well, everybody, should we have a cheers?
Box wine? No, no, no, not box wine, not quite.
It's...
convenience store wine.
I asked staff-san to get me the cheapest one.
Hydrate up!
Thanks, Watson.
This will definitely keep me hydrated.
Not like I just had a ton of coffee before this or anything,
but here we go.
乾杯しましょう。
Let's have a toast.
Are you guys ready?
You ready for a cheers, everyone? Everyone at home?
Calliope fancy-pants Mori.
What can I say?
お、いいね。いいね。外国勢も乾杯したいね。いいね。
Oh, nice. Nice. The overseas guys want to toast too. Nice.
Alright, well let's cheers!
乾杯！
Cheers!
To 3D for Myth!
Oh man, that does taste like convenience store wine.
コンビニワイン。うん、間違いないね。
Convenience store wine. Yeah, no doubt about it.
間違いない。
No doubt about it.
Ah, sometimes you just gotta loosen up, deadbeats.
Sometimes you just gotta loosen up.
You know, here, I wonder...
While I'm here drinking this wine, maybe you can
take a couple screenshots of my face.
スクリーンショットして
Take a screenshot
and use the hashtag. Check out my face.
そして、他の表情もありますね。色んな表情。
And there are other expressions too. Various expressions.
ちょっと見せて、見せてみよう。
Let me show you, let's try showing them.
Check it out.
My expression. どや顔。可愛い、可愛い。
My expression. Smug face. Cute, cute.
Hello!
Yo, yo, yo. Cute, cute.
色々ありますね。
There are various ones.
ツンデレ顔。
Tsundere face.
ツンデレ顔、ちょっと怒ってる。
Tsundere face, a little bit angry.
おい。おい、おい、おい。
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
そして、あ、悲しい、悲しい顔もありますね。
And, ah, there's also a sad, sad face.
悲しい。
Sad.
このワインね。もっと安い奴飲んでみたい。
This wine... I want to try drinking an even cheaper one.
I would like to try drinking an even cheaper wine,
but oh well, this is all we have.
そして、びっくり顔。
And, surprised face.
びっくり。
Surprised.
うわあ！
Whoa!
本当？
Really?
ふざけんな。
Don't mess with me.
勘弁して。
Give me a break.
Give me a break!
うまい。うまいよ。
Good. It's good.
But I have to finish this glass. I have to. I promised myself that I would.
I was inspired by, by Lamy-senpai.
Lamy-senpai got to drink sake, nihonshu I think, nihonshu it was,
on stream for her 3D debut. So I figured I'm going to do the same.
As one of the only alcohol-okay members of EN.
Ah, let's see what chat has to say. 'Kawaii'.
Oh, 'wami', 'wami', 'wami'.
Based. Lamy's great. Yeah.
Where's the 'gah'?
Chat, you're right. Hold on, hold on. I got you, I got you.
Alright listen, よく聞いて。
Alright listen, listen carefully.
かあー！
Gah!
If you missed it, I'll do one more time. Hold on. We're almost done.
かあー！
Gah!
That one had a bit of a different tone to it.
Alright, done with the wine.
ワイン終わりです。
Wine is finished.
I can't, I can't do too much because, you know, we have stuff to do.
Oh, hey!
What's going on here?
Little Skellington's. Hey, buddies!
Thank you for all the Super Chats, everyone.
These are... this is my garden of Super Chats.
All my deadbeats sending in supers, they're coming in with roses, coming in hot.
Look at them gather. Oh!
Hey, buddies!
My supers!
Oh, so cute. Pat, pat, pat.
Hold on, hold on.
Oh, who's a good deadbeat? You're a good deadbeat.
You're a good deadbeat. Who's been a good...
Hey, it's me! It's you!
可愛いね。
Cute, isn't it.
What... what's that? What's that, deadbeat? You want me to step on you?
Oh gosh, okay. Hold on, hold on.
Deadbeat, you've been bad.
悪い子。
Bad boy.
悪い子。Bad deadbeat, bad.
Bad boy. Bad deadbeat, bad.
You've been bad. Bonk, bonk, bonk, bonk.
Yes, 助かる、助かる。Oh, you know what?
Yes, I'm saved, I'm saved. Oh, you know what?
You know what I also have?
I have my scythe.
My scythe, my... what is it?
Well, I have... I have my big, my big scythe. You know, Ricky, right?
But I have something else I want to show you. Yeah.
他の何かありますよ。特別な奴。
I have something else too. A special one.
An instrument. You saw it before. Hold on, I'm going to go grab it again, okay?
You stay right there. Stay right there.
I'm going to go get the scythe.
Ah, I got it! I got it, I got it!
Everyone, look! It's the scythe-bass!
Pretty cool, right? ほら見て。
Pretty cool, right? Look at this.
めっちゃ素敵ですね。
It's really wonderful, isn't it.
You can play it, of course.
I'm, I'm messing around.
But but...
you don't only have to play it.
No, no, no.
You can use it as a weapon if you want.
ちょっと見て。
Watch this.
I'll show you, I'll show you, okay?
I've been training a lot, so...
Okay, get this stance perfect...
Downstroke! Uppercut!
And... 回り！
And... spin!
Heh! And back around! Ha!
いい感じですね。
Feels pretty good.
Isn't it cool?
Look at it!
It has multiple purposes!
But but, did you know back in the day,
farmers used to use the scythe
to harvest the crops and the grass,
cut the grass like this. Yeah?
That was the original use of the scythe.
And then us reapers decided
that it was such a waste of a great tool
to not use them to take people's lives,
as a... murder weapon. Yeah.
Aw, look at the little Deadbeat playing!
He's having so much fun!
Aw, look at how cute.
Alright, so as I was saying,
this is usually how we reap the superchats
and the souls and stuff like that
down in the fields. We kind of do a similar thing
to what the farmers used to do back in the day.
What... huh?
何してるの？
What are you doing?
Deadbeat, what are you doing?
怪しい。
Suspicious.
What's this? Oh!
Are you stealing the superchats?!
Hey! おいおいおい、Deadbeat, stop!
Hey! Hey hey hey, Deadbeat, stop!
スパチャ盗んでる！
He's stealing superchats!
マジか？
Seriously?
Hey, wait! No no no, not that!
Wait! That's my scythe!
勘弁して！
Give me a break!
Wait a minute. I can fight back!
You want to fight me, Deadbeat?
Alright. That's fine.
You do know who you're dealing with, right though?
I am the Grim Reaper's first apprentice.
Okay then! If it's a fight you want...
it's a fight you'll get! Come on!
Got it! Yeah!
That's what you get.
ふざけんな！
Stop messing around!
まだ生きてる？ He's still alive!
Still alive? He's still alive!
おいおい、that's not funny, Deadbeat.
Hey hey, that's not funny, Deadbeat.
Stop laughing at me!
We're gonna have to use more than just weaponry
to get back at this Deadbeat.
Okay fine, fine, fine, fine.
We'll figure something else out.
Until then, come at me!
Hah! Ha! Uppercut! Uppercut!
Come on now!
He really knows how to use a scythe!
Oh gosh! Ha! Stop, Deadbeat!
Come on now! Back off!
邪魔！
Back off!
Let's finish this!
Yeah! That's what I'm talking about!
Let's go! Get Morivated! Woo!
Woo! Yeah, baby! Burn, baby, burn!
Burnt so many evil skeletons.
But who's gonna help me enjoy my 3D now?
Those guys were my backup dancers, camera crew...
I didn't think they'd get so money hungry and rowdy.
Oh, will you guys hang out with me?
My friends are here!
My friends came to party, everyone!
As you expected, I've got my buddies here!
My Myth friends! They came to hang out with me.
So, I guess it's time to do Myth-related things!
Come on, come on! Come on now!
Come on out, friends!
But here's the catch: You can't see them.
They're invisible. They're invisible... I think.
Where's the... where's the camera?
They're going to be my camera people.
Well, I have... I have two camera guests today.
Come on over! We've got Ninomae Ina'nis is here!
I can't believe I've died!
They're so...
Ame-chan, help me! I'm dying!
And Ame! Ame's here too!
You can't see them though.
They're mysterious spirits drifting in...
in the wilderness of the Underworld. Hi!
And you've got the camera now!
You've got all the power! All the power.
So, they're going to help me get the best angles.
And then I think we have Kiwawa and Gura in here, yeah?
Who are those?
Yay! Hello!
Go to the left! Go to the right!
Look at that! What's this?
We can go home after this, right Calli?
Well, we'll talk about that a little bit later.
So I got to say, I'm worried about Kiara,
your voice sounds like it's dying.
Yeah, because of your sick-ass performance!
Whoa! Oh yeah!
You ripped my voice.
Can you stop ripping my voice, please?
No!
Won't do that.
What do you guys think of this? This crazy stage.
It's on fire!
It is on fire. Literally.
Bring down the house.
Look at the audience!
Ina's on the camera!
Yeah, Ina's on the camera now.
Ina's in control.
Alright, well, we're gonna hold that thought,
and Ame, what do you want me to do?
You first, you know what I'm going to ask.
I do?
Are you going to ask me to do the worm?
Do the worm! Do it! Do it! Do the worm!
You know what? Alright, here's the thing.
I'm going to do it to prove it can be done.
Okay? Ina? Ina?
No, you put that camera... Wait, wait, wait.
I have one advice, Calli.
I have one piece of advice, Calli.
How about, if it's difficult for you,
the worm, how you normally push yourself up...
You can bounce yourself off of your boobies.
What the f-?
Really? You want to... かんべんして.
I want to fucking かんべんして.
Really? You want to... Give me a break.
I want to fucking give me a break.
Okay, alright, alright, let's go.
Alright, I can do this. Hold on.
No, I'm strong.
Hey, you saw me lift this scythe.
Alright, hold on. No, it's the worm. Let's go.
Good form! Do the worm!
She's worming! Oh my god, she's worming!
My back hurts. Okay, okay.
Now see if you can get up.
Oi, oi, oi!
I'm gonna get you for this.
Our payback!
Wait, what? What?
Hey, this is only the beginning here, you see.
Okay, Kiara, do you have any requests?
Yes, excuse me, excuse me, ma'am.
No, no, not you, you're the camera person.
Okay, okay, fine. Watson is in control.
What is your request, Kiara?
Eh, so I want something cute,
and can you please do the Caramelldansen dance...
I do. I do. You're taking me way back.
Alright, here we go.
And then full body and also close up,
please, camera. Both, both.
Both? That's an impossible request, client!
That is a tall order. I guess a zoom in.
However you see fit to do it, Watson.
Okay, okay, I shall move in.
Okay. This is the... boing boing. I'll just say.
This is gonna get me DMCA'd.
It's the Caramelldansen.
It's okay, we'll fix it in post.
Let me do it more intense. It's like this.
You guys are gonna tire me out before the end.
Oi, oi, oi.
Is it my turn? Is it my turn?
Okay, Gura, what's your request?
Cartwheel.
What was that? Cartwheel?
Are you... are you kidding me?
Let's go! Do it! Do it!
Can she do it? Let's see. This is dangerous.
I'm trying to get you in. Let's go.
Cartwheel! Let's go! Cartwheel!
Alright, here we go.
She's doing it!
Come on, man! Okay, okay.
That wasn't bad. Action roll!
Action roll?
Yeah!
Protect your spine.
That was the action roll.
Oh, I thought you wanted another one.
Alright... well, I guess that's it for all the requests...
No! No!
Alright, alright. What do you want me to do, Ina?
Watson's turn on the camera.
Alright, Calli...
Wait, Calli. What?
I want you to give us the most cutest...
Wait, why are you turning around?
I'm scared. Why are you turning around?
No! Why are you turning around? Leave me be, woman!
Why are you running? Why are you running?
Leave me be! No, no, no. やだ!
Leave me be! No, no, no. No way!
Okay, okay, okay.
I want you to give us the most cutest...
もえもえきゅん！
Moe moe kyun!
うわー！
Whoa!
Thank you for coming to Kawa-P Mori's 3D!
アイ、アイ！
Aye-aye!
It's time to... You can't run away!
You can't run away!
Moe moe kyun?
Yeah, full body, put your heart into it.
Come on! Come on, you can do it!
We've been waiting for years!
Do you want to cause the entirety of
these skeletons to cringe so hard
they die a second time?
Oh, step it up! It's on fire!
Might as well put out the fire with some...
With some, you know, embarrassment,
second-hand embarrassment.
With tears of joy from the Dead Beats.
Is this really what you want, Dead Beats?
Let's look at chat.
Chat, is this really what you want?
They're saying yes! They're saying yes!
Go, Calli! Go!
Just do it!
Just do it! Go!
Alright, fine.
Kawai-P...
Let me think about the choreography.
Okay, she's thinking, she's thinking.
Ina's the spin master!
Alright, what's the best camera
in this world, for real?
She's like a pro, for real.
Alright, start from here.
Oh, cute!
Alright, we can do a little...
Oh, Kawai-P! Okay.
Alright, here I go. Here I go.
もえ...
Moe...
きゅん！
Kyun!
うわー！
Whoa!
You sons of...!
It's all your fault! It's all your fault!
This is the Dead Beats' diet. No...
It was good! It was good!
Cute! Oh, look at that face!
Oh, give me that face... Oh, this is...
Okay... Cute!
Wait! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Is that gonna get me banned? What?
What? Wait a minute.
Looking at those nice shoes. Ooh.
Very nice, right?
You want to give everybody a full body look?
Yes! From bottom to top scan!
Scan it!
What did we say in the rehearsal?
You gotta what? Show the what?
Show the what? What'd you say, Ina?
Get in the slit!
"Get in the slit" is what she said.
I did not!
Yeah, you did!
We're exposing you now, okay?
I did not!
Oh, hi Dead Beats.
Hello, Dead Beats. You know what you're doing.
I did not! Alright...
I did not!
Do you have any up-close things you guys want to see?
Ooh! Your eyeballs!
I mean, your pupils! Eyeballs!
How close can we get?
Eyes. Eyes. Strange things.
Oh, cute! Oh, close!
Oh, gloss! Glossy! Sorry.
Hello. I think we saw your brain.
Oh, really? It wasn't very big, was it?
I don't know, we're gonna have to check...
Yeah, check the video.
Ina, why are you doing that with the camera?
What the...?! Why are you...?!
Oh, my...! Oh, yeah, Ina...
Why are you getting so weird with the camera right now?
Ina!
It's for me!
Oh, you know what? This is for Watame-senpai!
Oh, 脇ピー!
Oh, Waki-P!
Let me kind of pretend to be Watame...
Alright, Watame-senpai impression.
わきわき？
Armpit-armpit?
いいな。これ。先輩大好き！
Nice. This. I love you, Senpai!
You good, Ina?
You good, bro? Bro.
Here's the other one. For Watame-senpai.
How do they compare?
This is Watame-senpai's property.
Left side, right side.
(Waki song/humming)
脇ピー, Watame...
Waki-P, Watame...
I wonder. Hold up.
I'm sorry.
Oh, sick! They amped up the...
Here we go! Here we go!
I have no heart.
ほら見て、船長。見て。
Look at this, Captain. Look.
船長、見て。
Captain, look.
Oh my god! I've seen this before somewhere.
あほーい！
Ahoy!
Like you're on a trampoline!
See, now I'm having fun,
now that you guys aren't puppeteering me
like evil geniuses.
Wait... I just realized,
I have... I have some power here.
Power of the Ancient Ones. What does that mean?
I'll tell you to freeze!
Oh! Now I can't...
Ina's frozen her arms!
What are you doing? Ina's posing her!
Oh, no! Wait! You're like a Hololive Figure!
Why can't I move?
No! She's puppeteering her!
What's she doing? She's the puppet!
What is she doing to me? Freeze!
No, no, no! This is evil!
This is evil! Ballerina! Okay, you're back.
Oh my god. I don't know if you guys could see that,
but there were forces moving me.
I think it was Ina.
I might be dead here, you know,
but I still have my power.
We're ghosts, so yeah,
we can move stuff.
I guess so. Oh, so does that mean I can move objects as well?
Do you have power to move stuff too, Ame?
Want to try?
You try first, it's your idea.
Okay. All right.
Well, let me get the scythe, the kama...
Well, let me get the scythe, the scythe...
普通のカマ。
A regular scythe.
I'm gonna get the regular scythe.
Here it is.
What do you think, Ricky?
Uh, no Kiki, just Ricky.
Here, would you like to hold it...
...Ina of the Void?
Wait, what did you say? "Would you like to hold it?"
Then we know she's just holding it.
No, no, no, I'm holding it with my powers!
Yeah, with her powers.
Mind ghost powers.
That's right. Hah!
This is my final power!
The scythe, the kama gives you power!
The scythe, the scythe gives you power!
Final attack!
かっこいい！
Cool!
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing? Stop, stop, stop!
It's just Ricky moving on his own.
Don't worry about it. It's fine.
Look at how well... you can really talk with that scythe, huh?
Yeah, I'm used to it.
Looking good. Please don't hurt me.
I'll think about it.
I guess, wait, hold on.
Let's see how low I can go.
Are we doing limbo?
It's limbo time, ladies!
I'm there! I'm there!
Oh, that's a good height!
How low can you go? How low can you go?
Hold it properly!
It takes a lot of power!
All right, we gotta switch.
She's dancing too much.
All right, Ina back on the camera.
Watson's got the scythe.
Oh god, you have to watch out!
Oh, the scythe behind me!
You said I was moving too much.
That's pretty cool!
How low can you go? How low can you go?
All right, final level.
How low are you gonna make me go?
This okay?
How low can you go? How low can you go?
Don't hurt yourself!
I went low! I went low!
You're more flexible than I am.
Everybody's more flexible.
Look at that wink! Oh my god!
You were pretty flexible. You had all those dance moves.
And you do like this...
That BAN... BANされちゃう。
That BAN... It'll get banned.
I saw something there.
No you didn't.
Okay, I did not.
Do we have time for one more request?
Sure! We have more time.
Can you give us some sick kime-pose...
Can you give us some sick finishing pose...
...and then I want the camera to do a 360 as if you're a figurine?
Ooh! That's a good idea!
Okay, let's see.
Maybe with the scythe.
Ah, with the scythe.
Cool. Okay, okay. Got this.
All right.
And now 360, slowly and smoothly.
Go, smooth!
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Do your best, do your best!
It's a figurine on sale right now! Let's go!
Limited edition! Pop-up parade figurine!
Oh yeah, that doesn't have the scythe, though.
Yeah!
I can do a with-a-scythe version.
Oh yeah, that looks good with the scythe too.
Just like my figures.
I'm really good at standing still.
Nice! Oh, look at that figurine!
Ina's camera work! I'm doing that.
That was sweet! That was enough!
Ame's skills are super good with the camera.
Anyway, this is a cool pose. This is the last thing you see before you die.
Hoi!
Can I get the camera? I want to see something.
You're sitting down now? You were on the camera this whole time.
I want to get like a... Whoa!
あ、危ない！気をつけて！
Ah, careful! Watch out!
あ、あ、あ、stepping...
Ah, ah, ah, stepping...
Step!
Oh, careful!
ダメ！
No!
Step! ギリギリ！
Step! Just barely!
Please don't step on me!
Oh, no! Little Dead Beats, you've been bad.
Bad, bad little Dead Beat. I gotta punish you.
Punishment time!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
No! Remember me!
Aaaaaah!
I'm banned! That's it Watson, that's it Watson. I'm banned.
No! Ina, Ina was on the camera!
No, stop it! Think of the children!
You can't always do this!
Hold on, I'm banned. It's over.
It's over! Woo! Let's go! 3D debut and I'm banned from YouTube!
Banned, banned! I'm banned all the way!
Anyway, anyway, anyway, anyway...
Anyway, thank you ladies for coming to party with me for a little bit.
That was a lot of fun!
I love... yay! I love...
Very cute.
Thank you very much. Thank you Guawa as well for joining in.
Yeah!
Thank you so much, guys!
I wish I could control the camera.
It's okay, Gojira. Yeah, we'll have more chances down the line.
Yeah, definitely! Thank you, Ina. Thank you, Ame.
I love you guys! You guys are the best. Thank you Guawa.
I'll see you guys later. Bye!
Bye! See you later! Dead party!
Bye friends! See you later friends.
There they go! Off into the distance.
Goodbye friends! And now we are here with only me...
If you don't mind, I'm gonna get a little drinky. Where's my drink?
Hold on, I have my water. Mizu. I'll drink Kiara's water bottle because she's not here.
That's okay, she's resting. Anyway...
So, I would say I'm all alone now... Sadness.
But I'm not alone, because I have some friends here with me now.
You guys have seen me do some 3D stuff in the past, right? Not Ohirome, but like concert and stuff.
And at those times I always asked my Holo-senpai to come hang out with me.
But this time, I wanted to do something special. So...
Yo? Question mark? Friend time? More guests?
Indeed, more guests are here. Let's see, I see a lot of guesses.
Ayo Adams? There's no Adam. Ayo? Ayo?
A lot of people are saying Kohai. Not Kohai. In fact...
代、代、代、代先輩が来てくれた。
A very, very senior colleague has come for me.
So, without further ado, ladies and gentlemen, let's do a song. Here we go!
Oh, it's a fine day to die, Dead Beats!
Graveyard Shift (feat. BGV)
Introducing BGV on the Calliope Mori track, let's go!
Step! Step! Step! Step! Everybody!
Are you guys ready to rock? Yeah!
All right guys, Graveyard Shift. Let's go!
It's always been "life vs me" since the earth stood still,
Cryin' mercy, mercy, as they run for the hills.
Gotcha in my sights, and that's all that it takes,
Watch ya bend to the scythe, but call it nature's mistake.
Fate's your blind date for today, but lock your doors for tonight,
Pretend that you escaped me 'til I jump you like "sike!"
In spite of freaks like you, the mood could use a lift,
Was workin' easily until it jumped to the Graveyard Shift!
HELLO 死神くん 生命なんてチリ紙
Hello Mr. Reaper, life is like tissue paper,
だって CALLI IS CRAZY なら俺はジェリー
Because if Calli is crazy, then I'm Jelly.
EVEN MR. SAITAMA NEVER KILL US
その辺の有象無象なら一噛みでイケるかな
Maybe I can take those masses in one bite.
腐ったってタイト どこでもフレッシュでタイト
Rotten but tight, fresh and tight everywhere.
WORKING DEADみたい 詰め寄るぜバイト
Like Working Dead, I'll press you, part-timer.
テーブルで眠るミイラをビルド 締まったタップリいただきにきたってワケさ
Building a mummy sleeping on the table, I've come to take the full tap.
「お迎え」はNO THANK YOU
A visit from death is No Thank You.
浮き足だて LET'S GO CRAZY これば WARNING WARNING WARNING
Get excited, let's go crazy, this is warning, warning, warning.
危ないんじゃない？ 常識を壊す私たち
Isn't it dangerous? We break common sense.
誰も真似できない事しましょう
Let's do something no one can imitate.
DEAD LINE 飛び越えて笑い飛ばしちゃう！
Jump over the deadline and laugh it off!
精神自在 死神 THE PARTY KILLS AT RIGHT
Free-spirited Reaper, the party kills that're bright.
Can find us hanging by the mausoleum doors,
Living our best lives alright, find some due time,
This scene's designed to reach your head,
GONNA PARTY DOWN LIKE HELL DO THE RIP TILL I BURY YOU DEAD!
守るべき才能 不徳な 貪欲の通りだが マジに強く 毒に 欲 のような 婆タイム
Talent to protect, immoral as greed goes, but seriously strong, a crone time like poison and desire.
ガラパゴス 日本でガナる ラップさばかばら
Galapagos, barking in Japan, rap etc etc.
ラップして稼いで MILLION DOLLAR
Rap and earn a million dollars.
無理するなら中止しちゃう だからいつも自由に生きて自由に死ぬ
If it's too much, I'll stop, so I always live free and die free.
熟に死んで サブステ 鼻出すぜ 全てアンデッド
Die maturely, sub-stage, I'll stick my nose out, everything is undead.
来いよ
Come on.
Chanting tunes in the night? Give humans a fright,
Am I losing it or un-alive's actually alright?
What to do...
Death is only half as mighty,
as I'll be a crew...
...about to filter you,
...sound killer for two.
I got a friend in the undead,
suddenly it's all new.
No more "bones to pick",
the skeletons in the closet,
hunter hanging with the prey,
know who's finally lost it.
ひっくり返したら
If you turn it over
忌み神もアンデッドも
Both reapers and the undead
あら、
Oh,
これは Warning, Warning, Warning
This is Warning, Warning, Warning
危ないんじゃぜ、セイッ！
It's dangerous, Say!
都市を壊す私達
We who break the city
誰もマネできないコトしましょ
Let's do something no one can imitate
DEAD LINE 飛び越えて笑い歌っちゃう！
Leaping over the DEAD LINE, laughing and singing!
Sage, Junkie, Shinigami
Sage, Junkie, Reaper
The party killers upright
Can find us hanging...
...by the mausoleum doors,
Living our best lives alright
Find someone to type
this eyesore sign reach your head,
for now party down
like it's afterlife eternity till we bury you dead!
21グラムは
21 grams is
まだ消えちゃいない！
hasn't disappeared yet!
これはやっぱり Warning, Warning, Warning
This is definitely Warning, Warning, Warning
危ないんじゃぜ、セイッ！
It's dangerous, Say!
都市を壊す私達
We who break the city
誰もマネできないコトしましょ
Let's do something no one can imitate
DEAD LINE 飛び越えて笑い歌っちゃう！
Leaping over the DEAD LINE, laughing and singing!
ZOMBIE!
Sage, Junkie, Shinigami
Sage, Junkie, Reaper
The party killers upright
Can find us hanging...
...by the mausoleum doors,
Living our best lives alright
Find someone to type
this eyesore sign reach your head,
for now party down
like it's afterlife eternity till we bury you dead!
Thank you very much everyone!
Thank you!
First, we have a 紹介、紹介してください！
First, we have an introduction, please introduce yourselves!
わーい！
Yay!
せーの！生きてる奴が全くいねえ街へアンデッドがぶっ飛びまーす！
Ready! Let's blast off to a town where there's no one alive at all!
ラッパーでフランケンのFraと、
I'm Fra, the Frankenstein rapper,
ボーカル担当キョンシーのシノラ！
And the vocalist, the Jiangshi Shinra!
よろしくよろしくよろしく！
Nice to meet you, nice to meet you, nice to meet you!
アンデッド！アンデッド！嘘...
Undead! Undead! No way...
声でっかいね、この二人。でも大好きです。
These two are so loud. But I love them.
ポッポアンデッド！
Pop-pop undead!
Thank you so much for coming. 来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming. Thank you for coming!
こちらこそありがとう、呼んでくれて。
No, thank you for inviting us.
Of course!
いやいや、全然。
No, no, not at all.
So beautiful.
Beautiful, ありがとう。
Beautiful, thank you.
あ、Thank you, Calli.
Ah, thank you, Calli.
Thank you.
Not you!
No.
Beautiful, oh.
No beautiful.
おいおいおいおい、ちょっと待って。
Hey, hey, hey, hey, wait a minute.
So-so.
俺何かやっちゃいましたか？
Did I do something wrong?
違う違う違う。
No, no, no.
So-so. Excuse me.
おいおいおい。でも実はこの二人は私の大先輩です。
Hey, hey, hey. But actually, these two are my big seniors.
いえいえ。
No, no.
あ、すごい back in the day, these two, we knew each other in the underground.
Ah, way back in the day, these two... we knew each other in the underground.
Long time ago, so...
...本当に先輩ですよ。
...they're really my seniors.
Yay!
Thank you for coming.
そんな、いえいえ。
No, no, not at all.
いえ本当に。これじゃあ...
No, really. This is...
...Japanese 謙遜。
...Japanese modesty.
Japanese 謙遜。でも本当は先輩だと思ってるってこと。
Japanese modesty. But in truth, I really do think of them as my seniors.
あま、ヤハヤハ。
Ah well, yeah yeah.
いえヤハヤハ。照れ照れ。
No, yeah yeah. So shy.
So cute!
No no no.
Cute!
No cute.
おかえり。
Welcome back.
So-so. I'm so-so.
Very very cute.
超 very cute.
Super very cute.
No no no, 甘やかしちゃだめ。
No no no, don't spoil her.
My man is based. Yes, based.
So basically, these two are part of BOOGEY VOXX, they're a music unit, undead music unit.
So basically, these two are part of BOOGEY VOXX. They're a music unit, an undead music unit.
Yeah, um, they've been making amazing music for a long time. But the truth is...
...these two are actually going to be stopping their musical activities, I think this month. But it has been an amazing ride.
ちょっと日本語で説明してください。
Please explain in Japanese for a moment.
えっと、まあ俺ははっきり言って全然英語わかんないから勘で説明するぜ！
Well, to be honest, I don't understand English at all, so I'll explain with my intuition!
嘘嘘！あの活動について。活動について！
Lies! About the activities. About the activities!
ごめんね、ごめんね。そこはわかってるよ。
Sorry, sorry. I know that.
あの、BOOGEY VOXXはね、音楽のVTuberとして活動しているんだけれども、
So, BOOGEY VOXX has been active as music VTubers,
3月6日をもってね、二人組みでの活動を終了することになって、
but on March 6th, our activities as a duo will come to an end.
でだからね、ずっとカリオペとはライブ一緒にやりたいねって言ったんだけど、
And so, we've always said we wanted to do a live together with Calliope,
滑り込みでね、こうやって一緒にkick-assセッションするチャンスをもらえて本当にありがたいと思っているし、
and I'm really grateful to have the chance to have this kick-ass session together at the very last minute.
まあ3月6日までまだまだBOOGEY VOXXは活動していくんで、
Well, BOOGEY VOXX will continue to be active until March 6th,
今日俺たちに出会ってくれたDead Beatsも、ぜひ俺たちのこと覚えてっててください。よろしくお願いします。
so I hope the Dead Beats who met us today will remember us. Thank you.
Dead Beats is so cry.
The Dead Beats are crying.
Please remember. Please remember!
（投げキッスの音）
(Blows a kiss)
やめろって！
Stop it!
おいおいおい。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
やめろって、本当に。
I told you to stop it, seriously.
こわいって。
It's creepy!
Well, they said they're very happy to have a chance
to perform with me on stage because we always wanted to,
right? We always wanted to perform together on the same stage.
So now, before their musical activities together end,
we get a chance to do that, and I think that's really amazing.
So, we've got another song to do.
This will be the last song for today.
This song is called "CROWN". Please enjoy.
Hey! Hey! Alright! One last time!
Yeah! Alright everybody, this has been Calliope Mori with BGV.
Check it out. Step across.
Yeah! Just breathe.
バーチャルお寿司のトラック 宣誓。
Virtual Oshushi's track, swearing-in.
声が聞こえたんだ。
I heard a voice.
神様は手の平返しが上手
God is good at changing their mind.
Geek to da JOBS. 荷も to da JAWS.
Geek to the JOBS. Cargo to the JAWS.
でも俺のmindはサバンナじゃねえ JOBS
But my mind isn't the savanna, JOBS.
Cuz, I'm NERD motherf**ker. up the 矜持 to the JOB
Cuz, I'm a NERD motherf**ker. Up the pride to the JOB.
文脈を突破
Breaking through context,
したらもう戻れない だけどこの世界じゃ誰も俺らを殺せねえな
and then there's no going back. But in this world, no one can kill us.
Turn me up my homie.
エゴサーチの果て 届くくらいじゃフライヤー 呼べないぜバイブ
The vibes at the end of an ego-search won't call for a flyer.
負けずに嗅ぎ取れ Boys & Girls
Don't give in, sniff it out, Boys & Girls.
俺たちのマイク 病気と確信のバックラッシュ
Our microphones. Sickness and the backlash of conviction.
研ぐ度増えるチップの数
The number of chips increases every time we sharpen.
好きなときに食うとんかつ お前も立ってりゃいつかさあ
Eating tonkatsu when I want. If you keep standing, someday...
病むよな 病むよな 一人で飲むのアルコール
It's depressing, right? Drinking alcohol alone.
俺のこの声が明日へのバックボーン
My voice is the backbone for tomorrow.
テキーラはワンショットじゃつまんねえ
One shot of tequila isn't enough.
いつものクラブ いつもの席でお前のこと...
In the usual club, at the usual seat, thinking of you...
Never imagined my passion would lead to a success story.
Shout outs to every worldian who's got love for me.
Wanna share that fabulous glory.
One-man show got nothing for me.
Self-serving walk the road alone no high hopes for the staff at your party.
Remember rehab days.
Light in the smoke-filled nights.
A pack of big-dreaming strays beneath those factory lights.
Broken boring kid exploring bridges between worlds.
Found a voice amongst the noise, hey listen, out said girl.
Looked for the chance in my midst, would not back down or back out.
But I was pessimistic, almost missed it, drowning in doubt.
Will I ever make it big, is it worth it to try?
Like could I really see my picture on that billboard sign?
Am I out of my mind? Crashing back to days I felt spineless.
仲間'S 優しさで I was saved by that kindness.
With the kindness of my friends, I was saved by that kindness.
What I find like the pages of the story that binds us.
We progressed, became our best, the footsteps adhering behind us.
このままで
Just as it is.
零れてた
Overflowing.
恋心 涙の数きりないけど
My love, and countless tears.
ただ走った
I just ran.
ただ辿り着いた
I just arrived.
今懸けるよ 幸せを
Now I'll stake my happiness on it.
Yeah! Yeah!
CLAP! Come on, CLAP! CLAP!
CLAP! CLAP! Thank you! Yeah!
Calliope. Yo, what's up Fra?
Yo, カリ、こんなところまでありがとう。
Yo, Cali, thanks for coming all this way.
ところで俺たちが明日吸う予定のそっちの空気の味は？
By the way, how's the air over there that we're planning to breathe tomorrow?
ほら見て見て先輩、I've come a long way.
Look, look, Senpai, I've come a long way.
Still making moves from the views we knew from back in the day.
俺もそうだ、長すぎる一年。お待たせさん。
Me too, it's been a long year. Sorry to keep you waiting.
止まりそうな夜は背中を見ていたよ、ジョーズ。
On nights that felt like they'd stop, I was looking at your back, Jaws.
Had my back from the start, so I gotta say ありがとう。
Had my back from the start, so I gotta say thank you.
Be it this world or the next that we'll meet on every road.
Still awake in my bed, above CDs I couldn't sell.
That's what you make, so instead, let it be your reason to rebel.
Far as this Reaper can tell, I was investing in me.
Penniless, sleeping in hell, that was a test for my being.
Seeing this dream brought to life before me.
Every song that restored me, early mornings and chores, things they all led to Your Mori.
Always stay roaring into mics and facing all that comes fast.
Me still gonna pour my life blood into this so Death can be happy.
No matter compass for us, one thing that never did change.
We're still the same wild vagabonds from a far-off age.
But in the name of refraining from dragging on things fast.
The victory march is on so pass along beyond this Mic-pass!!
本当のチャンスは俺たちに踏み絵を強要しない。
A true chance doesn't force us into a loyalty test.
この才能、このダストと言葉にしよう。さあやっておしまい。
Let's put this talent and this dust into words. Now, let's get it done.
Simon says でも耳を貸すな。Anyway says またライフよりかます MY SELF JUST THE BEAT
Simon says, but don't listen. Anyway says, I'll rock more than life itself, JUST THE BEAT.
橋をかけることこそがドリーム。
Building a bridge is the dream.
それを渡って向こう岸に行くことがリアル。
Crossing it to the other side is reality.
いつも半歩先に居る 好奇心のゴースト 縦髪握る俺のウィル。
Always half a step ahead. Curiosity's ghost, I'm holding onto its mane, my will.
THIS IS THE MY WILL!
死んでもいいと思える瞬間を 死んでもなお求めてる。
I'm still seeking that moment where I feel it's okay to die even after death.
欲深き覚悟 受け取ったマイクで 全てを言葉にしたい。
Greedy resolution. I want to put everything into words with this mic I've received.
神様 俺は世界だけじゃ物足りない。
God, the world alone isn't enough for me.
さよならも
Farewells too...
すり傷にしながら 獣道をゆく
Taking scratches as we walk the path of beasts.
僕らだって
We too...
今 手にしたんだ
have now grasped it.
だから歌うよ この声を
So I'll sing out this voice.
CROWN (feat. BGV)
あの場所へ...
To that place...
コインと涙を抱きしめて...
Holding tight to coins and tears...
今叫ぶ...
Now I shout...
Sing it!
幸せだ...
I'm happy...
Thank you so much, BOOGEY VOXX!
ありがとう、カリオペ！
Thank you, Calliope!
ありがとう！Thank you! またねー！
Thank you! Thank you! See you later!
Bye-bye!
またな！
See ya!
See you around!
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Wow. エモい。エモいねなんか。
Wow. Emotional. It's so emotional.
すごい。Very emotional.
Amazing. Very emotional.
Man, those guys... They've really been there for me
ever since back in the day when I was nobody.
They always cheered me on.
So, a big ups to BOOGEY VOXX for being who they are,
and may their journeys continue,
and I hope that they still create wonderful things.
Thank you so much, you guys. That was amazing.
I'm glad that you liked it. Thank you.
Well, I guess now that we're here...
...and it's just me alone again on this big stage.
But I'm not alone because I have wonderful Dead Beats.
Dead Beats everywhere. I'm not alone.
I'm not alone because you guys are here.
That's always how it's been.
Thank you so kindly. Really, truly.
Now speaking of live shows...
I recently made a big announcement about the
Mori Calliope New Underworld Order Blu-ray!
Blu-ray! Blu-ray, Blu-ray, Blu-ray, Blu-ray!
If you didn't get a chance to get it, check it out!
This is how you can find it. You go to my channel.
Hey look, that's me!
You can also check it out in the description of this video.
You can find a link to the Blu-ray.
But there's the trailer, click that.
Go down... Yes, baby! Thank you for making this video, J-Chad.
Go down to the description, click that little blue link right there,
and you can choose what store you get it from.
Either of those links, okay?
And the shipping may be cheaper if you choose a local place.
But if you're in the States, you definitely want to use
the Calliope Mori official shop
because the shipping is going to be way, way cheaper there.
Take a look, there's the Blu-ray!
And with the Limited Edition...
...you get a special tapestry. 特別なタペストリーもありますよ。
...you get a special tapestry. There's a special tapestry too.
Check it out! ボリュームいっぱい！
Check it out! It's full of content!
There's so many songs. So many songs.
So, um... it's really a fantastic piece.
I would love it if you would check it out,
especially if you didn't get to see the show.
And then on the Twitter, you can check it out on...
...the Twitter. On my Twitter.
If you scroll down, you can find the tweet there, click that link.
As a matter of fact, go ahead and check out and follow
the official Mori Calliope Artist Twitter.
That pretty much gets notified about everything right away.
If you want the earliest news about me and what I'm doing,
go follow the official Artist Twitter.
And that's all I have to say about the Blu-ray.
Please get the Blu-ray and enjoy. Enjoy!
Show it to your friends and family—just kidding, don't do that.
Um, please enjoy the Blu-ray and enjoy watching
all your favorite Mori performances, because it's really amazing.
And I think the audio has been kind of like specially,
you know, arranged and put together.
I watched the whole thing, and it's good. It's good.
It's good sound quality, is what I'm trying to say.
Now, we also have another thing.
As you may all have guessed...
...I too have 3D merchandise!
It is... Tada!
Mori Calliope Pendant & Accessory Stand Set
A very special pendant accessory set.
Now before you say, "Wait a minute, that's just for the ladies, Calliope Mori!
What the heck? I can't get that!"
Wrong! Wrong you are. Anyone can wear this ice, okay?
Anyone. It'll look cool on anybody.
And you know what? If you really don't want to wear it
as a necklace, you've got two other options.
You can kind of, you know, make a keychain yourself.
You're going to have to use some tweezers, but you can make a keychain out of it,
which is pretty cool.
Or you can set it up just like this as a collector's piece
with the special scythe acrylic.
And it just hangs down right from there. It's got my signature on it.
So you can, you know, put it somewhere special.
Show your friends, "Hey, look, that's the special Mori Calliope pendant."
I really wanted some cool jewelry for me.
So, anyway, that's my 3D merchandise.
A cute pendant. Everybody else's is kind of...
so far, right?
Um, with...
with Ina and Gura, they had kind of like life essential things.
I wanted to do something that is kind of like
out of the way of that, I guess.
So here's this pendant.
やった！ (Yatta!)
Yay!
So yeah, anyway.
You can purchase this after
the big Myth collab on the 5th.
Everybody's 3D merch will be available,
so please wait until then.
Um...
I guess that's it.
Wow.
We did it. We did a show.
Here, in this big stage,
with all of you together with me.
Um, thank you.
Well, before this place burns to the ground,
I just want to say thank you so much everyone.
For always supporting me
and for looking out for me.
I'll keep doing my best.
And I guess I'll catch you on the flip side.
I guess I gotta go back to the overworld
cause there's still stuff to do.
There's lots more to do!
Alright! Well, I gotta go.
Uh, goodbye everyone.
PEACE!
Mori Calliope 3D Showcase #Mori3D