(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D SHOWCASE
JULY 21 (Fri) 20:00~ (WIB) 22:00~ (JST)
#KureijiOllie3D
Eh? Udah jam segini?!
Eh? This time already?!
Nooo, telat!!!
Nooo, I'm late!
Gini-gini amat rupa kamu abis bangkit dari kubur?
So this is how you look like when you're fresh out of the grave?
Yak, waktunya berdandan!
Alright, time for a makeover!
Sepatu udah, baju udah, pita udah.
Shoes check, uniform check, ribbons check.
Sip, udah lengkap semua.
Nice, everything's ready.
Yey! Akhirnya bestie aku showcase-an juga! Woah!
Finally, our Bestie will do a showcase!
Gimana keadaan di sana?
How's the situation there?
Back dancer sudah siap semua.
Back dancers are on standby.
Stage sudah siap.
The stage is also clear.
Mantap deh, lancar jaya.
I'm sure it'll be a smooth show.
Hmm, kira-kira kalau segini snacksnya cukup nggak ya buat Ollie?
Hmm, are these snacks enough for Ollie?
Ollie-senpai makannya banyak nggak sih, Om?
Doesn't Ollie-senpai usually eat a lot?
Oh, jangan lupa keripik kaca! Keripik kaca!
Oh, add glassy chips! I want glassy chips!
Ah, jangan dong. Kalau batuk pas tampil gimana dong?
You don't want to make her cough on stage.
Kalau begitu kita banyakin saja kali ya air minumnya?
Shall we bring more drinks instead?
Ah, itu dia!
Ah, that's good!
Akhirnya udah sampai sini.
I've come this far.
Semuanya...
Everyone...
Semuanya juga udah nge-dukung Ollie.
Everyone's been supporting me.
Yuk, bisa yuk!
Come on!
Ikeru zo! Ollie!
I can do this!
Do your best, Ollie!
Ollie! Let's freaking go!
Go, go, let's go!
Semangat Ollie! Sekarang waktunya kamu bersinar!
Good luck, Ollie! It's your time to shine.
Good luck!
Aku tau kamu bisa, Ollie.
I know you can do it, Ollie.
Go for it, Ollie!
Break a leg, Ollie! It's in the bag!
You got this! You got this! You got this!
Makasih, teman-teman.
Thank you, everyone.
Okay.
Waktunya bikin semua orang nangis.
Let's make everyone weep with joy!
Lullaby, lullaby, wonder hearts be collide,
who am I, in a place we've never been before?
I'm reaching out for the moon and stars beyond it.
Lullaby, lullaby, is it you I will find?
The moment that I hit you, you can't avoid the issue,
you're disconnected from the world you thought you were part of.
Hope you close your eyes and let go of your eyes have met no
body else decides the words you see in your heart.
Step up to the party's over here come one come all jump into the fire,
step up you are whatever you wanna be, you are free that's all we desire.
When you pass through the field of fantasy, there's a world with a rhythm for you and me.
Lullaby, lullaby, how can I find the love, lost in time there's an answer here in the stars for me.
All the way across the galaxy, go on forever.
Lullaby, lullaby, I will follow the signs 'cause I know when I reach the end it's you I'll see.
No we can't waste our time here it's now or never.
The valence force of nature, this visit of our future,
sometimes I know it feels like fate is never on our side.
I'm standing inside the vortex, wonder how you here beside me,
you're all I need to lead me into a perfect sky.
Step up to the party's over here come one come all jump into the fire,
each of us could be as fierce and proud and power will never go tired.
Wind up the party's right here come one come all let's follow the North Star,
step in you are whatever you wanna be you are free it's what we all are.
Dance away the world and the love comes to life, drive into the future ready to get part.
Lullaby, lullaby, wonder hearts be collide, who am I, in a place we've never been before?
I'm reaching out for the moon and stars beyond it.
Lullaby, lullaby, is it you I will find, how I feel left behind some of them to a new closed door.
How I know who you are, how I wanna know it all.
Maybe it's a case I don't wanna wait, even if it's right or wrong, I don't wanna worry.
If we didn't waste our time here it's now or never.
ZOM-BA-LA-LA!
Super kawaii zombie idol...
クレイジー・オリーです！
...K-K-K-K-Kureiji Ollie!
And welcome to my 3D showcase!
Selamat datang di showcase Ollie!
Welcome to Ollie's showcase!
オリーのお披露目へようこそ！
Welcome to Ollie's 3D debut!
Let's go! Zom-ly! I see all of you guys in the chat!
Ollie lihat kalian semua di chat kok!
I see all of you in the chat!
ヤッホー！
Yaho!
Wah, there's a lot of people watching!
Wow, there are so many people watching!
Don't forget to use this hashtag right here.
Yang nonton kan banyak kan ya, jadi jangan lupa pakai hashtag di sebelah sini ya!
Since there are so many of you watching, don't forget to use the hashtag over here!
見てる人多いから、このハッシュタグも使ってくださいね！
Lots of people are watching, so please use this hashtag as well!
お願いします！
Please!
Nah, dengan begitu bagaimana? Ollie's 3D!
So, how do you like it? Ollie's 3D!
I can move around now! Wey wey wey wey wey!
Keren kan?
Cool, right?
もうどうですか、オリーの3D？可愛いでしょ？
So, what do you think of my 3D form? Cute, isn't it?
And with this new acquired form, I get to dance while I sing now!
I don't just do a boring karaoke!
I don't just do boring karaoke anymore!
I sang 'U' from Millennium Parade and Belle! Did you guys enjoy it?
Ya, karena sekarang udah 3D, Ollie sekarang udah bisa joget.
Yeah, because I'm 3D now, I can finally dance.
Ollie nyanyi 'U' loh! Gimana tadi? Keren nggak?
I sang 'U'! How was it? Was it cool?
さっきもオリーが踊ったよ！
I was dancing just now!
ちゃんとアイドルっぽくなってたかな？
Did I look like a proper idol?
I had backup dancers too! Danced with me but uh...
I had backup dancers too! They danced with me but uh...
...they kind of ran off after we finished.
Tadi sempat ada backup dancers juga, cuma mereka langsung kabur habis udah selesai.
There were backup dancers earlier, but they ran away immediately after we finished.
そしてバックダンサーさんたちもあったね。
And we had backup dancers too, didn't we?
みんなのおかげで『U』が盛り上がった！ワーイ！
Thanks to everyone, 'U' was really exciting! Yay!
And look! I'm not just dancing anywhere! I'm dancing in what I call the...
...Ollie Streamland!
次はオリ...
Next, Ollie...
そうだ、えーと、ここをね、オリの立ってる場所は、オリの夢の世界！
So, the place where Ollie is standing right now is Ollie's dream world!
It's a dreamland because it's full of the things that I love!
Ini dunia mimpi Ollie,
This is Ollie's dream world,
Karena... Aduh capek gila bener!
Because... Man, I'm seriously crazy tired!
Di sini ada banyak hal-hal yang Ollie sukai gitu.
There are many things here that Ollie likes.
ここにはね、えーと、オリの好きなものが...
Here, um, things that Ollie likes...
...いっぱいあるよ！
...are everywhere!
ちょっと見に行こうかな！
Shall we go take a look?
じゃあ最初は後ろ！ From the back!
First, the back! From the back!
Kalian lihat gak? Itu ada...
Do you see it? There's a...
苺牛乳の噴水！
Strawberry milk fountain!
It's a strawberry milk fountain!
Because I always love strawberry milk! Pink milk!
そうだよ、えーと、苺牛乳がめっちゃ好きなので、
That's right, um, I love strawberry milk so much,
噴水があります！
so there's a fountain!
と... えーと...
And... Um...
窓開けてー！
Open the window!
Buka jendela!
Wow!
ほら、すごいでしょ？
Look, isn't it amazing?
そう、えーと、オリはね、えーと、遊園地が好きなので、
Yeah, um, Ollie, um, loves amusement parks,
後ろも遊園地があるよ。
so there's an amusement park in the back too.
見えるかな？ ゴンドラ。
Can you see it? The gondola.
Can you guys see it? Ada kayak gondola gitu.
Can you guys see it? There's like a gondola.
There's an amusement park right behind where I'm dancing!
Very cool!
And then if we go over here...
こっちにあったら...
If we go over here...
ほら、いっぱい花があるよ。
Look, there are lots of flowers.
彼岸花、オリの好きな花。
Spider lilies, Ollie's favorite flowers.
My favorite flowers, higanbana!
My favorite flowers, spider lilies!
And I'm sure you guys have noticed but...
...ada Bapak Yagoo!
...there's Mr. Yagoo!
Sungkem, Bapak Yagoo.
My respects, Mr. Yagoo.
Terima kasih Bapak, berkat Bapak saya bisa debut jadi 3D.
Thank you, Sir. Thanks to you, I can debut in 3D.
A chess piece!
And you guys can clearly see it, but below...
...Yagoo-san, there's like a shogi piece.
...Mr. Yagoo, there's like a shogi piece.
Well, I guess that's for another day.
Yeah! Woo!
And that's it!
Actually, I'm not the only one who can move around because...
...Teman-teman Ollie bisa gerak juga.
...Ollie's friends can move too.
えーと、そして、オリだけではなく、
Um, and, not just Ollie,
もう一人が3Dができたよ！
another one became 3D!
えーと、うー！ うどーん！
Um, ugh! Udin!
Udin! Eh, gimana teman-teman? Hehe.
Udin! Hey, how is it, friends? Hehe.
Kece kan, ya?
Cool, right?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Aduh sudah datang. Wah!
Oh, they've arrived. Whoa!
Keren, keren, keren. Banyak Udinnya, ya!
Cool, cool, cool. There are so many Udins!
Aren't they cute?
Just dancing all over the place!
Kalau gitu, Ollie kayaknya butuh satu Udin deh untuk nemenin Ollie.
In that case, I think Ollie needs one Udin to accompany her.
Ada nggak ya?
Is there one?
Udin? Udin-udin?
Udin? Udin, Udin?
Oh, itu dia! Udin!
Oh, there he is! Udin!
Say hi to the camera!
Hai!
Hi!
Oh, good job, good job!
Muter-muter, muter-muter! Spin around!
Spin around, spin around! Spin around!
Ah!
Now show us your butt!
And that twerk!
Aha!
めっちゃいい！ Keren kan?
That's so good! Cool, right?
Udin high five! High five! High five!
Hui!
Pendek banget gila, ih!
You're so crazy short, jeez!
Anda pendek banget, jadi sulit kan?
You're so short, so it's difficult, right?
まぁいいでしょう。
Well, that's fine.
うん。やっぱ。
Yeah. I knew it.
Ya, kalau gitu, udah! Lu sana pergi! Hush!
Well then, that's enough! Go away! Hush!
Yah, じゃ、えーと、楽しかったね。
Well, um, that was fun.
Berikutnya, Ollie masih ada beberapa hal yang pengen Ollie lihatin kepada kalian,
Next, Ollie still has a few things I want to show you,
jadi jangan kalian ke mana-mana.
so don't go anywhere.
I still have so many things I want to show you guys,
so don't go anywhere!
よし、えーと、それでは次の曲に行こうかな！
Alright, um, well then, let's go to the next song!
Let's go!
わっはー　ウィーアーゾンビ　ゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombie, zombie
Yeah　死にたい死にたい　死んでもゾンビ
Yeah, wanna die, wanna die, zombie even if dead
会いたい会いたい　書ききれないじゃない
Wanna meet, wanna meet, can't write it all
いつだって痛いの痛いの飛んでいけの
Always, "pain, pain, fly away"
なんでなんで　寂しさだけの　がちゃがちゃしてるんだ
Why, why? Just loneliness is clattering
わっはー　ウィーアーゾンビ　ゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombie, zombie
傷を持って　蜜を塗って
Bearing wounds, smeared with nectar
何度だって恋をする過程
Process of falling in love over and over
気付かせて　蜜を吸って
Make me notice, suck the nectar
何度だって恋がしたい
Want to fall in love over and over
腐っちゃってる　I love you, I love you
I'm rotting, I love you, I love you
腐りかけもいいわ
Half-rotten is fine too
腐っちゃえば　I love you, I love you
If I rot away, I love you, I love you
腐りたいけど違う
I want to rot, but it's different
わっはー　ウィーアーゾンビ　ゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombie, zombie
ドキドキがもっとしたいな
I want to feel more heartbeats
わっはー　ウィーアーゾンビ　ゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombie, zombie
どうしても　すべて嫌なまま
No matter what, everything stays unpleasant
なっちゃったんで　しょうがないね
It happened, so it can't be helped
わっはー　ウィーアーゾンビ　ゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombie, zombie
噛み応えも　足りない足りないよ
Not enough to chew on, not enough
噛み付いて　ビューティフル無い無いよ
Bite down, there's no beauty
ディスコ吐いて　打っちゃう脱帽
Vomit disco, strike, hats off
日和見れば　でもそれじゃおかしくなって
Looking at the situation, but that'll get weird
傷を持って　蜜を塗って
Bearing wounds, smeared with nectar
何度だって恋をする過程
Process of falling in love over and over
気付かせて　蜜を吸って
Make me notice, suck the nectar
何度だって恋がしたい
Want to fall in love over and over
ダメダメ
No, no
私になっちゃってるの アイラヴュー ヘイラヴュー 腐りかけもいいね
I'm becoming myself, I love you, hey love you, being half-rotten is nice too
君もなっちゃえば アイラヴュー ヘイラヴュー 二人だけのシークレット
If you become one too, I love you, hey love you, a secret just for the two of us
ゾンビになっちゃって アイラヴュー ヘイラヴュー 死なないからいいじゃん いいじゃん
Becoming a zombie, I love you, hey love you, it's fine since we don't die, right?
ゾンビになっちゃえば アイラヴュー ヘイラヴュー 正気じゃないじゃないじゃないな
If you become a zombie, I love you, hey love you, it's not sane, not sane, not sane
We're ゾンビ ゾンビ 惹きがもうすごいの
We're zombies, zombies, the attraction is already amazing
We're ゾンビ ゾンビ 狂ってもしょーがないね
We're zombies, zombies, it can't be helped even if we go crazy
狂ってもしょーがないね
It can't be helped even if we go crazy
ジンガイ ジンガイ 死んじゃうよ
Non-human, non-human, you'll die
段々ノリに 会いたい 会いたい 抱きゃいいじゃん
Gradually getting into the rhythm, I want to see you, I want to see you, just hug me
いっせーのーで いっせーのーで
On the count of three, on the count of three
飛んじゃいけの なんで なんで
Why can't I just fly off? Why, why?
寂しさだけ残っちゃってんだ
Only loneliness is left behind
Capek...
I'm tired...
Capek banget, teman-teman.
I'm so tired, friends.
Akhirnya, Zombie...
Finally, Zombie...
Giga-san-ssu Zombie... (remix)
Giga-san's Zombie remix...
ゾンビも歌った。
I sang Zombie too.
もう、いっぱい練習しましたよ。
I practiced a lot.
I practiced a lot, you guys would never know.
Ollie latihan banyak-banyak banget.
Ollie practiced a whole lot.
Capek.
Tired.
ゴレフ。
*collapses*
大丈夫です。
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
お腹空いたな。
I'm hungry.
次、Ollieのおうちに行こうか。
Next, shall we go to Ollie's house?
Ke rumah Ollie aja kali ya?
Maybe we should just go to Ollie's house?
Teman-teman, ayo ikut Ollie.
Everyone, come with Ollie.
Kita ke rumah Ollie, yuk.
Let's go to Ollie's house.
Everyone, we're going to my house.
ラーメン食べたい。
I want to eat ramen.
Let's go!
まーがん！ラーメン！ラーメン！ラーメン！
Ramen! Ramen! Ramen! Ramen!
着いた、着いた！
We're here, we're here!
We're finally here at the ramen shop...
No, it's not the ramen shop.
It's my house!
Sini itu rumahnya Ollie, ya.
This is Ollie's house, okay.
ラーメン屋じゃないよ。
It's not a ramen shop.
これはOllieのうちだよ、うち。
This is Ollie's house, my home.
うち。
Home.
えっとね、ここはTVがあるはず。
Well, there should be a TV here.
Di sini itu ada TV.
There used to be a TV here.
There used to be a television here.
And over here used to be a sofa.
But I don't see it anymore.
It's a little bit sad and frustrating.
Agak kesel ya teman-teman.
It's quite annoying, friends.
Tapi ya sudahlah.
But whatever.
Ollie udah lapar, jadi kita nggak usah pikirin lagi kali ya.
Ollie is hungry, so let's not think about it anymore.
腹がもうペコペコだから、まいっか！
My stomach is growling, so whatever!
食べようか、ラーメン。
Shall we eat ramen?
Let's just go and make some ramen.
行こう！
Let's go!
The kitchen should be this way.
Ini kok nggak ada orang ya?
Wait, there's no one here?
Self-service kali ya?
Maybe it's self-service?
セルフサービスかな？
Self-service, maybe?
じゃ、着いた！
Well, we're here!
This is the kitchen.
Ini adalah dapur.
Kalau gitu, Ollie cari dulu...
In that case, Ollie will look for...
あ、どこだ？湯切り、湯切り？
Ah, where is it? The strainer, the strainer?
ガサガサ、ガサガサ。
*rustling, rustling*
見つけた！
Found it!
ヘヘ。Ini ya teman-teman, Ollie udah belajar.
Hehe. This is it friends, Ollie has learned this.
湯切りだよね？
It's called yukiri, right?
そして動く...
And then you move it...
だから湯切り！
So it's yukiri!
Ini namanya yukiri.
This is called yukiri.
から... 動きに。
From... the movement.
Kita masak aja.
Let's just cook.
So hungry!
な... よいしょ。
Na... there we go.
緩やかに。
Slowly.
Just slowly.
There we go.
And with that...
Let me just put this down.
ガサガサ。
*rustle rustle*
And our ramen is done!
完成、完成！
Finished, finished!
Selesai juga.
It's finally done.
美味しそう！
Looks delicious!
じゃ、食べようか！
Well, shall we eat!
Kita langsung makan aja kali ya.
Let's just eat right away.
Let's go and have a munch!
エマン。Kalau Ollie yang masak itu...
When Ollie is the one cooking...
...paling mantap.
...it's the absolute best.
セルフサービス、かっこいいですね。
Self-service is pretty cool.
Kita makan sambil duduk kayak lady gitu kan ya.
Let's eat while sitting like a lady.
よいしょ。
There we go.
じゃ、いただきます！
Well then, let's eat!
うーん、美味い！
Hmm, delicious!
Mantap banget, teman-teman.
This is so good, friends.
美味しい、美味しい！
Delicious, delicious!
It's so delicious!
ああー！
Aaah!
Terus habis itu, kita habisin kuahnya.
And after that, let's finish the soup.
よいしょ。
There we go.
ふう！
Fuuh!
ごちそうさまでした！
Thank you for the meal!
Thank you so... Oh gosh.
I have myself to thank.
Thank you, Ollie!
That was really good!
Hehe!
And then, what else should we eat?
Some dessert, maybe?
この後、デザート食べようかな？
Shall I eat some dessert after this?
うーん...
Hmm...
え、あれ？
Eh, what?
誰かお客様？
Is that a customer?
Is that a customer I see?
Halo, apakah Anda pelanggan?
Hello, are you a customer?
わあ！Itu pistol!
Woah! That's a pistol!
That's a gun!
銃ですね！
It's a gun!
やばい！
Oh no!
Ini untuk yang kayak ginian, Ollie masih belum siap mentalnya!
For this kind of thing, Ollie is not mentally prepared yet!
心の準備はまだですよ！
I'm not mentally prepared yet!
I can't with this kind of stuff!
Well, you know what? That's okay!
Because I myself have my own gun!
Ollie juga punya pistol sendiri.
Ollie also has her own gun.
Lihat nih ya, rasakan suaranya! Hahaha!
Look at this, feel the sound! Hahaha!
Lebih besar kan?
It's bigger, right?
もっとデカイでしょ？
It's even bigger, right?
It's even bigger than yours, right?
Well then, take this! 喰らえ！ Rasakan ini!
Well then, take this! Take that! Feel this!
Wait! Okay! Angkat tangan! Saya angkat tangan!
Wait! Okay! Hands up! I'm putting my hands up!
Makasih. Jangan... jangan... um...
Thank you. Don't... don't... um...
Jangan lukai saya?
Don't hurt me?
Please don't hurt me! Please don't hurt me!
Oh, okay! What? You want me to raise my hands higher?
Angkat lebih tinggi lagi tangannya? Oh!
Raise your hands even higher? Oh!
Oh, itu mau anda? Um...
Oh, is that what you want? Um...
Kayak gini?
Like this?
kenyataannyaだだだだ... もうセーフかな？
In reality... is it safe now?
Kepepet-pepet amat moy... kaget!
It's so tight... what a surprise!
Well, you know what? That's fine.
Well then, after this I'm going to show you guys...
Whoa! Aaah!
Dipikir-pikir lagi ya...
Thinking about it again...
Seharusnya itu tadi senjata Ollie pakai untuk nembak.
I should've used that weapon to shoot earlier.
When you think about it, I should've just used my gun.
FPSが上手ければよかったな...
I wish I were better at FPS games...
1, 2, 3 やら今だけ！
1, 2, 3... just for now!
予測不能ガチャで！
In an unpredictable gacha!
NEW [zom]BIE!!
遥か遠くも知ってた
I knew it from far away.
有能なさ 15 minutes
My talent, for 15 minutes.
見逃すな走る先に
Don't miss it, where I'm running.
ほら描いた 縦横無尽スカイニング
Look, I drew it, an all-around skyning.
表舞台構いなし
No concern for the main stage.
無常主義 飽き飽きなのよ
I'm tired of impermanence.
魔法さゾンビパウダー
It's magic, zombie powder.
私には丁度いいのよ
It's just right for me.
画面越しの頂点へ
To the top beyond the screen.
伝説の大和魂
The legendary Yamato spirit.
アブストラクトに踊ろう
Let's dance abstractly.
本能より確かな実力
Ability surer than instinct.
添いでこの地 あらあら
Along this ground, oh my.
逆らさずビンビン刺した
Stuck it in without resisting.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's okay even if you laugh at me.
前には出れない面影 暴走して
The trace that can't come forward, going wild.
Victory to the world's
手に入れたバッジと冒険は
The badge and adventure I gained
きっとかけがえないはずよ
will surely be irreplaceable.
見せてみてよ この境地へ
Show me, to this state of mind.
いらっしゃいませ！
Welcome!
クールなプレイ重ねて
Pile up the cool plays.
見せてあげるよゾンビの底力
I'll show you the true power of a zombie.
見切れたリロード急いで
Hurry up the cut-off reload.
ここは居場所 乱界並べた豪華な月運
This is the place, luxury moon-luck lined in the chaotic world.
広大すぎる台地の上
On top of a plateau that's too vast.
ここはどこだ王座
Where is this, the throne?
拾いあげ 顔あげて
Pick it up, look up.
理想 私も強くなってくわ
Ideal, I'm getting stronger too.
執着心 根っこから
Attachment, from the roots.
残されるのは尺ねぇ
It's annoying to be left behind.
おじけ界にOnce, suspicious
In the world of fear, once suspicious.
弱い揚げトリップ・トゥ・トリップ
Weak fry, trip to trip.
研ぎ澄まされた感性
Sharpened sensibilities.
あれれ ほぐれていただけ
Oh my, it was just loosening.
Join and fighting これから
Join and fighting from now on.
仲間じゃないの 全部わかって
Aren't we comrades? Understanding everything.
泣いたって辞めないさ
I won't quit even if I cry.
これがうちの希望になるとも知らずにね
Without knowing this will become our hope.
Victory to the world's
共に刻みゆきたいんだ
I want to carve it together.
熱きド真ん中を
The hot dead center.
心地いいの この狂気に
It feels good, in this madness.
染まっちゃって
Getting dyed by it.
B.P.M 走ったって
Even if the BPM runs.
A.I.M はブレないで
Don't let the aim waver.
潜って 潜って まだまだ
Dive, dive, not yet.
フィルター越しの遊びを超えて
Beyond the play through the filter.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's okay even if you laugh at me.
ただみんな いつかチャンピオンと飛ばすだけ
Just everyone, flying with the champion someday.
Victory to the world's
絶対追い抜くよ あの光るダイブ軌道を
I'll definitely overtake that shining dive trajectory.
忘れられないほどの勝利を
A victory so great it can't be forgotten.
願っちゃって
Wishing for it.
境地を行こう GG！
Let's go to that state of mind, GG!
Hah?
Huh?
Uuugh...
Kayaknya Ollie barusan mimpi enak deh.
I think I just had a wonderful dream.
Habis jadi pro gamer gitu.
I was like a pro gamer or something.
Hah, ini tangan kaki pada... oh, di situ.
Huh, my arms and legs are... oh, they're there.
Tadi bisa copot gitu.
They just came off like that.
Oi, kaki! Kur kur kur kur kur kur kur kur kur...
Hey, leg! [bird calling sounds]
Good kaki, good kaki, good kaki.
Good leg, good leg, good leg.
Heh, ah, okay.
Sekarang... uh, udah bisa.
Now... uh, I can do it.
Udah bisa berdiri. I can stand now.
I can stand now. I can stand now.
Now about my other arm... ah, there it is.
Heish! Sssh... tangan... back... issh!
Heish! Sssh... arm... back... issh!
Ha! Baru lagi! Seperti... baru lagi. Hehe.
Ha! Good as new! Just like... brand new. Hehe.
Ah! It's because of that damn... dam...
I don't know what to call her.
Ollie nggak tahu itu tadi harus bilang apa, dorobou tiba-tiba.
Ollie didn't know what to say, a thief suddenly appeared.
Mou, kono dorobou-neko-san!
Geez, this thieving cat!
Ma, mou inakunatta kara, daijoubu ka na?
Well, she's gone now, so it should be fine, right?
Udah nggak ada jadi seharusnya udah nggak apa-apa kan ya?
She's not here anymore, so everything's okay now, right?
Mou anshin-anshin.
What a relief.
Oh?
Apa?
What?
Moshi-moshi?
Hello?
Ha-heng!
Ha-heng?
Ha... ha-heng?
Jangan-jangan... ini!
Don't tell me... it's this!
Ha-heng!
Bisa bilang yang lain selain ha-heng nggak?
Can you say something other than 'ha-heng'?
Mualas!
How annoying!
Halo, selamat datang!
Hello, welcome!
Yeay, Ollie omedetou!
Yay, congrats Ollie!
Oke, silakan perkenalkan diri.
Okay, please introduce yourselves.
Halo, aku Ayunda Risu dari Hololive ID Generation 1.
Hello, I'm Ayunda Risu from Hololive ID Generation 1.
Yeay!
Kemudian ada Yopi!
Next we have Yopi!
Yopi-pi, Airani Iofifteen, hello!
Yeay, makasih udah dateng! Ollie seneng!
Yay, thanks for coming! Ollie is so happy!
Eh, Ollie nanti kamu jangan lihat Twitter ya.
Eh, Ollie, don't check Twitter later, okay?
Ada apa? Ada apa dengan Twitter?
What's up? What's wrong with Twitter?
Jangan lihat Twitter nggak apa-apa.
Just don't check Twitter, it's okay.
Jangan-jangan... jangan lihat Twitter kita berdua, jangan.
Don't... don't look at our Twitters, don't.
Oh, oh... begitu kah? Oh, oh, baiklah.
Oh, oh... is that so? Oh, oh, alright.
Oke, mumpung nih kalian di sini. While you guys are still here.
Okay, since you guys are here. While you guys are still here.
Enaknya kita main nggak sih? I think it's fun if we play.
Wouldn't it be fun if we played something? I think it's fun if we play.
Boleh! Ayo, gas! Mari!
Sure! Let's go! Come on!
Tapi jangan yang susah-susah ya, Ollie takut, ID satu tidak boleh berkata kasar.
But nothing too hard, Ollie's scared, Gen 1 shouldn't use harsh words.
Ya, kalau gitu, mari kita main tebak-tebakan... let's play some charades.
In that case, let's play a guessing game... let's play some charades.
Jadi rulesnya simpel ya. Ollie akan memperagakan sesuatu, kalian harus menebak.
The rules are simple. Ollie will act something out and you have to guess.
Apabila benar, kalian boleh ngerikues apa pun dari Ollie.
If you get it right, you can request anything from Ollie.
Oke, apa pun? Apa pun? Eh, aku mikirin apa nih? Apa pun?
Okay, anything? Anything? Eh, what should I think of? Anything?
Apa kamu yakin bisa, Yopi? Aku nih temen-temen...
Are you sure you can do it, Yopi? Me, friends...
Apa pun! Ini, ini itu kan... gara-gara Risu-senpai di chat pada nulis 'malas' semua 'malas'.
Anything! This is... because of Risu-senpai, everyone in chat is writing 'lazy'.
Ya udah, jangan malas-malas lagi kalau gitu! Ayo semangat!
Well then, don't be lazy anymore! Let's get pumped!
Nggak boleh! Nggak boleh malas!
No way! You can't be lazy!
Kalau gitu, kita langsung masuk ke pertanyaan per... pertama kalian.
In that case, let's go straight to your very first question.
Oke, kalau gitu, pertanyaan pertama! Eto... sato!
Okay then, first question! Uh... one!
Ninja! Ninja! Issh! He-e!
Mudah ya? Issh! He-e! Terlalu mudah.
Easy, right? Issh! He-e! Too easy.
Theme: Ninja
忍者
Ninja
Harusnya aku yang jawab. Hehe, anda kalah cepat. Ya ampun.
I should've answered. Hehe, you weren't fast enough. Oh my god.
Kalau gitu, apakah ada... oh tunggu sebentar.
In that case, is there... oh wait a second.
Ini mumpung nih, mumpung banget. Kayaknya kalau Ollie berpose pakai sesuatu yang keren, keren juga nggak sih?
Since we're here, it's a great opportunity. Wouldn't it be cool if Ollie posed with something cool?
Boleh! Tunggu, Ollie ambil pistol dulu ya.
Sure! Wait, Ollie will get the gun first.
Oke! Ah, buat melawan ini tadi, apa... dorobou.
Okay! Ah, to fight this earlier, what was it... the thief.
Dia, si 'Doro-Zombie'.
Her, the 'Thief-Zombie'.
Keren kan? Berpose pakai ini kali ya.
Cool, right? I'll pose with this.
Ets! Boleh, boleh. Kalau gitu, Yopi ada rikues nggak?
Hey! Sure, sure. In that case, Yopi do you have a request?
Ah, ini... kamu jalan ke belakang terus kayak ke samping gitu lho. Ngerti nggak?
Ah, this... you walk to the back and then go to the side like that. Get it?
Kamu jalan ke belakang terus langsung kayak balikin badan ke sini gitu lho. Kayak pose habis nembak gitu lho.
You walk to the back and then immediately turn around to here. Like a post-shooting pose.
Kalau gitu... na na na! Satu, dua, tiga... PLING! Ck-ya!
In that case... [singing]! One, two, three... [SFX]! Ck-ya!
Gitu kah? Ck-ya! Tembak hatiku kakak!
Like that? Ck-ya! Shoot my heart, big sister!
Jedarr! Jedarr! Jedarr! Woi! Bah keren sudah.
Bang! Bang! Bang! Hey! Wow, that's cool.
Kalau gitu berikutnya Ollie juga bakal pakai ini kali ya.
In that case, next Ollie will probably use this too.
Oke, kalau gitu kita langsung ke... pertanyaan kedua. Eto... sato!
Okay then, let's go straight to... the second question. Uh... one!
Oh? Uh? Apa tuh?
Oh? Uh? What's that?
Melihat! Melihat! Bukan, bukan.
Looking! Looking! No, no.
Kecil... an-ya? Petting... Robo?
Small... ? Petting... Robo?
Ah, mengelus kepala.
Ah, headpatting.
Apa sih?
What is it?
Aa...
Pendek!
Short!
Hah?
Huh?
Muda?
Young?
He-heng.
Apa sih?
What is it?
Kecil...
Small...
...dipet-pet.
...patted.
Pendek!
Short!
Apa?
What?
Tinggi, tinggi!
Tall, tall!
Tinggi!
Tall!
Hai?
Hi?
Ini tuh apa?
What is this?
Apa sih?
What is it?
Komentar juga ada yang...
There's also a comment...
Gak sampai!
Can't reach!
Yopi!
Anya!
PENDEK!
SHORT!
Theme: Alien (宇宙人)
Theme: Alien
Iya, tadi pendek.
Yes, earlier was short.
Ini UFO.
This is a UFO.
Gak pendek bukan saya juga ya?
Not short isn't me either, right?
AKU 150!
I'M 150!
Ah pendek, berisik!
Ah short, noisy!
Oke, Sempai...
Okay, Senpai...
...mau minta pose apa?
...what pose do you want to request?
Oke.
Okay.
Aku mau minta pose apa ya...
I want to request what pose...
...kayak kamu tuh...
...like you...
...tangannya diletakin di depan bibir gitu...
...your hand is placed in front of your lips like that...
...terus tangan satu lagi ke belakang...
...then the other hand is in the back...
...kayak pose cute-cute gitu loh.
...like a cute-cute pose.
Segini?
Like this?
Iya, muuu gitu.
Yes, muuu like that.
Terus badannya agak maju dikit ke depan.
Then the body moves forward a bit.
Muuu gitu.
Muuu like that.
Gini?
Like this?
Aaa kawaiii!
Aaa cute!
Keren.
Cool.
Oh, tasukaru.
Oh, helpful.
Hehe.
Tapi di belakangnya ada pistol.
But there's a pistol in the back.
Gimana ya?
How about it?
Gak apa-apa, gak apa-apa.
It's okay, it's okay.
Shoot a bullet through my heart lah ya.
Shoot a bullet through my heart.
Wah keren, keren, keren.
Whoa cool, cool, cool.
Kalau gitu...
In that case...
...ini yang terakhir ya?
...this is the last one, right?
Oke.
Okay.
Sip kalau gitu yang terakhir.
Great if so, the last one.
Satu...
One...
Hah?
Huh?
Joget!
Dance!
Theme: Idol (アイドル)
Theme: Idol
Idol, daaaa!
Wahhh!
Whoaaa!
Keren, keren, keren.
Cool, cool, cool.
Pintar, pintar, pintar.
Smart, smart, smart.
Bagus sekali kalian berdua jago.
Very good, you two are great.
Iya nih.
Yeah.
Tante Ollie yang paling jago mendemonstrasikan.
Auntie Ollie is the best at demonstrating.
Kyawww!
Dah, ada request apa?
Done, any other requests?
Oho.
Pose apa ya? Hmmm...
What pose? Hmmm...
Kayaknya...
I think...
Ada ide nggak?
Any ideas?
Pose unicorn!
Unicorn pose!
Ke...
Li...
...kayak gini?
...like this?
Iya, jadi pistolnya jadi tanduk gitu.
Yeah, so the pistol becomes a horn.
Gini?
Like this?
Iyaaaa!
Yessss!
Kenapa sih?
Why?
Kok gini?
Why like this?
Badan kamera bisa miringnya pas gitu loh.
The camera body can tilt just right like that.
Unicorn.
Unicorn aja cuma kayak gini.
A unicorn is only like this.
Kalian ya...
You guys...
...nih ku-ketiakin nih!
...here's my armpit!
Yaudah.
Alright.
Menjijikkan! Dadah, Kobo.
Disgusting! Bye, Kobo.
Kalau gitu terima kasih...
In that case, thank you...
...teman-teman sudah datang.
...friends for coming.
Hayooo!
Nonton sampai akhir ya!
Watch until the end, okay!
Oke, oke.
Okay, okay.
Kita nonton dari kursi VIP di sini.
We're watching from the VIP seats here.
Oh, keren.
Oh, cool.
Keren eh.
Cool hey.
Kalau gitu...
In that case...
...bye bye!
Bye bye!
Bau ketiaknya dong, bau ketiaknya dong!
Smells like armpits, smells like armpits!
Nih ketiak ketiak ketiak!
Here, armpit armpit armpit!
Memang itu dua rada...
Indeed those two are a bit...
...rada miring ya.
...a bit tilted.
Miring, ditaruh dulu deh Mozambique-nya.
Tilted, let's put the Mozambique away first.
Hoo, kalau gitu...
Hoo, in that case...
...teman-teman jangan lupa loh...
...friends, don't forget...
...kalian pakai hashtag-nya Ollie #KureijiOllie3D.
...use Ollie's hashtag #KureijiOllie3D.
Don't forget to use my hashtag by the way guys.
Make it trend in Twitter!
That'd be pretty cool.
Wah bye bye bye bye.
Whoa bye bye bye bye.
Anda juga hei.
You too, hey.
Saya kok miring?
Why am I tilted?
Halo?
Hello?
Moshi-moshi?
Halo halo?
Hello hello?
Ohhh!
Ollie Super Sama!
Itu password-nya.
That's the password.
Aaahhh!
Hambura mantap!
Hambura is great!
Crazy! Hambura!
Apa-apaan anda?
What are you doing?
Halo selamat datang di 3D Ollie!
Hello, welcome to 3D Ollie!
Selamat datang para pendek!
Welcome, shorties!
Yeeey! Selamat datang!
Yeeey! Welcome!
Hai hai!
Hi hi!
Aku dipanggil sempai...
I'm called senpai...
...aku disemangatin jadi senang Ollie.
...I'm cheered on so Ollie is happy.
Hehehe.
Nah ini gimana nih?
Now what about this?
Mana ramen-nya?
Where's the ramen?
Nggak.
No.
Ramen-nya nggak ada buat kalian.
There's no ramen for you guys.
Kalian di sini tuh bukan buat ramen tahu nggak sih?
You guys aren't here for ramen, you know?
Kalian di sini buat main game.
You're here to play games.
No way! Aku di-scam tadi!
No way! I was scammed earlier!
Kata Kaila, 'Ayo Kobo ikut makan ramen gratis'.
Kaila said, 'Come on Kobo, let's go eat free ramen'.
Woi! Berarti kalau main game...
Hey! That means if you play games...
...hadiahnya dapat ramen.
...the prize is ramen.
Hadiahnya dapat pose gratis ya bukan ramen.
The prize is a free pose, not ramen.
Mohon hoax-nya jangan disebarluaskan.
Please don't spread the hoax.
Waktunya makan, pose gratis dan ramen.
Time to eat, free pose and ramen.
Oke deh kalau gitu. Yodehh.
Alright then. Okay.
Iya ramen ramen ramen.
Yes ramen ramen ramen.
Kalau gitu kita bakal main charades.
In that case we're going to play charades.
Kalian tahu kan peraturan-peraturannya?
You guys know the rules, right?
Ya udah tahu.
Yeah, we know.
Kalau gitu kita langsung main saja kali ya.
In that case let's just play right away.
Oke skip tutorial.
Okay skip tutorial.
Nanti saja aku nyonteknya.
I'll cheat later.
Bisa gitu.
Can do that.
Ombak ombak.
Waves waves.
Kalau gitu, belum belum belum...
If so, not yet not yet not yet...
...kita mulai ya.
...let's start.
Kalau gitu satu...
If so, one...
Satu...
One...
Astaga.
My god.
Aa...
Berpikir!
Thinking!
Nongkrong! Nongki!
Hanging out! Hangout!
Aa...
Buang air besar!
Taking a dump!
Ayo, apa? Apa? Nggak tahu.
Come on, what is it? What? I don't know.
Umm... Smashy?
Eh, sumo? Wah, keren nih di chat udah pada langsung betul.
Eh, sumo? Wow, cool, people in the chat already got it right.
Jongkok!
Squat!
Bukan!
No!
YAGOO!
Theme: YAGOO
Heh? Apa?
Huh? What?
Oalah, YAGOO yang itu... Yang pose itu, kan?
Oh, that YAGOO... The one with that pose, right?
Yang fotonya hitam putih itu, lho.
The one with the black and white photo.
Benar, benar, benar.
Right, right, right.
Kalau begitu, Zeta, anda bisa minta request. Tapi sebelum itu, Ollie ingin mengambil sesuatu yang keren. Bentar ya.
In that case, Zeta, you can make a request. But before that, Ollie wants to get something cool. One second.
Apa? Apa, guys? Berunding dulu. Aku belum siap.
What? What, guys? Discuss first. I'm not ready yet.
Aku tahu! Apa ya? Aku mau Muryou Ramen aja deh.
I know! What should it be? I just want Free Ramen.
Ayo cepat! Nih, dari depan nih.
Come on, hurry! Here, from the front.
Keren nggak?
Cool, right?
Wuih, pedang! Apaan tuh? Cahayanya dari kepala asli.
Whoa, a sword! What's that? The light is coming from the head, for real.
Duh, ini benaran barusan...
Man, this just happened...
Mau lihat magic nggak? Nih, bukan sulap bukan sihir ya.
Want to see magic? Here, it's not a trick or sorcery.
Mana? Mana? Bukan sulap apa tuh?
Where? Where? What kind of magic is that?
Waaah! Magic! Birunya mentereng!
Waaaah! Magic! The blue is so bright!
Keren kan? Ini tuh...
Cool, right? This is...
Gila! Keren banget! Jadi biru!
Crazy! So cool! It turned blue!
Kalau gitu, ada request pose apa?
In that case, what pose request do you have?
Kalau potong kaki pakai pedangnya bisa nggak?
Can you cut your leg with the sword?
Astaga, lu brutal banget!
Goodness, you're so brutal!
Apa nggak ada yang lain gitu?
Is there nothing else?
Aduh... aku mau... pose Excalibur.
Oh man... I want... Excalibur pose.
Excalibur? Oh, kalau gitu Excalibur... Ini kan ya? Bentar.
Excalibur? Oh, in that case Excalibur... It's like this, right? Wait.
Aduh berat deh. Jreng! Kayak gini ya?
Man, it's heavy. Ta-da! Like this, right?
Iya, iya, benar, benar! Bisa dicabut nggak?
Yes, yes, right, right! Can it be pulled out?
Keren nggak?
Cool, right?
Mantap guys! Keren, keren, keren!
Great, guys! Cool, cool, cool!
Kalau gitu kita ke ini ya, pertanyaan berikutnya.
In that case, let's move on to the next question.
Mau, mau, mau!
I want to, I want to!
Oke, Kaela, ayo jangan kalah! Satu!
Okay, Kaela, come on, don't lose! One!
Aing... Ini sulit ya? Eh, sulit... Sulit.
I... Is this hard? Uh, hard... Hard.
Eh, kodok? Bukan...
Eh, frog? No...
Ini Angga! Anggar! Anggar!
It's Angga! Fencing! Fencing!
Kepiting! Kepiting!
Crab! Crab!
Bukan, bukan. Kalau gitu ini deh namanya apa.
No, no. In that case, what is this called.
Hah? Stretching?
Huh? Stretching?
Pemanasan? Olahraga?
Warming up? Exercise?
Bukan!
No!
Akrobat? Olahragawan?
Acrobatics? Athlete?
SKJ! Itu! Itu dia di chat udah ada yang hampir... oh udah ada yang benar.
SKJ! That's it! Someone in the chat is almost... oh, someone is correct.
Aku nggak lihat chat. Apa?
I'm not looking at the chat. What?
Kalau gitu... Marine-senpai! Marine! Mau tidur... terjatuh.
In that case... Marine-senpai! Marine! Going to sleep... falling down.
Oh, itu termasuk betul deng. Apa yang mana?
Oh, that's actually correct. Which one?
Jawabannya PIRATE!
The answer is PIRATE!
Theme: Pirate
Waaah! Bajak laut! Aku nggak nyontek sama sekali kok.
Waaaah! Pirate! I didn't cheat at all.
Oke. Dari tadi 「宝鐘マリンです」 Ahoy!
Okay. It's been "I am Houshou Marine." Ahoy!
Oke, oke, oke, ya sudah aku mau menghukum.
Okay, okay, okay, anyway, I want to punish.
Request! Bukan hukum! Kok menghukum?
Request! Not punish! Why punish?
Eh, boleh, boleh... roleplay boleh nggak roleplay gitu?
Eh, can we, can we... can we do a roleplay?
Oke, gimana, gimana?
Okay, how, how?
Oke, kamu sekarang ke dapur, terus kamu motong bawang... bawang bombay atau bawang apa kek...
Okay, now you go to the kitchen, then you cut onions... onions or whatever...
...bikin ramen tapi pakai pisau itu.
...to make ramen but use that knife.
Aku pengen ke dapur cuman malas, di sini aja ya? Aku roleplay.
I want to go to the kitchen but I'm lazy, just here okay? I'll roleplay.
Oh, ya sudah boleh, boleh, boleh. Cuman motong aja.
Oh, well that's fine, fine, fine. Just cutting.
Motong sambil kayak ceritanya ada ini, ada customer kayak, 'Ayo mau pesan apa?' gitu-gitu. Oke.
Cutting while acting like there's a customer like, 'Hey, what do you want to order?' and such. Okay.
いらっしゃいませ! 何食べる? 美味しいね味噌, 味噌いいね。 じゃ, お待たせ!
Welcome! What will you eat? Miso is good, miso is good. Here, thanks for waiting!
Yang dramatis! Yang dramatis terus!
The dramatic one! Keep it dramatic!
Ha? Yang lebih dramatis? SELAMAT DATANG! Ke kedai ramen chop saya! Ingin makan apakah anda?
Huh? More dramatic? WELCOME! To my ramen chop shop! What would you like to eat?
Tahukah kalian kalau daun bawang itu sangat baik untuk kesehatan anda?
Do you guys know that green onions are very good for your health?
Gigit! Kok macam ngiklan!
Bite! It's like an ad!
Udah deh. Oke lah, oke lah, oke lah. Malu gua.
That's enough. Okay then, okay then, okay then. I'm embarrassed.
Kalau gitu ini yang terakhir ya. Kaela, ayo bisa!
In that case, this is the last one. Kaela, come on, you can do it!
Oke, Kaela, ayo Kaela! Ayo Kaela aku bantu!
Okay Kaela, come on Kaela! Come on Kaela I'll help!
Iya, aku juga bantu. Kalau bantu, aku paling membantu!
Yes, I'll help too. If it's about helping, I'm the most helpful!
Ini sulit... sulit. Bukan... hmm bukan beneran sulit sih.
This is hard... hard. No... hmm it's not actually hard.
Menjaga keseimbangan? Bukan!
Keeping balance? No!
Terbang? Mabuk?
Flying? Drunk?
T-pose? Ayo jawab dulu. Ikan pesut lah, ikan pesut.
T-pose? Come on, answer first. Irrawaddy dolphin, Irrawaddy dolphin.
Ikan pesut? Iih!
Irrawaddy dolphin? Iih!
Apa sih? Ini, ini nih! Sudah, sudah! Sosmed, sosmed!
What? This, this! Enough, enough! Social media, social media!
Ikan lele? Joker? Superhero? Superhero!
Catfish? Joker? Superhero? Superhero!
Hero! Kok lu jago?
Hero! Why are you so good?
Theme: Hero
Superhero! Itu Kaela! Itu Kaela yang jawab! Bagus Kaela!
Superhero! That was Kaela! Kaela answered that! Nice Kaela!
Itu Kaela yang jawab? Iya, iya Kaela yang jawab itu.
Was it Kaela who answered? Yes, yes, Kaela answered that.
Oh sorry, suara kalian mirip-mirip. Iya, iya mirip emang.
Oh sorry, your voices sound similar. Yeah, yeah, they really do.
Ayo yang lain jawab. Hukumlah, hukumlah.
Come on, others answer. Punish, punish.
Loh, jangan dihukum dong. Apa ya?
Hey, don't punish. What is it?
Aduh apa ya? Umm...
Man, what is it? Umm...
Imut-imut kayak gini dihukum?
Cute like this and I'm being punished?
Masa sih?
Really?
Nah ya udah, kalau gitu...
Well then, in that case...
...itu pose paling tsundere kalau gitu.
...give us your best tsundere pose.
Oke, oke.
Okay, okay.
Ha!
Bukannya tsundere bawa pedang gitu ya?
Isn't a tsundere supposed to carry a sword?
Serem ya.
It's scary.
Bukannya aku suka sama kamu ya!
It's not like I like you or anything!
別に君のこととか好きじゃないんだから、
勘違いしないよね！
It's not like I like you,
so don't get the wrong idea!
ぶっ飛ばすよ！
I'll blow you away!
Sangat-sangat mendalami peran sekali.
Truly getting into the role.
Iya suka-suka mau, mau, Onegaishimasu, Kakak.
Yes, whatever you want, please, Sister.
Ya udah kalau gitu tadi serem makasih ya udah datang.
Alright then, that was scary, thanks for coming.
Ini ya makasih juga udah ngundang kita.
Thanks for inviting us too.
Makasih, makasih. Pedangnya disimpan lagi, Mas.
Thank you, thank you. Put the sword away, Sir.
Iya, iya. Nanti kusita.
Yes, yes. I'll confiscate it later.
Bye bye. Bye bye, Senpai!
Ayo, ayo, ayo ambil ramennya.
Come on, let's take the ramen.
Woi, woi, ramennya jangan diambil!
Hey, hey, don't take the ramen!
Nah barusan adalah Gen 3.
Well, that was Gen 3.
Tunggu, ini Ollie tancep lagi ke kepala Ollie kali ya.
Wait, let me stick this back in my head.
Chotto matte ne.
Wait a second.
Ittai!
Ouch!
Ketancep lagi.
It's stuck again.
Mou... Dokka Kenka?
Man... A toxic fight?
Ya kalau gitu kan tadi udah ada Gen 1, udah ada Gen 3...
Well, since we had Gen 1 and Gen 3...
...berarti seharusnya ada satu Gen lagi nggak sih?
...there should be one more Gen, right?
Moshi-moshi.
Hello?
Halo, halo, halo, di mana Ollie?
Hello, hello, hello, where is Ollie?
Kok serem ya?
This is scary.
Siapa ya? Halo, halo.
Who is it? Hello, hello.
Kayaknya aku tadi mendengar ada seseorang yang mencurigakan.
I think I heard someone suspicious.
Enggak kok, apa sih?
No, what do you mean?
Ayo buka! Hoi! Ayo, ayo, ayo!
Open up! Hey! Come on, come on, come on!
Hehe, horror dayo.
Hehe, it's horror.
Siapa kak ini? Horololive? Silakan perkenalkan diri.
Who is this? Horololive? Please introduce yourself.
Hai! Aku adalah...
Hi! I am...
I'm Pavolia Reine dari Holo ID Generasi 2!
I'm Pavolia Reine from Holo ID Generation 2!
Dan... Halo,
And... Hello,
aku Anya Melfissa dari Holo ID Generasi 2.
I'm Anya Melfissa from Holo ID Generation 2.
I don't talk like that.
Itu Anya Melfissa plus Shinto ya?
Is that Anya Melfissa plus Shinto?
Mirip gitu.
It's similar.
Oh my god.
Apaan itu banget?
What was that?
Lucu kan? Gemoy, gemoy!
Cute, right? So cute!
Kalau kalian pengen pose lagi, kalian harus main game.
If you want to pose again, you have to play a game.
Oke, baiklah. Game apa tuh?
Okay, fine. What game?
Kita bakal main Charades.
We're going to play Charades.
Oke, kalau kalian bener baru boleh pose lagi.
Okay, if you're right, then you can pose again.
Aku sih kayaknya jago banget nggak sih main ini?
I think I'm really good at this game, right?
Aku udah kepikiran mau request Ollie ngapain.
I already have an idea of what to ask Ollie to do.
Masa?
Really?
Ya udah kalau gitu kita langsung masuk aja nih ya.
Alright then, let's get right into it.
Pertanyaan pertama, stop!
First question, stop!
Oi!
Hey!
Zombie.
Theme: Zombie
Zombie! Let's go!
Kalau gitu... aduh, biar seru nih, kan dari tadi Ollie sendiri kan ya.
In that case... to make it more exciting, since Ollie's been alone this whole time.
Ollie panggil teman dulu kali ya biar bisa pose bareng.
Let me call a friend so we can pose together.
Eh siapa tuh? Siapa tuh?
Oh, who's that?
Woi! Udin!
Hey! Udin!
Aku jadi ngeri gitu diteriakin.
I got scared being shouted at.
Jadi nanti Ollie bakal pose sama Udin. Gemoy banget!
So Ollie will pose with Udin. So cute!
Udin muter! Muter!
Udin, spin! Spin!
Wah goyang ngebor hanya untuk tante.
Wow, doing the 'drilling' dance just for the auntie.
Aduh makasih banget ngebor banget nggak sih?
Oh, thank you so much, that's really 'drilling' isn't it?
Kalau gitu ada request apa nih Reine?
In that case, what's your request, Reine?
Aku mau kamu kayak... kamu tahu nggak sih kalau orang tuh dance off gitu?
I want you to... you know when people have a dance-off?
Aku mau kamu sama Udin kayak twerk-off gitu loh.
I want you and Udin to have a twerk-off.
Demi apa?
Are you serious?
Udin lu bisa?
Udin, can you do it?
Ya udah, ditantang tuh. Akan kita coba.
Alright, challenge accepted. We'll try it.
Ayo kita lihat siapa yang paling jago.
Let's see who's the best.
Ya pasti saya dong.
Obviously it's me.
Ini pantat aku nggak kelihatan, agak sedih ya.
My butt isn't showing, that's a bit sad.
Nggak apa-apa kayak dikipasin gitu.
It's okay, it's like being fanned.
Dikipasin pakai rok ya.
Fanned with the skirt.
Iya betul banget. Wah seru banget.
Yeah, exactly. Wow, so fun.
Sepertinya dejavu gitu deh.
Feels like déjà vu.
Mohon maaf sebelumnya saya tidak bermaksud.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
Tasukaru. Terima kasih.
Helpful. Thank you.
Oke yuk kita langsung aja kali ya.
Okay, let's just get straight to it.
Ini yang terakhir kali ya satu buat Anya gitu.
This is the last one, one for Anya.
Anya semangat.
Anya, good luck.
Oke siap.
Okay, ready.
Oke kalau gitu... satu!
Okay then... one!
Duh ini susah ya.
Oh, this is hard.
Udin bantu gua, Din.
Udin, help me.
Buat aku sesimpel itu ya.
Make it simple for me.
Kan kamu pro-nya, bisalah.
You're the pro, you can do it.
Gitu.
Like that.
Ngapain? Menyihir?
Doing what? Casting a spell?
Oh oke, Puppet Master gitu.
Oh okay, like a Puppet Master.
Theme: Sorcerer 魔法使い
Theme: Sorcerer
Sorcerer!
Keren banget ya!
So cool, right!
Keren, keren, keren, Game Master. Game Master.
Cool, cool, cool, Game Master. Game Master.
Lucu banget!
So cute!
Iya, kalau gitu ada request apa ya?
Yes, so what requests are there?
Oh, iya. Kamu sama Udin.
Oh, right. You and Udin.
Mumpung Udin ada di sini...
Since Udin is here...
Eh, aku pengen lihat kalian panco bisa nggak sih?
Eh, I want to see you guys arm wrestle, can you?
Bisa nggak ya? Din.
Can we? Udin.
Kita pengen lihat kalian panco, adu panco gitu bisa nggak ya?
We want to see you arm wrestle, like an arm wrestling match, is it possible?
Kita gandengan aja deh.
Let's just hold hands.
Panco sepertinya... gandengan aja nggak apa-apa.
Arm wrestling seems... holding hands is fine.
Tete.
Sister.
Lu pendek sih!
You're short!
Ih, kayak gini.
Eh, like this.
Ah, Tete!
Ah, Sister!
Tete tapi aku nggak punya...
Sister, but I don't have...
Tete...
Sister...
Bukan aku yang bilang!
I wasn't the one who said it!
Aku sadar diri kok, tidak apa-apa.
I'm self-aware, it's okay.
Kalau begitu, makasih, aduh Holoro-ku tersayang!
In that case, thank you, oh my dear Holoro!
Selamat ya, Cece!
Congratulations, Cece!
Congratulations for the 3D!
Tonton sampai menang, Ton.
Watch until victory.
Jangan lupa kalian nge-tweet pakai hashtag ini dong!
Don't forget to tweet using this hashtag!
Udah, udah pasti dong.
Already, definitely.
Kapan-kapan mampir tonton sampai habis susu stroberi yang di fountain kamu boleh nggak?
Can I drop by sometime and drink all the strawberry milk in your fountain?
Oke, sip!
Okay, deal!
Oke banget, oke banget.
Very okay, very okay.
Yes, thank you banget.
Yes, thank you so much.
Kalau gitu, bye-bye!
If so, bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Semangat!
Bye-bye! Good luck!
Thank you!
Wah, barusan adalah teman-teman Ollie dari Holo ID.
Wow, those were Ollie's friends from Holo ID.
Iya nggak, Din? Seru nggak?
Right, Udin? Was it fun?
Barusan dadakan.
That was sudden.
Heeh, emang.
Yeah, indeed.
Gitu lah, ada apa tuh di chat?
That's how it is, what's in the chat?
Kalian cepat banget, Ollie cuma bisa baca 'tasukaru' aja.
You guys are so fast, Ollie can only read 'tasukaru'.
Kalau gitu, ehm...
In that case, um...
Sebenarnya masih ada banyak nih, teman-teman. We still have a few more things that we want to show you.
Actually, there's still a lot more, friends. We still have a few more things that we want to show you.
So don't go anywhere, jangan go ke mana-mana.
So don't go anywhere, don't go anywhere.
え、この後はまだいっぱい、いっぱいあるよ！
Eh, there's still plenty more after this!
だからね、えーっと、ついて来いよ！
So, um, follow me!
Let's go!
Yah, kalau kalian pengen sikat miring sudah pasti awalnya harus kita sanggupin. Iya nggak?
Well, if you want to do the 'sikat miring', you definitely have to be able to do it first. Right?
Kalau kalian nggak sanggup, ya sanggupin!
If you can't, then make yourself able!
Kalau niat kalian sudah bulat. Kalau gitu niatnya itu kita lempar ke atas.
If your intention is firm. Then let's throw that intention upwards.
DONG! Sundul sayang.
BOOM! Header, dear.
Nah, ini kalau sundul sayang udah harus miring ya diagonal ya teman-teman, 45 derajat.
Now, for 'sundul sayang', it has to be tilted diagonally, friends, 45 degrees.
Nah, kalau udah sampai sini, berikutnya kalian ingin... DONG! Kicup manja.
Now, once you're here, next you want to... BOOM! Spoiled kiss.
Nah di sini pun kalian harus 'chuma' gitu lho, harus ada asmaranya.
And here you have to pout like that, you know, there must be romance.
Setelah kalian sudah sampai sini, kalian pengen... DONG! Iris tipis.
After you get here, you want to... BOOM! Thinly slice.
Iris tipis, se-tipis-tipisnya mungkin ya guys, kayak lagi masak gitu.
Thinly slice, as thin as possible guys, like when you're cooking.
Potong manis. Nah, iya kan?
Sweet cut. See?
Kalau kalian habis ngiris pengen itu pengen dicincang itu kan makanya kita potong-potong.
If you just finished slicing, you want it minced, right? That's why we cut it up.
Setelah kalian potong-potong kita tinggal... DONG! Sikat miring.
After you cut it up, we just... BOOM! Sikat miring.
Nah, tuh. Udin aja bisa. Apakah kalian bisa mengikutinya juga?
See? Even Udin can do it. Can you follow it too?
Jadi kalau kita gabungin semua ya teman-teman, tolong ikuti tutorial ini dengan baik.
So if we combine everything, friends, please follow this tutorial well.
Mari kita mulai.
Let's begin.
Pertama, kalau nggak sanggup, ya sanggupin!
First, if you can't, make yourself able!
Lempar niatnya!
Throw the intention!
Sundul sayang! DONG!
Header, dear! BOOM!
Kicup manja! DONG!
Spoiled kiss! BOOM!
Kemudian kita iris tipis. Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Then we thinly slice. Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Potong manis! Sret!
Sweet cut! Slash!
Dan Udin tahu berikutnya apa?
And Udin, do you know what's next?
Sikat miring!
Ya, sama teman-teman, kalian baru saja menghabiskan satu menit kalian tidak melakukan hal yang berguna.
Yes, friends, you just spent one minute of your life doing nothing useful.
Sekian!
That's all!
Mari kita ke scene yang berikutnya.
Let's move to the next scene.
Pemirsa, setelah ini kita akan kasih kalian tutorial caranya untuk bikin sikat miring.
Audience, after this we will give you a tutorial on how to do the 'Sikat Miring'.
Yah, kalau kalian pengen sikat miring sudah pasti awalnya harus kita sanggupin. Iya nggak?
Well, if you want to do the 'Sikat Miring', you definitely have to be able to do it first. Right?
Kalau kalian nggak sanggup, ya sanggupin!
If you can't, then make yourself able!
Kalau niat kalian sudah bulat. Kalau gitu niatnya itu kita lempar ke atas.
If your intention is firm. Then let's throw that intention upwards.
DONG! Sundul sayang.
BOOM! Header, dear.
Nah, ini kalau sundul sayang udah harus miring ya diagonal ya teman-teman, 45 derajat.
Now, for 'sundul sayang', it has to be tilted diagonally, friends, 45 degrees.
Nah, kalau udah sampai sini, berikutnya kalian ingin... DONG! Kicup manja.
Now, once you're here, next you want to... BOOM! Spoiled kiss.
Nah di sini pun kalian harus 'chuma' gitu lho, harus ada asmaranya.
And here you have to pout like that, you know, there must be romance.
Setelah kalian sudah sampai sini, kalian pengen... DONG! Iris tipis.
After you get here, you want to... BOOM! Thinly slice.
Iris tipis, se-tipis-tipisnya mungkin ya guys, kayak lagi masak gitu.
Thinly slice, as thin as possible guys, like when you're cooking.
Potong manis. Nah, iya kan?
Sweet cut. See?
Kalau kalian habis ngiris pengen itu pengen dicincang itu kan makanya kita potong-potong.
If you just finished slicing, you want it minced, right? That's why we cut it up.
Setelah kalian potong-potong kita tinggal... DONG! Sikat miring.
After you cut it up, we just... BOOM! Sikat miring.
Nah, tuh. Udin aja bisa. Apakah kalian bisa mengikutinya juga?
See? Even Udin can do it. Can you follow it too?
Jadi kalau kita gabungin semua ya teman-teman, tolong ikuti tutorial ini dengan baik.
So if we combine everything, friends, please follow this tutorial well.
Mari kita mulai.
Let's begin.
Pertama, kalau nggak sanggup, ya sanggupin!
First, if you can't, make yourself able!
Lempar niatnya!
Throw the intention!
Sundul sayang! DONG!
Header, dear! BOOM!
Yah, sama teman-teman,
Well then, friends,
kalian baru saja menghabiskan satu menit kalian
you have just spent one minute of your time
tidak melakukan hal yang berguna.
not doing anything useful.
Sian! Mari kita ke scene yang berikutnya.
Too bad! Let's move on to the next scene.
Dengarkanlah suaraku
Listen to my voice
IDENTITY
id:entity voices
Berdiri di tengah terangnya kilau cahaya
Standing in the middle of bright glittering light
Ohayou konbanwa kami serukan kepada dunia
Ohayou, konbanwa, we shout out to the world
Mengudara 'tuk hari ini
Broadcasting for today
bagian dari diri yang manakah
which part of myself
Yang harus kutunjukkan?
Should I show?
Ku tak dapat pernah memutuskan
I could never decide
Lalu suatu hari pesan-pesan berdatangan
Then one day, messages started coming
Kata-kata perih membuatku kehilangan arah
Stinging words made me lose my way
Senyuman di balik layar sanggupkah untuk kupertahankan?
The smile behind the screen, can I maintain it?
Tak pernah ingin kecewakan siapa pun di luar sana
Never want to disappoint anyone out there
Namun di saat banyaknya suara
But in the midst of many voices
Manakah yang ku harus dengar?
Which one should I listen to?
Mencoba mendengarkan suara di dalam hati
Trying to listen to the voice inside my heart
Inilah diri yang ingin ku selalu tunjukkan
This is the self that I always want to show
Berbagai suara yang berpadu
Various voices that blend
dan menjadi satu
and become one
IDENTITY
Hari-hari berlalu dan sekarang ku di sini
Days go by and now I'm here
Berdiri di tepi panggung ini menyambut dunia
Standing on the edge of this stage, welcoming the world
Tetapi ku tak sendiri bersama lainnya sekarang
But I'm not alone, with others now
Seakan seperti keluarga bersatu dalam perbedaan
Like a family, united in diversity
Namun di saat banyaknya perbedaan
But in the midst of many differences
Dapatkah harmoni tercipta?
Can harmony be created?
Bergandengan tangan berjuang raih mimpi bersama
Holding hands, struggling to achieve dreams together
Semua bersorak dengan suara gempita
Everyone cheers with a thunderous voice
Menyebarkan kebahagiaan di mana pun itu
Spreading happiness wherever it is
Bergemuruh
Resounding
Panggung yang lebih besar kini menunggu
A bigger stage is now waiting
Waktunya telah tiba tanpa adanya ragu
The time has come without any doubt
Dengan semua warna suara menjadi harmoni
With all colors of voices becoming harmony
Sebenarnya
Truly
Hilanglah semua rasa bimbang di hati
All feelings of doubt in the heart are gone
Inilah diri yang ingin ku selalu tunjukkan
This is the self that I always want to show
Berbagai suara yang berpadu
Various voices that blend
Dalam perbedaan takkan pernah tergoyahkan
In diversity, will never be shaken
Dan menjadi satu IDENTITY
And become one, IDENTITY
Ohayou konbanwa otsukaresama deshita
Ohayou konbanwa kita 'kan jumpa lagi
Ohayou, konbanwa, we will meet again
Capek! So tired.
I'm exhausted! So tired.
But that's okay.
疲れたけど、楽しいよ！
I'm tired, but it's fun!
Sangat menyenangkan!
It's so much fun!
Dan apakah kalian melihat kita tampilnya di mana?
And did you guys see where we are performing?
皆見てる？今...
Is everyone watching? Right now...
...ID Arena にいますよ！
...we are at the ID Arena!
Welcome to ID Arena!
And it's Ollie-themed as well! So with it there, with it there, with it up there, it was so good! I see all of you guys too!
Hi! Wah, seneng banget! Seneng kan? Keren kan?
Hi! Wow, I'm so happy! You're happy too, right? It's cool, isn't it?
Top-A Ollie! Uh oh, barusan adalah Identity Voices.
Top-A Ollie! Uh oh, that was Identity Voices just now.
Tapi bukan hanya itu, kita... Ollie ada beberapa pengumuman nih.
But that's not all, we... Ollie has a few announcements.
Yang pertama namanya... wait, so merch that I prepared for everyone!
The first one is... wait, so merch that I prepared for everyone!
Ini dia merch yang Ollie siapkan buat kalian! うちのみなさんのために用意しました！
Here's the merch Ollie prepared for you! I prepared this for all of you!
それでは、これだ！ドン！
So, here it is! Bam!
The SUPER KAWAII ZOMBIE COACH JACKET! Yeah!
So, um... I noticed that most of my goods, not all of them were wearable.
Nggak semuanya portable gitu kan ya.
Not all of them are wearable, right?
Ini Ollie ingin membikin sesuatu yang bisa kalian pakai langsung.
Ollie wanted to make something that you can wear directly.
Kita bilang aja nih seragam kalian. You guys can see this as your uniforms!
Let's just call this your uniform. You guys can see this as your uniforms!
So I worked real hard so that you guys can have this.
It's going to be really cool! Unik banget sih.
It's going to be really cool! It's very unique.
Yang aslinya jauh lebih keren. The real thing is a lot cooler than it is.
The real thing is much cooler. The real thing is a lot cooler than it is.
お手元でもっとかっこよかったよ！ぜひぜひね！
It's even cooler in person! So by all means!
Ini nanti bakal dijual berbarengan bersama Reine dan Anya setelah mini live kita.
This will be on sale along with Reine and Anya's after our mini-live.
After our mini-live, this will be on sale, so make sure that you guys are readying your pockets! Ne?
After our mini-live, this will be on sale, so make sure that you guys are readying your pockets! Right?
Oh, いっぱい、いっぱい買ってね！
Oh, please buy lots and lots of them!
Kemudian ada satu lagi nih pengumuman, yaitu ini, ini... hehehe.
Then there's one more announcement, and it's this... hehehe.
Eksklusif hanya untuk kalian yang nonton, Ollie akan bikin...
Exclusively for those of you watching, Ollie is going to make...
Yeah! I'll be making a game! It's a ゲームをつくりますよ！
Yeah! I'll be making a game! I'm making a game!
Untuk detailnya, nonton aja nanti sampai akhir stream!
For the details, just watch until the end of the stream!
If you guys want to know more about the details, make sure you watch until the end of the ohirome stream!
Oh, kemudian yang terakhir, ada sesuatu yang Ollie ingin sangat... b-b-b...
Oh, and lastly, there's something Ollie really wants to... b-b-b...
...nggak bisa ngomong. Sorry, so nervous.
...I can't speak. Sorry, I'm so nervous.
Ada yang ingin Ollie sampaikan kepada kalian.
There's something I want to tell you guys.
I want to really tell you guys. 言いたいことがあります。
I want to really tell you guys. There's something I want to say.
Tolong dengarkan ya.
Please listen.
Nah, um... actually I already summed it up over here.
Sebenarnya udah Ollie rangkum sih ya kata-katanya Ollie di sebelah sini.
Actually, I've summarized my words over here.
I already have everything written out, but just so that we're on the same page...
...I want to say thank you from the very bottom of my heart because...
...you know, if it weren't for you guys, if you guys didn't give me a chance to get on this stage...
...I would've only been an undead. Ollie mungkin nggak akan ada di sini.
...I would've only been an undead. Ollie might not even be here.
Dan berkat kalian Ollie juga tetap di sini. It's thanks to you guys that I'm still here.
And thanks to you, Ollie is still here. It's thanks to you guys that I'm still here.
そうね、みんなのおかげで、オーリーはここに立っているよ。
That's right, thanks to everyone, Ollie is standing here.
こんなに... だからね、めちゃくちゃ感謝してるよ。
This much... so I'm incredibly grateful.
Mm, ini agak emoi ya. It's a little bit emotional, but I really do mean it.
Mm, this is a bit emotional. It's a little bit emotional, but I really do mean it.
I know it's a little bit cliché, I know you guys hear it a lot, but this comes for me personally...
...the very deepest part of my heart. Ini datang dari hati Ollie yang terdalam.
...the very deepest part of my heart. This comes from the deepest part of Ollie's heart.
Oleh karena itu, terima kasih banyak.
Because of that, thank you very much.
いつも応援してくれて、本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for always supporting me.
Um, and again, I love you guys all so much!
You guys mean the world to me. You guys never know. So thank you very much.
Wah, emoi na! Agak sedikit emosional ya.
Wow, how emotional! It's a little bit emotional.
Udah nangis belum? Are you guys crying? Hehe.
Are you crying yet? Are you guys crying? Hehe.
Oh, kalau gitu... ada satu lagi nih. Kalau belum itu, belum selesai nggak sih?
Oh, in that case... there's one more. If we haven't done that, it's not over yet, right?
If we haven't sung that, it's not over yet, isn't it? あれはまだあるよ！
If we haven't sung that, it's not over yet, isn't it? That is still to come!
みんな知ってる？Do you guys know? Apakah kalian tahu?
Does everyone know? Do you guys know? Do you know?
Mm, THE LAST SONG! Of course, from the very first thing that I've ever produced myself!
Yeah! Kalau gitu kita langsung aja tanpa basa-basi lagi.
Yeah! Then let's just get straight to it without further ado.
This is the final song! Lagu terakhir! 最後の曲！
This is the final song! The last song! The final song!
JOLLIE JOLLIE! Yeah!
クーレイジオリー！！
KUREIJI JOLLIE!!
へ？私？
Eh? Me?
退屈な日常
A boring daily life
このままでいいの？
Is it okay to stay like this?
通知いって携帯
The notification goes off, and on my phone...
見てるばかりで何で？
...I'm just staring at it, why?
ハート止まっていても
Even if my heart has stopped
心震わせたいの
I want to make my soul tremble
これからが Show time
From now on it's Show time
歩き出してこうか
Shall we start walking?
One Two Three で星を見つけて
Find a star with One Two Three
Four Five Six で君を見つけたの
Found you with Four Five Six
Seven Eight Nine で夢を見つめて
Gaze at a dream with Seven Eight Nine
9, 8...
7, 6...
5, 4...
3, 2, 1
行くぞ!!
Let's go!!
ツギハギカラダに
To this patchwork body
溢れていくよ memory
Memories are overflowing
ズキズキアタマに
In this throbbing head
特効薬の 我爱你
The specific remedy is 'I love you'
ツギツギ脳内に
One after another in my brain
ポップなメロディ
Pop melodies
ウキウキなパーティー
An exciting party
おい! おい! おい! おい!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
ARE YOU READY? YEAH!
JOLLIE JOLLIE NIGHT
ドレスコードなんてないの
There's no such thing as a dress code
SHINY TIMES NOW
煌めいていくよ舞台
The stage is starting to sparkle
CRAZY KUREIJI DANCE
踊るようなジャーニー
A journey like dancing
見つけちゃったの
I've found it
とっておきの居場所
My very special place
LET'S GO!!
SUPER! MEGA!
HYPER! SISTER!
CHO KAWAII CHO YABAI!!
Super cute! Super amazing!!
KUREIJI KUREIJI KUREIJI KUREIJI
SUPER! MEGA!
HYPER! SISTER!
CHO KAWAII CHO YABAI!!
Super cute! Super amazing!!
OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE
SADLIER な事もたまにあるんだ
Sometimes things are a bit sadlier
ヤダヤダ
No, no
SADLIER な雨が降ることもあるんだ
Sometimes sadlier rain falls
まだだ まだだ
Not yet, not yet
だけど IT'S ALL RIGHT!
But it's all right!
おい! いける暇 NO TIME! おい!
Hey! No time for that! Hey!
これからが SHOW TIME
From now on, it's show time
虹がかかるよ
A rainbow will appear
鼓動がするくらい
So much that my heart pounds
今が好きなの
I love right now
時忘れるくらい
So much that I forget time
熱狂して万々歳
Let's go wild and celebrate
体温上がってるトゥナイト
My temperature is rising tonight
BPMは上限無い
There's no limit to the BPM
際限ないこの鬼才
This boundless genius
皆に共有したい!
I want to share it with everyone!
アストロの端天の足りない
Not enough of the astro's edge of heaven
あそこ固まる超絶世界
A transcendent world gathering there
主役アタシ以外に無いじゃん?
There's no main character but me, right?
PUT YOUR HANDS UP ミュータント集会
PUT YOUR HANDS UP, mutant meeting
ミラーボール反射してブルーライト
Mirror ball reflecting blue light
アンサンブルでデンジャーじゃない?
Isn't it dangerous in an ensemble?
今夜は誰も眠らせないよ
Tonight, I won't let anyone sleep
JOLLIE JOLLIE JOLLIE NIGHT
徹頭徹尾自信満々
Full of confidence from start to finish
意気揚々と目配せして
Winking triumphantly
ヒトの進化に還元
Contributing to human evolution
GIVE ME GIVE ME 褒め言葉
GIVE ME GIVE ME words of praise
ハイスコアヘアスタイル
High score hairstyle
メンタルゲージも MAX
Mental gauge is also MAX
ハトに豆鉄砲食らわせて
Catching the pigeons off guard
急転直下で OH CRAZY!
A sudden turn, OH CRAZY!
ツギハギカラダに
To this patchwork body
繋がってく想い
Feelings are connecting
カチコチハードに
In this stiff heart
詰め込んだ願い
Wishes are packed
ツギツギ皆に
One after another to everyone
愛してよ 我爱你
Love me, 'I love you'
JOLLIE JOLLIE all I need
KUREIJI PARTY NIGHT
ツギハギカラダに
To this patchwork body
溢れていくよ memory
Memories are overflowing
ズキズキアタマに
In this throbbing head
特効薬の 我爱你
The specific remedy is 'I love you'
おい! ツギツギ脳内に... おい!
Hey! One after another in my brain... Hey!
おい! ポップなメロディ おい!
Hey! Pop melodies! Hey!
おい! ウキウキなパーティー おい!
Hey! An exciting party! Hey!
ARE YOU READY? YEAH!
JOLLIE JOLLIE NIGHT
ドレスコードなんてないの
There's no such thing as a dress code
SHINY TIMES NOW
煌めいていくよ舞台
The stage is starting to sparkle
CRAZY KUREIJI DANCE
踊るようなジャーニー
A journey like dancing
見つけちゃったの
I've found it
とっておきの居場所
My very special place
LET'S GO!!
SUPER! MEGA!
HYPER! SISTER!
CHO KAWAII CHO YABAI!!
Super cute! Super amazing!!
KUREIJI KUREIJI KUREIJI KUREIJI
SUPER! MEGA!
HYPER! SISTER!
CHO KAWAII CHO YABAI!!
Super cute! Super amazing!!
OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE
HEY! JOLLIE JOLLIE!
LET'S PARTY NIGHT!
STAY UP ALL NIGHT LONG!
JOLLIE JOLLIE JOLLIE YEAH!
HEY! JOLLIE JOLLIE!
LET'S PARTY NIGHT!
STAY UP ALL NIGHT LONG!
KUREIJI PARTY NIGHT!
HEY! JOLLIE JOLLIE!
LET'S PARTY NIGHT!
STAY UP ALL NIGHT LONG!
JOLLIE JOLLIE JOLLIE YEAH!
HEY! JOLLIE JOLLIE!
LET'S PARTY NIGHT!
STAY UP ALL NIGHT LONG!
JOLLIE JOLLIE JOLLIE YEAH!
ほれよ! オリーでーす!
There you go! It's Ollie!
Udah nonton Jollie Jollie? Gimana perasaannya Jollie Jollie?
Have you watched Jollie Jollie? How was it?
Makasih semuanya udah nonton sampai sini...
Thank you everyone for watching until now...
Ollie seneng kalian bisa datang ke showcase-nya Ollie yang pertama...
Ollie is happy you guys could come to Ollie's first showcase...
...dan nonton sampai showcase Ollie yang pertama ya...
...and watch until Ollie's first showcase...
Makasih...
Thank you...
いつも推してくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you for always supporting me.
Makasih selalu mendukung Ollie...
Thank you for always supporting Ollie...
Thank you so much for your support!
We actually made it!
I'm so happy!
Well, I'll be on a bigger stage next time!
So until then, see you guys next time!
Bye-bye!
おつくれいじー!
Good work, Kureiji!
I've always wondered how it'd be like if we spent our days together.
Coming soon.