(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
- Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
- Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
- Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
- Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
[Attention For Visitors]
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
公演はまもなく開始いたします。
The concert will be starting soon.
注意事項：演出による光の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援は可能です。
Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK.
コンサートグッズ第2次販売受付中！
Second round of concert merchandise now on sale!
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
DRAWN TO DAWN
The concert will be starting soon. 公演はまもなく開始いたします。
The concert will start shortly.
Attention For Visitors
演出の一部に、激しく明滅する箇所がございます。声出しでの応援が可能です。
Flashing lights will be used. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
DRAWN TO DAWN
The concert will be starting soon. 公演はまもなく開始いたします。
The concert will start shortly.
Attention For Visitors
演出の一部に、激しく明滅する箇所がございます。声出しでの応援が可能です。
Flashing lights will be used. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
DRAWN TO DAWN
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Drawn to Dawn — Fan Messages
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Drawn to Dawn — Fan Messages
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Kiara! Ina!
Thank you all so much for coming to...
...Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis's first concert, Drawn to Dawn!
Ki... Thank you, thank you.
Ki-ki-ri-ki!
I am Takanashi Kiara, and...
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone! It's Ninomae Ina'nis!
That's right, it's finally time for our concert! Is everyone hyped?
Before we kick things off, we have some important safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of any recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
But what... But what if I'm smoking hot?
Oh, Kiara...
If you start feeling unwell at any point, please don't push yourself. Just reach out to the nearest staff member for help, and hydrate!
For everyone's safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This includes moshing...
No moshing, I mean it!
Moshing, diving, sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively, or throwing objects towards the stage.
Climbing onto the stage, intentionally blocking the aisles, or rushing toward the front is also (surprise!) not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting, erratic lightstick movements, or any extreme motions that might interfere with the experience of those around you. Be considerate!
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or the venue staff, you may be asked to leave the venue.
Yes, please keep in mind that the venue organizers, performers, and staff cannot be held responsible for any accidents, equipment damage, or trouble caused by failing to follow instructions.
Additionally, any costs for damages resulting from ignoring these rules will be the responsibility of the person involved, so be careful, guys, okay?
There are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today, and you might appear in footage or photos.
These may be used for promotional purposes later on, so please keep that in mind.
And finally... big news! Today's concert will be in two parts!
There's a part for Kiara and a part for me, so please look forward to both of them!
All right! That is it for the rules. The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! See you!
Tako-tori! Tako-tori! Tako-tori! Tako-tori! Tako-tori!
「オイ！オイ！オイ！オイ！」
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
「オイ！オイ！オイ！オイ！」
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
「オイ！オイ！オイ！オイ！」
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
「AHOY MATEY!」
AHOY MATEY!
「オイ！オイ！オイ！オイ！」
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
A!
幽閉利口逝く前に
Before locking up the clever one...
ユーヘイじゃ利口に難儀ダーリン
Locking up the clever one is a pain, darling
幽閉ストップ知ってないし
Don't lock me up! It's not like I knew
勘弁にしといてなんて惨忍
Give me a break! You're so cruel
人様願う欠片のアイロニ
The wishes of the people feel like scraps of irony
だれもが願う無機質なような
Everyone's wishing for a mechanical kind of thing
一足先に始めてたいような
Wanting to get in on it before everyone else
先が見えないヴァージンハッピーショー
A virgin happy show with an unpredictable future
無いの新たにお願い1つ
I don't have a single brand-new wish
愛も変わらずおまけにワーニング ワーニング
The same love as ever, plus a warning, warning
無いのあなたにお願い1つ
I don't have a single wish for you
張り詰めた思い込め
Putting all my tense thoughts into it
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯をむき出してパッパッパ
Baring your fangs, pa-pa-pa
照れくさいね
This is so embarrassing, isn't it?
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯を突き出してパッパッパッ ハハ
Letting your fangs poke out, pa-pa-pa-pa, haha
YOU ARE KING
無邪気に遊ぶ期待期待のダーリン
Playing innocently, you're the darling I've been wishing for
健気に見笑う痛い痛いの消える
When you laugh admirably, all of my pain disappears
無様に〇ねる苦い思いも無くなって
And I can die clumsily, my bitter feelings fading too
ラララ ブウ ラッタッタ
La-la-la, boo, rat-tat-tat
嫌い嫌いの最低泣いてダウン
I hate it, it's the worst—I burst into tears and I'm down
毎度新たにお願い1つ
Every time, I have one new wish...
愛も変わらずピックアップのワーニング ワーニング
The same love as ever, plus a picked-up warning, warning
無いのあなたにお願い1つ
I don't have a single wish for you
張り詰めた思い込め
Putting all my tense thoughts into it
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯をむき出してパッパッパ
Baring your fangs, pa-pa-pa
邪魔くさいね
This is so bothersome, isn't it?
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯を突き出してパッパッパッ ハハ
Letting your fangs poke out, pa-pa-pa-pa, haha
YOU ARE KING
Kikiriki! Welcome to Day 1 of Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara. Let's kick it off!
瞬く 星の降り立つ
The twinkling stars landing...
欠けたステップを繋ぎ合わせた
...piecing together the chipped steps...
メモリー
...into a memory.
聖なる従者が集う
Where the holy servants gather,
神話の理
the principles of myth,
祈りに耳を澄ませ
listen closely to the prayers.
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice,
あらがう言葉
the words that resist,
導く鼓動が呼ぶ
the guiding heartbeat calls.
ほむら降り注ぐ空に 身を焦がして
Burning my body in the sky where flames pour down,
乱れた空が描いた イミテーション
an imitation drawn by the chaotic sky.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみせる
I will survive even the many trials that pile up.
I will live to keep on fighting till the dawn
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
Louder!
数えれば先の見えない
With an invisible future...
ゼロの境界 迷い込んだとしても
...even if I wander into the border of zero...
何度も繰り返される 孤独の終焉
...the end of loneliness repeated over and over,
そこに残ったアンサー
the answer left there.
Don't break, we will never give up
Don't break, 羽ばたくそして
Don't break, and then flap my wings,
消せない強さは 時の標
the unerasable strength is the guidepost of time.
灰が舞い上がる大地 身を焦がして
Burning my body on the land where ashes soar,
凍る夜明けの中 目を覚ます
waking up in the freezing dawn.
刃交じり合う切っ先 交わした契りは
The promise exchanged at the tips of clashing blades...
Rise and truth, turn to light after pain to the day
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go run, what awaits me in the dark
Could you tell me, please, where I need to go
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice,
みなぎる決意は 影を払う
the overflowing determination dispels the shadows.
ほむら降り注ぐ空に 身を焦がして
Burning my body in the sky where flames pour down,
乱れた空が描いた イミテーション
an imitation drawn by the chaotic sky.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみせる
I will survive even the many trials that pile up,
Blazing flame, 遠く未来照らす
blazing flame, illuminating the distant future.
Luminous, and in the next life, I promise I will find you
Clap your hands!
Lying down on the floor late night and you don't know
Don't know, don't know what to do
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right, if yes or no
The storm hits hard and you're losing the way
Just take a chance and dance in the rain
'Cause you got the key, never throw it away
Don't forget, don't forget what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So go ahead and do it, do it
If you want it, let's get to it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
So don't be afraid, trust your heart, keep your head in the game
(Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid)
Gotta make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait
Start a fire today
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
We ain't looking back, take the fast lane now
In the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud
Going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed
That's how we like it
You heard what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So take a step and move it, move it
'Less you try you won't get through it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
So don't be afraid, trust your heart, keep your head in the game
(Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid)
Let go of the past tonight
Choose the future only you define
Even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive
From the ashes you rise
Clap!
Everybody!
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
So don't be afraid, trust your heart, keep your head in the game
(Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid)
Gotta make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait
Start a fire today
Ah, yeah!
Ah!
Kikuriki!
Hello! Welcome, everybody, to...
Takanashi Kiara and Hololive English's first-ever concert...
...'DRUM TO MY OWN DRUM'!
I can hear you guys so clearly, and I can see you guys so clearly!
Kikuriki! Kikuriki!
Oh my god! We are in Los Angeles!
So, we started off with the iconic and classic songs of mine, 'HINOTORI' and 'SPARKS'!
Don't we love those songs? Was that hype?
Yeah, you guys know, like, 'HINOTORI' was my first-ever original song to put out, and it was like the beginning of my music...
...career.
...history, my musical journey,
and it's a song that means a lot to me,
and it's just so hype.
It was also the first ever time that I appeared in 3D, I think,
long time ago, at Fes in Japan, right? Remember?
Good times! Yeah!
Thank you so much for cheering so loudly. You did so well!
Yeah!
I have been training so hard the past months in the gym,
trying to get stamina for this day,
because I think I learned about...
...learned and relearned about 20 choreographies!
Yeah! Crazy, right?
Damn, that was a lot of work.
But finally the day has come to show it all to all of you.
I want to say hi, by the way,
to all the live viewers worldwide.
There are so many cinemas showing this concert right now!
Hello world!
Can you hear me? I wonder if I can hear them.
Can I hear them over the continents?
Well, that's you guys!
But I think I can hear them, yeah!
Also, there are some girls watching on YouTube right now,
like Ollie and all the EN members!
Hi! Thank you!
So excited!
I... I have to give a little bit of an announcement from my side, actually.
Because it's very important, it has to be in the free part because...
...everybody needs to hear this.
My new album, Fogel Frei, you bought it, right?
Thank you!
But in case you didn't, a second round of album sales has begun!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
So if you missed it previously, or you want a new copy,
starting from Saturday, March 28th at 11:00 PM,
I don't know which time zone!
Who knows, we'll find out, probably JST.
You will be able to order Fogel Frei again!
So please, everybody, order Fogel Frei!
So far, the songs that I performed up until now were not even from Fogel Frei!
But don't worry, I'm squeezing everything in that I can!
Okay guys!
You probably are aware of this,
but the free part usually ends...
...after an MC.
But "Free part, you only had two songs?"
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah!
Don't worry, I told staff, we can't be having that!
I want the free part to have a little bit more, yeah!
So it will continue a little bit more
and then it will cut before another MC, so just so you know.
And then, once it cuts, please...
...streaming tickets are available still, in the description and in the pinned comments!
Probably there!
Yeah! So make sure to get your ticket because what you haven't even seen yet is my colleague,
Ninomae Ina'nis, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah! The concert is split in half,
so today you only have me in the free part,
but later, if you want to see more of me and Ina,
go get streaming tickets! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
So with that, it is time to move on...
...to many other songs!
All right!
Are you ready?!
All right! Here is the next song. Enjoy!
Passing by familiar roads,
I couldn't find...
...the reason why.
Who I am, you couldn't know,
stuck in the ruins...
...of my delusion.
In-between pseudo-reality,
my own desire...
...keeps me near you.
Moving faster than the light can,
I'm in the absence of...
Not looking back
Did I lose my way?
I can see the day
When I can reach you again
And then can I let go?
I can hear your voice
Leading me through the void
Fade away
To the grey
Eternally, I'm walking by
The lights flash before my eyes
Told to move, a silent step for me
Still I'm reaching out to you
Connections are my source of light
A temporal soul, so I'll survive one day
Eventually, the light, it will lead me back to you, see me
Fever night
I'm tired of the same song
Every day like it's on repeat
I need a risky breakdown
Oh honey, the night is young
We don't need a steady, simple melody
Can you make it a little more eternal?
Take me away, like it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music?
Baby, meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive, move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, got me dancing, fever night, fever, run through me
鼓動と鼓動を合わせて Follow my heartbeat
Aligning our heartbeats, follow my heartbeat
パラパラパラパラパラパラ 聴かせてあげる
Para-para-para-para-para-para, I'll let you hear it
心拍数合わせて Follow my heartbeat
Aligning our heart rates, follow my heartbeat
Pacing four with a bump
I'm in a trance with the way that you're moving
You got me shining, glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild
Who cares who's watching us, so baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive, moving my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, got me dancing, fever night, fever, run through me
Baby, can we dance until the daylight, crazy?
That's the sound of making of you
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.