(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis 1st Concert 'Drawn to Dawn' を応援しています！
Supporting Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis 1st Concert "Drawn to Dawn"!
二人のライブが素晴らしいものになりますように！！
May your concert together be a wonderful one!!
初のライブ開催おめでとうございます！
Congratulations on your first concert!!
二人の活動を後ろから応援出来て幸せです！！
I'm happy to be able to support you from behind!!
いつまでも応援し続けます！
I'll support you forever!
たくさん練習してきた事、皆に魅せてきてね！
Show everyone everything you've practiced so hard for!
二人とも、ずっと応援してるよ！
I'm supporting you both forever!
最高のライブになりますように！！
Wishing you the best concert!!
The concert will be starting soon.
[Announcement] The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
[Notice] Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Merch] 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
DRAWN TO DAWN Special Items
[Merch] "Drawn to Dawn" Special Items
二人のライブが最高に楽しいものになりますように！
Hope your concert is the most fun ever!
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Title: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
[Title: Attention For Visitors]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Title: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering is ok.
[Attention For Visitors]
[Flashing lights warning / Cheering is ok]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演まで今しばらくお待ちください。
[Text: The concert will be starting soon.]
Attention For Visitors
[Text: Attention For Visitors]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Text: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
開演まで今しばらくお待ちください。
[Text: The concert will be starting soon.]
Wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah...
ひとつ　ふたつ
One, two...
数えては
As I count them,
消えていく星に
To the stars that fade away,
願いを込めて
I make a wish.
The concert will be starting soon.
開演まで、いましばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while longer until the show starts.
録音・録画・アップロードは禁止されています。
各プラットフォームの規約に従いお楽しみください。
Recording, filming, and uploading are prohibited.
Please follow the rules of each platform.
Attention For Visitors
[Notice] Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Merch] 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Attention For Visitors
[Title: Attention For Visitors]
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Fan Messages and Illustrations
Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis 1st Concert
"Drawn to Dawn"
[Title: Drawn to Dawn Concert]
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
[Title: Attention For Visitors]
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Fan Messages and Illustrations
DRAWN TO DAWN
応援メッセージ
[Title: Drawn to Dawn]
[Fan Support Messages]
The concert will be starting soon.
開演まで、しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment until the show begins.
Attention For Visitors
激しい光の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
[Attention For Visitors]
Be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
DRAWN TO DAWN
応援メッセージ
[Title: Drawn to Dawn]
[Fan Support Messages]
開演まで、いましばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
演出の都合上、フラッシュ・強力な光を放つ機器の使用はご遠慮ください。
声出し・応援、大歓迎です！
Attention For Visitors
Please refrain from using flashes or strong lights for production reasons.
Vocal cheering and support are welcome!
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
キアラ！ キアラ！ キアラ！
Kiara! Kiara! Kiara!
Wah! Wah! Wah! Wah!
KIARA! INA! KIARA! INA! KIARA! INA!
Thank you all so much for coming to...
Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis's
first concert, "Drawn to Dawn"!
Thank you, thank you!
KIKKERIKII!
Yay! I am Takanashi Kiara, and...
Good morning, afternoon, evening everyone!
As you know, I'm Ninomae Ina'nis!
That's right, it's finally time for our concert!
Is everyone hyped?
Before we kick things off, we have some important
safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of any recording
equipment are strictly prohibited during the show.
Also, the venue is smoke-free,
so please refrain from smoking inside.
But what if I'm smoking hot?
Minus Kiara! Hehehe!
If you start feeling unwell at any point,
please don't push yourself.
Just reach out to the nearest staff member
for help. And hydrate!
For everyone's safety, please avoid
any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This includes moshing...
No moshing! I mean it!
Moshing, diving, sitting on shoulders,
jumping excessively, or throwing objects.
Climbing onto the stage, blocking the aisles,
or rushing the front is also not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting,
erratic lightstick movements...
...or any extreme motions that might
interfere with others. Be considerate.
If you don't follow the staff instructions,
you may be asked to leave. Nooo!
Please keep in mind that the organizers,
performers, and staff cannot be held responsible...
...for any accidents, damage, or trouble
caused by failing to follow instructions.
Any cost for damages from ignoring these rules
will be the responsibility of the person involved.
So be careful guys, okay?
There are cameras in the venue today,
and you might appear in footage or photos.
These may be used for promotional purposes,
so please keep that in mind.
Y'all are looking cute!
And finally, big news!
Today's concert will be in two parts!
There's a part for Kiara and a part for me,
so please look forward to both of them!
Alright, that is it for the rules!
The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! See you soon!
TAKO-TORI! TAKO-TORI! TAKO-TORI!
DRAWN TO DAWN
[Logo: Drawn to Dawn]
Kiara! Kiara! Kiara! Kiara!
Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina!
TAKO∞TAKOVER
[Song: TAKO∞TAKOVER]
Enlightened by the powers that be
The ruler of a world run on INAsanity
It’s clear to me they still can’t see
I’m just a normal girl
Empowered by the Ancient One’s call
We’re gonna be punstoppable, we’re not a cult
Nonsensical and nautical adventures lie in wait!!
Gimme a ONE EIGHT!!
ICHI! HACHI! TAKODACHI!
ONE! EIGHT! TAKODACHI!
Ina Ina Ina
Ina Ina
俺のイナの世界線
My Ina world line
守るためにタコになろう！！
To protect it, let’s become a Tako!!
OISHO!!
ICHI! HACHI! TAKODACHI!
ONE! EIGHT! TAKODACHI!
Ina Ina Ina
Ina Ina
いいタコになりますように
I hope I can become a good Tako
INAsanityで踊りましょう！
Let’s dance in INAsanity!
OISHO!!
Think of all that you could be…
We’re talking evolution, leave it all to me!
Maybe just touch of purple ink…
What’cha think?
It’s a song you can’t ignore
The Ancient Ones are calling you to be so much more!
Just put your hand in mine and be reborn…
INA blink!
Tell me WAHt those legs are for?
俺のイナ運ぶためです！
To carry my Ina!
You could use 6 more!
感謝感謝！！ありがたい！！！
Thank you, thank you!! I’m grateful!!!
We could all get matching ears!
They aren’t really ears though…
Eh-??
Sleepy eyes to fight your fears!
例えばイナいないの世界！！！
For example, a world without Ina!!!
Alright, listen to my song, am I striking a chord with you?
Stringing you along, so don’t let me get bored of you!
80 million strong and we’ve still got some more to do
Everybody shout! World DomINAtion!!!
Can I bank on your emotion?
Do I have you invested?
I don’t WAHnna hear you say that you’re not INAterested!
Your unwavering devotion isn’t all I’ve requested
Do you care? Are you aware that you’re my dearest creations?!
Oya oya! A cute little takodachi found its way here.
Experimentation might be necessary…
Takos….we HAVE to cook!!
いいタコだちの作り方！
How to make good Takodachi!
ひっくりかえして　丸くして (Nice!!)
Turn it over, make it round (Nice!!)
コロコロまわして　焦がさずに (いいね!)
Roll it around, don’t let it burn (Good!!)
外はカリっと　中ふわふわ
Crispy outside, fluffy inside
できたらソースで　さあいただき！
Once it’s done, put on the sauce and let’s eat!
By the powers that be
The ruler of a world run on INAsanity
It’s clear to me they still can’t see
I’m just a normal girl!
Empowered by the Ancient One’s call
We’re gonna be punstoppable, we’re not a cult
Nonsensical and nautical adventures lie in wait!!
Gimme a ONE EIGHT!!
ICHI! HACHI! TAKODACHI!
ONE! EIGHT! TAKODACHI!
Ina Ina Ina
Ina Ina
俺のイナの世界線
My Ina world line
守るためにタコになろう！！
To protect it, let’s become a Tako!!
OISHO!!
ICHI! HACHI! TAKODACHI!
ONE! EIGHT! TAKODACHI!
Ina Ina Ina
Ina Ina
いいタコになりますように
I hope I can become a good Tako
INAsanityで踊りましょう！
Let’s dance in INAsanity!
OISHO!!
Ina-san Ina-san (WAH!)
Let's all shout WAH! (WAH!)
ICHI! HACHI! TAKODACHI!
ONE! EIGHT! TAKODACHI!
Ina Ina Ina
Ina Ina
いいタコになりますように
I hope I can become a good Tako
INAsanityで踊りましょう！
Let’s dance in INAsanity!
OISHO!!
WAH! WAH! WAH! WAH!
Everybody shout! World DomINAtion!!!
ICHI! HACHI! TAKODACHI!
ONE! EIGHT! TAKODACHI!
Ina Ina Ina
Ina Ina
俺のイナの世界線
My Ina world line
守るためにタコになろう！！
To protect it, let’s become a Tako!!
OISHO!!
ICHI! HACHI! TAKODACHI!
ONE! EIGHT! TAKODACHI!
Ina Ina Ina
Ina Ina
いいタコになりますように
I hope I can become a good Tako
INAsanityで踊りましょう！
Let’s dance in INAsanity!
OISHO!!
INAsanity!
World DomINAtion!!!
DRAWN TO DAWN
[DRAWN TO DAWN] TAKANASHI KIARA / NINOMAE INA'NIS 1ST CONCERT
[Title: DRAWN TO DAWN]
Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis 1st Concert
キキリキ！Drawn to Dawnの初日へようこそ！
Kiki-riki! Welcome to Day 1 of Drawn to Dawn!
小鳥遊キアラです。盛り上がっていきましょう！
I am Takanashi Kiara. Let's kick it off!
瞬く星のゆりかご
A cradle of twinkling stars,
欠けた台詞を
connecting the missing lines...
繋ぎ合わせた memory
...of memory.
聖なる従者が伝う
The holy attendant tells
神話の理
the logic of the myth,
祈りに耳を済ませ
listen to the prayer.
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice.
荒ぶる鼓動は
The raging heartbeat
弱さを焦がす
burns the weakness.
炎降り注ぐ空に
Burning flames raining down in the sky,
身をやつして
disguising myself.
乱れ咲く赤は
The red blooming wildly
紅化粧
is the crimson makeup.
数多 重なる試練も
Surviving through the numerous trials...
生き抜いてみせる
...I will show you.
I will live to keep on fighting 'til the dawn
もっと大きく！
Louder!
たとえば
For example,
先の見えない
at the boundary of zero
零の境界
where the end cannot be seen.
迷い込んだとしても
Even if I wander in,
何度も繰り返される
repeatedly...
孤高の終焉
...the lonely end that repeats.
そこに残った answer
The answer left there.
Don't break, I will never give up
Don't break, 羽が朽ちても
Don't break, even if my feathers rot.
消せない強さは
The unerasable strength
時の導
is the guide of time.
炎降り注ぐ空に
Burning flames raining down in the sky,
身をやつして
disguising myself.
乱れ咲く赤は
The red blooming wildly
紅化粧
is the crimson makeup.
数多 重なる試練も
Surviving through the numerous trials...
生き抜いてみせる
...I will show you.
Lies and truth, come to light at the break of day
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go wrong, what awaits me in the dark?
Could you tell me please, where I need to go?
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice.
漲る決意は
The surging determination
暗闇を晴らす
clears the darkness.
炎降り注ぐ空に
Burning flames raining down in the sky,
身をやつして
disguising myself.
乱れ咲く赤は
The red blooming wildly
紅化粧
is the crimson makeup.
数多 重なる試練も
Surviving through the numerous trials...
生き抜いてみせる
...I will show you.
Blazing flames, show me the path to luminance
And in the next life too, I promise I will find you
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Clap your hands!
Lying down on the floor
Late night and you don't know, don't know
Don't know what to do
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right
If yes or no, don't know
Don't know what to do
The storm hits hard and you're losing the way
Just take a chance and dance in the rain
'Cause you got the key, never throw it away
Don't forget, don't forget what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay (kay, kay, kay)
So go ahead and do it, do it
If you want it, let's get to it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
(Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid)
Gotta make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait
Start a fire today
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
We ain't looking back, take the fast lane now
In the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud
Going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed
That's how we like it, you heard what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay (yeah, yeah)
So take a step and move it, move it
'Less you try, you won't get through it
Everybody's gonna know your name!
'Cause sparks light the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
(Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid)
Let go of the past tonight
Choose the future only you define
Even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive
From the ashes you rise
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Everybody!
'Cause sparks light the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
(Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid)
Gotta make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait
Start a fire today
(Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way)
Oh yeah! Woo!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Kikkeriki!
Ah, hello! Welcome everybody to...
Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis' first ever concert,
Drawn to Dawn!
Ah! I can hear you guys so clearly,
and I can see you guys so clearly! Ah!
Kikkeriki!
Oh my God, we're in Los Angeles!
Yay!
So, we started off with the iconic and classic songs of mine,
HINOTORI and Sparks!
Don't we love those songs? Was that hype?
Yeah! You guys know, like,
HINOTORI was my first ever original song to put out,
and... yeah, it was like the beginning of my music...
musical history, my musical journey,
and it's a song that means a lot to me and it's just so hype.
It was also the first ever time that I appeared in 3D I think,
long time ago at Fes in Japan, right? Remember?
Good times! Yeah!
Thanks so much for cheering so loudly, you did so well. Yeah!
I have been training so hard the past months in the gym,
trying to get stamina for this day,
because I think I learned about...
learned and relearned about 20 choreographies. Yeah!
What? Crazy right?
Damn, that was a lot of work.
But finally the day has come to show it off to all of you.
I want to say hi by the way to all the live viewers worldwide,
there's so many cinemas showing this concert right now.
Hello world! Can you hear me?
I wonder if I can hear them.
Can I hear them over the continents?
Well that's you guys. But I think I can hear them, yeah.
Also there is some girlies watching on YouTube right now,
like Ollie and all the EN members. Hi!
Thank you! So excited.
I have to give a little bit of an announcement from my side actually.
Because it's very important it has to be in the free part,
because everybody needs to hear this.
My new album, Vogel-frei, you got it right? Thank you.
But in case you didn't, a second round of album sales has begun!
So if you missed it previously or you want a new copy,
starting from Saturday March 28th at 11pm,
I don't know which time zone.
Who knows, we'll find out, probably JST.
You will be able to order Vogel-frei again!
So please everybody order Vogel-frei!
So far the songs that I performed up until now
were not even from Vogel-frei, but don't worry,
I'm squeezing everything in that I can. Yeah.
Okay guys, you probably aware of this,
but the free part usually ends after an MC.
But free part you only had two songs.
Nah nah nah nah, don't worry, I told staff we can't be having that,
I want the free part to have a little bit more. Yeah.
So it will continue a little bit more
and then it will cut before another MC so just so you know.
And then once it cuts, please streaming tickets are available still
in the description and in the pinned comment. Probably there.
Yeah, so make sure to get your ticket
because what you haven't even seen yet is my colleague Ninomae Ina'nis,
right? Yeah yeah yeah, the concert is split in half
so today you only have me in the free part
but later if you want to see more of Wawa and Ina,
go get streaming tickets! Yay!
Okay, so with that it is time to move on to many other songs.
All right. Are you ready?
All right, here is the next song, enjoy.
Music: 40mP
Passing by the metal roads,
I couldn't find the reason why.
Who I am you couldn't know,
stuck in the ruins, my disillusion.
In between the dual reality,
my own desire keeps me near you.
Moving faster than the light can,
I'm in the absence...
...never looking back
Did I lose my way?
I can seize the day
When I can reach you again
Then can I let go?
I can hear your voice
Leading me through the void
Fade away
To the gray
Turn it up, I'm walking by
The lights are flash before my eyes
Alone, the silent symphony
Still I'm reaching out to you
Connections are my life
A soul for soul so I'll survive
...survive Pompeii
Eventually the light
Will lead me back to you see me
I'm tired of the same song
Every day like it's on repeat
I need a risky breakdown
Oh honey, the night is young
You don't need a steady, simple melody
Can you make it original?
Take me away, like it's just the two of us
Somewhere beginning...
Do you feel the music?
Baby, meet me underneath the strobe
I've come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, keep me dancing
Fever Rhythm through me
この心の音を合わせて
Match my heart's rhythm
You follow my heartbeat
聴かせてあげる
I'll let you hear it
心の音を合わせて
Match my heart's rhythm
Taste your color rhythm
I'm in a trance of the way that you're moving
You got me shining, glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild
Don't care who's watching us, so baby
Meet me underneath the strobe
I've come alive
Moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, keep me dancing
Fever Rhythm through me
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, keep me dancing
Fever Rhythm through me
Baby, meet me dance until the daylight
Baby, let's dance until the daylight
Crazy
The sound I'm making of you
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.
[Text: The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.]
無料チラ見せパートは以上となります。
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[Text: The free sneak peek part has ended.
Thank you for watching!]
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.