(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
FORTUNE SPINNER
Okay, we reached the destination.
Right on time!
Is everyone ready?
You bet!
Let's go!
Alright then!
Ready...
set...
JUMP!
Cowabunga!
hololive English Medley
- Breaking Dimensions & Connect the World -
We're ready to greet the world
We're voyaging forward with
courage to run toward
a brand new start
Let's go live
Bridging the distance across
the sea
Endlessly
Cheerfully
Meeting heart to heart!
Look up at the horizon
Together as one
A star is on the rise
And it's only begun
The pivotal moment
we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah!
It's a timeless story
with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up!
Big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far
But we're striving, thriving
Here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing
We're making our way to
the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world
that we live in
We'll greet every day
with new intentions
Break conventions
run right through
This is it!
Smashing barriers left and right
That's our Myth
Strong as we ever were scaling heights
It's endless
So get together, let's reunite
Reach up, reach out the future's bright
We're ready to seize the day
traversing the pathways
discovering highways to everywhere
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation, a dream unfurls
Let's make friends, making a moment of history,
joyfully follow me
we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now, setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question we'll break through
We'll keep aspiring to excel
(Don't relent!)
It's awe-inspiring, going well
(That's our myth!)
So light the fire and let's rebel
(Represent!)
The future's brighter, we can tell!
We're ready to
We're ready to change the world
Yeah! Woo!
Uh-huh, myth medley, myth medley, myth medley, myth medley.
Wait, what are you doing?
Oh, you too? Both of you guys are acting a little strange.
We're doing crazy things.
Why are they being so silly? We have a show to do!
Come on, Ina, come on, come on!
Ina, come on, come on! 頑張れ！
Ina, come on, come on! Do your best!
I know the floor is nice, but...
It is really nice. It's smooth.
Uh, sorry. 皆様、皆様。
Uh, sorry. Everyone, everyone.
Thank you for coming to the show today to celebrate Myth's, you guessed it, fifth anniversary!
Yippee!
Was the medley a nice throwback? We've made so many songs together.
Yeah, nostalgic, yeah.
Putting it all together like that is like really emotional.
And it's not just like our fifth anniversary, it's also Hololive English as a whole! Five years!
Don't do that!
We're so...!
We're so old! Old! We're old! Yippee!
They're old too. We've also achieved so much in the last five years, you know?
Yeah, we had three EN concerts. My voice cracked, but that's also...
Let's go!
And we had a lot of friends join us over the years. And this, you know, in the end I'm just really happy to be performing with you guys. It's so much fun.
Yeah! We can't get too emotional just yet though, because we have a show to do! Mm-hm! Yes!
Anyways, anyways, there's a hashtag right here, right here.
Yes, yes, important.
Over here. Take lots of pictures, screenshots and post them on social media. #Myth5years. Woo! Make us trend!
Trending, get it trending! Number one!
If you want. You don't have to if you don't want to. Just kidding, if you don't do it we'll be sad.
We'll be angry. We'll get you. Okay. Choosing violence.
Besides that, everybody, this is important. I'm just checking...
...making sure you guys are all here legally. Ta-da! Oh my! Did you guys all receive a ticket-sama? Hmm?
...making sure you guys are all here legally. Ta-da! Oh my! Did you guys all receive a ticket? Hmm?
Oh, I remember that. Ah, it's me! It's me! That's me! We look so cool! Yeah, so cool!
Yeah, I think I gave you mine at the bar. It was kind of spicy, remember?
I accosted you on the street, if you remember correctly.
Oh? Oh, that's what you're up to.
I... I... I might have trespassed.
Oh? What?
おやおや？ Hey, wait, why did you do that? Ina would do such a thing! Why did you do that? That's wild.
Oh my? Hey, wait, why did you do that? Ina would do such a thing! Why did you do that? That's wild.
Don't worry about it. Hehe. Okay.
You know my... Ninomae... Inaness? Sorry.
What did you do? You don't want to share? Nothing, I did nothing illegal.
Don't tell me, keep your secrets.
It's fine, I'm used to it for five years. Keep your secrets.
Well, now that we know that everybody's here with their tickets and they're allowed to be here, we'll be singing a lot on this stage today in different combinations and different fun songs and so on.
But speaking of the stage... Oh yeah! Oh yeah, look at the stage! Look!
Let's move floor! Okay! Beautiful stage! Beautiful! Gorgeous! お洒落！ Fancy!
Let's move floor! Okay! Beautiful stage! Beautiful! Gorgeous! Stylish! Fancy!
Look, there's a chair! Can I sit on it? Couch, can I lie on it?
Get your priorities straight.
Look at the chandelier! Can I swing on the chandelier? Oh my god, swing on the chandelier? Everything is so sparkly.
Wait, Kiara, look at that.
I'm looking at that.
Is that a heart?
What's the heart... what's the heart for?
Looks expensive.
Oh, look!
Did it just change color? It just gained some color.
Ah, I wonder why.
Could it be that it's reacting to everybody's reactions in the chat and their feelings?
It's changing color according to that! Are you guys getting excited?
So you guys have an important job to do now, right?
Yes. Yes, as they're always doing something.
You guys are always busy.
It must be that. It's their power and their energy.
It's flowing through us!
Well, I look forward to seeing how it develops from here out.
So, you know what you're gonna do, right? You're gonna get out your keyboards and you're gonna type some things.
Nekomancer. Yeah!
Give us your energy!
Give it to us!
Yeah, not like we're trying to shake you down or anything.
I feel it. I feel like shaking them down.
Oh okay, all right. We're choosing violence again today.
Why are you so violent?
You're in a violent mood.
It should be wholesome and untainted.
Five years later, she's done.
Oh no, they know the real me now.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm always the one that makes it wholesome, Ina.
It's all deep in our souls. I apologize.
Yeah, there's not a lot of time for yapping too much today, it would seem.
We're going to dance our hearts out and sing our hearts out for you guys.
And oh man, we've been doing a lot of that these days.
I think everybody in Myth deserves a trophy.
A little reward. A reward.
A treat, perhaps.
Cookie? Cookies?
Cookies are good too.
Maybe a cookie-shaped trophy... or a trophy made out of a cookie.
Or a trophy-shaped cookie.
Yes! Yes please.
You hear that, management? You better be having some rewards for us!
Yes, please. We're demanding.
Yeah, well, that's fine. That's okay.
In that case, I know how we can kick this off.
Kick it off?
Yeah, so maybe it's like a little cheesy, but I thought maybe the three of us could like jump in the air...
...and go 'Wheee!' like 3-2-1 jump! And then the camera goes 'Vroom!'
We like fly into the air and go to the next song.
I get it, I get it. I get too.
Done it before.
Okay! Then let's do it! No punching, no violent thoughts, Ina.
Don't punch the camera. I know what you're thinking.
Just one uppercut?
Not one. Zero.
Okay, let's do it. Okay, here we go. On my count. Ready?
Next song, start!
Three, two, one...
JUMP!
つまんないデイズ 燦々ね
Boring days, so brilliant, huh?
奇跡願ってるだけの人生
A life just wishing for miracles
Watch me Do-to-to-do-to-do Hit you
道理無視のミュージック
Music that ignores logic
Won't be free だって 未だ Free だ
Won't be free, because I'm still free
The party ain't started
HEY タクシー ちょっと 宇宙まで
HEY Taxi, take me to space
街中は 音を立てて
The city makes a sound
夜を急かす 魔法みたいだ
It's like a magic that rushes the night
人生は 一瞬にして
Life is, in an instant
解ける魔法 それならば
A magic that unravels, if that's so
駆け抜けて 思い通り
Run through it, just as you wish
邪魔な馬車 飛び乗って
Jump on that bothersome carriage
Driving 私を大変身 Make up
Driving, I'll undergo a huge transformation, make up
我儘に マニマニ
Selfishly, money-money
煌めきに 注意
Watch out for the sparkle
Shut up な 街で Dancing
Dancing in a shut-up city
さよなら Good-bye デッドプラン
Sayonara Good-bye, dead plan
Let's go 喝采を 浴びて皆様 御覧あれ
Let's go, shower in applause, everyone, please watch
ビビディ・バビディ・ブーワー
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa
やりたがって しょうがない
Can't help wanting to do it
ガラスの靴 踊って Tonight
Glass slippers, dance tonight
ビビディ・バビディ・ブーワー
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa
こんなに 足跡ないなら
If there are no footprints like this
自由に取ったもん勝ちでしょ
It's a win for whoever takes it freely, right?
DANCE! ラリリロ どんな問題も解決
DANCE! Raririro, solving any problem
白紙も正解も間違いも 愛して 本当の私の理想
Blank sheets, correct answers, and mistakes too, love them, my true ideal
なんてね 世界は 限界の気配がして
Just kidding, the world feels like it's reaching its limit
歌を歌えば Dancing Jumpin' Jumpin' out
If I sing a song, Dancing Jumpin' Jumpin' out
チキチキバンバン チキバンバン
Chiki Chiki Bang Bang, Chiki Bang Bang
ギリギリまで Give me ちょっと 今 発散してしまおうか
Until the very limit, give me a little, shall we let it all out now?
まだまだビビッちゃって
Still getting spooked
巧みにダンスしちゃって
Dancing skillfully
八分目じゃ足りないわ
Eighty percent isn't enough
ついに導き出した君に Answer
To you who finally derived the Answer
ハイになるまで 踊ってよ
Dance until you get high
邪魔な馬車 飛び乗って Driving
Jump onto the bothersome carriage, Driving
私を大変身 Make up
I'll undergo a huge transformation, make up
我儘に マニマニ
Selfishly, money-money
煌めきに 注意
Watch out for the sparkle
Shut up な 街で Dancing
Dancing in a shut-up city
さよなら Good-bye デッドプラン
Sayonara Good-bye, dead plan
Let's go 喝采を 浴びて皆様 御覧あれ
Let's go, shower in applause, everyone, please watch
ビビディ・バビディ・ブーワー
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa
やりたがって しょうがない
Can't help wanting to do it
ガラスの靴 踊って Tonight
Glass slippers, dance tonight
ビビディ・バビディ・ブーワー
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa
こんなに 足跡ないなら
If there are no footprints like this
自由に取ったもん勝ちでしょ
It's a win for whoever takes it freely, right?
Hooray.
Let's get started.
Tan-di-di-di-kep-ko.
Easy-breezy-done.
え、頭の中でこのクリーマーは
In my head, this creator
私のペルソナに繋がる
Connects to my persona
生まれ立てのアイデアと情熱があるが
With fresh ideas and passion,
疑うこともなく 際限あるものが群がる
Limited things swarm without a doubt
What about you
誰の短気もそっと膨らませ
Gently inflating everyone's short temper
いつたまらないを掻き切るの先に待つ結末は
The end waiting after scratching through the unbearable
霧の中待機万全 たまに掲げるよ数分間
Ready in the fog, I'll hold it up for a few minutes
選べよ自分 景気づけに
Choose for yourself, to cheer things up
景気づけに 呑めば共に残すいくつも化した
If we drink to cheer up, many things will be left behind
例えばここで息高く
For example, taking a deep breath here
Show me how it hits you more
今夜限りの Special moment
This night's only special moment
Give it with no hesitation
時間忘れて 狂おしいほどの情熱
Forget the time, a passion so intense it's maddening
Kick it back, coming up next level
The future's only colored by the cleverest of rebels
飽和した状況 限りステイ
In this saturated situation, staying within limits
狂気だんだんと 種が芽吹く
Madness gradually begins to sprout
Easily 見せる証拠 見慣れた再投下 浴びるほど
Easily showing evidence, a familiar re-injection
Nekkyo!
Passion!
Just a little madness, you can take the drive out of me
Nekkyo!
Passion!
Can't hide it's a new generation creation
Nekkyo!
Passion!
Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
Nekkyo!
Passion!
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
Too rough
Too loud
Unburned, unrefined
Find out
The cloud of noise it's only in our minds
Right now
It's time
No doubt we're moving on
I'm drawing my ideal world
Outside their lines
燃えたたせ その瞬間
Let it burn, in that moment
かき気づけば 悩ましい瞬間
If I notice, a troublesome moment
Breaking all expectations
常世忘れて 狂おしいほどの情熱
Forget the world, a passion so intense it's maddening
廃すればなし 罪禍の眼差し
If discarded, there's no gaze of sin
高鳴る衝動 情熱
A throbbing impulse, passion
追い風 止まない
The tailwind never stops
Never hitting the brakes to prove I got what it takes
to manifest a world you never discern is real or fake
so come on
Nekkyo!
Passion!
Just a little madness, you can take the drive out of me
Nekkyo!
Passion!
Can't hide it's a new generation creation
Nekkyo!
Passion!
Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be
Nekkyo!
Passion!
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion
愛憎もこれこそもう 自分の背中襲うような
Love and hate, exactly like this, attacking my back
夢があればそれでいい 垂れ流せよワード
As long as there's a dream, let the words flow
よりもひたすらにあがく
More than that, just keep struggling
止まない雨はないと信じ いまに様変わる
Believe no rain is endless, soon things will change
Life's a gift, prolific, you bet to be specific
Broad strokes blowing smoke blink and you'll come miss it
These words illicit visions of a future so exquisite
A masterpiece you've never seen, wait in the few committed
知らないことがあれば研究
If there's something you don't know, research it
できないことがあれば練習
If there's something you can't do, practice it
姿勢を前のめり熱中
Lean forward and get absorbed
成功の真反対にある失敗が一番の近道
Failure, the opposite of success, is the shortest path
You can do it 最高の次は満ちた
You can do it, after the best comes completion
It's about time
Stars aligning all deserving I'm already on my way
解き放てよトゲ 歪みが降るから
Release the thorns, for distortion falls
自由中まで
Until you're in freedom
I'll self-find it all, this blind resolve
Gotta go with my own way
This is some vivid striking, Nekkyo!
This is some vivid striking, Passion!
Nekkyo!
Passion!
This is some vivid striking, Nekkyo!
This is some vivid striking, Passion!
誤解すんなよ こんな滑稽な
Don't misunderstand, it's laughable
サッと過ぎ去る毎日（エブリデイ）
How time flashes by every day
Another prisoner of fate no one could fake out
Stay awake now, you know you wanna fire away
Now there's no question where the fault lies
These days I struggle just to empathize
もう戻らないって分かっているんだろう
There's no going back, and you know that
Cast a blessing on my cursed role
And feed this bleeding egotistical soul
Before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれ出た意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
身分不相応の嫉妬に塗れた
Dripping in jealousy that's a bit too daring
ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
An ecstasy that's just a little bit lacking
誤解も解けないまま私 人を傷つけて
I hurt somebody without ever opening my eyes
一粒の才すらないわ
But there's no talent here, it's clear to see
転がり落ちたジゴロサイ
The rigged dice rolls and falls
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I ever notice your love and affection
Cast a blessing on my cursed heart
Why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか神様教えてくれますか
Pray tell me, God
どうか神様 教えてくれますか
言葉少なに貴方に捧ぐ
I give to you silently
今に消えてしまいそうなこの命を
My life that's about to burn out
嗚呼 愛おしいセピア色した
Ah, and these sepia-toned sights
何より大事なこの景色を
They're most precious of all
もう少し見ていたいよな
I wish I could see them a bit more...
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
If I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The devils on my shoulder never let me be
Obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
Somebody save me
My world is caving in cuz I thought I deserved it all for free, yeah yeah
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい青い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
Should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
晴れあられ 今踊れ踊れ 恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny hailstorm, now dance, dance, play with yearning, clap your hands with the cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今をも取り戻せ 酔狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Mingle with the flowers, reclaim the present, play with eccentricity, now dance right here
比夕の輪 散る窓 過ぎて行く
The circles of evening sun pass the window where they scatter
よりどりみどりさ 祭り囃子
A vast selection of festival music
有るも無も 過去も 放り込み
Throw in everything, existence and non-existence, even the past
よく身を揉み行け 痛い痛い
Rub your body well, it hurts, it hurts
人生より道 廻り道
Life is more about detours and roundabouts
生きたいように 嫌われや
Live as you want, even if you are hated
晴れあられ 今踊れ踊れ 恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny hailstorm, now dance, dance, play with yearning, clap your hands with the cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今をも取り戻せ 酔狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Mingle with the flowers, reclaim the present, play with eccentricity, now dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらぱっぱ
Yuru yururirara yururira pappa
昼を待ち 窓際 過ぎてった
Waiting for the day, passing by the window
さあ酸いも甘いも 祭り囃子
Now, both sour and sweet, festival music
味わい尽くしてしまいましょう
Let's taste it all to the fullest
さあ何から平らげよう
Now, what shall we devour first?
人生気付けば 野のごとし
When you realize it, life is like a field
命の花を 打ち上げましょう
Let's set off the flowers of life
晴れあられ 今踊れ踊れ 恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny hailstorm, now dance, dance, play with yearning, clap your hands with the cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今をも取り戻せ 酔狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Mingle with the flowers, reclaim the present, play with eccentricity, now dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらぱっぱ
Yuru yururirara yururira pappa
花よ花よ 誇りなさい
Flower, oh flower, bloom with pride
包み隠すことなく 君のまま
Without hiding anything, just as you are
上を向いて ごらんなさい
Look up and see
最後の日まで 花であれ
Be a flower until the final day
晴れあられ 今踊れ踊れ 恋焦がれ遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny hailstorm, now dance, dance, play with yearning, clap your hands with the cherry blossoms
花に紛れ 今をも取り戻せ 酔狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Mingle with the flowers, reclaim the present, play with eccentricity, now dance right here
晴れあられ 今踊れ踊れ 誰彼も遊べ 桜手打て
A sunny hailstorm, now dance, dance, everyone play, clap your hands with the cherry blossoms
離れ離れ でも花火挙げて 酔狂に遊べ さあここで踊れ
Separate, but let's set off fireworks, play with eccentricity, now dance right here
ゆるゆるりらら ゆるりらぱっぱ
Yuru yururirara yururira pappa
あぁしたい　こうしたい　どうしたい？
まだ出し惜しみみたい
I want to do this, I want to do that, what do you want to do?
Seems like you're still holding back
石の上にも残念
でもそんなんじゃええ塩梅　サキュレーション
Three years on a stone, it's regrettable
But that's a good seasoning circulation
ずっとまどろむ　ストーリーテラー
掌の上の様な　エモーション
A storyteller dozing forever
Emotions like on the palm of a hand
カラカラ　飛び出し　いい気味だなって
君は決め顔で　せーのっ！
Rattling, popping out, thinking "serves you right"
You say with a smug face, "Ready, go!"
永遠を願った夢に　終わりを告げる朝がきた
To the dream that wished for eternity
The morning that signals the end has come
嘘吐き　零れ落ちた　その涙
見つめ、見つめ、見つけた心
Liar, those tears that spilled over
Staring, staring, and found the heart
甘く　ほろ苦い　カラメルのように
Sweet and bittersweet, like caramel
絡まるリボンは　呪いの鎧　だけど
The tangled ribbon is armor of a curse, but
この気持ちは　そう この気持ちにしか
This feeling is, yeah, only to this feeling
きっとならないから
It surely won't become anything else
君と手と手繋いで
ひとつ　ひとつ　叶えていこう
Holding hands with you
Let's fulfill them one by one
僕らの物語は　今日も続く　約束
Our story continues today, a promise
色とりどりの　真っ黒な歴史
愛おしい　私の歴史
Multicolored pitch black history
My dear history
誰も知らない　真っ白なページ
更新していく
Unknown to anyone, a pure white page
We'll keep updating it
話したくない　綻びは
The flaws I don't want to talk about
話したくない　喜びで
With the joys I don't want to let go of
接ぎ接ぎだらけのこの心
This heart full of patches
償い　紡ぎ　繋いだところ
Where I compensated, spun, and connected
憧れ　焦がれ　愛し焦がれ
全部、全部、全部、全部！
Longing, burning, burning with love
Everything, everything, everything, everything!
プリンのように　ひっくり返して
カラメル　キャラメル　My all favor
Like a pudding, flip it over
Caramel, caramel, My all favor
いたい　いたい　ここいたい
Ouch, ouch, it hurts here / I want to be here
聴き流したままで　パズルのピース
Just let it slide, a puzzle piece
でもそんなんじゃやだ！ でもそんなんじゃダメ！
僕ら決め顔で　せーのっ！
But I don't want that! But that's no good!
We say with a smug face, "Ready, go!"
次の切り札は　自分で選ぶの
The next trump card, I'll choose it myself
運命の赤い　リボンを手繰り寄せて
Pulling the red ribbon of destiny close
この気持ちは　そう この気持ちにしか
This feeling is, yeah, only to this feeling
きっとならないから
It surely won't become anything else
君と手と手繋いで
ひとつ　ひとつ　叶えていこう
Holding hands with you
Let's fulfill them one by one
僕らの物語は　今日も続く　約束
Our story continues today, a promise
色とりどりに　真っ黒な歴史
愛おしい　僕らの歴史
In many colors, pitch black history
Our dear history
残さず食べて　全部糧にして
更新していく
Eat it all up, make it all nourishment
We'll keep updating it
Yay!
What... what are we doing?
Welcome back, Calli!
Oh, hi!
Hey!
You guys look a little tired.
I thought we were posing for the Myth album cover...
...which is not coming out, by the way.
Misunderstanding, misunderstanding.
Why don't we have a mixtape? Well...
Someday, someday.
Did you guys enjoy the songs so far?
Yeah!
What did you think? Yeah! Was it fun? Yeah, yeah, yeah!
We did a really cute one, Ina.
Yeah! Caramel ribbon cursetard!
Yeah, you guys's voices... your voices fit really, really well with that.
Yeah, your voices fit really, really well with that.
Oh, thank you! Yeah, it's a really cute song.
Yeah, I... me and Ina were like 'what song should we do together?'
Yeah, me and Ina were like 'what song should we do together?'
And I was like 'Ha! I wonder if Ina would let me do a Monogatari song?'
I was like 'Monogatari please!' And she's like 'Ha! Yes!'
Excuse... you're talking to Ninomae Ina-nis, you know?
Of course I'm gonna say yes!
But we all like Monogatari, right?
Me too, yeah! I could've done it too, huh?
Sure, yeah, I would've done it.
We could've had her doing the...
Now I want to see that! I can do it now! I can do it now!
Oh, we should've done it as three people.
It's even more cute.
But I also sang it as cute as I can.
But that was really fast though.
Yeah! Oh yeah! Except mine... was not cute.
It was annoying as hell!
You guys know I could rap that fast.
Like I was so surprised.
It was kind of crazy. Impressive.
Yeah, well, well, well. I did my best. It was like enough,
enough this, oh you know, she did it.
And then plus the dancing was pretty cool, so.
Oh yeah! Ganbatta! Good job!
Oh yeah! Good job! Good job!
And Ina too, very impressive!
Oh my god, I really challenged myself.
The dancing has leveled up so much.
Yeah! Kakkoii!
Yeah! So cool!
Cute, beautiful! Yeah, demure.
Yeah, that was... there was a lot of fun,
but it was difficult.
Of course, my heart rate shot through the roof,
but we did it. We did it.
It was great.
And then, and then me and Ina did some air guitar.
Yeah!
To my original song, "Seppia".
It's a very, very close song to my heart.
And thank you for playing the guitar, by the way.
Yeah, yeah. I loved the purple guitar.
Yeah, so cool. It was so cool.
Well, what's still missing now?
Well, there are a couple songs missing, aren't there?
Yeah, like the Wawa song...
...my solo...
...combination...
A lot of, a lot of cute...
...and mine and Calli's combination song, "Thunder".
I wonder... I wonder... I wonder,
I wonder, I wonder...
I will just say that the song for me and Calli
was also chosen kind of by...
...well, suggested by me.
Thank you for being okay with it.
It's a nice song. I guess I don't want to spoil
anything, but it's pretty good.
And my solo will be... uh, epic and hype.
So look forward to that.
What's the music? Can you give a hint?
Can you give a hint?
I know it's about to happen pretty soon here, but...
No, no. No, no, dammit! No!
Okay! All right! Why? I'm a toddler, why?
Yes, we still have a lot of our show left over,
so don't tune out.
There's lots more! Stay with us!
Stay right here! Yeah, don't move.
Wait and continue to watch until the end!
And use the hashtag! Don't forget that!
Okay! Hashtag!
Are we ready to move on?
Move on!
Okay, what should we do? No, what should...
...we should play with the camera.
What do you want to do, Ina?
What do you want to do the most?
I know what I should do.
Oh?
What you gonna do?
Humble myself...
Not something violent, right?
Not something violent... oh, okay,
she's gonna do something violent.
She is doing something violent.
Hit myself! Yah!
Dear God, I've come to repent my sins.
Confessions of a Rotten Girl
Lyrics: SAW TOWNE, Music: SAW TOWNE
Let Your blood wash me clean, for I'm...
I'm...
I'm a rotten girl.
I swore I'd never sin again,
But my patience is running thin.
Temptation flowing through my veins,
And bound by the shackles of shame.
I promised I'd indulge no more,
But my heart I can't ignore.
In my dreams, they're turning up the heat.
I'm a dirty, rotten girl.
I'm locked underneath the bleachers,
Just watch, look beyond the smoke and mirrors.
Heart struck, shunned an unbeliever,
Our operation would never be complete.
Red hot, tension in every whisper,
Snapshot, quiet moans and muffled whimpers.
Come on, can't you feel the fever
Rising up, rising up to the sky?
And stems of toxic fear gripping my skin,
The Lord said, "Help My child, don't give in to sin."
It's driving me crazy, the urge to forsake Thee,
And something shifts within this wicked play.
I swore I'd never sin again,
But my patience is running thin.
Student Council breathing down my neck,
I wonder if they're hiding from me.
Forbidden fruit before my eyes,
And a taste that solidifies.
My regrets, rewriting history,
I'm a double-standard girl.
Someone, please tell me what to do,
Because honestly, I just can't stop.
I've been trying so hard, and I can't stop.
What would God think? And I... I know...
...I'm supposed to be a good girl, but...
...somehow, I just can't control myself.
Every time I see them touching skin to skin,
My mind goes... My mind goes... AAAHHH!
Could he be our idol, cheerleader for the light?
With all his disciples, subliminally driven by?
Please, somebody save me! The urge to forsake Thee,
Still something shifts within this wicked play.
The power resting in my hands,
While my God has other plans.
And salvation, I can live my life
As an ordinary girl.
I can't resist them anymore,
'Cause I smell some BL galore.
All the trauma from a couple souls,
Could never be the devil in me.
And I'm a sinner 'til I die,
What's the harm if I don't mind?
The taboo that empowers me,
I can live a sinful life!
Confessions of a Rotten Girl
チェックワンツー！
Check one-two!
チェックワンツー！イェーイ！
Check one-two! Yay!
1日ヒーロー
1-Day Hero
あーもう無理！文化祭
Ah, enough already! School festival
言葉にダンスに... キャパオーバーです
Words, dancing... I'm over capacity
心配無用のおまじない
A magic spell to stop worrying
きっと報われるその努力…
Surely your efforts will be rewarded...
笑顔になぁれ
Turn into a smile
ドキドキしてる
My heart is racing
ありえないくらい本気だし
I'm more serious than you'd believe
まほうがかかる
The magic is working
今日限りヒーロータイム
A hero time for today only
何とぞね？
What do you say?
Let's go!
baby kiss 照れないで
baby kiss, don't be shy
気持ち伝えてよ！
Tell me how you feel!
好き！
Love!
(好き！)
(Love!)
好き！
Love!
(好き！)
(Love!)
相思相愛スキ
Mutual love, like
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup runs
髪が乱れても
Even if my hair gets messy
好き！
Love!
(好き！)
(Love!)
好き！
Love!
(好き！)
(Love!)
絶対忘れない青春の1ページ ハイ！
A page of youth I'll never forget, High!
あー超気持ちいい文化祭
Ah, this school festival feels so good
隣で笑ってる君のおかげだ
It's thanks to you laughing by my side
弱気な私変えてくれた
You changed the timid me
絶対最強のパートナー
The absolute strongest partner
マジでありがとう
Truly, thank you
カクセイしてる
We're awakening
ファンサの効力マシマシで
With fan service power maxed out
まほうつよまる
The magic gets stronger
終わりなきヒーロータイム
A never-ending hero time
延長ね？
Extending, right?
Let's go!
baby kiss 隠さずに
baby kiss, without hiding it
気持ち伝えよ！
Tell me how you feel!
好き！
Love!
(好き！)
(Love!)
好き！
Love!
(好き！)
(Love!)
相思相愛スキ
Mutual love, like
おやつ食べたいし
I want to eat snacks
帰宅いいですか？
Can I go home now?
ダメ！
No!
(ダメ！)
(No!)
ダメ！
No!
(ダメ！)
(No!)
ごめんうそ嘘
Sorry, just kidding
こちらこそ帰さない ハイ！
I won't let you leave either, High!
TakaMori for five years!
Can you guys keep it going?!
いくよー！
Here we go!
カリちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Calli-chan super cute?
(カリちゃんは超かわいい！)
(Calli-chan is super cute!)
キアラちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Kiara-chan super cute?
(キアラちゃんは超かわいい！)
(Kiara-chan is super cute!)
Big ups! Everybody!
Danke schön!
Are you ready?
3, 2, 1, Go!
まほう解けちゃうね…
The magic is fading...
最後に聞かせてよ
Let me hear it one last time
好き？
Love?
大きな声で好き！
With a loud voice, I love you!
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup runs
髪が乱れても
Even if my hair gets messy
好き！
Love!
(好き！)
(Love!)
好き！
Love!
(好き！)
(Love!)
絶対忘れない
I'll never forget
青春の1ページ ハイ！
This page of our youth, High!
ななななななな イェーイ！
Na na na na na na na, Yeah!
オトノケ
Otonoke
半端もんが居場所預かんだ...
A half-wit taking charge of a place...
誰が開いたかパンドラ
Who opened Pandora's box?
あとは何があっても知らんがな
Whatever happens next, I don't care
四時四十四分待ったら
Waiting for 4:44...
六百六十六分様が
The 666 lord
噛まなくちゃ晩御飯
Has to bite, or no dinner
指を食い合したんなら文字通りお疲れ様やん
If you bite your fingers together, literally good job
剥げた剥げた剥げた剥げた剥げた剥げた
Peeled, peeled, peeled, peeled, peeled, peeled
憑きに憑きた先で君が剥げた
I became possessed, and you peeled away
タコと坊主が目ぇかみ合ったら
When the octopus and the monk's eyes meet
瞳が重なったら
When our eyes cross paths
心体頭 漲ってゆく何だか
Mind, body, and soul start to overflow
背中に今 羽が生えたならば
If wings were to grow on my back right now
暗闇からさらば
Farewell to the darkness
飛び出して行く彼方
Flying away to the great beyond
心体頭 懐かしい温かさ
Mind, body, and soul, a nostalgic warmth
足元に今 花が咲いたならば
If flowers were to bloom at my feet right now
暗闇からさらば
Farewell to the darkness
飛び出して行く彼方
Flying away to the great beyond
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
Living on over and over, inside of you
瞼の裏 闇の中
Behind your eyelids, in the darkness
胸の奥に居着いてるメロディー
A melody dwelling deep in your chest
リズムに
In the rhythm
狭窄な顔だど真ん中
With a narrow face, right in the center
積み上げてくトップスター
Stacking up as top stars
鬼とチャンバラ 叙情の大虐殺
Sword fighting demons, a lyrical massacre
狂乱の海原 花火散らし シャラララ
A chaotic ocean, scattering fireworks, sha-la-la-la
払いたいんなら 祭り囃子の札束
If you want to clear it, here's a wad of festival money
誰が開いたかパンドラ
Who opened Pandora's box?
あとは何があっても知らんがな
Whatever happens next, I don't care
六百六十六年待ったか ちょう久しぶりの娑婆だ
Did you wait 666 years? It's been a long time back in the world
餓鬼や若輩 まだこっち来んじゃねえよ 莫迦が
Brat or novice, don't come over here yet, you fool
今確かに目が合ったな こっち来いよ 茶しばこう
Our eyes definitely met just now, come here and let's have some tea
剥げた剥げた剥げた剥げた剥げた剥げた
Peeled, peeled, peeled, peeled, peeled, peeled
眠り飽きた先で君が待ってた
Beyond tired of sleeping, you were waiting
タテとホコが肩を抱き合ったら
When the shield and spear embrace
光が差したら
When the light shines through
心体頭 漲ってゆく何だか
Mind, body, and soul start to overflow
背中に今 羽が生えたならば
If wings were to grow on my back right now
暗闇からさらば
Farewell to the darkness
飛び出して行く彼方
Flying away to the great beyond
心体頭 懐かしい温かさ
Mind, body, and soul, a nostalgic warmth
足元に今 花が咲いたならば
If flowers were to bloom at my feet right now
暗闇からさらば
Farewell to the darkness
飛び出して行く彼方
Flying away to the great beyond
何度だって生きる お前や君の中
Living on over and over, inside of you
瞼の裏 闇の中
Behind your eyelids, in the darkness
胸の奥に居着いてるメロディー
A melody dwelling deep in your chest
リズムに
In the rhythm
Fortune Spinner
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the Muses whisper "truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
A wild chase
A frantic pace
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
I'm always spinning fate
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I spin back 'round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance
A daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
I'm taking fate into my hands
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
New song, new song, new song!
New song!
やったー！
Yatta!
Yay!
It's our first song as a trio, you guys!
Yeah!
あ、そうか！
Oh, true!
Just, oh, now that I'm thinking about it...
Yeah...
...it's only like two minutes.
That was a workout.
Like I guess it's because all the zoomers like it short nowadays, huh?
That's what everybody's saying.
They say...
Not me.
Certainly not.
But yeah, unfortunately this was also the last song for this live. Eh!
But the music video for our 5th anniversary song Fortune Spinner will premiere...
...on the Hololive English official YouTube channel right after this concert!
So make sure you stick around, okay?
Don't miss it.
She said don't miss it.
Make sure you watch it a lot and loop it a lot.
Please!
Onegaishimasu.
Please.
そうですね。そうですね。
That's right. That's right.
We still have some celebrating to do though, right?
That's right, I think it's time because it's the end that we kind of celebrate ourselves here. Five years!
Are we ready for that?
Yes, we are ready, okay, let's do it! Let's do it! Oh!
What is that cake over there that is not mine?
Be-be-be careful. Come on, come on!
Think about how delicious it looks.
Yeah, now I can't see.
Look how big it is!
It's almost bigger than Ina.
Hey, stop, stop, stop, not now, not now!
Hey! Don't pick off the strawberry!
Hold your horses, let's eat it later and celebrate later, later, later.
And look, the trophies!
We can do the award show, right? It says somewhere...
Where did we actually get those trophies?
Yeah, they were listening. Thank you!
They followed our shopping list accordingly.
Okay, five years, we deserve an award.
Yeah, we had so many meaningful accomplishments, so let's see what they all are, okay?
Should I start? I'll take mine.
Achoo! All right.
God bless you.
Cha cha cha cha cha!
Achoo!
Oh, bless me. Sorry, I'm not trying to disrupt your award too much.
What did you get? What did you get?
Hi! My award is... let's see... I think it says...
Most Meals Cooked Award ~ Takanashi Kiara
Most cooked, cooked the most...
She's cooking!
...in Holo EN!
Let her cook!
Let her keep doing it, she has been cooking low, she has a lot of meals.
She got a lot of meals.
Yes, thank you. I think that's what that's about. Mostly it's about, you know...
...me living a healthy lifestyle and cooking many meals at home, yeah. I wish I could cook for you girls someday.
I hope you guys enjoyed my performances today.
I am so proud to like stand here with my genmates, even on this day after so many years.
I will continue to work hard, of course, so that I can maybe gather even more awards.
Um, I will put this on my shelf at home...
...where my cats will also probably put a lot of fur on it or knock it down.
Is it out of real glass? It's kind of heavy.
You gotta be a little bit careful, but yeah.
Thank you guys so much. I love you guys. It's been an honor so far.
So let's do our best together. Thank you for this award!
Who's the next one? Who's next? Is it Ninomae Ina'nis?
Me? Oh, what could my award be, let's see.
Most violent.
Yikes! Why?
Most violent. 100%.
You do it to yourself.
My award is... oh yes... oh yes... I already know.
Most Time Spent on the Floor Award ~ Ninomae Ina'nis
It is... Most Time Spent on the Floor!
Oh that I believe, yes!
Oh my god! Congratulations!
Thank you, thank you, thank you. I know you guys probably think I would never get this award but, you know...
...I worked so hard this year to stay on the floor.
Very unprecedented.
And, uh, yeah. Not only did I stay on the floor, I, you know, really did my best to...
...practice dancing and singing this year to perform well with you guys, and I hope that you guys see that as well.
Thank you so much for all your support.
I'll continue to do my best with these girls.
Let's keep doing it. Thank you! Myth, Myth!
Hello, hello! And last but not least...
Coming up is Mori.
Our sneezer.
Total sneezer today.
The most sneezes-sneezer in the Myth 5th anniversary showcase.
Most blessed.
Best Worst Luck Award ~ Mori Calliope
Actually my trophy is for... ja-jan... Best Worst Luck Award!
...especially in games where there are microtransactions.
Ah, that's not so good.
Yeah, I mean I've seen it happen in real time.
But the dedication, the determination to pull a signed card or not. I'm not gonna give up yet!
Real quick, I'm gonna be very sappy.
I really liked that line: I'm not gonna give up yet.
...gonna give up yet because, because...
...I'd like to think that we're not gonna give up yet
because there's still so much that I want to do,
the three of us together...
Together!
And I didn't think that I would be here
five years from the start with you guys.
Same.
Yeah.
I really thought I'd be out of here.
Same!
Same.
But now, I can't - I can't see a future
where I'm not here with you guys, so...
Aww! That's so sweet!
Oh shush... okay...
So because of that, I'm not gonna give up yet.
I don't want to give up yet.
So let's do our best!
Doing our best!
Oh yeah, the wrap-up jingle is playing!
I'm just gonna start talking about nothing
because it annoys me when they play the jingle to tell me to stop.
Tell us! Tell us!
This morning I ate a bagel
and it had cream cheese on it. It was delicious!
But it went over my macros,
so I'm in big trouble with my trainer!
It's fine, it's fine!
Anyway, you can't get rid of me!
Hahaha!
You can't get rid of any of us, hopefully!
Alright everybody, all good things come to an end, unfortunately.
But thank you so much to the hololive EN community
for supporting us continuously for five years.
Thank you to the girls today
and all the staff-san that supported us also
for this celebration, who gave us the trophies!
Yeah!
Once again, congratulations to us!
To us! Yay!
To us! Oh yeah!
Yeah! Thank you! Thanks everybody!
Bye bye! Bye bye!
Peace!
Thanks! Go check out the merch!
Check out the merch!
Merch!
Merch please!
Ta-da! The merch announcement!
次は、グッズのお知らせです！
Next is the merchandise announcement!
ホロライブEnglish -Myth- 5周年記念グッズが発売されます！
We have hololive English -Myth- 5th Anniversary Celebration merch being released!
詳細を見ていきましょう。チェックしてね！
Let's look at the details. Check it out!
まずは、ミラーアクリルパネルです。
First up, we've got the Mirror Acrylic Panel.
イラストの周囲や背景が金属質の鏡のような雰囲気になっています。
It's designed so that the surroundings and background of the illustration have a metallic mirrored vibe.
うわぁ、すごくかっこいい！このイラスト、本当に大好きです。
Uh, so cool! I absolutely love this illustration.
皆さんも気に入ってくれると嬉しいです。
Hope you guys do too.
次は、コレクションカードです。
Next up, we have the collection cards.
これらのカードは光沢のあるメタリック仕上げで、3種類のデザインから選べます。
These cards feature a shiny metallic finish, and you can choose from three different designs.
また、裏面は全員でお揃いのデザインになっています。
Also, the backside is matching for us all.
推しのカードをぜひ手に入れてくださいね！
Make sure to get the one from your oshi for sure!
次は、コインメダルです。
Next up, we have the coin medals.
ピカピカの5周年記念コインメダル！
Our shiny 5th anniversary commemorative coin medals!
メンバーごとに1つのデザインがあり、裏面は共通のデザインになっています。
There's one design for each member, and the back side also has a common design.
オリジナルのパッケージに入った、アンティーク調の金メッキ仕上げです。
They come in an antique gold-plated finish inside the original packaging.
わぁ、すごくキラキラしてる！
Ooh, so shiny!
わぁ、どれも良さそうですね！でも、次に紹介するものに特に注目しています。
Oh man, everything looks so good! But I'm especially interested in what we have to show you guys next.
次は、アニバーサリーハットです！
Next up, we have the anniversary hats!
まずは、アニバーサリーハット - 森カリオペ。
So first up, Anniversary Hat - Mori Calliope.
柔らかくてふわふわした生地を使っています。
This one uses a soft, fluffy fabric.
デス先生の部分は取り外し可能なので、なしで被ることもできます。
The Death Sensei part is removable, so you can also rock it without him.
ぜひチェックしてください、すごくスタイリッシュです！この形が大好きなんです。
Make sure that you check it out, it's super stylish! I love the shape so much.
メンバーのDead Beatsのみんなと一緒に投票で決めたので、皆さんに楽しんでもらいたいです！
And all of my member Dead Beats voted on it together, so hope that you guys will enjoy!
次は私の！小鳥遊キアラのアニバーサリーハットです。
Next up, we have mine! The anniversary hat from Takanashi Kiara.
こんな感じです！装飾パーツは取り外し可能です。
Looks like this! Decorative parts are removable.
リバーシブル仕様で、裏返すと違う色になります！
It can be worn reversibly, inside out, so you'll have a different color then!
今まで私にはなかったバケットハットのデザインです。すごくおしゃれですよ！
And it's a bucket hat style design, which we didn't have before for me. Very fashionable, I must say!
最後は私の帽子！アニバーサリーハット - 一伊那尓栖。
Last but not least, we have my hat! The Anniversary Hat - Ninomae Ina'nis.
リボンの部分は取り外し可能で、パッチもすごく可愛いです。
The ribbon part is removable, and the patches are super cute too.
被ればタコダチになれます！イエス！
You can wear it to become Takodachi! Yes!
リボンの有無で、色々なスタイルが楽しめます。
And yeah, you can mix and match with or without the ribbon for different looks.
皆さん、ぜひグッズをチェックしてください！
So everybody, be sure to check our merch out!
これで5周年記念配信を終了します！
And that concludes our 5th year anniversary stream!
アルティメット・ミス！
Ultimate Myth!
Thank you for an unforgettable 5 years! I can't wait for even more amazing things in the future! Buckle in! It's going to be an exciting ride ahead!! GO NEXT!
Thanks for 5 years together, everyone! Are you ready for more?! It's already been the best journey a Reaper could ask for, but let's run forward into the future! I can't wait to see what the future holds for us and my Myth girls! Love you all! Goodbye for now!
Thank you all for being here! These 5 years were super crazy with so many ups & downs but looking back, the good and happy memories are so much more! Every moment shared together will forever stay deep in my heart and I'm looking forward for more! Love you all so much! KIKKERIKI!!!