(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
うぇーい...
Weeei...
Good...
morning...
afternoon...
evening...
It is...
Tako Time!
And we're back!
Oh, all these bees!
All these bees!
Okay, there's not that many, haha.
There's not that many.
But bees!
But it seems...
the life of a farmer has been buffed.
So, let us begin.
Let us begin.
ほっほっほっほっほっ
Ho ho ho ho ho
なるほどね。
I see.
ほっほっほっほっほっ
Ho ho ho ho ho
I see, I see.
Now it's time to see the pumpkins.
Oh wait, I gotta...
I gotta plant these first.
Important.
No, don't eat!
Our precious money! Eat bread.
Yes.
There has been farmer buffs. I don't know how...
good it will really be, but at the same time, I'm not aiming to be the top.
I'm aiming to live...
a slow life.
Cuz that is... that is me.
Trap door over...
the waters? Are you a genius?
Oh, all the bees are ready.
Oh!
Why can't I hold all these bees?
Okay, we do need to...
get more iron and stuff for the...
We... we do have more honey, actually.
For now, we will...
Uh...
We need to get more honey.
Well, I don't know how much we can get.
But we also have to plant...
Ah...
I can't breathe, there's so much to do!
Trade egg for watermelon? No...
They added eggs to the shop!
I was going to be...
dominating the world with eggs.
Now I gotta go around...
like the Little Match Girl, and be like...
Eggs... Eggs for sale!
Please, eggs for sale!
Ooh, so much money from the pumpkins, though.
That like, doubled my money.
Wait, pumpkins are powerful!
Need to get sugar.
I feel like I missed a couple. I did, I did.
I have quite a bit of eggs already.
And pumpkin pie sells quite well as well, and there's...
There's a lot of eggs here, too.
Oh my goodness, we're gonna...
We're gonna have so much to cook!
Let's see how much money we can get ready.
What am I missing? Sugar.
I should've been more diligent about sugar.
They're all of a sudden laying so many eggs!
I mean, they are selling sugar at the place, too, but...
it would be a waste because they do grow quite fast.
I mean, actually, we might as well go sell all the pumpkins, too, right?
And then we can, we can increase...
the amount of...
Wait, we didn't cook all the iron.
We need more wood.
Actually, didn't we get more co— Oh, we have coal.
And then we'll make a whole bunch of hoppers.
Yeah, that's what we'll do.
Pie.
We'll sell all our pie.
Yeah, the dreams of the egg empire has died in a day.
My egg-pire.
Pumpkin pie is not too bad.
I hope it's not too bad.
It has become more worthy to make.
Selling... the difference between pumpkin and pumpkin pie, that is true.
It is much less work to...
make... the pumpkin, you know?
So like, the extra pumpkin that we get...
is just... less work, I guess.
And we have a lot of pumpkins!
A lot of pumpkins.
Oh, losing out on pum— oh!
Efficiency.
I don't think I can leave my farm today.
I must farm.
I also wanna try out the minigame.
I heard parkour.
Nyah nyah nyah nyah...
Okay.
Oh, we might reach one million today!
One million!
No watermelon, unfortunately.
But they raised pumpkins too, so...
I assume pumpkins will be worth selling now.
They grow so fast.
Nyah nyah...
Maybe if pumpkins are good enough, we'll just increase the number of pumpkin farms.
Nyah nyah.
I'll sell some pumpkins, actually.
Coz I have so many.
So many pumpkins...
Okay, so when I go to town, I need to buy more honey.
I'll buy... uh, three stacks of honey. I don't know if all these bees are worth it, to be honest, but...
Okay.
I'll take a whole bunch of pumpkins to sell.
I don't need you.
I'll breed you.
Take all of you.
Okay, gotta quickly get to the... the place and then see how... how much money I can make.
We'll see how the stocks are, too.
Another Shulker would be nice, too. Maybe.
Oh yeah, daily quest.
Oh yeah!
They said they're gonna increase the points, but I think they decided against that, so I would have to respec if I wanted to.
Mmm.
Hello! / Hello!
今日、暗くない？ / 暗くないです！
Isn't it dark today? / It's not dark!
いいな、いいな。え、ファーマーどう？
Nice, nice. How is farming?
おー、まあ、忙しいです。
Oh, well, it's busy.
そっかー。
I see.
あのさ... / はい。
Hey... / Yes?
種売ってよ、かぼちゃとか。
Sell me some seeds, like pumpkins.
かぼちゃ？
Pumpkins?
なんか、蜂の... 蜂とか、蜂蜜とか売ってよ、まつりに。
Like, bees... or honey, sell them to Matsuri.
お？ 蜂を？ 蜂蜜ですね。
Oh? Bees? Honey, right?
なんでも売ってよ、売ってよ。
Sell me anything, sell me.
おー。
Oh.
じゃ、あとで、マーケットで売るから。
Then, later. I'll sell them at the market.
よろしく！売っといて、フリーマーケットで。買うから。 / はい！
Please! Put them up on the flea market. I'll buy them. / Yes!
Ooh.
It's the same as cake now.
Eheh.
Mm-hmm.
We're gonna be rich!
すいません、ダイヤの、ダイヤの装備落とした方いますか？
Excuse me, did anyone drop diamond... diamond equipment?
あ、それ私のだ
Ah, that's mine.
ゴミだから。ゴミじゃね？
Because it's trash. Isn't it trash?
あげる、あげる。
I'll give it to you.
あ、ゴミ？ (Laughs)
Ah, trash? (Laughs)
ゴミだって！ダイヤなのに。
She called it trash! Even though it's diamond.
あの、多分、壊れかけなんでしょう。
Um, it's probably about to break.
あ、わかった。
Ah, I see.
Alright, alright, alright. I want to deposit my money.
So that... so that we have one million dollars!
We're rich!
22円だぞ、ねぽらぼ。
NePoLaBo is 22 yen.
マジ？それは買うべきだよな。
Really? Then you should buy it.
買った方がいいよ。
You'd better buy it.
そうだよな。
Yeah, right.
どろぼう行こうかな、今のところ、買うなら。
Maybe I should go for Dorobou, if I'm buying right now.
グッズとして売るのさ、うなべん買ってもいいんじゃない？
For merchandise, wouldn't it be fine to buy Unaben?
いや、それはそう。 (Laughs)
Well, that's true. (Laughs)
でも、勝たなきゃだからさ。
But we have to win.
そうだよね。迷うんだ。
True. I'm torn.
一旦、一旦、じゃあ...
For now, for now, let's...
株主になりたいよ、私だって！
I want to be a shareholder too!
やっぱり、ねぽらぼかな？
After all, should it be NePoLaBo?
ねぽらぼだよね。
It's NePoLaBo, right?
What is this?
Feather?
What's that?
あ、お金。
Ah, money.
I need to bring more money.
Oh no, I'm going to fall below.
How much more do I need? I had...
...the calculator.
やったー！
Yay!
ギリギリだった、ギリギリ！
It was so close, so close!
クリアできましたね。
We managed to clear it.
ありがとう、ありがとう！
Thank you, thank you!
死ぬほど矢だらけ！ (Laughs)
It's deadly full of arrows! (Laughs)
Open this.
Oh, the fighters.
It's... it's...
大丈夫ですよ。
It's going to be okay.
あ、株の在庫が無限に調整...
Ah, the stock supply has been set to unlimited...
Yep, that's done. I can buy them all.
Oh, Daijoubu desu yo.
Oh, everything is okay.
株買い占めよう！
Let's buy up the stocks!
すごい、みんな殺到。
Wow, everyone is rushing in.
やっぱねぽらぼが安いから。
After all, NePoLaBo is cheap.
これ、1万はどうやったら設定できるんですか？
How do we set this to 10,000?
1万、これ100連打するしかないんじゃない？
For 10,000, don't we have to click 100 times?
え、きつい！ (Laughs)
Eh, that's tough! (Laughs)
無制限になった？あれ？
Did it become unlimited? Huh?
え、今日確か1万まで買えるんだよね。
Eh, I'm pretty sure we can buy up to 10,000 today.
Alright.
I believe...
...we saw... (Laughs)
Oh, a ring!
株無限？株買い足せる？
Stocks are unlimited? Can we buy more?
おうちいく？え、え？
Going home? Huh?
So, I mean, last time, she was supposed to buy some eggs.
And then, they started selling it...
...in store.
And I was like, "It's okay, you can buy from the store. It is fine."
And then as a joke, I was like, "I'll just have you work..."
(Laughs) "...I'll just have you work at the farm."
But I think she took it a bit literally, as if I was going to make her work at my farm.
But...
I was just going to... I was just going to ask, quote-unquote...
...Subaru-senpai to work, you know?
I just haven't decided...
...which one.
Hold on, I need to make...
Do I have any wood?
I need to make some fences. I need some wood.
Okay.
I forgot honey!
Ah, distraction!
Okay.
Oh, I have sticks.
Oops.
Where's a good place?
I guess I don't really need...
I just need one fence.
I have enough eggs. I'm too lazy to get them out of the pen...
...inside.
Okay.
Make it look nice.
Oh! One try.
Hey, hey.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Wait, do you have to be...
Oh, no, no, no. My torches!
As you can tell, my aim isn't the greatest.
Hey!
Come on...
I have a name tag.
But I don't want to name it entirely her name, you know?
It has to be...
I need an anvil?
Oh, that's right.
I can make an anvil, right?
Haro.
I can't...
Oh, I'm dumb.
Haro!
おい。
Oh, wait.
All right, you shall now watch over the farm.
Yes, cuz this is where we parted ways last time.
Okay, I got, I got to work now. I got to work... Wait, I didn't even sell all of my carrots!
I didn't sell all of my carrots! And my pumpkins. I came back, I didn't even get honey.
Ah, how could this be? The inefficiency.
イナ！
Ina!
はい！
Hi!
来たよ！
I'm here!
本当に大丈夫ですよ。見てください、ここ。
Really, it's totally fine. Look at this, right here.
え、何？
Eh, what?
もうスバル先輩働いてますよ、うちのファームで。/ え！やばい！
Subaru-senpai is already working at our farm! / Eh! No way!
やばいやん！
That's crazy!
やばい、うちのファームでなんか一匹脱出してやばいんだけど。
Oh no, one of them has escaped from our farm, this is bad.
あ、これ動きを見…せてるってこと？これ。
Ah, is it... is it showing us its moves?
はい！そうなんです！
Yes! Exactly!
マジかよ！ありがとう。ちょっとじゃあ、卵もらっていきます。
Seriously?! Thank you. Well, I'm gonna take some eggs then.
いいえ！大丈夫です！
No, it's fine!
イナズエッグください。プリーズ、イナズエッグ。
Please give me Ina's eggs. Please, Ina's eggs.
はい。
Here.
あれ？ / あれ？
Huh? / Huh?
サンキュー！
Thank you!
はい。
Yes.
ディス卵はイナズエッグですよね？
This egg is Ina's egg, right?
いや、落としたりします…どうしようね。
Well, if you drop it... what should we do?
いやいやいや。
No, no, no.
大事にしますよね？
You'll cherish it, right?
いやいやいや。大事に、大事にね、してくれる人に渡した方がいい。サンキュー、イナ！
No, no, no. I should give it to someone who will really cherish it. Thank you, Ina!
はい！
Okay!
や、なんか100%食べるエルフさんに…フレアさんに…
Yeah, like, to the Elf-san who will 100% eat it... to Flare-san...
売ると思…
Sell them, I think...
これ、俺のイナの卵って言って…
Saying "This is my Ina's egg"...
ですよね。
Right?
Maybe we should get like a stack of eggs and then put it up on the market.
After I name the stack.
ね？
Right?
Ah wait, it's sign.
Cuz I don't really know how to sell on the market.
Is it similar to other things?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Farm Support Bee. Jump boost.
Why, sell these again? Or do I breed them?
Where's the other one? There it is.
Okay, what do I have on?
I can breed this one.
I had to make a whole bunch of hop... I forgot.
Need whole bunch of chest.
How many do I need? I can make six right now. Okay.
Mmm.
Mmm...
I need to buy more of these too.
Nye, nye-nye, nye-nye-nye, nye.
Do I want it from there?
That seems a bit slow.
Another apiary on top?
I can put the beehive on top. Except it'll just load up a bit slow into here.
I mean... hmm...
So I could do it in like a...
...like a hive-apiary-apiary-box.
You know what I mean?
That means like the more rarer bees...
...are gonna end up in the second apiary and then breed again,
and then put the hive on top.
So, I'll get this.
I don't know how effective this will be...
...but...
It'll just be a bit slow, I guess.
I mean, if anything, I can just load it up manually if it needs be.
I don't think it's gonna clog.
Would it?
Only hoppers and stuff is allowed for the bee stuff.
The hive and the apiary. That's the only automation that's allowed.
But I think it's pretty slow enough that it's not gonna clog that much,
as much as you guys are gonna think. Maybe?
Oh, and then maybe I put a...
...box.
This is gonna be really tall.
I put a box.
Wait, I need more wood.
And then that box will lead into...
...the breeding thing.
Now it's just a whole tower!
Ah, blocks.
Do this.
And then this.
Ah, but then it's gonna be a pain to load it up!
But then we can only have five of these stuff.
One, two, three... It's like a 1 to 2 ratio.
Hoppers work sideways too?
Yeah, but I've done it now. I can't change it anymore!
Now I have to commit.
Okay, I'll take this out since...
...oh, I can breed that one.
This means I can put all the bees...
extra bees in here.
Nya nya nya nya...
Okay, okay, okay. Calm down, Ina. You gotta...
You gotta... Oh, there's so many bees all of a sudden.
Ah, ah, don't panic, don't panic!
Okay, you will, first of all, harvest these things.
And then, don't need copper.
Don't need egg for now. Okay.
Get all the carrots, enough to sell.
And then you will go back.
And then...
And then you will sell, and then buy honey.
And buy more apiaries and the hive.
Maybe I don't need extra hives.
I don't think I need extra hives, actually.
I have enough bee production. It'll just be over- over-load.
It'll be a waste of honey.
And it'll save money. I'll just get the apiaries.
Okay, so I can get two more apiaries.
And then...
Ah, I forgot to plant.
Ah, I keep forgetting to plant the carrots.
The bee tower. Tower of bee.
Tower of bee.
I can leave you here.
Unless I go ahead and sell these too, uh.
Leave the hopper. Leave hopper for now.
And then...
Yes, okay, okay, okay.
Ah, I missed these... Okay, no, no, no, we can grab these carrots real quick.
My inventory is not completely...
All right guys, put up a shopping list for me.
Two apiaries.
Um... Three stacks of honey.
Um...
I think that's it.
Okay, okay. We're good, we're good.
I should have collected some eggs... No, no, no, do not regret, do not backstep.
Do not backstep.
There are like bigger fields out here, maybe we should have done that instead of that little corner by the water.
Nya nya nya nya...
It's okay, it's too late.
Oh! I know pumpkins not so bad.
Pumpkins, not so bad.
Nya nya nya...
I mean we made our goal of having more than one million.
There we go.
That's a lot of money.
The town is quiet.
The calm before the storm.
Okay, how... how much do pumpkins sell for? Oh, wait! I feel like...
I feel like we just sold pumpkin instead of pumpkin pie.
Just full pumpkin.
Okay, should we... Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Before... before I forget...
Two apiary, two... three stacks of honey.
Oh yeah, they nerfed the cost for this too.
One, two apiary...
What's sixty-four...
...times three?
One-ninety-two.
Uh... One-ninety-two.
Okay. And then... I kind of want to see...
Do we still have a bit of time until... until... thingamajiggy.
Let's go check out...
Yeah, they didn't, okay, okay, okay.
Before that, we've got to deposit our money.
But before that, we've got to deposit our money.
Because we're safe... Safe investment.
Okay, okay.
We can try puzzle.
謎解き... エリトラ使用禁止。 No elytra allowed.
Puzzle... Elytra use prohibited. No elytra allowed.
Hold on, let me get my coffee. I didn't drink coffee today, can you believe it?
I know I shouldn't at this time of the day, but I can't live.
I can't even use the brush, because you have to be level three Alchemist to use it.
Oh, I sleep completely fine after drinking coffee, so it's not... it's not a problem.
It's not a problem. Okay, I'll try easy.
Is this the puzzle?
This must be the puzzle.
Only after everyone is present. Okay.
Everyone here? Yay! Okay, let's go.
上がろう。
Let's go up.
We've got to rise.
Oh... Too far.
Wait, oh, I did fall. Oh no, I've got to start again.
Arise... My speed was too fast.
こっちかな？
Is it this way?
どっち？
Which way?
こっち？
This way?
え、いける？
Wait, can I go?
Maybe I'll get momentum.
Wait, where is the entrance for this?
Oh, it would be nice to have jumping boots.
I can push the blocks?
お！お！
Oh! Oh!
あ、なるほど。
Ah, I see.
なるほど。
I see.
あー、ははは、そういうこと？
Ah, hahaha, is that how it is?
そういうことね。
So that's how it is.
そういうことですね。
So that's how it works.
なるほど。
I see.
あ、でも...
Ah, but then...
I see. That's why they have these little things.
あは！
Aha!
That's why it's a puzzle.
おい。
Hey.
え、いける？
Eh, can I make it?
いけた！
I made it!
イェーイ！
Yay!
There are multiple boxes.
One honey!
One copper!
And...
うわぁあ！
Whoa!
こんなことぉおおおーー！
How could you do this to me?!
聞いてない！
I wasn't told about this!
聞いてないっ... Wait, there's more.
I wasn't told about this... Wait, there's more.
あ、そういうこと？そういうこと？
Ah, is that how it is? Is that how it works?
うぇーい、うぇーい、うぇーい、うぇーい、うぇーい、うぇーい、うぇーい、うぇーい！
Wheee, wheee, wheee, wheee, wheee, wheee, wheee, wheee!
あ！
Ah!
お...
Oh...
Another puzzle?
Path on side?
Path on the side?
Was I supposed to...
Retry now?
Is it because I got hit?
Is there a path on the side?
どこ？
Where?
Darn...
There's a sideway path, aha.
I didn't really look.
Darn...
Oh!
Oh, the lag!
戻った。
I'm back.
Wait, did you guys see? I didn't see it.
Darn... Darn... Darn... Darn...
どこ？
Where?
A little more, I guess?
Darn...
On the left.
So this way... I was facing this way and it was on my left, so this is on my right.
But further down...
Darn... Darn... Darn...
Down below?
Left now.
My left or your left?
What's on my left now.
Why don't I see it? Am I blind?
Left, left, still no.
Left side?
But how?
One more... Oh!
Darn...
Ah, this one! Okay.
Ahhhh! I missed it.
Darn... Darn... Darn... Darn...
Darn... Darn...
Oh, the lag! It's scary.
Darn... Darn... Darn...
Oh!
Ah! Ohhh!
Thank you, voices in my head.
Huh...
戦う？
We fight?
What's the puzzle now?
Uh!
Wah!
Ah, the poison!
Bread.
負けたくない！
I don't want to lose!
Noooo!
The poison!
Ah... the time...
I should have brought more food. I didn't think there was going to be fighting involved.
I thought it was just... I thought it was just puzzles.
I would have brought more bees and stuff.
Oh well.
I just have my farming bees on.
It paid...
Money is everything.
What did I get? Oh...
I mean, I got some... I got some copper out of it.
どんだけやばいんだ？
How bad is it?
っしゃ！
Alright!
たぶん... I got 5,000 out of it.
Probably... I got 5,000 out of it.
うーん...
Hmm...
Right, I got to go before the honey runs out.
Money is everything.
So wise.
たたった、たたった
(humming)
1、2、おっけー
One, two, okay.
Okay.
I'm gonna put this...
I guess I didn't really need to take that down. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Ah, that blocks the path, so put here.
And then we grab the hopper.
いや、でも、ミニ規模だったら一人でもいけるか？
But if it's a small-scale one, I can probably do it alone.
おら、やってみようかな、これ。い、い、い、い。
Alright, let's try this. Hop, hop, hop, hop.
にゃー、にゃー、にゃー、にゃーにゃー
Nya, nya, nya, nya, nya...
Oh, I need one more hopper.
たたっと...
(humming)
I should have enough iron. Okay, okay, okay.
たたった、たたった、た
(humming)
Now we can just have one independent.
But now I don't have enough chests!
It's like the milk and cereal... conundrum.
It's like when I have enough milk,
I run out of cereal.
And then when I have enough cereal, I don't have enough milk.
Okay, our bee tower is almost complete.
Effective or not, it is our bee tower.
We made it! And we will be proud of it.
あ！ あ！
Ah! Ah!
ふっ！ ふっ！ ふっ！ ふっ！
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
やった！
I did it!
There we go.
I was lazy.
にゃんにゃんにゃんにゃん
(humming)
But like, I guess... oh, we don't have enough iron, huh.
I was about to say we could just have one system here where it's just...
...the hive to apiary.
たらたらた、たたたた...
(humming)
We can just have individual ones, I guess.
にゃにゃにゃにゃ...
(humming)
And then... there, okay.
Hey, laziness is the starting point of all innovation!
Don't you ever doubt that.
てててて...
(humming)
I wonder how you would put that into Japanese though.
Maybe I'll ask Google.
Google先生！
Google-sensei!
Tatsugina of the mountain? 山のイナちゃん、山のイナちゃん。
"Tatsugina of the mountain?" Yama no Ina-chan, Yama no Ina-chan.
Is there like a Japanese translation of that? We should make the whole translated meme thing.
Laziness is the starting point of innovation.
怠惰は、イノベーションの出発点である、ある、ある。
"Laziness is the starting point of innovation" ...aru, aru.
た、た、た、怠惰...
Sl... Sl... Sloth...
脳が震える！
My brain trembles!
あれ、怠惰だったんですよね？Re:ゼロの。
Ah, that was 'sloth', right? From Re:Zero.
怠惰だったっけ？覚えてない。
Was it sloth? I don't remember.
です！
...desu!
怠惰です。よし。
It's sloth. All right.
いや、まあ、イナが怠惰だったら、イナベーションって言うかな？
Well, if Ina was sloth, would you call it 'Ina-vation'?
怠惰はイナベーション。
Sloth is Ina-vation.
Taida is innovation.
おお、株が上がった！高...
Oh, the stock price went up! High...
It rose. It's time for the kabu.
It rose. It's time for the stocks.
It's time for the kabu.
It's time for the stocks.
ああ、下がった、76。
Ah, it dropped to 76.
It dropped 76.
It dropped to 76.
頼む、NeFoLaBo、プラス100！
Come on, NeFoLaBo, plus 100!
ああ、Luna Railway、マイナス47？
Ah, Luna Railway -47?
頼む、頼む、NeFoLaBo。
Come on, come on, NeFoLaBo.
プラス...
Plus...
あ、おお、おお、よかった、よかった。は、は、は、またセーフ、セーフ。
Ah, oh, oh, thank goodness. Haha, safe again, safe.
ああ、NeFoLaBo HD、マイナス11？ああ、痛い...
Ah, NeFoLaBo HD -11? Ah, it hurts...
痛い。
It hurts.
心が痛い。
My heart hurts.
ああ、お腹痛い。
Ah, my stomach hurts.
ああ、どうだった？
Ah, how was it?
ゴミだな、よ。
It's total trash.
ポルカ泣いていていいそう。
'Polka crying is fine.'
悲しい。
So sad.
悲しいな。
How sad.
株が上がっても、22に戻れる？
Even if the stocks rise, can we return to 22?
Even if it rises, can we return to 22?
Okay, maybe open... I guess the axe will last a while, so it should be fine.
Need more sugar if anything. Maybe we should make a more easier sugar...
Need more sugar if anything. Maybe we should make an easier sugar...
...farm. One that doesn't like curve around.
...farm. One that doesn't curve around.
いや、株がプラス100いっても...
Even if the stocks go up by 100...
starting pointに戻る？
...do we return to the starting point?
辛いの。
It's painful.
辛いんですが...
It is painful...
いや、demo, there is still one day left, you know?
But there is still one day left, you know?
You know, it's not all hope lost.
You know, all hope is not lost.
I feel like pumpkin is just the way to go because it grows so fast.
And it's worth a hundred.
Like, I turn back and like half of it is already like grown.
I think we go pumpkin.
カブ？ な、な、な。 パンプキン。
Turnip? No, no, no. Pumpkin.
パンプキン。
Pumpkin.
You know, how about I just get rid of all these carrots and just go kab- pumpkin, kabocha.
I think pumpkins are the way right now.
Like, it's kind of insane how fast they grow.
Like, we'll sell the rest of these carrots...
...cause I can't even use the carrots for pumpkin pie.
Like, if I have extra pumpkin, I can just make pie as- as long as I have the eggs and...
...sugar.
But the carrots is like, I just- I just have to sell the carrots.
I think we should just invest in pumpkin.
I think that's the play.
Yeah, and like, it replants itself.
All right guys, change of plans.
The bees remain. Pumpkin... pumpkin. Carrots, I'm sorry.
You have been eliminated.
Like, insert intense BGM.
After a long day of consideration...
...carrots...
...I'm afraid you have not met the expectations of the top farmers.
HoloLive's top farmer program.
You can now pack your bags and leave.
Carrots, I'm afraid your time in the competition is over.
You fought valiantly and you've held your place over the last four days.
But your efforts were just not enough...
...to combat inflation.
わあ！
Wah!
ねね、お金持ちや！
Nene is rich!
イナちゃんどんな感じ？
Ina-chan, how are things going?
あ、にんじん、もう辞めるかな。
Ah, I think I'm quitting carrots now.
ねねもにんじん辞めた。
Nene quit carrots too.
もう、かぼ… かぼちゃ。 かぼちゃが良い。
Now it's pump- pumpkin. Pumpkin is good.
かぼちゃ上手いよね。
Pumpkin is great, isn't it?
上手い。
Great.
上手すぎるよね、キリがないな。
It's too great, there's no end to it.
かぼちゃ、かぼちゃショル。
Pumpkin. Pumpkin rules.
かぼちゃしよう。 かぼちゃしか勝たん。
Let's do pumpkin. Pumpkin is the best.
Yes, it's kabocha time.
Melon technically could work, but it'll take time to...
...you know...
...cook it, so...
We can make pumpkin seeds on our own...
...which is good.
And then we shall...
...pumpkin.
ふふ、ここのかぼちゃ。
Hehe, the pumpkin here.
And then we shall pumpkin.
Yeah, they didn't- they didn't put melon seeds in the thing. But I think...
...I don't know, I'm- I'm content with Kabocha.
I love pumpkin.
Pumpkin pie...
...as meme-y as it has become over the years, I love pumpkin spice lattes.
Wait, wait, did I replant pump-
Nah.
Wait, I mean, I guess we can keep one carrot right here, cause this one is not really ideal for pumpkin raising.
All right, pumpkins here.
Yeah, I heard the jungle is quite far, so...
...you need an Elytra, and I don't really want to do that. Like...
...if I did that earlier and I got it, then maybe it would have been worth it, but right now, I feel like that's just time wasted.
You know?
Mm, pumpkin.
Nya, nya.
I wonder if there should be like...
An amount, an exact amount. Cuz I know I'm not...
...not ever gonna be close to being first, but like...
...what if we end with an exact amount?
I think that'll leave a more lasting impression.
How about we aim for 1-8-1-8-1-8?
Haha!
1.8 million. I think that's doable.
I don't know if I can get the exact amount, but that's something we can work towards, you know?
I think cuz 1.8 million is definitely doable.
We just have to spend a little bit more time on getting things, and then like...
...last can be spent on like trying to get the exact number, you know?
I wonder how many I should make.
Okay, that's... that's more than enough.
And then...
...how about we do this?
And I make this all into water, right? I think.
Mhm.
And then I put...
Okay, where did I put my bucket?
Got to fix the water here.
There we go.
And then... that will grow here.
Ah... hmm...
Is 18 million possible? I don't know.
I don't know.
Okay, how about we get more dirt and then like increase this?
I mean, we could do one more here, but then it'll like cover up the pathway.
Okay, I'm... I'm just gonna do that.
I think like 18 million would just win the game though.
Okay, let's get a whole bunch of dirt.
Go all in and gamble.
Dirt.
Dirt, dirt. Okay.
Can I gamble my way to 18? Yeah, but I can also lose all my money.
You guys are forgetting the other side of gambling.
You guys just want to see me suffer.
Ah!
You guys have a problem.
You guys have a gambling problem.
You need to go get some help.
Geez.
I can quit whenever.
That's what they all say.
Okay, this should give us...
...at least a couple more...
...lines.
I need to get another hoe though.
Wait, I can make one...
...so it will last longer.
Oh, I guess this is just gonna be water already, huh?
I forgot.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mmm...
And then one over.
I should've done this earlier.
And then, one will grow here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wait, no.
No, this should be one more over.
No, wait, wait, wait, I can just do it...
Yeah, I can just do it here.
Okay, okay, okay. That's fine.
It's not as expected, but...
...it will still work.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's fine, it's fine.
This is as big as I want the farm to be.
And I'll just put like...
Mm-mm...
...so I don't overstep every time...
...I go backwards and farm.
Like, I know I can use a fence to make it look better, but...
...I'm a little lazy right now.
So I can just look backwards.
Yes.
Let's block off this area.
Ah!
素晴しい
Wonderful.
It's dirt cheap!
And then...
...we go get some eggs that have spawned.
Yes.
I'm gonna make some pie with the leftovers.
Mm-mm-mm.
Oh.
Good, good, good, okay.
Thank you, chickens. Ah! Let me out!
And fill this all with pumpkins.
Hm hm hm...
Hm hm hm, hm hm.
I wonder if I should make a whole bunch of...
Mmm...
Easier to get sugar.
Ah, do do do...
Oh...
No, not right now. Pumpkins will wait.
I spent enough time. Put away the fishing rod for now.
Oh, more ramen!
Tada. Look.
Create a pumpkin empire!
And just fill tons and tons with pumpkins.
Oh...
I can become the Pumpking. Hehehe.
I have left the recipe of... the pumpkin pie recipe...
...passed to generations on... that farm. Go seek it.
Something, something, pumpkin.
Ooh.
And then I return to the beginning...
...and start again. Never-ending pumpkin.
Da-da-da-da...
Ooh...
Ooh, I already have almost 500k from just...
...doing things with pumpkin.
What if I make the pumpkin field even bigger?
Just find a bigger land. Hehehe.
But I want it to be kind of close so I don't have to like move to harvest.
And then I return...
And then I farm...
...pumpkin.
Ooh...
Do do do do do...
Expand towards the sugarcane for more lines?
You could be right.
You might be onto something.
1.8 isn't too far off.
We'll have to go get a new axe soon. And a hoe.
I think I'm gonna make the diamond hoe cuz I don't think they sell the diamond hoe.
Hmm...
I think we're gonna...
We c- We could totally aim for...
...more than that. Oh, I wonder how much we can aim for.
Let's see what we end up with...
...tonight, and then like, if...
...if it comes down to it, we can like, I don't know, buy stuff or gamble.
to try to reach a good number.
You know?
We should go for 6.7 million.
6.7...
Well, some people would like that.
We'll see how much we end up with, cuz like...
You know.
So, we don't know what we're gonna end up with.
Aim for 8, 8, 8, 8?
Ah! It broke.
Maybe I should replace it with um... something else.
I'll think about it later.
Let's just see how much we make from this whole round of pumpkins.
Like repeating numbers I think is also...
...memorable...
...if we can get there.
Remember to farm the sugar? Yeah, I should, shouldn't I?
Ah!
It pushed me! It made...
...it made me drop my seeds! Stop!
Oh, I don't have a hoe! No!
It ruined my farm.
Okay, let's go make the diamond hoe.
Do I have wood left? I do. Okay.
I think my diamond is inside, though.
Oh, I should check. Oh.
I need to take some of these and put them in the...
...in the box above.
That's some of the manual stuff we gotta do.
It's working, it's working.
Oh yeah, this one needs a little bit of manual work too, forgot.
Ah, that's fine.
Um, okay. Let's drop...
...pumpkins in here. Oh, we have a full box! Okay.
Get some eggs.
Wait, can we make an axe?
No.
Shame, shame. Not enough Pikapika stones.
Shame, shame. Not enough shiny stones.
That's okay, we can just buy it. It's not that expensive.
Grab some eggs.
Ah!
Ooh, that's a lot of eggs, actually.
So we're now lowest on sugar. So we can adjust the sugar farm a little bit.
We should fill this up too.
Wait, we got to fix that one.
One first.
Second... yes.
Ta-ta-ta...
Okay.
I'll probably make like two rounds of...
...of pumpkin, one round of sugar,
...one round of egg. Every time I get sugar, I'll get egg.
There's other gaps?
I don't think so.
It just hasn't grown.
We do have to stop by the shop soon, though, to even grab a different axe...
...as well.
Okay, go.
I can put it on the dirt fence, but like,
I would have to raise the water level a bit.
And then I would have to like...
...climb over, because it's most likely going to fall outside into the water.
Oh, I mean we easily made...
...1.8.
Hm hum, hm hum, hm...
Nice.
8.1?
Heh.
Okay, one round down. We'll do one more round...
...of pumpkin.
Oh, I missed some.
Ah!
And then, I think we can go sell after that,
...because I think the axe is going to break, too.
Do, do, do, do...
Ah, so peaceful.
Hm hum, hm hum, hm...
Oh no, not again.
Yeah, my axe is definitely going to break soon.
Okay, how about we go until the axe breaks, and then we'll just go... have to go buy a new one anyways...
...and sell the pumpkins.
Right, thinking? Not such efficiency.
Hehe.
Gold Yagoo.
Whoa!
SSRB.
Na-na-na...
Ah! We almost have a million in our wallet,
...just from...
...just from farming!
I think 8 million might be doable if I keep going.
If I don't stop farming until...
...the last day.
Should we aim for it?
I don't know. I feel like...
...I feel like it could be doable, because I'm also going to be selling stuff, too.
Ooh.
Ah...
And then we'll just sell all the cheaper pieces too.
Cuz that's just going on its own.
Honest work...
...for 1,018,000...
...880,000, eight, eight...
...yeah, yeah, yeah. I forgot how to count numbers.
The axe is about to break soon.
Come on, break! Break!
Break!
Maybe we should even make the pumpkin field even bigger.
Okay, we might just extend this way.
Like towards the sugar canes.
That way we can just... I think it's more efficient than a different row.
I think that's a great idea.
We have so much money!
It's, yeah, it was exactly like the 1% battery left.
1% that lasts like five million ages.
We'll get the sugar cane.
You laid an egg too?
Thanks for your contribution.
We go grab the egg.
Hello!
Get every last one.
And then we can deposit another million!
Pie. Pumpkin pie.
We are doing so well today.
We'll buy another pickaxe and another axe.
We're doing so well!
Automation is set outside of the hoppers for... the bees.
さっき取り忘れてたからか。はや。
Is it because I forgot to take it earlier? That was fast.
あ、これ。待って。
Ah, this. Wait.
あ、これそっか、これそっか。
Ah, I see, I see.
And then, pumpkin pie!
Yummy!
Selling my last... carrots.
carrots too...
あれ？なんかみんな静かにやってる。儲かってますか？
Huh? Everyone's working so quietly. Are you making good money?
え？
Eh?
スイカは？
What about watermelons?
あ、ビビ何に気づいたん？
Ah, Bibi, what did you notice?
あ、気づいた？
Ah, did you notice?
なんか今気づいた。
I think I just noticed.
気づいた。よしよし。
You noticed. Good job.
The pumpkin crew.
Shift double click?
Doesn't work though.
No more carrot.
うらー！
Urah!
ちょっとスイカも探しましょう。
Let's also look for watermelons.
ある程度稼いだら、うん。
Once we've made a certain amount, yeah.
やっとファーマーの時代きた！
The farmer era has finally come!
きたねー。探すわ。
It's here! Let's search.
探しましょう。
Let's search.
確かに、ちょっとだけ探しに行く？
True. Shall we go search for a bit?
Is it really worth getting melon?
Is it really that worth?
It is kind of true,
cause you get what, like...
how many slices per melon harvest?
6? Nice. 6. That is quite a lot.
やばい、ロケット花火...
Oh no, firework rockets...
Should I?
That could change a lot.
Is it an investment...
that I should make?
A portal?
Warp.
I don't think there's any enchanted...
axes or tools.
There's no enchantments.
How many...
Will it be worth it, you think?
よいしょ、よいしょ。
Yoisho, yoisho.
Oh, I miscalculated.
You have to be holding a stack and shift-double-click...
ああ、なるほど。
Ah, I see.
Ah, but Elytras are scary!
I'm gonna deposit more money 'cause I don't need it.
Maybe it'll be worth it.
Actually, I don't need money right now, so I can deposit everything.
Okay.
Ah, Elytras are scary.
It's been a while, too,
so I'm not...
not the most confident, to be honest.
Okay, let's go prepare.
Like, is there really a...
a portal to the jungle?
I mean, it's big if true, but...
trust my skill.
I wonder if I should bring my bees.
Big if true.
I mean, I'll leave the extra tools in here.
I'll bring a new pickaxe. I don't need the hoe.
I need a sword. I have enough bread. I can make more bread, I have wheat.
Okay.
Breeder, I don't think needs refilling 'cause like...
it's like every 5 minutes and I put a whole stack of honey, so it should last the entire...
thing.
Maybe I'll take this.
Oh, regeneration is good.
Okay, I'll at least put two combat bees in, just for traveling, just in case.
Hoppers are fine.
It's fine, it's fine. I think this is good.
Okay. Which way, though?
Which way?
Okay, wait, wait, wait. Let me, let me remember the coordinates to my house.
All right.
Where's my notepad?
137, 65, 64. Cool.
Okay.
Shield? I have shield. Except I don't like using shields when I'm like flying, because it covers my view.
And you don't really need it.
Okay, I wrote it down, so it should be fine.
But which way should we fly?
18 degrees from North, that's very specific.
But there is one gate I saw.
でもね、今やっとね、400万、8までいった...
But you know, I finally got 4 million, up to 8...
400万？
4 million?
ま、行ってみようか。
Well, let's go check it out.
遠い！
It's far!
Okay, let me mark that down.
I mean, there must be a reason this warp gate is here, right?
There must be a reason.
ね？
Right?
Well, we can take a look. I wrote down the coordinates.
Which direction are we going? South.
Woah!
I'm sure that's probably looted already.
We need what? Jungles?
え？早いじゃん！
Eh? That was fast!
I think they added...
I didn't really need the Elytra. I mean, I guess it's... nice.
I almost typed in "suika".
Ah, okay.
え、早かったね。
Eh, that was fast.
Oh, cocoa.
Is there more, I wonder? There must be more around here.
I guess they might have added the portals so that we can... Oh, there's more right there.
That was so quick.
Well, leap of faith was nice, I guess.
Though... Oh, that's a lot of seeds.
もっと持って行くか。
Should I take more?
もっとあるかも。
There might be more.
I need the jungle... I don't think I really need cocoa. Cocoa is honestly a waste of time.
Let's be real, now that we have suika.
There's really no need to make multiple recipes.
ね？
Right?
What, cookies? No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Suika is cookie. New cookie.
Watermelon is cookie. New cookie.
We love watermelon.
Capitalism.
Ah, that was a very short trip.
That was a very, very short trip.
Now do we... Okay, the thing is, now do we replace all the pumpkins with suika?
Now do we... Okay, the thing is, now do we replace all the pumpkins with watermelon?
Or do we just expand?
I guess I can go faster too, down, back and forth.
まあまあまあ。
Well, well, well.
Okay, let's go back.
こっちでしたよね。
It was this way, right?
この辺... え、ここも、ここもジャングルじゃん。
Around here... oh, here too, here is also jungle.
Ah, there it is.
かぶって、ししろフーズはどうなって... あ、ししろフーズ...
And on top of that, how is Shishiro Foods doing... ah, Shishiro Foods...
ボチボチでした。
It was so-so.
In the shipment of watermelon... What? Chat do the math!
So close.
いや、まず... あ、どうしよう、どうしよう、どうしよう、どうしよう？
No, first... Ah, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do?
どうしよう、どうしよう。
What should I do, what should I do.
じゃ、ここ、ここ、ここを...
Then, here, here, here...
ここをメロンにしよう。ここ。
Let's make this part melon. Here.
ね。
Right?
で、
And,
こうやって...
Like this...
And then we compare one row to one row. I think that's the easiest.
I'll harvest these. Oh, I forgot.
My bad, I was just a little too excited.
So, it'll all end up being like, um...
what grows faster, growth-wise, ne?
what grows faster, growth-wise, right?
Like if it grows as fast as the pumpkins,
then it's worth switching honestly everything to pumpkin.
But if it grows closer...
If it grows same speed...
Oh, my...
Because if it ends up being that way, you know...
Pumpkins are good for pumpkin pie, so I can leave like...
...a little bit.
But...
"If you alternate crops, they grow faster?"
Well, kind of... Is that, or is it actually proven?
I've never heard of that anytime in my time playing Minecraft.
I need to...
"Automation other than the bee stuff is prohibited."
Although, I don't know if people read pinned comments.
Let's be real.
I mean, they start growing.
Okay, now I have the sign up. Oh.
Maybe I should block...
Maybe I should do the trapdoor thing now, now that I think about it.
Like, I might kind of need...
Okay, so I'll get rid of these for now, and we'll see how many...
...how many slices we get per watermelon. I feel like...
Ten.
Wait, 1,500?
Guys, I think we're gonna replace all our pumpkins with watermelons.
Okay, it does vary a little bit.
But it's like...
...a lot!
Yeah, they... I think they grow the same speed as the pumpkins.
Hey, guys.
I think it's time for the switch.
Don't... don't care about the pumpkin pie. I mean, I guess pumpkin pie is like...
...per pumpkin pie is 500, but like, I can leave like one row of pumpkins.
Like, I have enough pumpkins growing. Like, they grow really fast.
I think... I think it's time, guys.
I think it's time to invest...
...in the pumpkin stonks—I mean, the watermelon stonks.
What happens if I do this? Okay.
It's time. A new era has arrived.
Quick, before they nerf this!
Quick, before they nerf the watermelon!
I must reach my goal.
We must taco-takeover.
Ah, more, more!
And now we go... Ah, we must hurry before they fully grow.
Okay, we left that one, okay.
No, we must harvest all the pumpkins...
...before we're operating on a loss!
The suika per minute must increase.
The watermelon per minute must increase.
*gasp* Raid incoming.
Oh no, we must go... after we harvest.
I'm sure there will be some sort of reward.
Should we just stay and farm?
But the suika... The suika...
But the watermelon... The watermelon...
お、そんなに？行かなくてもいいかも？
Oh, so many? Maybe I don't need to go?
行かなくてもいいんじゃないですか？
Isn't it fine if I don't go?
もうファイターの皆さんと、ね？
I mean, we have the fighters, right?
Remember who you are! Ah, my brain!
Ah... Who, who am I?
Okay, I'll leave the eggs in here.
Ah, my head.
We must make haste.
All right, all right, I'll go.
I'll go participate in your... in your games.
I'll go participate in your games...
I'll just take these two.
And then I'll fly over, and then switch gears, okay.
Ah, thank you for your lucky egg.
And I'll deposit my money.
Yare yare.
Good grief.
Do I have the ramen? Oh, I do, okay.
きちゃん、お金入れて...
Ki-chan, deposit the money...
ああ！ああ！
Ah! Ah!
あ、来た！いくぞ！
Ah, they're here! Let's go!
ファイター頼む、やってくれ！
Fighters, please, do it!
まさかそんな...
No way...
あ、なんか来た！なんか雑魚出た、雑魚！
Ah, something came! Some small fry spawned!
助けて！何も見えん！何も見えん！
Help! I can't see anything! I can't see anything!
頑張ってくれ！これ当たってんのかな？
Hang in there! Is this hitting?
いや、でも、なんか前より少ない気がするけど...
Yeah, but, I feel like there are fewer than before...
みんな、気をつけるんだ！
Everyone, be careful!
え？なんか前より少ない...
Eh? There's definitely fewer...
画面がもう...何だ、これ？
The screen is already... what is this?
これ4分でやれるのかな？手伝って！
Can we do this in 4 minutes? Help!
ちょっと微妙...ちょっと削りいかないと、やばいかも。
It's a bit tricky... We might need to chip away at it, or it'll be bad.
頑張って！攻撃！
Do your best! Attack!
お、そこ行くのやめて！痛い、痛い、痛い！
Oh, stop going there! It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Ah, I forgot... the armor.
ノエルには身に覚えがない！
Noel has no recollection of this!
あ、これ倒せないの？どこ行った？
Ah, can we not defeat this? Where did it go?
痛い！痛い！何、何、何？
It hurts! It hurts! What, what, what?
何これ？何これ？
What is this? What is this?
Yeah, are we doing damage? Doesn't seem like we're doing much damage...
味方もめっちゃ痛い！よいしょ、あ、でも、いい感じ、いい感じ！
Allies are hurting a lot too! There we go, ah, but it's looking good, looking good!
やばいやばい！おお、おお！
Oh no, oh no! Oh, oh!
痛い！気をつけないと！
It hurts! We have to be careful!
危ない危ない！何これ？！
Watch out, watch out! What is this?!
おー！燃えてる燃えてる！
Oh! It's burning, it's burning!
燃えてる！うわー！
It's burning! Uwah!
装備が、装備がさ...
The equipment, the equipment is...
そこやめてー！
Stop right there!
よしよしよし！頑張れ！
Okay, okay, okay! Do your best!
頑張れ！
Do your best!
いけるいける！いやでもいけるよ！
We can do it! Yes, we can still do it!
やばいやばい！熱い熱い！
Oh no, oh no! It's hot, it's hot!
あ、熱い熱い熱い！
Ah, it's hot, hot, hot!
お、お、お...
Oh, oh, oh...
行くぞ！農家だってやれるところ見せてやる！
Let's go! Let's show them what a farmer can do!
おー！
Oh!
おい！あ！
Hey! Ah!
あ、痛い！
Ah, it hurts!
大丈夫？あれ、何であんなのあるの？
Are you okay? Wait, why is there such a thing?
おお！
Oh!
何か、来ない？何かいる！
Is something coming? Something is there!
おおー！うわー！
Ohhh! Uwah!
飛び交ってる！
They're flying around!
まずいまずい！まずい！
This is bad, bad! Very bad!
待って待って！やばいやばい！
Wait, wait! Oh no, oh no!
よいしょ！ミニオン！ミニオンどうにかする！
Yoisho! Minions! I'll deal with the minions!
おらー！
Oraaa!
危ない危ない！
Watch out, watch out!
たたた、戦え！
F-F-Fight!
おい！よし、いけいけ！
Hey! Okay, go go!
後ろ後ろ！痛い痛い！
Behind you, behind you! It hurts, it hurts!
他にも出てくることないよね、これ？
There won't be any more appearing, right?
よしよし！おらー！
Okay, okay! Oraaa!
やべ、やべ！おっしゃー！あ、いける、いける！
Oh no, oh no! Yeah! Ah, we can do it!
来い来い！
Come on, come on!
やったー！いぇーい！
We did it! Yay!
いぇーい！
Yay!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いぇーい！
Yay!
ちなみに倒せたので、これ、株のルーレットが特別仕様になります。
By the way, since we defeated it, the turnip roulette will have special rules.
いぇーい！きたきたきた！
Yay! It's here, it's here!
株、株！
Turnips, turnips!
よし、ちょっと...株どうする？株は今どれくらい？
Okay, wait... What about turnips? How much are turnips now?
株がほぼ、ほぼプラスになりますね、特別報酬で。
Turnips are almost, almost guaranteed to go up as a special reward.
やったー！みんなありがとう！
Yay! Thank you everyone!
いや、ほぼプラスなんですけど...
Well, it's almost guaranteed to go up, but...
私、スイカに戻らないと。
I have to get back to the watermelons.
株は後で売っても大丈夫ですからね。
It's fine if I sell the turnips later, right?
後で売っても問題ないですからね。
There's no problem selling them later, right?
スイカが、イナを待っている。
The watermelons are waiting for Ina.
これ持って行くか。
I'll take this with me.
で、これと、これですね。
And, this and this.
たまごも入れて、ご飯はここ。メロンは大丈夫。
Put the eggs in, and food goes here. Melons are fine.
じゃ、スイカ。行こうっか。
Now, watermelons. Let's go.
行こっか。
Let's go.
Two million! おお！
Two million! Oh!
Two million!
Yeah, eight million, I think... I'm seeing the light.
I'm seeing the light.
Eh, pumpkin? Do we really need pumpkin pie?
I don't think we need pumpkin, guys.
We must... we must take advantage of this watermelon... while it lasts.
Um, um, I'm going all in on the Suika stonks.
Um, um, I'm going all in on the watermelon stonks.
Oh, did I freeze?
I got two scythes, guys.
I didn't even realize.
Am I still frozen? Okay, I'm good. Okay.
Hey.
I'm locked in.
My goal...
...it will happen.
Suika mode!
Watermelon mode!
Wait, how is Nepolabo?
I mean 86?
86! I think it's time to sell, guys.
That's like almost four times.
I think it's time.
Big stonks.
Okay, when we go sell the Suika, we will...
Okay, when we go sell the watermelon, we will...
...we will sell our stonks.
Sell, sell, sell!
Oh.
Yeah, I need to... I need to fix the floor here.
Need to get some wood to...
...add trap doors.
Yeah...
Oishii, Suika, oishii, Suika, oishii, Suika.
Delicious watermelon, delicious watermelon, delicious watermelon.
My stonk.
Sell only half?
Are you a stonks master?
Are you saying that it might go up even higher?
Do you believe? What are the chances?
Can it go much higher?
So what are the stonks? Every hour...
...Shishiron, she spins a roulette that has the plus...
...minus percent.
And because we just defeated the raid boss...
...it was a special roulette that's mostly positive.
So basically everything went up. It's...
...a good time to sell.
We have one more update to the stonks...
...so, for today at least.
Okay, one box full.
And then we'll go get some wood too for trap doors.
We'll sell the rest of the pumpkin.
Just a few more Suika.
Just a few more watermelon.
Oh, plentiful Suika. Yes.
Oh, plentiful watermelon. Yes.
Oishii.
Delicious.
You know, I haven't had really good watermelon in...
...a long time.
It's not like I'm never a fan of melons, like, I don't really like cantaloupes and stuff too...
...because like nine out of ten times, they just...
...taste awful. They have no taste.
It's not even sweet.
I mean, the ones in Japan aren't... aren't that bad, but like...
...like, nine out of ten times I've had it, it's just been bad.
It's hard to get good melons.
Watermelons too, I think. It's always a...
...toss in the air if it's good or not.
Okay, this is full.
Now I shall get some...
You know what? I'll get the easier ones here.
Fill my inventory with suika and go sell.
Fill my inventory with watermelon and go sell.
Yeah, like, if you want to get like really good ones, like consistently, they're so expensive.
And then at that point, I'm just like... I'm not a big fruit person at all, either.
So it's like, at that point, I'd rather just eat something else.
Like, I'd rather have cherry tomatoes than just random fruit.
Okay, maybe a little more rounds.
Like, those who are brave enough to venture, you shall be rewarded...
...with suika.
...with watermelon.
I'll stand like...
...on this side, so even if it falls, it falls into my inventory.
Yes.
And then this one is fine.
Yeah, and I always see like these like tricks that people are like,
"If the watermelon sounds like this when you hit this part of the watermelon, it's a good watermelon." I'm just like,
I like these tips, but I'm never going to remember it when I'm actually buying watermelon, although like...
...I never remember it when I actually need it.
Which is the problem.
And it's like, it's not like 100% true, either. Like, I've had...
...situations where I got the watermelon, and it's just not that great.
Okay.
We go town, we sell.
What are we going to buy?
Are we going to buy anything? I don't remember.
Oh yeah,
I guess I could fly. Eh, Elytra is broke. We shall walk today.
Oh yeah, we're going to do the stonks, stonks. Sell half stonks, okay.
Stonks. Stonks.
Watermelon is good if you soak it in stronger juice, but like...
...at that point, is it really worth eating the watermelon if it needs support from something else?
Like, I'd rather use that amount of nutrition and calories on eating something...
...better...
...or yummy, you know?
Oh yeah, we gotta sell.
We gotta sell.
おいしいな、おいしい。
Delicious, delicious.
Let's go.
必殺技の名前つけるかマジで悩む...
I'm really torn on whether to name a special move...
Okay, 80k for... not full.
That's why it just puts it back.
You guys are... You guys are...
I'm holding it.
Shift, double click.
Ah...
I am double clicking.
Alright, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter.
Okay, okay.
Hold with the cursor, not hand.
You can't see the cursor? My cursor's right here and I'm...
Like... if you do this...
どこにいるんだろう
Where is it, I wonder?
I don't know what... you guys can be like, 'Oh my goodness, Ina's being efficient.' That's fine.
Your instructions are all over the place.
ゆっくり移動しいのでね
Since I want to move slowly.
Okay.
I mean, that's not too bad. I mean, I think you earn a certain amount when you... I guess you earn more when you're harvesting than actually...
...selling it. But still.
It's still pretty good.
Buy more Shulkers? You're right. Should we buy like two more?
Oh, that's stonks! Sorry, I forgot.
I was too excited about my melons, and you guys telling me ten thousand different things.
Why does it say minus 15%? But, I mean, unit price still rose, so...
That's good, right? I have 14,000.
So, how many we sell? 7,000?
Yeah? Do I sell all of it? Hm...
Hmm...
You know what, I'm going to sell everything.
No, I mean, I guess I could just leave the... the rest, because I still have 4,870...
Hmm... What do I sell now?
No, I bought it at... Oh.
Oh.
I guess I didn't sell last time so I just can't... Oh wait, it's that... Oh right!
Yeah, I'm going to sell all.
Wait, I can only sell...
One?
No... Oh...
Wait, but then that means I'll never reach the daily limit.
Oh...
1枚10万円でしょ？
One slice is 100,000 yen, right?
Hmm, how about if I put in...
えっ、金な...
Wait, no money...
Yeah.
Then I'll buy shulkers.
えっ、金な...
Wait, no money...
4 million! We're halfway there!
Buy three?
No, we have how many? 150? Okay, we can buy three.
Okay, okay.
We've done it.
Now it begins.
Our suika journey.
Boxes, boxes for days.
Yeah, I didn't bring rockets because I was lazy to go back. I was already committed.
Okay.
This is it, the beginning of my journey.
Second last day.
I must do a lot today, just in case they change their mind tomorrow and nerf...
...the suika.
What happened to the bees? I should check, because I think it's level 2.
That's maximum, so it'd be nice if we can get some level 2.
Okay, level 2 money boost.
But yield and money boost ones...
If not, we can just toss them for...
...higher breeding.
This one and this one can be breeded.
I feel like it's just more convenient or more...
...probably more efficient to do some of these manually.
Because if there's like... Of course, these are like automated, but at the same time, some of them is like...
Okay, farm money 2.
This one I can breed.
Put in here? Okay.
Because I can't choose what to put in, so...
...if I don't want to care about it, then I can just leave it like this, but if I want the most yield...
...I think the final one I should like... always ask for...
Put in the hopper? That's true.
I forgot you can put it in the hopper.
And...
Like this.
Okay, we start? Okay.
Like, the skills are random no matter what you put in. The more important thing is their rank.
Because if you put in two super rares, you'll get four bees out of it, with a chance of getting more super rares.
It's not that they inherit skills or anything, I think.
Oh yeah, I need to get some wood for the trap doors.
Or I can just pluck the bottom. But I think it's better to have trap doors, because that means I can just walk over.
Like these ones, I like fall into the water, right?
You know what? Let's do that right away.
What's the price on the melon slices? I think it was like... 50 per melon slice?
Slabs are more efficient?
I guess slabs could work too, huh?
Is it 55?
I thought buying back is 55?
So slabs are better is what you guys are saying.
Okay, I will trust you. I will trust you...
...unless it's kind of annoying to put.
Like this, right?
Or do I put one below? Yes? No? Half a block lower?
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Iわかる。
I understand.
It's... it can work both ways, but I think this way is better.
Okay, a little bit of time lost, but I think it's a good investment of time.
Oh, wait.
I have to be careful I don't block off the entire water.
Especially that one row with the open water.
The melon won't grow on the slabs, right? 'Cause it's a... it's a slab.
If it does, then I'll just have to bonk you guys, that's all.
See, I'm getting split answers now.
I guess we'll see once I harvest.
Oh, ground and grass. Okay, okay.
Man, this is why sometimes I don't want to ask chat, 'cause it just messes up my brain.
My brain is already going at like 300 miles per hour, and then I ask, and then I get like 50 different answers.
I'm just like, "Well, now I'm overthinking again..."
...and doubting myself when I shouldn't be.
So, I do believe in myself. But, like, no matter how many times I say there's no need to backseat what I'm doing...
...people don't listen, so...
Okay, one last... Good, we're good, we're good.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. Good.
I would get more mods, but I have trust issues.
And now, it won't fall in the water.
Like, unless I can clone myself, I don't really trust them to actually act...
...the way I want them to. So...
Okay.
Na-na-na-na-na-na...
Stonks.
I know it's not much, but I feel like...
...I feel like we're doing so well with the...
...with the watermelons. I feel potential here.
I feel the potential.
Maybe we'll even have extra change to go get a takodachi.
Like, if we manage to reach our goal, we can go buy a takodachi.
Hehe, hehe, hehe...
Yeah, and then every time we go back, we fill the shulker.
Oh, this one's already full.
It may not fully grow back by the time we make rounds, but I think it's enough to keep filling the shulker.
Sweet, sweet money.
I have a feeling that melons might— I don't know...
...I wouldn't be surprised if melons are nerfed.
I guess knowledge is power.
Hehehe.
Mmm, suika. I want some watermelon.
Mmm, watermelon. I want some watermelon.
When is watermelon season? Is it like summer?
I assume it's summer.
Sometimes fruits have the weirdest, like, prime time.
It should be summer.
Okay, maybe I'll be on the lookout for some... some suika.
Okay, maybe I'll be on the lookout for some... some watermelon.
Hehehe...
The cube watermelons, I wonder if they taste any different...
...or if they're just for looks. I think it's just for looks, but like...
...at the same time...
...what if it does taste sweeter? Or a little different?
Like aesthetics versus— oh, I missed some.
Aesthetics versus taste.
Most square ones are inedible? What?!
No, that's such a waste of watermelon!
Melon.
I mean, I guess they still earn money out of it.
But what is... what is the point of...
...point of watermelon if not to eat?
I want a watermelon helmet.
Rest assured, everything is counted normally. Oh.
High-speed suika mining!
Speed, speed, speed!
I guess it's like just for display?
But like, that's the thing. That's the thing I don't like about melons.
It's like they are used as a symbol of like...
Like, what's that word?
It's like it's not... It's not used as what it's intended for,
and it's just... It's just empty.
It's just a sign of wealth, to just...
...show off your wealth and gift people...
...to show that you're wealthy.
Instead of...
"Hey, I tried this watermelon, it was delicious, so I bought one for you."
It's so sad... I mean, I know there are people who like...
...have their entire like...
...farm built for it, but I'm just like, "Ooh..."
...the potential of melon...
But I know I've had really expensive melons before, though.
But those are pretty good. It's just the ones that are only made to be gifted...
...instead of eaten. I'm just like...
Hmm. What if it was pretty and tasty?
What if it was pretty and tasty?
You know, you know?
Instead of "it looks nice", it's like "it looks nice and it's tasty."
Can't have both worlds.
It's just like...
That's the thing. It's like the thing with apples, right?
I think it was apples.
Like, some are bred...
...like, bred to look really, really nice,
but like, they're so tasteless.
Like, they look really nice...
...and plump, and they're huge.
But when you bite into it, it's just like... water.
I think it's the worst with apples.
Because like, you go to the supermarket...
...and all of the things that are like... like, piled on each other...
...is the big, red, juicy apples.
And then you're like, "Oh my goodness, it looks so good, I want to eat one."
And you buy some.
And then you eat it, and you're just like...
"What am I eating?"
It's like an apple that's meant to be displayed than eaten.
I like apples. I love apples.
I used to eat apples a lot.
It's just so hard to find good apples, too.
Oh, I love Royal Gala apples.
That's like the only apple Mommy buys.
That's like the only kind she buys.
Oh, it almost filled another one.
Which is the reason... Oh, I need another axe.
Wow, we had to go get another axe.
I mean, it's a good investment.
But yeah, it's like...
...the reason I know Royal Galas is because that's the only thing Mommy buys.
And then like, 'cause I didn't, back then I didn't know like...
...the different types of apples.
So I would go to the supermarket, like, when I was living by myself,
I was like, 'I'll go to the supermarket,' I was like, 'Oh, I could use an apple.' And then...
...I should've known the name of the apples I always eat.
So I expect like the taste of Royal Gala, and then I buy that...
...that one other one that is tasteless. And I'm just like, 'Ugh...
...this isn't the taste of apple I remember.'
It's mushy, it's not sweet...
...it's not sour either. It's just... it's just the texture and everything is just...
...it's almost like grainy, you know, when you bite into it.
Mmm, yeah, it must have been the Red Delicious. It's like...
...they shouldn't have named it the Red Delicious. I'm sure it's good marketing...
...if you call it the Red Delicious, but it's like...
...it's not that delicious.
It... it's a scam!
Like, imagine a foreigner goes to a mart and they're like, 'Ooh, Red Delicious!'
'It must be a delicious apple because I know what "delicious" means.'
And then they'll forever be scarred.
And then they'll think that all Western apples, or, not just Western...
...all apples are not that great in this country because they had that one apple at the mart...
...and it was called the Red Delicious. And if that was the Red Delicious, then how...// (corrected typo "Red Delicous" in transcription)
...and it was called the Red Delicious. And if that was the Red Delicious, then how...
...how much worse are the other apples going to be?
Ah... the disappointment, immeasurable.
Their day, ruined!
I can't believe I'm having a little rant about apples.
What is it about apples? Talking about bad apples.
But I do like the green ones, actually. I forgot what they're called.
What's the... what was the Granny something? Granny Smith.
I do like Granny Smith. I like the fact that they have a strong brand...
...of being like that sour apple, you know? Like, at least...
...their branding of the apple is on point, you know?
It's like the sour, sweet apple.
I love Granny Smith.
It's like if I want sour candy, like, I would go out to just get a Granny Smith instead.
Like, it's that good.
But then, I guess, I do like sour things.
I like sour candies, too. I haven't been eating that many candies recently...
...but my go-to sour candy is literally Sour Patch Kids. Like, whenever...
...I feel like indulging myself in cheap American candy, I go for Sour Patch Kids.
Like, it just... it just is a good level of sweet and sour.
Ah, one more... Oh, there's some pumpkins left in there.
Yeah. What other fruits?
I mean, I think the only reason I would actually, like, eat fruit back in the day...
...was because my mom is buying it.
And then, I'm just like, 'Hmm...
...she packed it into my lunch so I have to eat it.'
Like, I don't go out of my way to buy fruits and eat it unless, like, somehow I have a random craving...
...for an apple or something, and then I would... I would be in the mart, and I'll be like...
...'Oh, I guess I'll grab one apple from the bulk section.' But...
...you know, I don't, you know, add it into my grocery list on purpose.
Oh... There you go.
Grapes... that's the thing. A lot of the things that I...
don't really like...
It's because like...
Sorry, Mom. Please close your ears.
It's because like she fed me too much of it...
...during school lunches.
Because grapes are really easy to add into like...
...packing lunches, right? So, I would have grapes like...
...every single day...
...basically.
And I would still eat it because I want to finish my lunch, but...
at some point, I'm just like...
I kind of... I kind of would like some other fruits...
...if it was to be.
And then some... And it's like, it's fine if it's good grape,
but at the same time...
Oh, I get what you're talking about now.
Okay.
If it's like this and then you go like...
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Your instructions before were really unclear.
Just letting you guys know. I understand now, but...
You guys were like, "Shift double click!"
But that didn't work. Instructions unclear.
I get it now. Okay, anyways, what was I talking about? Grapes.
Yeah, and then like... Of course, since...
...she's always packing lunch for three people at the same time,
we would buy stuff in bulk.
But then, you know, fruits go bad pretty quickly,
so sometimes I would grab a grape,
but then it would be like...
a little too squishy, if you know what I mean, like as if it's like borderline...
...not good to eat.
And then I would feel iffy and not eat it,
but then some of them just taste bad in general.
And then if that happens multiple times, I'm just like...
"Oh, maybe I don't like grapes that much after all."
I mean, I don't have anything against grapes,
so I would still eat it if it's on my plate, but...
it's one of the things where I'm just like, I don't want to go out of my way to get...
...buy grapes and eat it.
And also the fact that I don't like raisins that much.
I think like Shine Muscat is fine because Shine Muscat all kind of...
...tastes the same, I'm sorry.
But like normal grapes, I think there's just a big gap difference between good grapes and bad grapes.
Like, I don't mean that in a bad way that Shine Muscat all taste the same because...
...they taste good.
They all have the same taste, basically.
That's a lot of hate from Ina, my goodness. Have you been hanging out with a certain predator?
Maybe...
I may have...
gone to...
lunch with her, perhaps.
Sorry, influence of my rival.
Cuz like, I was supposed to go out...
...to lunch with her, like last time she was here, but I was sick...
...the entire time.
And then by the time...
...I got better, I was like, "Hey!"
"Hey, I think I'm better enough to go eat, hang out now!" And then she was like, "I'm literally at the airport!"
So...
So I told her we'll go out for...
our food together next time she's here. And she was like, "Oh, I'm back!" I was like, "Oh, let's go, food, hungry!"
Yes, that's... that's what happened.
Okay, as long as my inventory is full, we can go sell.
Wait...
A little less...
...full, because we need to carry the actual shulker boxes.
And we're... we're almost at 2 mil from just chatting and suika gathering?
And we're... we're almost at 2 million from just chatting and watermelon gathering?
Okay, we need... how many? We need five slots free, okay.
The suika's done.
The watermelons are done.
The rise of the farmers.
This is Act... Act 3.
I wonder how much money everyone has right now.
Okay, all right. I think that's good enough for now.
And maybe we'll grab another axe too. Remind me to grab another axe.
Farm yield boost... Farm money boost. Oh.
You think farm money boost always is good? Is better than everything else?
You think farm money boost is always good? Better than everything else?
Getting a lot of combat bees.
The yield... not as much as...
I do have a lot of farm money boost level 2s.
15 mil?
15 million?
こっちも 一緒に しれっと...
This one too, quietly together...
Okay.
And we're in the 14-15 million range.
It's gonna take a long time.
Okay, now this is... okay, now that's how you do it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Makes sense.
Hoshiki.
I'm gonna be number one, e-e-yup!
Yes, the games are rigged from the start!
Only two slots available for hard mode.
Okay.
Oh, so much money! I didn't think I was gonna have this much money.
I wish I had this much money in real life.
Actually, I guess it's Yen. We gotta subtract for that.
It's still a lot of money.
Do, do...
Mm, hm-hm...
Dah, dah, dah, dah, dah, dah...
Oh...
Do, do, do, do, do...
Ta, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta...
6.7... Wait, we reached 6.7?
Ooh...
Wait, I feel like 8 mil is doable, like...
...even within today.
Ah...
We can do it.
Ta, ta, ta...
I feel like if suika is not nerfed tomorrow...
...we can actually aim for 18.
Like, we still have melons to sell.
Ta, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta...
Ooh...
Yeah, might as well just keep doing this in case they nerf it tomorrow.
Hehehe...
It's not bad. It's basically a...
...a... let's just say...
...a stock market.
Ah, 6.9!
Ta, ta...
Yeah, I should get rid of all the extra stuff in my inventory. You're right.
I just hope I do get a... if I get a little better...
...bee... in the meantime...
...that's good. If not...
...X_X.
Thank you. Thank you for the reminder.
Uh, how much is the axe again?
Ta, ta, ta...
I want to start off at zero to see what the next... next trip is going to be.
Farmer... fighter...
30,000. Okay.
Withdraw 30,000.
Did Luna-senpai also start...
...suika?
Perhaps.
Suika.
Okay.
Ta, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta...
Everyone has learned of the suika.
Yes.
Oh, sheesh. Hehehe...
I mean, it was pretty easy to get.
Is this the suika game we heard about?
The suika game?
Guess I don't need torches. I'll leave this here.
Ta, ta, ta, ta, ta...
Okay, back to the suika.
Not that suika game? Are you sure?
Ooh...
Oh, I forgot to drink my coffee.
Mm...
Now anyway, let's check the bees.
I do have a couple of like farm money boost level 2s,
but then like it gets rid of the level one yield.
It would be nice to get one with both level 2s.
Oh, I forgot where I left off.
But I think we can get to 8 mil today.
We just got... We basically just have 1 mil to go.
Yeah.
I think level 2's the highest skill level wise, so...
Our dreams...
No, it's just like...
the... the higher rarity stuff you breed,
you get more bees instead of like...
If you breed, I think like, two rare ones, you get...
um, you get two bees. If you breed normal ones, you get one.
If you breed two super rare ones, you get four bees at the end.
And then, whatever four bees you get, it's not like...
it inherits skills, it's just random.
Hm... Two bees? What about 9S?
Two bees...
To bee or not to bee, that is the question.
Whether 'tis nobler in the mind to suffer... I forgot the rest.
That wasn't my soliloquy back in high school.
My one... My soliloquy I chose, because literally like everyone chooses "To bee or not to bee," I chose Macbeth.
Because Macbeth, I think, is a more interesting story in my opinion.
Ah! Oh, kabu.
Ah! Oh, stocks.
Not that I can do anything anymore.
Okay, I think I can do twice and then go to the box.
Like twice is basically almost one full shulker.
I, personally, did not like King Lear as much.
Not as like... Ooh! That's a big raise.
Not as like literature, but like just...
as a human being, I always found King Lear so frustrating to read.
Like, you guys get me, right? I'm just like...
I was like...
King Lear... Ozora Construction! 285!
I was like, "King Lear, you're such a fool!"
And I will never feel bad for you.
And like...
So basically, like from what I remember of King Lear, it's like...
King Lear is like, "Oh, I'm stepping down from the throne.
Uh, my children, you will take care of me, right?"
And then the eldest is just like, "Uh... uh..."
And then like the second... second child... I don't know how many children he has...
the second child is like, "Ah, oh, um..."
cause of... cause of him,
And she... and he...
In the end, like, you would think, you know,
that he would be like, "Oh, I was wrong all this time!"
"Our youngest daughter..."
"How could I have not seen? It was you."
I don't think he even regretted. He just...
...he was just lamenting over his own sad life
instead of being like, "Ah..."
"...young daughter,"
"I should have always listened to you, who actually cared for me."
And then, the only thing I agreed...
...was when...
I do agree that it is a tragedy,
but my English teacher explained...
...it is not a tragedy because of King Lear, because...
...to him, and to me, too...
...tragedy is loss of potential.
And in this case, King Lear is not...
...part of this tragedy. The tragedy is for the youngest daughter,
because she had so much potential,
but it's lost because of the foolishness of King Lear.
That's the tragedy.
Not what tragic fate that King Lear is...
...having.
And I was like, "You know what? You're right."
You're right.
Anyway, sorry. That was my little...
...high school English...
...part.
That's why I never really liked King Lear.
But Macbeth, I thought Macbeth was a very interesting...
...story.
Which is why I chose it to be my soliloquy...
...like reading, memorization thing.
Othello... Othello was...
...wasn't that memorable to me. Like, the...
...most memorable one was...
...Macbeth, of course.
And then, it was King Lear, because I didn't like King Lear that much.
Do I still remember it? Uh...
"She should have died hereafter."
"There would have been a time for such a word."
"Tomorrow, and tomorrow, and tomorrow..."
"...creeps in this petty pace..."
"...to the last syllable of recorded time."
I'm starting to forget it, now that I'm actually reciting it.
Something, something...
...fool.
Now that I'm put on the spot, I don't remember it.
I can still recite it, I just can't right now.
I think this happens to me so often, where it's like, I know it,
and I know all the names, all the things that I like,
but then like, when someone actually asks me,
like...
"What's your top favorite anime?"
I'm just like, "Uh... uh..."
And then someone asks me, "What's your favorite movie?"
The name suddenly slips out of my mind.
And then, I start to doubt myself, I'm just like...
"Am I... do I actually like this?"
And it's really sad, in a way,
cause I know I really like it, but then like, when I'm put on the spot,
my brain just blanks,
and I can't answer.
And then someone asks me, "Who's your favorite character in this anime?"
I'm just like, "Uh..."
Suddenly, they don't seem like my favorite character,
and I'm just...
...I just like, very surface-level, like a series,
because I don't know the character's name.
But I know and have enjoyed the series for so long,
but their name just escapes my tongue,
that one moment I'm asked.
Oh, so if you do it the other way, it goes into the...
あ、なるほどなるほどなるほど。
Ah, I see, I see, I see.
I have learned.
There's watermelon ghost behind me.
There's a watermelon ghost behind me?
Oh, please give me more watermelons.
She can be taught! Haha!
This one... This one has a brain.
Nene?
Sir, we got an intelligent one here.
Actually, one that has a little more than nine int.
This one has a brain.
It speaks.
Almost one mil.
The dream is true.
What if I get the number today and I don't play tomorrow?
What if I take a break tomorrow?
And then, suddenly...
I have the number.
Although I do hope that I get home in time tomorrow. I should, I think.
Because I have to go somewhere a little further, so...
I know, I have to go outside tomorrow. Ah!
Yes, tomorrow's the last day.
I think, like, it would have been nice if they extended a day, but I think schedule-wise,
some members are just can't participate, so it's probably better to just...
some members just can't participate, so it's probably better to just...
Ah! Not again!
I think it was a good idea that they decided they're gonna keep it the same day.
Because, you know, there's a lot of members doing this.
Not everyone is free all the time.
Yeah, I was really unlucky. It's not often that the Minecraft servers go down, I think.
Is this full? No.
I'm learning.
I stream a lot... well, there was a record on this, but...
I do have to be away for family stuff for like a week or so, I think.
I'm probably gonna use that, hopefully, to also digital detox myself a little bit,
cause I feel like I've been watching too many shorts and stuff,
not being able to sleep properly.
I think it's about time. Might as well.
We're getting there, guys. Wait, I think we have... we have eight mil now.
Yeah, I bought a whole bunch of books to read, too.
So...
That was my goal, to read, I think, like... 30 books this year.
I'm only at, like, five.
And we're halfway through the year.
So, I think I just need to step up my reading game a little bit.
I mean, I read really fast. I don't know if you guys know, but...
I don't know what, like, a good speed is, but, like, I can finish... if I'm, like, in the zone, I can finish, like...
Hmm...
Let's see, what was my record?
Because I remember I finished, like, an entire book...
I forgot, like, 300... It was somewhere between 300 to 500 in, like,
one very short flight.
I forgot how long that flight was, but it was one of the shorter flights.
And that's one of the reasons I got, like, a more portable ebook reader.
Because, like, of course I can't own that many books...
...in Japan.
And having ebooks is just nice.
And then, whatchamacallit... And like, when I'm, whenever I'm, like, traveling to...
...the studio...
...or like...
Or like, whatchamacallit...
...or I'm going somewhere...
...like, it's usually, like, many minutes and stuff in the train rides, so I was like...
...I mean, I could scroll through, like, shorts or, you know, read stuff, but...
...it's probably better to start reading more books again.
I love ebooks. I think they're great.
So...
I mean, I like owning physical books, let's be real. If I had the choice, I would buy the physical books, but like...
...this is not my permanent place, and like, if I have to move out of it...
...then, it's just... books are heavy.
I remember when I was moving out of, like, my parents' place into the office...
...I already had so many books.
And it was so heavy.
And like, you can't just shove all the books into a box and carry it, cuz it's so heavy...
...and bulky.
So you have to make, like, so many multiple trips. I think I ruined some of the... Oh, yeah.
Did I?
Why do I have more seeds?
Ah, I guess we'll see.
So yeah, it's like, so I don't wanna buy that many... I already have a lot of books.
Especially with a lot of, like, art books and stuff releasing, and it's so easy to get them because I'm in Japan.
And then...
...all of a sudden, it's like, oh, I look at the bookshelf here and it's already full.
And I'm just like, oh, what have I done? So I can't really add any more books to that pile.
I'm trying to hold back.
Which is why I got the ebook stuff, cuz it's just much more easier to carry around, too.
And like, if I were to ship it back home, too, it's a lot of money. Books are expensive to ship because they're so heavy.
My manager is always like, you know, you can start like shipping back stuff...
...like books and stuff. I'm just like, but I need those books, they're my references.
They're my knowledge.
I need them while I'm here.
But I have so many... I literally have a mini-library back home.
Cuz like, the walk-in... there's like a walk-in closet, a small one...
...where the streaming setup is, and I just turned it into a mini-library.
And it's full of books from floor to ceiling...
...and it's running out of space.
It's like a happy, happy thing to worry about...
...but at the same time, I'm just like, what am I going to do with all these books?
But like, I wanna digitize some of the books...
...so I can at least, like, access them when I'm overseas, cuz like, I don't wanna rebuy...
...books that don't have digital versions.
Like, there are books where it covers, like...
...like anatomy and stuff that I wish I had, but...
...it's heavy to always carry around, and it doesn't have like an ebook version.
So I... I like...
...I like got all the pages I needed and I saved it for myself, and I'm just like...
...man, it'd be really nice if all my books that I own are digitized...
...so I don't always have to be like, ah, I could rebuy the book or not, whatnot.
It's kind of sad.
But I do understand, like, not all books can be digitized. I wish they were.
I wish they were.
And I saw this, like, really...
really fancy machine they use at like
A really fancy machine they use at, like...
like big libraries or like places they where they have to archive stuff. It's like...
...big libraries, or places where they have to archive stuff. It's like...
I don't know, like a $8,000, $15,000 machine where it like scans...
...I don't know, like an $8,000 or $15,000 machine where it scans...
the books like but without harming them. It's it looks really fancy.
...the books, but without harming them. It looks really fancy.
I'm just like, 'Ooh!'
I wish I had one of those.
But like those types of scanning machines they use it like at huge libraries and stuff, you know?
But those types of scanning machines, they use them at huge libraries and stuff, you know?
But it would really be cool.
Can it fit in a house? I can make it work.
I can make room!
But can I can I get like the amount of thousands of dollars' worth out of the machine if I were to buy it? No.
But would I get thousands of dollars' worth of use out of the machine if I were to buy it? No.
But then I do have like a semi setup if I do...
But then, I do have a semi-setup if I do...
Cuz like there are like reference books that I use really often that I have digitized.
Because there are reference books that I use really often that I have digitized.
It just needs a little bit of a slight setup with like my phone and stuff.
It just needs a little bit of a slight setup with my phone and stuff.
Cuz there are apps and stuff that turns your photos that you take into PDF, so...
Because there are apps that turn the photos you take into PDFs, so...
that is doable.
Yeah, so that's what I've been doing for like the... the ones I use a lot.
Yeah, so that's what I've been doing for the ones I use a lot.
And they're like very thick books, so I don't want to always carry it to Japan...
And they're very thick books, so I don't want to always carry them to Japan...
whenever I'm going back and forth.
But it's been helpful.
And then there was also me back in, back in university.
And then, there was also me back in university.
I used to carry like all my textbooks in my backpack...
I used to carry all my textbooks in my backpack...
and my backpack was like a literal literal weapon.
...and my backpack was like a literal weapon.
And my mom would always be like, "Stop carrying so much books in your backpack!"
And my mom would always be like, "Stop carrying so many books in your backpack!"
Cuz like I don't really have a locker in university. I have to carry all my books.
Because I didn't really have a locker in university. I had to carry all my books.
Like everything is money in university. You want a locker, you gotta rent it. You gotta do this, you gotta...
Everything is money in university. You want a locker, you've got to rent it. You want this, you've got to...
Like you got, you got a textbook that's one edition different from your... the one that's required for your course...
If you have a textbook that's one edition different from the one required for your course...
you can't use it. And it's just like...
ugh.
Man, university textbooks are such a scam.
You know what the most use I got out of my university textbook was?
Was when I was lacking height on my tablet.
It was when I was lacking height for my tablet.
I used it and it was the perfect height.
I was like, 'Oh!
Perfect height!'
I'm pretty sure it was my geophysics textbook...
which I never really looked at...
in the first place.
Last time I went back home, like I was just like spending time in the lab- like my mini library,
Last time I went back home, I was spending time in my mini library...
I was looking through all the books. I was like, 'Oh, I still have my textbooks!'
...looking through all the books. I was like, "Oh, I still have my textbooks!"
And then I was like, 'Oh...'
Like my mineralogy textbook and stuff, I use quite often because it's like a reference.
So I'm like, you know what...
あ、がちゃ。
Ah, gacha.
こんにちは！
Hello!
But then I'm like, I saw my geophysics one and I'm just like, "There's dents on the cover..."
...cause it was used to hold up my tablet for so long!
Anyways, that was my little... little tidbit.
Okay...
I feel like everyone's doing watermelon right now.
Okay.
So much money!
バンクが上がりません。あの、本当に素晴らしいあれだと思います。本当に、マジで。
My bank balance isn't going up. Um, I think it's a really great thing, really. Seriously.
なんだ、なんだ？
What's that? What's going on?
あずちゃん、反映されて...今されてる？お金？
Az-chan, is it reflecting... is your money reflecting now?
あ、そう、ちょいちょい。なんかでも、ログアウトして、入り直してます。
Ah, yeah, bit by bit. But I'm logging out and logging back in.
はい、すいませんね。
Okay, sorry about that.
はーい。
Okay~
なんかあったら言ってください。
Let me know if anything happens.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
数えられてますか？
Is it being counted?
おいか、ちょい、ちょい...
Oika, choi, choi...
ワンチャン入りますね。
There's a chance we'll get in.
おおおー
Ooooh~
頑張ってください、あずち。
Good luck, Azuchi!
頑張る。
I'll do my best.
I didn't think I would have this much money today.
Oh, we only have three minutes though.
We'll see how much we can...
...we can get though.
I'm busy! Okay...
Life of a farmer is so busy, man. A serious business.
Are you, are you farming bees?
Uh, a little bit. Do you need some?
Um, if you have one with Regeneration Level 2... What's it called again?
I might.
Oh, you might?
I could look.
Would you sell them to me?
I could, sure.
Hold on, hold on. I gotta sell, I gotta sell my goods first.
Okay.
And then I can go home.
Just letting you know that I'm interested in a Regeneration Level 2 bee.
Okay, I will... I will let you know in chat when I'm back home and check.
Okay.
Do you know where my house is?
No.
Okay, just walk straight from here.
That way, where I'm facing.
Is it north, is it south, south-west?
No, like, look, look at where I'm looking.
Okay.
Yeah, walk straight.
Walk straight.
And then you'll see a corner house near the water.
Okay, okay.
We have more combat bees, right?
I mean, there is some that are being born right now, so...
Buy it for 2 million?
Is Regen 2 that good?
あ、あずちゃん、回復のレベル２持ってない？
Ah, Az-chan, do you have a Regen Level 2?
レベル２ね。えっと、待って。持ってたら言います。
Level 2? Uh, wait. If I have it, I'll let you know.
持ってたら買います。
If you have it, I'll buy it.
Oh, Level 2 Regen Bee is the hot thing.
I think everyone can...
I forgot I had...
...fireworks.
...can equip up to two, and then farmers can just equip a little more.
Oh.
Some food...
Uh...
Okay, where's all the combat bees?
I haven't gotten a...
Dolphin's Grace.
I haven't gotten a rare... Okay, Regen level 2, there's one.
Water Breathing, Regen 1.
I think... I mean, this one also has Regen 2, it doesn't have any other skills.
Hmm...
Regen, Speed would be worth a lot.
Oh, this one is missing a bee, hold on, hold on, hold on.
This hasn't been cooking for so long.
There's another Regen... Regen 1, Fire Resistance.
My system was broken.
Is there another Regen 2?
Hello! Hello!
Hello!
Oh my god!
Realization.
I do have... hold on, let's see.
I love your farm!
Oh, thank you, thank you!
Well, I have, currently, two bees that have Regen 2...
...but one of them also has Speed 1.
Ah, Speed 1. What will be the price difference?
I don't know how much bees go for, honestly, but I can sell the super rare...
Honestly, I also don't know.
Yeah.
How- how- how much- what's your budget?
Oh, my budget?
Yeah.
I guess as long as it doesn't go over 1 million, so below 1 million would be ideal.
Okay, okay, okay.
The thing is, I also don't know the price market of the bees.
That's true.
Actually, let me go look at how much it is in shop real quick with my Elytra. I'll come back.
I don't know if there's anyone selling bees, Regen...
No, like there's like... there's a... there's a base price for the shop, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah, okay, okay.
Okay.
My chat is saying 9-9-9-9-9-9-9, but I'll make you a good deal.
I'll be right back, I'll be right back.
Please give me...
I think the super rare one is like a little less, but I'll check.
Where's my mouse? There you go.
Okay, 10,000 base price.
Regen is bonkers, man.
Hello!
All right, so, the base price that I can just sell it to the store is 10k.
10k?
But since it has... since it has options that you desire...
...I would like to say...
Um...
...50k for the one with the Speed...
Uh-huh.
...and then, just 20k for the one with just the Regen 2, how is that?
Ah!
Anya: I like to take the... the one with the speed, then.
Ina: Okay, okay.
Anya: Um, do you know how to transfer money?
Ina: I think we have to do it, um, at the flea market.
Anya: Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Ina: Okay, I'll see you at the flea market. Do you have food?
Ina: Oh, what are... what do you desire? I currently mostly have bread. I used to have pumpkin pie, but I sold it all.
Anya: Yeah, bread is fine.
Ina: Okay, okay, okay. I can sell you...
Ina: I can sell you 30.
Anya: Okay, okay, okay. I love bread honestly.
Anya: If you had more, I'd buy more, definitely.
Ina: All right.
Ina: Okay, okay, okay. I'll be at the flea market. I mean, we can walk together, I guess.
Anya: Okay.
Ina: Okay, okay, okay.
Ina: Did you know that no matter what we do...
Anya: Uh-huh.
Ina: ...we're gonna be number one in EN and number one in ID, I think!
Anya: No, 'cause I thought, I thought there would be more people from EN and ID playing.
Anya: Even Kaela... Kaela did log in, but only for one day, so like...
Ina: I mean, I think EN just finished EN Reco, which was also Minecraft, too, so...
Anya: Ah, you're right.
Ina: Yeah.
Anya: You're right, you're right.
Anya: But dang, are you gonna log in too for tomorrow? I mean, tomorrow is...
Ina: I think so. I think, if I get home in time, I'll... I'll...
Ina: I have to go out tomorrow, but, yeah.
Anya: Okay, okay, okay.
Ina: Okay, okay.
Ina: Ah! Who was it?
Ina: 神様？ 神様。
Anya: 神様だった。
Ina: Kami-sama? Kami-sama.
Anya: It was Kami-sama.
Ina: 神様。
Anya: 神様...
Ina: Kami-sama.
Anya: Kami-sama...
Ina: Okay, where's the flea market? Right there, okay. I need to learn how to use the flea market. Let's see.
Anya: Okay, okay.
Anya: Did you... did you get your mascot?
Ina: No, not yet.
Ina: Do you know how to use the flea market?
Anya: Um, unfortunately, no.
Ina: Why are the bees so expensive? Wow.
Anya: What do they have?
Anya: Aura slowness? Fire resistance? What is glowing for?
Ina: Oh, okay, okay. I'm... I'm putting it up, okay? You gotta...
Anya: Okay.
Ina: Okay, 50K.
Anya: I bought one with Regeneration Level 1 for like 30K. Why are these so expensive?
Ina: Well, you know, the sellers name the price. Okay, it's up there! You gotta get it. Go, go, go, go.
Anya: Where?
Ina: It's like on the second, second row? Yeah.
Anya: Ah, oh, oh. Ah, ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ina: Okay, okay, okay. Did you get it?
Ina: Yeah, I got the money!
Anya: Ina, I love you!
Anya: I was about to get scammed!
Ina: Maybe I'll put this one up for 30K, too.
Anya: Okay.
Ina: Okay, thank you. Oh, yeah, I need to sell you bread, too.
Anya: Oh, yeah, the food. The food, yeah.
Ina: Okay, I'll... I'll sell it for 10... 10 a bread.
Anya: Yeah, yeah, yeah. At this point, at this point...
Ina: Oh, wait, hold on.
Anya: It's okay, you can sell the food a little bit expensive to me. I'll tip you.
Anya: I wish I could... I wish I could tip you.
Ina: Really? Okay.
Ina: Listing... Wait, is it per... item or...
Ina: Ah, okay, okay, okay. It's per item. I mean, I'll go 15 per bread, and that should be fine.
Ina: Okay, the bread is up as well.
Anya: Oh my god, 51 bread! Oh, how can I tip you?
Ina: Well, if you ever have any extra... uh, equipment things that are left over, I think...
Anya: Oh, I have.
Anya: I have a bunch. What do you need?
Ina: I think I have one super rare and one rare, so like, if there's anything better you have spare of...
Ina: ...that, I think is fine. I don't really fight, I just farm, so...
Anya: You know, what do you need? Is it attack damage or kill reward or what? Might have some.
Ina: Oh...
Ina: Probably just like max health too, 'cause I'm just...
Ina: ...I'm just trying to survive in this world.
Anya: I'll give you one.
Ina: I'm trying to survive in this world, thanks!
Anya: Max health Level 2!
Ina: Thank you! Good trade, good trade.
Anya: Thank you.
Anya: Good luck farming.
Ina: Thank you.
Suisei: いな、な、な、な、な、な...
Suisei: Ina, na, na, na, na, na...
Ina: あ、タコだち！
Ina: Ah, Takodachi!
Suisei: タコだち、タコだち、タコだち...
Ina: タコだち、タコだち、タコだち...タコだち。
Suisei: Takodachi, Takodachi, Takodachi...
Ina: Takodachi, Takodachi, Takodachi... Takodachi.
Ina: 光ってる、うん。
Suisei: タコだち。
Ina: It's shimmering, yeah.
Suisei: Takodachi.
Ina: 私のタコだち！ 私...
Suisei: 私のお金？
Ina: 私のお金？ 私のお金？
Suisei: あなたは無い？
Ina: My Takodachi! I...
Suisei: My money?
Ina: My money? My money?
Suisei: Don't you have any?
何持ってるの？
What are you holding?
あ、あ、らーめん。
Oh, oh, ramen.
らーめん。
Ramen.
らーめん？
Ramen?
らーめん。
Ramen.
あげる。
I'll give it to you.
おまるは何してんの？
What is Omaru doing?
ロケット。
Rocket.
ロケット？
Rocket?
錬金？錬金してんの？
Alchemy? Are you doing alchemy?
タコダチ。
Takodachi.
あ、トレード。
Oh, trade.
トレードね。
A trade, I see.
あ！
Ah!
もっといいものが...
Something even better...
いいね、いいね。
Nice, nice.
めっちゃ新鮮。
So fresh.
く、これだけでいいんですか？
I-Is this all you want?
うん、タコダチ大事にしてね、みんな。
Yeah, take good care of the Takodachi, everyone.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
サンキュー！
Thank you!
やった！
Yay!
いえーい！やったー！
Yay! We did it!
いえーい！
Yay!
ギャンブル、ギャンブル、今調子どうですか？
Gambler, gambler, how are you doing right now?
調子？
How am I doing?
ギャンブルなんかやるんじゃないぞ。
Don't you go gambling.
何言ってるの？
What are you saying?
いいか？
Got it?
ギャンブラーなんかになるな。
Don't become a gambler.
なんか声変わってるんですよ、大丈夫？
Her voice changed somehow, is she okay?
これは、これはこの街たった一人のギャンブラーからの...
This is... This is advice from the only gambler in this town...
確かに。
True.
ギャンブラー、今日初めて見ました。
A gambler... I saw one for the first time today.
ギャンブルなんかするな。
Don't gamble.
そっか。
I see.
ギャンブラーってカジノから出ないからね。
Because gamblers don't leave the casino, you know.
I tried gambling and it was freaking rigged.
It was freaking rigged, don't gamble, Ina.
I tried once and I lost, I lost everything I bet and it was kind of sad.
I know, it's rigged, never touch it.
Never touch it, don't gamble.
Yeah.
Tako, Tako, Tako.
Takotakotako.
Okay, well, good luck with your adventures.
I shall deposit my money and continue to earn money before it gets nerfed.
Thank you.
If you have more food, I would love...
Okay, I shall, I shall let you know, okay. Take care.
Okay.
Yeah, bye-bye!
ギャンブルダメか。
No gambling, huh.
I think we can get to 10 mil today. Oh.
Oh yeah, has it been extended today? I thought it was gonna end normally.
I think today is normal schedule, no? That's what they said.
Unless they changed it again. Oh, okay, they did change it.
So, it's now later today. Okay.
Wait, we can totally get... That's just one harvest and we get to...
10 mil.
Wait, 18 mil is totally doable now.
I guess like at the end of the day, if like I want it to be exactly the amount that I want,
I can just list something on the flea market. Hopefully that doesn't count.
Okay.
Okay, Takodachi, you're a special one.
I should name you Ina so then...
I would've been held in her hands.
So we have to get as much as we can today to...
get as close to 18 as possible.
Cuz there's a non-zero chance melon will be nerfed.
Omapol was burnt to a crisp.
Hmm, kind of want a snack, but I don't have that much snacks.
I should've bought some.
I also had one meal today, one big meal.
Cuz we... It was a late lunch.
Cuz Susei and I went to eat.
Cuz Suisei and I went to eat.
But the restaurant didn't open until a bit later.
So we were just walking around until it opened.
Oh, they're burnt to a crisp.
I don't know what to eat, oh.
Maybe I should have ordered some snacks with the coffee...
...in hindsight.
Nyah. Nyah. Nyah. Nyah.
I mean, I can give her carrots. Carrots is food.
I mean, I can give her carrots. Carrots are food.
I have a whole bunch of carrots over there that I left.
Pumpkin pie is not really efficient right now.
But carrots, I can just harvest and replant and give to Onion...
But carrots, I can just harvest, replant, and give to Onion...
...or sell to Onion, because gift- gifting is not really...
...you know, a thing.
It is all business here.
It's all business here.
I mean, pumpkin pie is technically easier to make because you can buy the eggs...
...and the sugar now. Like, it was very undervalued last time.
But now you can, like, buy eggs and sugar, so...
...but it's still...
Because, like, you get so much pumpkin, but then at the same time...
...if watermelon grows...
...at the same time as a pumpkin, but it gives us slices...
...and the slices are dependent on the farmer's, like, yield skill...
...then it's much better to just do suika right now.
...then it's much better to just do watermelon right now.
Oh. Lost track.
Cuz like, the pumpkin you can sell it, but...
Because, like, you can sell the pumpkin, but...
...it's the entire pumpkin, not pumpkin slices.
But the suika, you sell the slices...
But with watermelon, you sell the slices...
...and you get multiple slices per harvest.
And that's money.
Yes, yes.
Actually, I think like we don't have solid plans yet, but like...
...Bae and I were talking about doing, making some stuff...
...for the Knight Academy side, prequel thing.
...for the Knight Academy side-prequel thing.
Or like, "We should try doing this and this!"
Just as like, fan content, nothing official, but...
I'm glad there has been very good reception...
I'm glad there has been a very good reception...
...to my delusions at 2 AM.
But I think it could be pretty cool.
2 AM is the best delu-time.
It's like 2 to 3 AM is like when everyone's, what you call it...
It's like 2 to 3 AM is like when everyone's, what do you call it...
...imagination just like bursts, and you're just like, "Oh!"
Yeah.
Exactly when you need to fall asleep.
Like, what- what was happening with Liz during...
...or Lady Bloodflame?
Like, was she being taken over?
Corrupted? What was happening?
The eyes turning blue...
...by- by Nurse Juliet? Oh...
I can- I can smell another delicious side story there.
Ah, let me cook.
Like this is... okay, this is my own delusion right now.
I'm not... I'm not speaking...
...in... in like...
...in... for what their story is.
But what if...?
What if...?
Like...?
What if in the alternate universe...
My delusion... Okay, this is my delusion speaking.
What if...
...something happened, and...
Oh, wait, wait. My bag is full.
My...
So...
Okay, hear me out, hear me out.
So, an incident happened, something...
...where...
...Lady Bloodflame...
...actually perished...
...protecting Nurse Juliet.
But Nurse Juliet...
...couldn't accept that fact.
And she has memory-holed...
...the fact that Lady Bloodflame has passed...
...and used her magic to bring her back to life.
But...
Oh...
But then...
...the magic, of course, doesn't always work the way...
...it was intended to, because she was not as experienced...
...when it happened.
So, the reason that Lady Bloodflame...
...has suddenly... her eyes started...
...becoming blue and stuff, and she had... her...
...her complexion has become darker, was because...
...the magic was... was running out.
And something is going to be so wrong.
Ah...
And Nurse Juliet doesn't realize this because...
...she just thinks that something's wrong because...
...she... she...
...decided to forget...
...the fact that this happened.
And Lady Bloodflame is already gone.
The angst! Oh, I can feel it!
The delusions... they're writing!
So, that's my 2:00 AM...
I mean, it's... it's kind of getting there. We're nearing midnight.
It's starting to ramp up.
And then during the Knight Academy arc...
...a couple of years after the Knight Academy arc, when...
...when...
...when the knights have now left... graduated from the academy...
...and are...
...going to earn their... their higher titles as knights...,s:
...going to earn their... their higher titles as knights...
...they hear of a rumor...
...of an isolated castle...
...where a witch... a witch resides.
But they cannot... and...
...and the witch's influence is now corrupting...
...the area around it, and they're now...
...they're now requested to go, you know...
...like, investigate.
And then, of course, they get to the castle...
...and then, from the shadows, you hear the clunk, clunk of...
...of the... the armor.
And then, you hear... you hear...
...a familiar sword being drawn. And you're just like...
'No, it can't be!'
And then, you see the... now-corrupted Senpai...
...walk out of the shadow protecting...
...Nurse Juliet. And you're just like, 'No!'
'Senpai! It can't be you!'
And then, battle ensues. Boss music.
And then, boss fight happens...
...and then before you land the final strike...
...you just can't get yourself to do it.
And then Nurse Juliet comes running, like, 'No!'
'She means no harm!'
...my delusions speaking.
And then you learn their backstory.
Please continue!
And then now their new task is to find a way to lay our dear Senpai to rest.
A way to break...
Not really a curse, I guess, but to like...
...undo the spell that prevents her from rest.
And you're just like, "Do we really have to do this?"
And it's like a... if it was like a visual novel, that's where like the path...
...to the story changes. It's like...
...you decide to find a way to let her rest forever, or like...
...no, you let them go and then try to find a different way to fix the problem of the area.
Like a ReCo-themed TTRPG? That sounds fun.
I mean, I think with the current like chapters and stuff, the reason why it's structured that way...
...was because, because they structured it that way in Chapter 1, you know...
...now they have to make sure we do everything for every member, right?
The recollection and the dungeons.
So there can't be that much variations to the structure.
I think like, if there's anything ever beyond what's planned...
...it's doable maybe, but...
...like right now, the current structure-wise, it's probably not as flexible.
Yeah, but I think like once we go through all the members...
...I'm sure they'll have more wiggle room if they want to do something different.
Because I did make suggestions on like, you know, possible other ways to implement...
...stuff using Minecraft and whatnot.
Like whenever I'm eating food and stuff, I just... because my recommended is all just...
...so random. Sometimes I run into these like...
...you know those like custom mods with like... surviving 100 days...
...in a zombie apocalypse in Minecraft, or stuff like that, you know?
Where they only have to do like...
...a couple of days' worth of content in Minecraft.
And then the servers will be like down until we can gather again, I guess.
Did NefoLabo fall?
Oh, good thing we sold!
Phew, good thing we sold everything.
Like, and then like, do something like that...
...but structure it similar to a TTRPG...
...where like, like it's not like 100% mandatory...
...or like you can just have, you know, talents who want to participate.
They can like... we can do like a pre-event week...
...where each like member can take time to...
...like create their own like character.
...that they can, you know, RP as...
...as if it was like a TTRPG. I thought that would have been pretty fun.
Like that way, like if there's someone who can't make the event and stuff...
...like they just don't have to make the character and stuff...
...and there's like, no, no pressure.
Yeah, it's kind of like mixing... I need another axe.
Let's go buy another axe next time we go sell.
It's like mixing kind of like the TTRPG, D&D structure with Minecraft, you know?
And then like, we can even have like the character...
...skins that we can create.
I think that would be more...
...what should I say?
...immersive.
Anyways, those, those are some ideas I tossed...
...to them, so...
...we'll see!
Like, I think it, it would seem so fun because I really enjoyed Mythbreakers, and like...
...hearing the characters and seeing all the fan creations...
...and like the fan art and everything.
Because like at the end of the day, I think like...
...what's like our EN Reco characters, too, like...
...it, it looks like us, us, but that's just the way it's structured, but...
...like TTRPG and coming up with the characters, and creating also like side content...
...where people can also feel like really...
Internet? I think it's fine.
Sorry, my internet dropped for a second.
But yeah, don't you think that seems really fun?
I think it, it sounds fun even from like a participant's point of view, too.
But at the same time, I just really like coming up with...
...random characters and stories.
Didn't hear you? Oh...
...I just meant to say, like, if we do it that way, I think it's...
...kind of fun. It sounds fun to me.
Why not make a TTRPG instead of Minecraft? 'Cause...
...people want visual content...
...instead of just TTRPG sometimes.
I'll be honest with you, my attention span sometimes does not last an entire...
...TTRPG session.
And I need something like actually, that I'm actively doing,
like Minecraft and stuff.
It's just like a more interactive way, I think,
instead of just imagining what's happening,
like if we can incorporate game elements.
Yeah.
'Cause like, not everyone is really into...
...just listening to a TTRPG session,
although there's a lot of people who enjoy it.
You know, there's someone who likes to watch action happen on the screen,
the... the young'uns who need visual...
...dopamine.
So it's like taking like the character creation
and like some of the settings...
...creation part of like TTRPG,
and incorporating something that's more active,
like Minecraft, mods, and stuff.
But like, it also has to be like the fun members have... like the participants have, right? Like not everyone is...
...good to always sit around and only talk for like, four hours.
Some people, to have fun, need active stuff to do.
Aka, me.
Like, what I'm realizing more and more these days is like, viewers having fun is one thing, but like if I don't have fun when I'm...
...like, producing... Ah! My axe! Okay, we have to go to town.
Like, if I don't have fun, then like, I don't want to.
Like, if I'm not having fun, I think it translates to whatever output I have.
It's something that I've just realized over the years.
Just like, enthusiasm and stuff is like... what should I say?
It's... it gets pretty obvious at a certain point where you're just like,
'Hey, I think this content creator is really enjoying, you know, what they're doing and stuff.'
And then sometimes it's like, oh, they're doing things out of obligation.
これ売って、これ売って、あとは...
Sell this, sell this, and then...
これどこで売るんだ？アルケミストか。
Where do I sell this? At the alchemist?
Oh! Anya!
Would you like some carrots?
I harvested some fresh carrots. I shall put it up in the shop.
Oh, yes, please! Yes, yes, yes! Carrots!
I don't know how carrot... how much carrots go for.
I don't know how much carrots go for.
Yeah, me too, I don't know.
I'll just put it at 15 for... They're pretty easy.
I'll just put them at 15... They're pretty easy.
All right, enjoy! I'll put up more later.
Thank you! Heck yeah!
That's why they say enthusiasm is contagious. So...
ハロー、イナ！あ、どうも！
Hello, Ina! Ah, hello!
Farmer is best!
先輩もあれやってるんですか？
Are you doing that too, Senpai?
え、スイカ？はい。
Huh, watermelons? Yes.
Yes, our watermelon.
みんな...
Everyone...
みんなスイカ。
Everyone is doing watermelons.
いや、多分... 多分これ...
Yeah, probably... probably this...
明日からできないんですよ。できないよ絶対に！
We won't be able to do it tomorrow. We absolutely won't!
今だよ今！やる！
It's now or never! I'm doing it!
どこ？
Where?
今日だってば！今、今日さ！本当に！今日。
I'm telling you, it's today! Right now, today! Really! Today.
今日！Today.
Today! Today.
これ売ってる？
Do I sell this?
Nice, nice.
Everyone understands.
あ、わため先輩！
Ah, Watame-senpai!
やっほー！
Yahoo!
先輩もあれやってるんですか？
Are you doing that too, Senpai?
スイカ？はい。
Watermelons? Yes.
やってないよ。
I'm not doing it.
遊んでる。
I'm just playing around.
あー！それもいいですね。
Ah! That's nice too.
やってます。
I'm doing it.
お、頑張ってんだ。頑張れー！
Oh, you're working hard. Keep it up!
はい、頑張ります！
Yes, I will work hard!
え、可愛い。可愛い！
Wow, so cute! Cute!
可愛い。もらった、これ。
Cute. I got this.
バウバウ？
Bao bao?
バウバウ！
Bao bao!
バウバウ、可愛い。
Bao bao, cute.
タコだちも可愛い。
The Takodachis are also cute.
タコだち。
Takodachis.
可愛い。
Cute.
スイカ頑張ってね。
Good luck with the watermelons.
はい、頑張ります。
Yes, I will!
うん！ファイトー！
Yeah! Fight!
She got them both. No wonder they haven't been coming around.
She has them.
She has them to help out.
She has them hostage. Oh no.
ノエルちゃん！はい！
Noel-chan! Yes!
途中までだけど、さっき一緒に行ったあれ、なんだっけ？ダンジョンの分け前を...
It was only halfway, but the share of the dungeon we went to together earlier...
お腹空いた。
I'm hungry.
お腹...
Hungry...
あ、私も... あ、食うの忘れたかも。
Ah, I also... Ah, I might have forgotten to eat, too.
うなたんに触れないで！うなたんのことそっとしておいて！
Don't touch Unatan! Leave Unatan alone!
How much are cookies?
おーりーごめんよー。オーケー。
Ollie, sorry! Okay.
500.
あと、あれだ、ラミィ、なんか、なんかあったら次おこぼれくれ。な、おこぼれ。
Also, Lamy, if there's anything, give me the leftovers next time. Okay? Leftovers.
おこぼれ？オッケー、おこぼれ。
Leftovers? Okay, leftovers.
めんどい...
Troublesome...
Oh, I'm getting hungry.
I guess it's been quite a long time since I did eat.
あはは、もう落ちてる！
Ahaha, she already fell!
わろた。落ちてて草。
Lmao. She fell, lol.
Talking does make me hungry.
すいちゃん、落ちてて草。
Suichan fell, lol.
そうだよね、すいちゃん。そりゃそうなりますわ。
That's right, Suichan. Of course that would happen.
ごめん、構ってやれなくて。
Sorry I couldn't pay attention to you.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
でも、今日のブートキャンプ楽しかったよ。
But today's bootcamp was fun!
ずっとゲームばっかりしてたからさ、なんか久しぶりに体動かして楽しかったわ。
I've been playing games all the time, so it was fun to move my body after a long time.
体動かす...
Moving your body...
クッキー売り暮らし！なんかクッキー売ってるじゃん！
Living by selling cookies! She's selling cookies!
Ah...
My connection's been spotty today.
Da, da, da, da...
...x.
スバル先輩が...
Subaru-senpai...
いやいやいや、遊んでて、遊ぼうと思って、すいちゃんと遊ぼうと思ってさ。
No, no, no, we were playing, I wanted to play, I wanted to play with Suichan.
みんな、結構やってる。
Everyone, they're doing it quite a bit.
お、やべ、違う、違う、違う...
Oh, crap, no, no, no...
I need to deposit my money just in case.
わー！
Wah!
One step closer to our dream.
No, I can't buy any more stonks today. I already hit my limit.
Let's see, let's see, let's see...
I'm so hungry.
Yeah, I'll harvest one round, and then... I'll see what I can eat.
Or maybe I can order something, who knows.
There's something... I think they have some specials going on at Macca's. Maybe I'll order that.
It's like... the Teriyaki Burger, but then it's like... Hokkaido Jaga-imo... something.
It's like... the Teriyaki Burger, but then it's like... Hokkaido potato... something.
I mean, there's stuff that's open like 24/7, so... I don't also need to...
...search something real quick, before it's too late.
Just got to make sure I'm not missing any pings.
Yeah, maybe I should order.
I can't tell you what I ordered, though. Kakaka...
Maybe I'll order from the convenience store.
Do the unforgivable Uber Eats from the convenience store?
Okay, we have like 40 minutes.
I shouldn't eat something too heavy.
Cuz I probably need to go to sleep relatively soon.
Does that mean IRyS is too far gone? Don't worry, she's not alone.
She's not alone.
これにしようかな。
Maybe I'll go with this one.
Are beacons allowed? I think...
so, cuz Nether...
star is technically gettable.
No, the thing is, I don't want efficiency because that will mess up the timing of the harvest.
Like, it would be harvesting way too fast.
Like, I would have to make an even bigger...
farm. It's too much work right now.
Fortune? But like, Fortune is not really needed
because it is kind of offset with the bees, that's the whole point.
Why would you put Unbreaking? That means that it kind of gives less...
I don't know...
Enchanting is not allowed in the first place, so like...
why only allow Unbreaking, you know?
I don't really need Haste Bee, I never felt the need for it. If anything, give me a better...
That reminds me, I should check the bees.
Like the higher level yield and money.
Like, I know you guys are questioning, "Why not this system? Why not this system?" but like, there's a reason.
And they're leaving it that way.
Seeing if there is any other...
regen tools.
There's speed 2...
It's not like they didn't think of all the balancing and everything to make this custom server.
I'll breed some of the...
Yeah, they're balancing it every day, too.
Like, there's a reason some of the system is blocked because they...
...they deemed that it was not balanced or it won't work.
You know?
I should sell the bees...
...that are like, rare and normal.
Yeah, just... just step back and enjoy.
We're not asking them to change the system.
It's just fun.
It's just how... how things are on... on Nene-mama and Ina's channel.
Of course, I go and try to...
...be efficient in some places...
...but sometimes being the most efficient is not fun.
It's all about fun!
If I'm not having fun, then there's no point of me doing it.
You know?
That's always been my motto.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's have fun!
Nyeh, nyeh, nyeh...
Like, the current balance of the melons growing...
...and me harvesting them, I think it's like... it's great.
It's just the right speed.
You know?
We're always asked...
...in our everyday lives to be...
...as efficient and...
...you know, hardworking as possible, but, you know...
...let's just...
...take a step back and relax.
Some days, it's okay to be a potato.
It's okay to be not efficient.
I must backseat Minecraft farming or I'll die.
I hope you have 911 on speed dial.
I think you're watching the wrong stream.
I mean, because like, originally, my plan...
...for this entire five days...
...was to see how much money I can make from just fishing.
But then, the other systems were kind of fun, so I like, changed tracks, you know?
Who knew mining... or breaking watermelons would be this fun?
Ah, capitalism.
Don't quote me on that.
Cos someone's going to make a meme with my image...
...and the caption just says: "Ah, capitalism."
Oh! 30 minutes?
We must hurry before the watermelons are nerfed!
Make haste! Make haste!
We got a whole family to feed!
18 million takos...
...turned to coin.
Ah...
素晴らしい。
Wonderful.
'You won't sell us for coin, right, Ina?'
Nice weather today.
Actually, it was kind of good weather today...
...because there was the typhoon, right? And there was the rain.
And then like...
It was...
...kind of like, not sunny...
...kind of cloudy, but not too hot or cold outside today.
It was a little humid, but it was nothing like really really bad.
From a high place.
12 million.
Ah!
That was quick.
Is it because the convenience store is closed?
Yeah, petrol.
You'll never know.
Ah, my slices!
Okay.
Money.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Oh, did I miss something?
Archaeological map featuring our, uh... utility shop.
まあ、is okayです。
Well, it's okay.
まあ、スイカがもっと大事。
Well, watermelon is more important.
スイカ、スイカ、スイカ、スイカ！
Watermelon, watermelon, watermelon, watermelon!
Wait... sorry! スイカ、スイカ...
Wait... sorry! Watermelon, watermelon...
Ina koko, Ina スイカ、Ina Ina スイカ？
Ina here, Ina watermelon, Ina Ina watermelon?
お腹スイカ...
My stomach is watermelon...
Inaお腹スイカ...
Ina is hungry...
Ina食べる、スイカ。
Ina eats watermelon.
Will I dream of suika later? Maybe.
Will I dream of watermelon later? Maybe.
I'll let you guys know if I dream of watermelon.
Oh, I forgot I had Elytra on!
Now I can move more speed.
Now I can move with more speed.
Oh, let's check the bees.
Oh, it's so full.
I like the super rare one with both level two.
Like, farm money and...
Oh, regen two and water breathe.
I don't know if she needs...
Need to get a new box.
Rarely though... Maybe I can sell the bee.
Oh, I don't know if people even like check to buy though.
There are some ones that stack, so that's good.
Next time we go sell our watermelon,
we can... maybe sell that regen two bee.
Maybe... maybe there's going to be a water dungeon that they need the water breathing for, you know, you never know.
But we gotta make sure we focus on the... the watermelon currently,
because I feel like they're definitely going to nerf watermelon.
too strong right now.
And now... 20 minutes left.
Cookie needs nerf, too?
But cookie needs like a... cookie needs more stuff, which is why I didn't really want to do cookie.
Like, it takes a bit of time to sell the... cocoa too, so...
Cookies aren't... compatible with capitalism.
What is it compatible with? I don't know if I want the answer to that.
Takorism.
Cookies as a currency...
...this place can finally... heal?
Ah, 13 mil!
Ah, I don't know if we can make 5 mil just from...
...if this gets nerfed, though... in one day.
Selling ain't it? You might be right.
Cuz you get so much more from just harvesting. Ah, I don't know...
You might be right.
It might just be a spam...
...cuz like, you'll still be able to sell afterwards.
It's just they might even nerf like... the percentages...
...of the bonus for farmers. I feel like that might be the case.
It's not about winning, it's about getting to 13 million...
...uh, 180,000... yeah, 81,118.
That's... That's our goal! It's not about winning.
It's about sending a message.
Ah, I'm running out of space. Okay, keep farming, keep farming.
What message are we sending? Ichihachi Takodachi.
Each... each, tuck, each.
We're already number one in Holo EN category?
That's right.
It's okay, I'm sure we'll figure out a way.
Maybe tomorrow stonks will also yield... maybe 1 million or so. That would be great.
Tomorrow is the last day.
Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, dot...
I think they must've opened the gates to like the nearest jungle biome.
They... they must have, on purpose.
I broke a plant!
*Gasp* Oh...
Wait... right here.
No, the efficiency is lost.
The threat... the threat Miko-chi was getting yesterday.
Yeah, others have... others have suika too.
I think there are some farmers, like... like Watame-senpai, I think she's just enjoying it now.
She did join in on the suika.
Which I think is also a good way to enjoy the server.
I thought I was going to enjoy until I came up with a new goal.
18 million.
Um, I tried the... the easy puzzle one by myself. I didn't realize there was going to be a fight at the end.
So I... I went in not prepared, and then...
...and then, watermelon. Yeah.
Watermelon.
Oh, I'm out of space.
Why can't I hold all these watermelons?
*Yawn*
I didn't realize, with the faster growth rates too...
...it's just... it's so relaxing, doing something that requires no thinking...
...at the end of the day, too.
Hmm... I love repetitive tasks without a thought...
...required.
This world requires too much thought.
No thoughts, just watermelon.
10 minutes.
Do I have one to make more chests?
I mean, at the end of the day, if it seems like we can't get to...
...18 million, then we can lower it...
...to one digit lower, you know? That can always be arranged.
We can just buy enough coins...
...to lower our... our earnings.
Or we go big, and then bet everything as big coins.
Who knows?
Maybe we'll hit that diamond mine.
But that's... that's only if it feels like 18 million...
...goal is not reachable tomorrow.
Cuz we don't know what the balance patch is gonna be.
Cuz getting the exact digits down, I think is gonna be pretty difficult.
But I think like... I could like just lower it enough and then like...
...cuz like I can... I can just like dig uh dirt and only get like one gold, right? So...
...maybe it is doable.
Like, like sell it and/or like get rid of money more than usual and then earn up one by one.
Four more minutes. Okay. Can I do it?
Or I can ask help from Anya to buy some specific amount of...
...money's worth of something.
Should I just sell today? I think I should...
Do I sell or...
I don't have enough space.
Oh, I guess I have a couple more.
Sell today? Okay.
I need to at least leave five for the... melon seeds.
Leave the stuff I don't need.
Alright, no need for egg anymore.
Okay, six minutes, that's plenty of time.
Okay, we shall free them into the wild tomorrow.
グレしか出ない！
これ、これ。
やばい。ちょっと一緒に、一緒に動いてくれ。
Only gray is coming out!
This one, this one.
No way. Come on, move with me, move with me.
グレしか出ない！
Only gray is coming out!
結構、結構ありだと思うんだけどな。
I think it's pretty good, though.
Now, forget about the bees.
がんばろう！
Let's do our best!
３千本いくぞ！
Let's go for 3000!
Or maybe I should just leave all the boxes out. Probably easier.
やばい、４分だ！
Oh no, 4 minutes left!
ちょっと待って。
急げ！急げ！
Wait a minute.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
よいしょ...
Heave-ho...
マッカンにおち疲れでやんす...
I'm exhausted from Maccan's... de yansu.
あっという間だ。スイカ今日いっぱい稼げた？
That was fast. Did you make a lot of money from watermelons today?
稼げたはず！
I should have!
稼げたか？
Did you?
へへ。
Hehe.
あ...
Ah...
Okay.
スイカ、スイカ、スイカ〜
Watermelon, watermelon, watermelon~
...が結構、一回で割と100万くらい行けるから、頑張れば。
...because you can pretty much get 1 million in one go if you work hard.
うん、うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
その手に持っているのは...
What you have in your hand...
タコです。
is a tako.
スイカ、スイカ、スイカ〜
Watermelon, watermelon, watermelon~
みんなスイカ人。やばい。
Everyone is a watermelon person. Oh dear.
シナジー指数マックスだったぞ。
My synergy status was at max.
スイカ、スイカ、スイカ...
Watermelon, watermelon, watermelon...
...のさんによると、金融後も5％...
...according to Nozomi-san, even after financial...
ただ、プラスの方は雑魚だから、その...
But the plus side is weak, so...
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
あ、バレてる。
Ah, I'm busted.
Ah, I can't open that.
いっぱい置いちゃっていけないね。一個ずつじゃないと。
We shouldn't place too many. We have to do them one by one.
Okay, it's all... It's all sold. Okay.
The farmers are panic-selling now. They know, they know. The nerf is coming.
Okay, yay! I'll deposit a little more.
メル、メル、メル...
Mel, mel, mel...
Three minutes. That's like... one round of suika. Let's go!
行け！行け！着いた！
Go! Go! I landed!
Do not forget the Farmer's Day. June...
June 4th, 2026.
The Day of the Suika.
The day of the suika.
行け！行け！
Go! Go!
The day the watermelon rose.
行け、行け、行け、行け！
Go, go, go, go!
あ！あ！
Ah! Ah!
Don't panic, don't panic. You have plenty of time. Okay.
All right. I think I shall get off for today. For now.
Thank you very much everyone...
Sorry, I mispressed!
So, thank you very much for coming to watch the stream today.
Um, hope you guys have a wonderful rest of your morning, afternoon, evening.
I'll try to be on time tomorrow, but not 100% sure, so...
will let you guys know. Tomorrow is our last day. Hopefully, we make it to our desired amount of money.
I pray. It won't be too bad.
Anyways, thank you! Until next time, take care! Bye-bye!
イェーイ、わー！
Yay, wah!