(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": false,
"max_retries_exceeded": true,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
わー〜
Wah~
Good morning, afternoon, evening...
It is Tako Time. What is this?
あ...
Oh...
アリーナで... バトルダンジョン...
Arena... Battle dungeon...
Oh, daily quests. Right.
はぁ...
Oh...
あれ？
Huh?
It seems I'm out of bees.
I can fix that.
I'm just going to put a whole bunch of bees...
...in here.
It cannot be... Sorry about the beep today.
So many!
Oh, there're a few in there too.
な、な、な...
Na, na, na...
Oh, I should've put like Shulkers or something so they can... they can figure it out themselves.
Oh, more bees.
I can sell some of the bees.
た、た、た...
Ta, ta, ta...
Yeah, there's no purple, okay, so...
Ah, it doesn't matter.
This isn't our number one source of money, anyway.
Okay, okay, okay, it's fine, it's fine.
Because...
Although,
we may have...
...gotten a slight nerf...
...to the money we earn by harvesting.
I think 18 million...
...is still within the grasp.
A slight nerf, I should say.
But with the amount we earned yesterday,
I feel like...
...we can earn a fraction of that today.
It won't be a prob...
But we got to be careful,
because...
...we don't have any...
...limits to stonks today,
which means I have to zero out...
...and sell...
...the stonks.
Cause they're gonna...
...sell automatically if I forget about them,
and it's gonna mess up our plan.
So at the first sighting of an increase,
we shall sell the remaining stonks,
and just forget about it.
Oh, yeah, we have five more extra...
...what-cha-ma-call-it...
...points today, which means...
...that if I finish getting the... wait,
but then I'll get money from doing the extra stuff.
That can't do.
Okay, I'll gather the rest and go sell.
I will make sure I don't get sidetracked from my goal.
Why not sell it at the lowest right now and sell later?
Because...
...I'm not too fond of uncertainties.
Three raids and only plus?
Is that what they said?
But the unknown is scary.
I mean, they did say the server's gonna be open a little bit after midnight,
so if I'm not feeling completely dead,
maybe we can do like a mini-game or something.
But high chance I'm gonna be dead because I went outside today,
and every time I go outside it means...
...I feel dead!
My stamina's running a little low today.
Yeah. I mean, I think I did my best,
participating in the event.
I had fun.
I got good food today.
I hung out with Biboo all day.
Biboonium has been recharged!
I did remember to headpat her.
Of course I won't forget. It's like the first thing I do when I meet her.
I have to say, we definitely aren't getting as much money as before, I feel.
But a couple of rounds and I think...
...we probably will.
I mean...
I mean, we're already like more than halfway to 1 million, so...
...it's not too bad. Had a good, good head start yesterday.
That feels like more than 25%.
That's what it is, though, but like...
percentages always feel weird because it's percentages, it's chance.
Chance has always been wonky. Sometimes, because...
...it just means it's not 100% of the time if it's not 100% of the times, you know?
Ina of the Mountain's cool today: "If it's not 100%, it's not 100% of the time."
My bees are equipped, always.
I know they're equipped because I'm too lazy to change them.
やまのいな〜
Yama no Ina~
Speaking of which...
I was recently craving some really peppery wings.
And I remembered the wings I had when I went to Nagoya once.
What was it? Sekai no Yamachan.
I talked about it before, I think, but I really like their peppery wings. It's so yummy.
Ah, my bag is full.
世界の山ちゃん美味しいよね。
Sekai no Yamachan is tasty, isn't it?
なんか最近食べたくなって...
Like, I've been craving them lately...
...and I opened Uber...
and I thought, "Wait, isn't there a Sekai no Yamachan nearby?"
...but when I looked at the time, it was morning...
朝、４時くらい。
Around 4 AM.
あ、そっか。
Ah, right.
4 AM in the morning.
I wanted to eat the wings out of nowhere.
So I was like, "Oh, is there like a Sekai no Yamachan nearby?" So I opened Uber.
And there was not, and I was like, "Is there none near me that deliver?"
And then I checked the time, and it was like 4:00 AM...
...in the morning! I was like, "Oh, of course they're not open."
But like, like if you just eat the wings, it's like really...
...because I usually order it with like extra pepper sauce, right?
So if I eat, eat the wings by themselves, it's really salty, but then...
...I heat up...
...some rice. Fresh, hot rice.
And then I take a bite of the wings with the rice, and oh...
...perfection.
Truly. Truly.
Yamachan's wings are... eh?
いや、山ちゃん辛いぞ。
No, "Yamachan is spicy"...
いなは言えないんですよ。
...is something Ina can't say.
They're like, "Sekai no Yamachan is really spicy." I was like, "Eh?"
え、辛くないんだわ。
Eh? They're not spicy.
サンタ？
Santa?
ほうほうほう
Ho, ho, ho!
サンタ！久しぶり！
Santa! It's been a while!
久しぶり！見て！
Long time no see! Look!
あっ！
Ah!
あー！タコダチ！
Ah! Takodachi!
ここにも飾っておくよ
I'll display one here too!
ありがとう、サンタ！
Thank you, Santa!
サンタ！
Santa!
ほうほうほう
Ho, ho, ho!
タコダチ...
Takodachi...
Why are you standing up though? Aren't you... aren't... aren't you an item? Aren't you supposed to be lying down?
Well, I'm not against it.
なんか、ししろんが「アイテム交換しないように、開けるの禁止です」と言ったとき、
You know, when Shishiron said, "To prevent item trading, opening them is prohibited,"
あ、サンタのプレゼントももらえないと思ったんですけど。
I thought, "Ah, I won't be able to get presents from Santa anymore."
そうですね、サンタって最初から、
But then, Santa from the start...
私が見てないところにプレゼントを置いていくのがサンタの仕事。
leaving presents where I'm not looking is Santa's job.
You know, when... when Shishiron said you're not supposed to give free items to people,
I was like, "Oh, Santa can't give me another present anymore?"
But then I realized, it is actually Santa's job to give presents when I'm not looking.
Ho, ho, ho!
Today is the last day of this event.
いや、このタコダチ、ホロ鯖にもあったらいいな。
Man, I wish this Takodachi was on the Holo Server too.
欲しい。
I want it.
でもホロ鯖は、なんかカスタムのアイテムあんまりないから...
But the Holo Server doesn't really have custom items, so...
いや、でもメンバーのマスコットくらいは大丈夫...大丈夫...大丈夫じゃないですか？運営さん？
No, but at least the members' mascots should be okay... right, managers?
I want the mascots in the Holo Server. But then, Holo Server doesn't have that many custom items, but then it's the members' mascots, so you know...
You know?
Maybe they can make an exception?
いや、でも今考えたら、なんかメンバーの頭とかあったっけ？ホロ鯖に。
But thinking about it now, did we have members' heads on the Holo Server?
We do have the heads of the members and stuff, right? In the Holo Server.
あった気がする。
I feel like we had them.
あ、でも、なんかマスコットは...まあ、作るために、お金かかるかもね。
Ah, but maybe mascots... well, to make them, it might cost money.
いや、でもなんか、持って帰ったらいいなと。
But, still, it'd be nice to take them home.
It would be nice to carry it back, but of course it takes the golden coins to create these assets.
been dirt.
I don't know if they're still better though. But,
watermelon.
I can't stop now.
It's like, it's like too late to stop.
I've committed.
や、でももうすぐいけるじゃん？
But we can get there soon, right?
We're already at 1.3 mil.
I believe, I believe...
You know, we thought 18 million wasn't doable, so we're aiming for 1.8.
But it's going to work.
So, my goal currently is to have...
1-8-1-8-1-8-1-8 yen...
at the very end.
Yeah...
arigatai English.
thankful for the English.
So, I went to eat with Bibo today.
Usually, I don't think I go out like...
one-on-one with her that often.
So, we usually have at least like one member who is very...
who is more...
Japanese pera pera, you know.
fluent in Japanese, you know.
Oh no!
So whenever we order,
we would stare at them with glittering eyes,
and be like,
I want this.
And we would have an ordering person.
But this time, it was just me and Bibo,
so of course, I was that role,
except I can't read.
So, as...
as...
naturally as...
naturally as possible,
I point to the menu and I go, "kore".
I point to the menu and I go, "this".
hitotsu.
One.
18？ はい、すみません...
18? Yes, sorry...
そんなそんな甘い考えは無理でした。
Such, such naive thinking was impossible.
えーっと...
Let's see...
あっ、お金もない... え、インベントリ空きが... あっ...
Ah, no money... eh, the inventory space is... ah...
あほ？
Idiot?
あほ。
Idiot.
And then I point to the next thing,
and go, "kore".
and go, "this".
うーん、ビーツ？
Hmm, beetroot?
あ、ほんまや！
Ah, you're right!
これ買おう！
Let's buy this!
うわーー！何これ？
Whoa! What is this?
回転...？
Spinning...?
絹豆腐こ先輩がやってたウィザーのあれか...
Is this the Wither thing that Kinudofuko-senpai was doing?
なるほど、なるほど、なるほど！
I see, I see, I see!
Tut, tut, tut...
Hey.
We're getting so close.
うーん、ふんふんふん
Hmm, hmm, hmm...
Mikoも始まるよ！
Miko's starting, too!
え、やばしんど。
Whoa, that's crazy.
Why not leave the box? I have trust issues.
Oh, we already got three boxes, okay.
イイナ！
Ina!
はい！
Yes!
おお、スイカですか？スイカ。
Oh, watermelons? Watermelons.
そうだよ、スイカだよ。スイカいっぱいだ。
Yeah, watermelons. Lots of watermelons!
イイナは何売ってんの？
What is Ina selling?
スイカです！
Watermelons!
え、でもイイナもファーマー？
Wait, but Ina is also a farmer?
はい！
Yes!
イイナ！ファーマー、最後まで頑張ろうね。
Ina! Let's do our best as farmers until the end.
頑張りましょう！
Let's do our best!
うん、頑張ろう。
Yeah, let's do our best.
おいっす。
Bye-bye.
マネー！マネー！金取り！金取り！本当金。
Money! Money! Taking the money! Taking the money! Real money.
We're almost there. Wait.
俺の分は忘れないで、はい。
Don't forget my share, okay?
We're so close.
I forgot... I forgot what I was gonna say.
What was it? Why did I lose track?
昨日...昨日何だっけ？
Yesterday... what was yesterday?
昨日...
Yesterday...
村給料。
Village salary.
あ、みんな、頑張って。
Ah, everyone, do your best.
あ、ラミィ！ししろんはいらないよって。
Oh, Lamy! Tell Shishiron we don't need it.
ね、一旦全部集めたって。
Hey, they said we should gather everything first.
あれ、どれかな？
Which one is it?
え？忘れてたわ。
Eh? I forgot.
Oh wait, we need another... Hold on, we'll deposit this.
We're so close.
We need two axes.
Oh, we have extra job points.
I do need three to use the brush, right?
Job Skill.
Alchemist.
ATM borrow cap?
ネガティブに行けるんだ！ You can, you can go into the negatives!
You can go into the negatives! You can, you can go into the negatives!
You can borrow money.
But you don't get much from alchemy either, no?
Oh wait, we have points left.
No, there's only two points left. We only got five extra points.
The levels down here don't mean anything.
Oh five, but you don't really get anything.
Alchemy quality stage 1... I guess I can go five. That's fine, okay.
I don't need HP for the raid, I've never went down below half.
ダブに賭けるしかねえ！
We have no choice but to bet on the double-up!
Yes.
たぶん無い。
Probably not.
And his... gaze has reached me.
Oh, I wonder if someone bought my regen bee.
Ah! I think they did!
Oh.
But I need food. I'll get some carrots.
The egg? I know, I've...
Oh, that's what I was gonna talk about!
Subaru-senpai promised me she wouldn't sell the egg.
And then she did.
Was...
そうそうそう、昨日。あれを見て、スバル先輩にDMを送ったんですよ。
That's right, yesterday. I saw that and sent Subaru-senpai a DM.
「先輩、先輩」
"Senpai, Senpai."
「売らないと言ったよね？ ね？」って。
"You said you wouldn't sell it, didn't you? Right?"
「約束しましたよね？」って。
"We made a promise, didn't we?"
「次回の...」
"I'm looking forward..."
「大空警察...」
"...to the next..."
「楽しみにしてますよ」って。
"...Oozora Police session!"
嘘をつく警察って...
A police officer who tells lies...
...いる？
...is that a thing?
So basically I saw that she sold the egg, and I was like, "Subaru-senpai..."
"You told me you weren't gonna sell it."
"You promised."
And then I was like, "I'm looking forward to the next Oozora Police episode!"
いや、でもさ、誰も...
But you know, if no one...
...買わないと、多分ね、スバル先輩が、
...buys it, Subaru-senpai will probably be like...
「いや、でも、誰も買ってないから...」
"Well, since nobody bought it..."
「売ってない！」って...
"...it didn't sell!"
...言うかも。
...she might say that.
If no one buys it, her defense would be like, "But no one bought it, so it technically didn't sell!"
Oh...
いや、でも、なんかアイデアがでました。
But somehow, I got an idea.
いや、でも名前書いてあるからね。
But wait, the name is written on it, right?
でも、イナがたまご売ったら、イナの名前書いてあるから、いいかも。
But if Ina sells the egg, Ina's name is on it, so that might be good.
あれは...
That one is...
偽物！
...fake!
こっちが本物だ！って。
'This one is the real one!' like that.
This says who is selling it.
So if I put up an egg there...
it has my name on it.
So like, 'That egg is fake!'
Egg war? Haha.
Oh, that was a good one.
あ、ここか。Oh, I forgot where it was.
Ah, here it is. Oh, I forgot where it was.
どこだっけ？トーチがここでした。
Where was it? The torch was here.
Quick, before it grows. Ah!
スイカ...
Watermelon...
ラグ？
Lag?
かな？
I wonder?
スイカ！
Watermelon!
来い！
Come!
よし。
Alright.
ラグ...
Lag...
Yeah, the other day... Or was it yesterday?
We went to eat some sushi.
We were talking about anime we were watching...
...and like, our favorite, like, fantasy animes and stuff.
And then my brain was lagging so badly.
I think she said something like...
...'Oh, I haven't been watching that many animes lately,'
'...but I watched...' or 'she is watching Witch Hat Atelier'.
And she watched Frieren...
...and DunMeshi.
And then, my brain lagged so much...
...so I was like... Right after she said that...
...I was like, 'Have you watched DunMeshi?'
And then she didn't reply, so I was like, 'Delicious in Dungeon?'
And she had this 'What is she saying?' kind of expression on her face.
And I was like, 'Wait, you don't know?' I thought... I thought... I thought maybe she didn't know the...
...maybe she knew the English title?
And then she was just like...
You know, I, I just said...
I just said the three anime that I watched.
Which are, actually...
Free! and DanMachi. I was like...
Oh.
Sorry.
Brain lag.
Yeah.
Did you have flashbacks to when IRyS told her
she just realized she had green in her name?
And does IRyS know that CC's Twitter handle
is actually Cecilia_ImGreen, not Im_Green?
She's green!
I think I only noticed because I was trying to find her...
Twitter for something. I typed her entire name
because that's usually what her handles are.
And it wouldn't pop up.
And I was like,
what's going on?
Sonically-charged shriek? Oh.
And then I checked
by going to her page and I was like, "Oh, it's ImGreen."
But it's fine.
It's fine.
I can laze around tomorrow.
Hopefully.
And then I will slowly roll over to Cali's place.
It's in the evening, so I can sleep in.
You know, I saw some comments saying,
"I didn't know Ina drank!"
or, "Can Ina hold her alcohol?"
Hmm.
Um...
Um, yeah?
Yeah?
I guess?
A little bit?
I don't know how, how I would be...
against CC though.
I know my place against the other girls.
But I don't know about CC.
But I don't really like...
having like drinking competitions or stuff like that.
I was never a fan of...
getting drunk-drunk, you know?
Or trying to beat someone to prove something.
Ah.
Yo, yo...
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm...
Mm, mm...
What country has my favorite drink? Japan. I love umeshu.
Hehe!
Mm, mm, mm...
What about sake? Sake for me really depends, like...
...what I'm eating.
Huaaah... Uuugh...
Wait, we're so close.
Hold on, hold on.
I think we must make our way to...
...sell and see.
To-to-to-to-to-to-to...
Oh no, spawn camp!
Not the Warden spawn camp!
Nooo!
To-to-to-to-to-to...
ATM.
Ah...
We're so close.
A little short.
Da-da-da-da-da...
Maybe I should have changed the color of my boxes.
I could have changed one of them...
Hehe.
Da-da-da-da-da...
Wait, I haven't even hunted a Warden in normal Minecraft.
Hehe.
Da-da-da-da...
Hmm-hmm...
Ah...
We're basically there.
Ta-da-da-da...
Phew...
アルケミストは今、どうなってるんですかね？おかゆ。
I wonder what's going on with Alchemists right now, Okayu?
アルケミストは初日の２倍だから、
Since Alchemist is twice of the first day,
初日の×４？ん？昨日、昨日から×２でもらえるようになった。
four times the first day? Huh? From yes... yesterday it became twice.
あー。
Ah.
結構稼げはするね。
They do earn a decent amount.
Huh.
I don't know what that means.
Haha.
I only know suika.
Ah, get pumped! Yeah, double-double! Double-double! Double-double!
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta...
Wait, I am hungry.
Hold on, let me deposit this so...
チキンフーズはそうだけど...
Chicken Foods is like that, but...
と思うんだけど、株は。株は儲からないと思うんだけど...
I think so too, but stocks... I don't think stocks are profitable...
We're so close, we're so close.
We're so close.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on. Let me go sell whatever stocks I have so I don't have to worry about it.
激安の電脳や。
That's a super cheap computer shop.
1人で回ってみる。
I'll try looking around by myself.
おりゃ！おりゃおりゃおりゃおりゃ！
Take this! Take this, take this, take this!
おりゃー！おりゃおりゃおりゃおりゃおりゃ！
Oraaa! Ora ora ora ora ora!
まじかこれ、やばいこれ！おりゃおりゃおりゃおりゃ！ハハハ！首が疲れてきた、これ。
Seriously?! This is bad! Ora ora ora ora! Hahaha! My neck is getting tired.
10万、10万、10万...
100k, 100k, 100k...
We have to match.
ビビにあのー、いっぱいあげる余裕はないと思ってるんだよな。
I don't think I can afford to give Bibi a lot.
10k. How do I get rid of money?
Gamble? But what if I win money?
That's a problem.
Hold on. Need calculator.
Okay, 1-8-1-9-8-9-5-3 minus 1-8-1-8-1-8-1-8.
Withdraw... 1-7-1-3-5.
The number... the number...
We have achieved... the number!
I have one way I could possibly get rid of 17,135 yen...
...is to enlist a little bit of help. A little bit of help.
None that are that good.
Or keep gaining until my... No, but then that's gonna add up everything, you know?
I need... I need someone to sell something for this amount.
Oh, "buy stuff until you're back under and then gain up a few"?
All right, how much was grass block again? 1 yen. Okay, okay, I think that's totally doable. That's so doable.
That's actually expensive.
Wait, hold on, let me make it more...
Let's make it... divisible by...
An easy number, like 20.
Need four more grass blocks.
Okay, okay, okay.
I already have two Takos. I have one on the farm and one in my hand.
それ信じたいな、そうじゃない。
I want to believe that, but that's not it.
The thing is, like...
50 yen.
Maybe we can make it 50 yen. Just need 10 more blocks.
Okay, okay, okay.
行くぞ、行くぞ、行くぞ！
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
カブが来る、カブタイム。
Turnips are coming, turnip time.
Yes, yes.
これぐらいなら痛くない。
This much won't hurt.
じゃあ30... 買っておこう。
Then, 30... let's buy them.
That's a lot of eggs!
All right, I can fly.
Wait, I need to see what...
...the egg is called.
なるほど、なるほど。
I see, I see.
あの、INAのたまごは
Um, Ina's egg is...
偽物
...a fake.
これが
This is...
本物
...the real deal...
まじガチ
...for real.
Okay, just one egg, maybe?
Wait, but then I don't want anyone to...
...to buy it, so it needs to be like really, really expensive.
Ah, not enough...
Oh wait, it does have...
Okay.
350?
But that never matters to me anyways.
Oh, minus 152...
ラーメン、めんどい。でもラーメン。
Ramen is a pain. But ramen.
足りない...
Not enough...
マジか？あ、本当だ。ししらーめんが増えている。
Seriously? Ah, you're right. Shishiramen is increasing.
ええと、今のうちにぽん酢を買っておこう。
Let's buy some ponzu while we still can.
Ah, thousand.
あ、頭も買っておきますか。
Oh, should I buy a head as well?
サンタ？
Santa?
サンタやばい！
Santa's crazy!
あ！SSRB！SSRB！
Oh! SSRB! SSRB!
え？え？
Eh? Eh?
出現、出現してる！
They spawned! They're spawning!
いや、これ...いつまで...
No, this... how long...
Wait, how much was it? 160... I don't think I wanna go click a thousand until 1260 something million.
クエストの、オッケー。
For the quest, okay.
行けない？美味くて。
Can't go? It's delicious.
Anything below 30 million is danger?
Do we have to stay here till 30 million?
いや、でもこのあと暇だから、これやってもいいかも。
Well, but I'm free after this, so maybe doing this is fine.
ま、イナも暇ですからね。何もできない。
Well, Ina is free too. Can't do anything else.
"It was about time I got a new mouse."
いや、そろそろ新しいマウス買おうかなと思ったので、全然...全然大丈夫ですよ。
Yeah, I was thinking of buying a new mouse soon anyway, so it's totally... totally fine.
Do you guys like the... the new cookie clicker?
Egg clicker.
No, no, there's no point unless I can do it manually, you know?
ええと、明日何食べようかな...
Let's see, what should I eat tomorrow...
死ぬな。
Don't die.
やっぱり明日、世界の山ちゃん食べようかな。
I think I'll eat Sekai no Yamachan tomorrow after all.
I didn't get to order it last time.
Last time?
Last time...
This time.
200万行けた。
I reached 2 million.
え、これ、これも全部やらなきゃだめか、これ。
Wait, do I have to do all of this, too?
意外と足りなくね？ 意外と足りなくね？
Isn't it surprisingly not enough? Isn't it surprisingly not enough?
うーん...
Hmm...
やば。
Oh my god.
A cool 1 million.
これはワープだもんね。
This is a warp, right?
アスレチックにも金がかかる？ じゃ、これさえも一回さ...
Parkour costs money too? Then even this, one more time...
I can't believe I'm doing this.
ほい、ほい、ほい、ほい。
Hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi.
Long click doesn't work, I tried.
いっかさー。
One more time...
あーと...
And...
もういいよね、これ。
This should be enough, right?
左下にあった。
It was in the bottom left.
There has to be the button guy.
There has to be the button.
保管庫の横... あ、これか。
Next to the storage... oh, is it this?
はいな〜
Hi there~
Hello!
何々？
What is it?
おお〜
Oh~
食べ物売ってないね
They aren't selling food, are they?
I look funny right now, just standing in front of...
...here for like 20 minutes.
動かん。
I can't move.
動かん。これ...
I can't move. This...
やらないと。
I have to do this.
すいちゃんが...
Sui-chan...
すいちゃんがくれたの、猫。
Sui-chan gave me this, a cat.
何々？
What is it?
昨日さ、すいちゃんがさ...
Yesterday, Sui-chan...
あの、これ渡しといてって。
...was like, "Please give this to her."
ああ、猫！
Oh, a cat!
そう、そう、そう、そう。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
これ。
This.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
すいちゃんがくれたの？
Sui-chan gave it to you?
ミニゲームやんない？
Wanna play a mini-game?
行かない？
Want to go?
あ、まじね。超面白い、ミニゲーム。
Oh, really. The mini-game is super fun.
何のミニゲーム？みんな何処行っちまったんだ？
What mini-game? Where did everyone go?
We squished really hard, it's eight.
行こう、みんなで行こう。あれ、人数多ければ多いほど、あ、5人までかな？マックス。
Let's go, let's all go. The more people the better, ah, up to 5 people? Max.
あ、そんな、マックスあるんだ。
Oh, really? There's a max limit?
マックスある。だから、5人までのがいいかも。
Yes, there's a max. So maybe up to 5 people is best.
確かに。え、でも今、えっと、ころね、みこ、るーな、ねねち、らみ？
True. But right now, let's see, Korone, Miko, Luna, Nenechi, Lamy?
あ、じゃ、5人じゃん。
Ah, then that's 5 people.
5人じゃん。あれ、5人だっけ？あたまがないんだ。あたま。
That is 5 people. Wait, was it 5? We don't have a leader.
あたまがない。
No leader.
あたまがずっとしてない、あれ、6人？
We haven't had a leader, wait, are there 6?
5人？
5 people?
そしたら1人、見学係とかになる。
In that case, one person can be a spectator.
あたまがそしたら、集まった。
If so, the leader... they gathered.
集まったよ、集まったよ。あのさ、ついでに声掛けようと思ったら、あいつアルケミストになった、多分。ねね。
They've gathered, they've gathered. You know, when I went to call out to her, she became an alchemist, probably. Nene.
え、アルケミストはダメなの？ミニゲームやったら。
Eh, are alchemists not allowed to do the mini-game?
よし。
Alright.
頑張ったぞ。
I did my best.
いいですね。
This is nice.
Okay, so basically...
Then...
...the right amount of money is in my bank account.
Whatever I end up earning, I just gotta make sure I spend it.
ね？
Right?
いいですね。
This is nice.
何しよう。
What should I do?
何にもできない、釣りもできない。
I can't do anything, I can't even fish.
いや、なんか卵に、何？
No, like, on the egg... what?
卵に、名前。
On the egg, a name.
卵に、名前付けたら、鶏もその名前じゃないんですよね？
If you name the egg, the chickens don't get that name, right?
Though, if you name the egg, the chickens don't have the...
...whatever the egg is named, right?
Release the chickens?
They're free?
No, but then if I break the thing, I would have to...
...I would have to spend the money again. Ah.
No names on the chicken. Okay.
Will they ever be free? I'll free them before the servers go down.
Oh, right. Food.
いや、でも、あれやったら、これ取れるかも。
No, but if I do that, maybe I can get this.
イナは悪い子じゃないよ。
Ina is not a bad girl.
Oh, mini-games give me money.
Oh, I do have a lot of eggs. I guess I can release these into...
おお！
Oh!
消えた。
It disappeared.
Oh, how about on there?
ほい！
Hup!
I can't see. Are they being born?
ほい！
Hup!
We shall see.
しゅうにゅうにたつ...
"Stand on income..."
フワモコの宝物？
"Fuwamoco's Treasure" ?
何かな？
What is it?
Oh, it was born!
It worked!
It's okay.
These chickens will be born into a peaceful world across the river...
...away from the chaos.
おお！
Oh!
ううー、ううー...
Ugh, ugh...
This is the problem of the century. It's like, when all of a sudden you're given so much time, what do you do?
I can't fish. It's gonna give me money.
Wait, I guess we have time as long as...
...as long as we sell or buy...
...we'll be fine. We can return to fishing, and then we can just...
Okay, let's do this.
Okay.
Now I can just...
chill.
My goal was to practice my Nihongo, that was the original plan.
Let's go back to the original original plan.
Oh wait, we gotta do the dailies, right! You're right.
I was gonna do the daily... Where do you do the daily?
Do I have to go to the puzzle place?
Huh?
Hello.
Egg.
Goodbye.
It earns me money, but I can just get rid of the money at the last little bit. Hold on, I need to make sure...
...I know what time exactly. Okay.
Eight, ten minutes before midnight. Okay, okay, okay.
In the minigame.
Oh, wait, I can fly.
なんか、仕事、仕事掴まえよう。
Let's find some work, some work.
仕事...
Work...
もう、今から入れる仕事...
A job we can start right now...
アスレ・イベント...
Athletic Event...
ミニゲームかな？
Maybe mini-games?
ここ？
Here?
Or is that parkour? Hold on.
ギャンブルは換金率が良くない。
Gambling has bad exchange rates.
まあ、そうね。
Well, yeah.
もう、エンジョイだ。
We should just enjoy it.
マジでエンジョイ用。
Seriously, it's just for fun.
Oh, this is rewards.
Mob Mob Derby.
Indian Block.
TNT Battle.
ここじゃない。
It's not here.
I can't do archaeologist stuff here.
Yep.
せっかくだし、やってみようか。
Since I'm here, maybe I'll try it.
Indian Block.
These are multiplayer.
戻ろう。
Let's go back.
どこ、どこ行けばいい？
Where, where should I go?
お借りしにきた、借金しにきた。
I came to borrow money, came to get a loan.
借金はちょっと不可でございます。
I'm afraid loans are not allowed.
私共の銀行でしたら...
If it were our bank...
そうなんです。
I see.
お客様の... 現在、信用の足りてないんですのね。
Currently, you don't have enough credit, customer.
信用が足りてない？
Not enough credit?
一円だけでもお借りすることはできないかな？
Can I not even borrow a single yen?
かなで先輩、ジャンプしてみて。
Kanade-senpai, try jumping.
音、聞こえるでしょ？
You can hear the sound, right?
持ってないよ！
I don't have any!
持ってないの？
You don't?
持ってないよ！
I don't!
In dungeons.
ダンジョンか。
Dungeons, huh?
持ってない。
I don't have it.
100！
One hundred!
Hello.
Hi!
Farmer Ina, what is your wisdom of the day?
Watermelon.
Watermelon, huh?
By the way, congratulations on laying those eggs.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Yeah, there are some fake ones on the market, but you know, you have to make sure you read carefully.
Oh my god, I can't believe it. What's the name? What will you name your egg?
Egg-y.
Egg-y?
Thank you, I'm so happy for you.
What are you up to?
腹減りもやばい確かに
I'm super hungry, too, honestly.
Um, I'm just doing my own solo leveling arc.
Solo leveling?!
Yeah, I've been solo leveling.
Go- Did you go like, 'Rise', and then, and then, like, stuff appeared?
Did you go like, 'Rise', and then, like, stuff appeared?
Yeah, I basically go, um, I forgot the main character's name, so let's just call it Kirito. I just basically go Kirito in the dungeon.
Yeah, I basically go... um, I forgot the main character's name, so let's just call him Kirito. I basically go Kirito in the dungeon.
Kirito?!
Well, I'm sorry. I watched like two episodes of Solo Leveling, and I haven't continued, and I forgot the main character's name.
Well, I'm sorry. I watched like two episodes of Solo Leveling, and I haven't continued, so I forgot the main character's name.
So, I'm, um, Kirigaya Anya. I'm Kirito.
So, I'm... Kirigaya Anya. I'm Kirito.
Ah, okay, I see, I see, I see. You look so strong!
Thank you!
And powerful!
Yeah, thank you, you too. I, I, I heard that farmers have been making a lot.
Yeah, thank you, you too. I heard that farmers have been making a lot.
Way more than we do.
How much do you guys make?
How much do you have?
Um, right now I only have 11 million. I'm pretty sure you have more.
Oh, that's a lot, though!
Yeah, but you guys, farmers, are earning the most, I feel like, because lots of farmers are earning a lot.
Yeah, yeah, I mean they buffed, like, melons a lot, and pumpkins and stuff, so...
Yeah, yeah, I mean they buffed melons a lot, and pumpkins and stuff, so...
I'm, I'm done. I, I reached my goal, and I have retired as a farmer, and now I'm just a NEET again.
I'm done. I reached my goal, and I have retired as a farmer, and now I'm just a NEET again.
Well, do you have any advice for me, who is still, you know, doing my nightly job as a fighter?
Well, um...
Senpai.
Make sure to eat your vegetables.
Oh, thank you!
You need the vitamins from the carrots.
True, I've been eating salmon. Look at my salmon.
Oh, salmon's good, too.
I was gonna fish just now, if you ever need some fish.
Oh my god. Oh yes, yes.
I'll let you know.
Yeah, let me know!
Let me know then.
I'm gonna fish until I have to sell all the fish and get all my money again.
Sayonara!
Goodbye!
Next time. Good luck!
Kirigaya An-
I forgot her name. Her other name. Not Kirito, though.
Okay, forget about archaeology, we're gonna fish. I'm gonna stick to my original goal. My roots.
Cow!
雑草刈りをね、雑草刈りは大事だから
Weeding, you see, weeding is important.
Cow.
Wait, the cow's bopping its head?
耕すということは...
To cultivate means...
No? Okay, maybe not.
Fish!
Okay.
Ah, fish.
So, how is everyone?
Ah, 10 yen per fish.
Sorry, the chickens are a little loud.
Relaxing from work.
Anyway, eat apple, anyway.
I'm hungry.
I guess it has been quite a bit since I ate now, now that I think about it. I ate pretty early.
とっと、とっと、とっと、とっと
To-to, to-to, to-to, to-to...
Ina ni... Ina is hungry.
たた、たた、た
Ta, ta, ta, ta...
Oh, this looks yummy.
とととととととと...
To-to-to-to-to-to-to...
Oh.
Ah...
I wonder if we can...
I don't want to venture too far, though, cuz...
that means that...
I might not get back home in time.
But we could go on an adventure.
Find some axolotls or something.
Rare pets.
Hm?
ねこ？ ねこ？
Cats? Cats?
ねこはいないかも。
Maybe there are no cats.
Don't cats spawn in villages?
I don't even know if there's villages or not.
I don't even know if there are villages or not.
Oh, my stomach growled so loud.
Ooh, leather.
ととととととと
To-to-to-to-to...
ととととととと...
Gamble for mascots with my 90 yen?
I have 100 yen now. I'm rich!
What can I get with 120 yen? Hmm...
Maybe a drink from the vending machine?
ととととと...
To-to-to-to...
How much? Each coin is like a thousand? Or was it ten thousand?
1,000 per?
Do we go earn 1,000 from fishing, and then go gamble our entire wallet away?
Ooh, new boots!
I got new boots.
I should wear like leather gear...
...to go to the casino.
The voices in your head really like gambling.
I think the voices in my head might need some help.
Ah, so beautiful. The sun is rising.
Hmm, how many salmon should I give? Oh.
Sponsor? 아니야.
Sponsor? No, it's not.
Wait, but then do I get money if... Ah, I guess it doesn't really matter. I wasn't going to spend it anyway.
I was about to say, if I grilled the fish, I'll get more money, but...
81 salmon? That's going to take a while.
That's going to take a long time.
I think my fishing rod is going to break before I get any good or better fishing rods.
Oh, I guess I could ask if she has extra netherite boots. She probably does, right?
No, I have... I have materials to make more fishing rods.
I should have stick. I know I have string.
Whoa!
Nautilus!
Bone!
What's the current leaderboard? Not sure.
Apparently, they posted it on like HoloPlus or something, but I haven't checked HoloPlus in a while.
Ah!
Okay.
Ah, Luna-senpai was second?
Was it the cookie?
I wonder if the cookie got nerfed.
Ah, only four stick?
Maybe we'll get more stick from the fishing. Don't you think?
Alchemists are in lead by a huge margin?
I remember when I was an alchemist.
It was very brief, and it was very dark.
First place is over 50 mil?
Yummy yummy.
Yummy yummy food.
50 million...
What would I do with 50 million dollars?
Do you ever think about what you would do if you win the lotto?
50 million dollar lotto.
Yes, dollars, not yen. Dollars.
'Cause we're thinking big.
Buy more Ina merch?
Make anime?
Live a slow life and enjoy myself... That too.
Honestly, I think even if I had like...
...like a hundred million dollars,
I probably wouldn't stop working.
I feel like a not-working life is kind of boring.
Commission Ina to draw Ina? I refuse!
Not even for 50 mil? Nah.
Oh, a rod!
But it's a normal rod.
That's just fishy, you know?
It's like, if there's a reason they're paying that much, they have other intents.
It's gonna be like... like, even after the job is done, they're gonna be like...
"Well, can you make this and this fixes? I paid..."
"I paid 50 million dollars, you have to!" And I'll be like, "Eh..."
50 million fried rice? No thanks.
I don't think I'll be able to ever finish that much rice.
A tripwire hook.
I'm getting some other items, which means there's possibilities of better fishing rods, right?
Okay, we'll get to 1,000 yen soon.
And we'll be able to buy a nice bento lunch.
Would I go to space for some of that 50 mil? I don't think I would personally want to go to space.
There's too many things that can go wrong.
They removed all the enchanted drops? That could be possible, actually.
Hey, it just means that I can... I can fix my fish— f— f—...
...fix my fishing rod. I had a tongue twister. Fix my fishing rod.
Fix my fishing rod.
Ocean is scary, too.
The ocean is scary, too.
The outside is scary.
The entire outside is scary.
But it always like makes me so...
But it always makes me so...
...curious, though. Like, what sort of...
...structure do you have to have physically to survive...
...all that pressure underwater?
It's so fascinating, the deep ocean.
Oh, what I should be doing, I should be cooking these salmon while I'm fishing.
Great idea!
Oh, maintenance.
Decreasing the number of 'Suspicious Sand' blocks...
That's in like 10 minutes? 12 minutes?
Well, it's just maintenance. They're not... They're not shutting down the server, it's just maintenance. It'll be back.
I think that's what it says.
Yeah.
When is it over? I have no idea.
I guess they'll let us know.
What happens when maintenance is over? That's when maintenance begins.
I hope not.
Give me more fishing rods!
Rawr!
Have I looked back at my 3D showcase? No. Past Ina is cringe.
Forget about Past Ina. Present Ina is where it's at.
What about Future Ina? Future Ina can take care of herself. It's fine, it's fine.
Maybe we'll actually be able to afford... one coin. One coin...
I'm so sleepy today. I'm gonna sleep so well.
Getting sleepy...
I don't know if I'll stay awake until the end.
Maybe I'll step away to eat for a bit, make some food.
Actually, I'll be right back. After this fish.
INA GETTING FOOD
[On-Screen Text: INA GETTING FOOD]
Huh, food...
I wonder if I have to disconnect or the... if the server will disconnect on its own.
I wonder if I have to disconnect or... if the server will disconnect on its own.
いただきます。
Let's eat!
何食べようかな？
What should I eat?
ふふふ...
Hehehe...
Yummy yummy...
Cabbage.
キャベツ食べる。
I'll eat cabbage.
Nyam nyam nyam nyam...
Nom nom nom nom...
How...
うーん...
Mmm...
Cabbage.
うーん...
Mmm...
No, we're going to disconnect soon.
No, it's a regular cabbage.
うーん...
Mmm...
Ina...
Sorry if I mute.
Oh.
Is this going to be okay?
I wonder if it's live maintenance or if they're going to shut the servers down.
うーん...
Mmm...
All right, dungeons are on a different server.
I don't mind.
Okay, let's go. Let's go participate.
Where'd I put my chest? Oh, there it is.
Okay, that should be good.
Where's my sword?
I think I can, well, my Elytra is almost broken.
Oh, my shield. Very important.
Where'd I put it? There it is.
Did I put the ramen in there somewhere?
Bees?
Should we? We don't have much time left.
Let's just grab two regen bees, I guess.
Slow falling, maybe?
It's okay, it's not gonna die right away.
I'm sure they got it.
So quiet.
今日は何でしょう？
What is it today?
あ、今日もハトタウル。あ、２体も！
Ah, Hatotaur again today. Oh, there are two of them!
うわー！
Whoa!
お、ボスだからか！
Oh, is it because it's a boss?
あ、後ろもやってるわ！
Ah, they're fighting behind us too!
うそ！
No way!
危ない、これ危ない！
Watch out, this is dangerous!
放送してないから怖いぞ！
Since I'm not streaming, this is scary!
熱い！熱い！熱い！熱い！
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
痛い！
Ouch!
よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ...
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
曲がったね！
It turned!
Oh, it turned.
早すぎて全然追いつけない！
It's too fast, I can't keep up at all!
攻撃が生きてる！
My attacks are landing!
危ない！
Watch out!
I don't think we're doing any damage.
ハトタウルが...
The Hatotaur is...
ファイター頑張れ！
Do your best, Fighters!
うわぁ、頑張れ！
Uwoaa, do your best!
意外とむずい。弱いな。
This is surprisingly hard. It's weak.
頑張れ！
Do your best!
神様も気まぐれだからね。
The gods are whimsical after all.
おりゃあ！
Oryaa!
ほいほいほい！
Hoi hoi hoi!
おいおいおいおい、やばいやばい。
Oi oi oi oi, oh no, oh no.
Yeah!
めっちゃ硬い。すごい、こいつ。
It's super hard! This guy is crazy.
やばい、硬い！助けてー！
No way, so tough! Help me!
逃げ...逃げろ逃げろ！
Run... Run, run!
これに勝たないと株価が...株価がやれる！
If we don't win this, the stock price... the stock price will plummet!
ぎゃあ！あっぷ...
Gyaa! Up...
ファイター助けて！助けて！
Fighters, help me! Help!
100万円くれたら戦いに参加します！
If you give me a million yen, I'll join the fight!
100万円で護衛しますよ！
I'll guard you for a million yen!
ファイター助けて！ファイター助けて！
Fighters, help! Fighters, help!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Do your best! Do your best!
負けない...
Won't lose...
この赤い... あれは何？
This red... What is that?
だれか助けて！
Someone help me!
ファイター！ファイター効く？
Fighter! Does Fighter work?
ファイター頑張ってますけどね。
Fighters are trying their best, though.
あ、100万円。
Oh, 1,000,000 yen.
戦います、戦います！わあ！
We'll fight! We'll fight! Whoa!
かっこいい！
That's cool!
回ってる！回ってる！回れ、回れ！
It's spinning! It's spinning! Spin! Spin!
ほら、危ない、ほら！
Look out, it's dangerous, look!
あつい！熱い、熱い！
It's hot! Hot, hot!
死ぬ、死ぬ、死ぬ！
I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die!
ちょっと、待って、待って、待って...
Oh god, wait, wait, wait, wait...
待って、また来た！また来た！
Wait, another one came! Another one came!
怖い、怖い、怖い！
Scary, scary, scary!
ファイターだろ、ファイターだろ！
You're a fighter, right?
おい、ちょっと、倒した？
Hey, wait, did we defeat it?
え、何これ、何これ？
Eh, what is this? What is this?
痛い、痛い、痛い！
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
待って... あ、盾が！
Wait... oh, my shield!
おい、おい、おい、おい！
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
やれる、やれる！
We can do this! We can do this!
おい、おい、おい、おい！
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
痛い！ハトタウルス、ハトタウルス！
Ouch! Hatotaurus! Hatotaurus!
待って、待って、盾が壊れそう。
Wait, wait, my shield is gonna break.
盾が壊れそう！
My shield is gonna break!
痛い、痛い、痛い！
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
ハトタウルス、強い！
Hatotaurus is strong!
痛い！HPきつい！
Ouch! My HP is low!
ああああああ！
Aaaaaaaah!
人間倒されそう！
The humans are about to be defeated!
あ、盾が！
Oh, my shield!
盾が！
My shield!
スース、スースもファイターじゃないですか？
Suu-san, isn't Suu-san a fighter too?
がんばれ！がんばれ...
Do your best! Do your best...
いける、いける！行け、行け、行け！
We can do this! Go, go, go!
ハトタウルス、ハトタウルス！
Hatotaurus! Hatotaurus!
行け、行け、行け！
Go, go, go!
ごはん、ごはん、ごはん！
Food, food, food!
あ、盾が... 盾が！
Oh, my shield is... my shield!
ハトタウルス！
Hatotaurus!
がんばれ！
Do your best!
2人ともいる！
Both of them are here!
行け、行け！なんで？なんで？
Go, go! Why? Why?
ハラデが数少ないファイター...
Harade is one of the few fighters...
助けて！やばい、やばい、ヘイト買ってる！
Help! Oh no, I'm pulling aggro!
助けて！ハトタウルス！
Help! Hatotaurus!
ファイター助けて！
Fighter, help!
ファイターが強い！
Fighters are strong!
おい、おい！ハトタウルス！
Hey, hey! Hatotaurus!
やばい、死ぬ！
Oh no, I'm gonna die!
ナイス！ナイス、ナイス、ナイス！
Nice! Nice, nice, nice!
痛い、痛い、痛い！
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
あと少し！
Just a little more!
ハトタウルス、硬い、硬い！
Hatotaurus is so tough!
いや、いや、いや！
No, no, no!
盾が！
My shield!
がんばれ！
Do your best!
ラーメン食って。強いな、ハトタウルス！
Eating ramen. Hatotaurus is strong!
うわ、うわ、うわ！
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
おい、おい、おい！
Hey, hey, hey!
はい、はい、はい！
Yes, yes, yes!
痛い、死ぬ！
It hurts, I'm gonna die!
前回もめっちゃ強かったしな。
It was really strong last time, too.
痛い、痛い、痛い！
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
ハトタウルス、強い！
Hatotaurus is strong!
わあ！くる、くる、くる！
Whoa! It's coming, it's coming!
盾が！
My shield!
体力足りねえ。
Not enough HP.
アルケミスト魔法使えねえの？
Alchemist, can't you use magic?
みんなで！
Everyone, together!
お前らハネでパタパタしてるだけか！
Are you guys just flapping around with wings?!
お前らハネでパタパタ...
You guys flapping with wings...
おりゃ！おりゃ！
Orya! Orya!
痛い、痛い！ファイターいる！
It hurts, it hurts! There's a fighter!
突っ込め！おりゃ！おりゃ！
Charge! Orya! Orya!
うわあ！いやだ！
Uwah! No!
しゅ、しゅ、しゅ、シュバゲリオン！？
Shu, shu, shu, Shubangelion?!
シュバゲリオン！？
Shubangelion!?
シュバゲリオン！
Shubangelion!
シュバゲリオン、強い！
Shubangelion is strong!
痛い、痛い、痛い！
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
シュバゲリオン！これやばいぞ！
Shubangelion! This is bad!
走り方やばすぎる！
Its running style is too crazy!
なんてこった。
Oh, god.
どこにいるんだ？いた！いた！
Where is it? There! There!
えええ！？
Ehh?!
すご...
Wow...
地面を舐めさせるんや！
Make them lick the ground!
あと2分しかない！
Only 2 minutes left!
どこ行った？飛んだ？
Where did it go? Did it fly?
あれ？どこ行った？
Huh? Where did it go?
どこに放たれた？
Where was it released?
あああ！
Ahhh!
あ、いた。
Ah, there it is.
いいよ！いいよ！
Nice, nice!
地面ダメ！地面ダメ！
Don't let it hit the ground!
いけいけ！
Go, go!
あと2分！いけ！いけ！
2 minutes left! Go! Go!
うわあ！
Whoa!
めっちゃ強い！
It's so strong!
今！今！今！
Now, now, now!
あと2分だ！
Only 2 minutes left!
おい！いけいけ！
Hey! Go, go!
うおおお！
Whoooa!
するするするする...
Sliding, sliding, sliding...
千早！千早！
Chihaya! Chihaya!
おらああ！
Take this!
いけいけいけ！
Go, go, go!
ああっ！
Ahh!
あ、うちら...
Ah, we...
あれが...殺害...
That was... a murder...
おお！
Oh!
いけいけいけいけ！
Go, go, go, go!
がんばれ！がんばれ！
Do your best! Do your best!
あと1分！痛い！
One minute left! Ouch!
あといつ？
When's the rest?
あとちょっと！あとちょっとよ、みんな！
Almost there! Just a little more, everyone!
おお！
Oh!
俺たちの勝ちだ！
It's our victory!
え？へへ。やべっ！
Eh? Hehe. Oh no!
走ってる！
It's running!
あとちょっとなんだ！
Just a little more!
いけ、いけ、いけ、いけ！
Go, go, go, go!
なぐれ！なぐれ！
Punch it! Punch it!
うわああ！
Whoaaa!
いけいけいけいけ！
Go, go, go, go!
あとちょっと！
Almost there!
やったー！
We did it!
よかったー！おめでとうございます！
Thank goodness! Congratulations!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
これですっきりやね。
What a relief.
守られましたね！
We were protected!
パチパチパチパチ。
(Clapping)
守られました！
We protected it!
それではルーレットを...
Now, let's spin the roulette...
これは...何？
What is... this?
これはルーレット...
This is the roulette...
おめでとうございます。
Congratulations.
カブカブカブ...
Stocks, stocks, stocks...
よろしくお願いします。
Please look forward to it.
え？2円？
Eh? 2 yen?
2円しかない。素晴らしい！
Only 2 yen. Wonderful!
カブどうなんだろう？
How will the stocks go?
頼む、頼む！
Please, please!
カブしか持ってない。
I only have stocks.
やばい、プラスこれ...
Oh no, plus this...
ししろフード、プラス500円！おめでとうございます！
Shishiro Foods, plus 500 yen! Congratulations!
え、ししろフード... 500！
Eh, Shishiro Foods... 500!
やることしかないじゃん！
There's nothing else to do!
泥棒建設、プラス200円！
Dorobou Construction, plus 200 yen!
おめでとうございます、泥建！
Congratulations, Doroken!
買いたかった... 泥建戻った！
I wanted to buy... Doroken is back!
ネネネ電鉄...
Nene Railway...
ネネ、ネネ、ネネ...
Nene, Nene, Nene...
おい、200円！
Hey, 200 yen!
ゼロ円？
Zero yen?
ゼロ円、ネネ電鉄。
Zero yen, Nene Railway.
おお...
Oh...
大空建設... ゼロ円だ！
Oozora Construction... Zero yen!
あ、大空建設は違う。
Ah, Oozora Construction is different.
これは戻れるか？
Can this recover?
プラス200円です！
Plus 200 yen!
さあ、最後。ねぽらぼホールディングス。
Now, the last one. Nepolabo Holdings.
これはちょっと...
This is a bit...
ねぽらぼ、ねぽらぼ...
Nepolabo, Nepolabo...
200！200！200！
200! 200! 200!
プラス200円！おめでとうございます！
Plus 200 yen! Congratulations!
以上！どうする？
That's all! What should we do?
上がった、上がった！
It went up, it went up!
わあ...
Wow...
200...
イナ、カブ...
Ina, stocks...
持ってない...持ってない...
I don't have... I don't have...
念のため... 念のためチェックしようか？
Just in case... Should I check just in case?
ここで...
Here...
うーん、どうしようかな...
Mmm, what should I do...
びび？びび？
Bibi? Bibi?
お前売るか？
Are you selling?
売る？でもみんな売ると安くなる。じゃ、やめて！
Sell? But if everyone sells, it gets cheaper. So stop!
うわー。
Wow...
こっち、ゼロ。
Zero on this side.
え、はよ売らんと...売るか？
Eh, sell it quickly... Sell it?
なんだよね。
Right?
売るか、売るか、売るか...
Are we selling, selling, selling...
所持金額100...
Money in possession: 100...
安っ！何これ高っ！安っ！
So cheap! What is this, so expensive! Cheap!
170円にしかなってないよとか言ってるから。いや、違う違う違う。
They're saying it's only 170 yen. No, no, no.
ありなのかな？オッケー。
Is that okay? Okay.
いや、カブとかさ...
No, the stocks...
みんなあんまわかんないから。
Because everyone doesn't really know.
Everyone bought Nepolabo.
My carrots.
Let's switch my bees back in.
Oh, yeah...
Oh, these also finished.
Ooh! Another Regen 2.
Well, I wanna finish eating my food.
Maybe you guys can stare at... dancing Inas while I eat. 'Cause I wanna eat before my food gets cold.
どこどこどこどこ...
Where, where, where, where...
Oh, Oozora was on a different server.
So the main one wouldn't go down. That's kind of smart, actually.
Ina is eating... Mic muted. There we go. I'll be right back!
INA IS EATING.. MIC MUTED!
Ina is eating... Mic muted!
Blegh! Hahaha.
My apologies, I was busy eating.
Nom nom nom nom nom...
That was yummy.
Hehehe.
Did the mic taste good? Oh wait, I forgot.
WO
sorry ate micro...
sorry ate microphone
can't speak
oh nyo
Ah, sorry guys, I pulled up my backup microphone.
No need to worry.
Hahaha.
Phew, good thing I have backups, you know?
Sometimes you just want to eat... you just want to eat some mics, you know?
And you have to make sure you eat them muted because they're going to scream if you don't.
You don't want your neighbors hearing that.
You don't want them to call the police.
Oh, I just had a great idea.
There we are, chat.
I don't know if it'll come to fruition, but I can try.
Oh, oh, my levels are gone because I died.
My twenty-something levels...
What is that? A bowl?
It's okay. If we can't repair the fishing rod, we'll just make a new one.
Tako. There you go.
Wait, we should have enough. I mean, we just have to get some sticks.
Started from the bottom, we're still here.
They're buying out stocks again?
They're... they're doing a... they're playing a dangerous game.
A very dangerous game.
Oh, not much salmon.
I feel like this happened before.
Where has this happened before? A faint memory.
One salmon.
Another time, another place.
Kabu... Haven't had turnips in a while.
Kabu [turnips]... Haven't had turnips in a while.
It's harder to have, like, different types of vegetables when you're in Japan,
which is why I eat cabbage a lot.
I'm sure there's a lot more, but like...
since I can't really cook for myself here, it's like I go to get the bagged salad and stuff,
but usually it's just like lettuce or cabbage with like some shredded carrots.
The very safe choices, you know, for salad.
I do find that, like, marts in America have more adventurous assortments of salads,
which I do appreciate... except the fact that they sell too much at once.
Oh, another salmon.
Like, the portions are a little too big.
Yeah, but then like, they go through the stock, like, in the marts and the conbini pretty fast, like, every day,
Yeah, but then like, they go through the stock, like, in the marts and the conbini [convenience store] pretty fast, like, every day,
so it does stay pretty fresh.
Which is the good part.
That's the thing because, like, I talked about this before, but like, marts in America, because the, you know, the land is so big,
everyone needs to drive to get to like a central location.
But since everyone lives in... like, the density of people in one area is so much higher in Japan,
there's so many smaller marts and convenience stores with fresh food you can get,
that you don't really need those bigger marts until you go out a little more into the rural areas.
A name tag.
I do, there's one...
Oh, veggie... uh...
Number of shares circulating in Holotown. As a result,
while selling still decreases...
the stock price, the fluctuations are much smaller than before. Thank you for your understanding.
Aha.
What are they talking about?
Oh, yeah. Well, one of the veggies that I really, really like grilled, actually,
is Brussels sprouts.
I really like grilled Brussels sprouts. Just, nothing fancy, just a little bit of oil...
...little bit of salt and pepper.
Mmm, Brussels sprouts.
I love grilled veggies in general. Grilled veggies are delicious.
That's the one thing I miss, I guess. Like, the barbecue-grilled vegetables.
Like, even when, like, our family would have a barbecue...
...in the backyard, I would only really be like...
...eating the veggies...
...and then a bit of meat here and there.
Nothing beats like actual barbecue with grilled...
...veggies.
Mmm.
I think really good grilled vegetables don't need sauce, just a little bit of salt.
Honestly, I don't even need salt sometimes, because...
...a good grilled vegetable has its own like...
...umami, you know?
Its own flavor.
Its own sweetness.
Yeah.
And that's the one thing, I guess, I kind of miss about...
...summer...
...and our family being...
...all across the world, is the summer barbecues.
And eating...
...outside in the backyard.
Like, mama Ina...
...likes gardening,
so our backyard used to look so beautiful.
Plus there were a lot of mosquitoes and bees, but...
...which is the part I didn't like.
But, it was still so, so pretty when the flowers bloomed.
It literally looked like...
...a garden out of, like, a Ghibli movie.
I was like, "Wow, it's so beautiful!" Oh, a stick!
One less stick needed to make the next fishing rod.
Speaking of mosquitoes, I got bitten yesterday.
I got bitten yesterday, I was like, "Ah..."
"...this year's first mosquito bite, I see."
My first donation of blood...
...to my mortal enemies.
Oh, it switched. It changed to suika.
Oh, it switched. It changed to watermelon.
But then like, I kind of like had a feeling I would get a mosquito bite there...
Oh, more shoes!
...'cause like, it was kind of in like a shaded area...
...beside a bunch of plants, I was like...
"I'm going to get a mosquito bite, aren't I?"
And then I did.
I just had that feeling.
I used to be like so much... I think it's a little less now.
Maybe it's returned a little bit, but I used to be so like, almost allergic to mosquito bites.
To a point where, like...
Ah! It broke! But a saddle!
I don't have a horse.
I like this one, too.
And then they swell so much, no matter how much I do, how much ice packs and medicine I put on it, it would swell so much.
But then, surprisingly enough, there was a... there was a time I wasn't as like, healthy, I guess?
And then, I never really got that many mosquito bites then.
And I was like, "These mosquitoes..."
They're... they're smart.
They know when the prey is not yummy.
How did they know?
Like they would fly by, and they'd be like, "Ugh, ugh, disgusting." And they'd just fly off.
What's happening? How can I return to that state?
Ah, another saddle. But I don't have a horse.
Okay, we must get stick.
Wait, are we even going to get 1,000...
...by the deadline? I don't know,
I'm not... I'm not too confident right now.
Wait, do I get money if I break leaves? I don't.
Give me stick. Give me more stick.
All these woods will be barren when I'm done with it.
I guess it doesn't really make a difference. Give me stick!
More stick!
Give!
I'm like the opposite of a typical Minecraft player right now.
Those who leave the, what-you-may-call-it...
...the one stump.
Now I just take all the leaves and leave the stumps.
My stick!
A divergent Minecraft player. That reminds me,
you know the movie series, Divergent?
I remember I really enjoyed the books before.
But then I barely remember now.
I used to really like those types of books like what's it...
...like the Divergent series, and Maze Runner...
Ah, more stick!
I even really enjoyed, what was that series?
The one with the... the blue dragon on the cover?
Eragon, yeah!
Oh, I have six sticks now. Okay.
Oh, I remember I used to be like... used to be addicted to reading books because of that series.
Oh, I already have string, okay.
I don't know how the books ended, though. I don't remember.
Because I remember like the last volume or something took forever to come out, right?
A year ago? What? Oh, it wasn't finished?
I might have to try and re-read it from the start.
But the books are so long, though.
Oh, the story is finished, but he wanted to make another one in the series? Ah, naruhodo.
Naruhodo.
Ah, the blast of the past.
That's the thing, like I can never read web novels,
because I just... like I can handle e-books now,
but like I can't read things when they're on the screen that much.
So whenever someone sends me a giant document online, I'm just like...
But I just, I just like physical books a lot more.
And physical books smell so good.
Sometimes, because like different books have different smells, right? Sometimes...
I just like, open the book and go...
I love walking into bookstores in Japan, because there's so many of them everywhere.
And just go...
I wonder when a good time to...
hand over the salmon to Anya is.
Ah, I don't have anything else to burn.
Can I burn my shoes? Can I burn this bowl?
Oh, I can.
Burn my bowl.
People leave books in the bathroom? Ooh...
I think...
you might have a moisture problem in your bathroom if your books start molding.
It's like, no matter how humid of a place you live in, you should...
Oh, a bowl.
you should be taking care of that...
moisture level in your bathrooms.
Oh wait, we were going to have 1,000 for the coin until we died.
And our dreams also died.
Dreams of finally entering the casino.
We have around...
30-ish minutes to be safe, but...
the final round up is, is in like, a little less than an hour...
ish.
Another saddle.
余った1時間...
The remaining one hour...
あ、あと3... いや、いや、いや、いや...
Ah, there's 3... No, no, no, no...
ここから5分後...
Five minutes from now...
株の精算が終わるかも。いや...
the turnip price calculation might be over. No...
始まる？終わる？
Is it starting? Or ending?
The war of kabu in 5 minutes.
The turnip war in 5 minutes.
The final battle of kabu.
The final battle of turnip.
Maybe I'll go just to watch.
I'm just gonna bring my popcorn again.
Oh, level 10 for fishing.
Okay, how about I make my way and bring the... bring the salmon.
I don't think the two coals are enough to cook all the salmon, yeah. I think 15 is a good number, right?
Anything else I can burn?
I burn this... Oh, I can. Okay, okay.
Alright, Anya, I hope you're ready...
My 15 salmons and a dream.
Someone left their shulker here.
Free elytra!
いいね。
Nice.
お水を取りに行きます。
I'm going to get some water.
I guess these are all kind of just like... extras.
Oh, what is this? I can't read.
ね、らみぃはネポラボに賭けてるからな。
Yeah, Lamy is betting on Nepolabo, after all.
じゃあ、あとはもう裏で作業するからな、一応。行ってきます。
Alright, I'll be working behind the scenes now, just in case. I'm off!
Enchanting boutiques? I guess they're really rare.
勝たせるつもりもないんだな。
They have no intention of letting them win.
はい、みんな。しゃがむ、しゃがむ。
Alright, everyone. Crouch, crouch.
俺は弱いから見ててやる。
I'm weak so I'll just watch.
さあ、どうなるかね？
Now, what will happen?
信じてますよ、ししろお。ししろお、ししろお！
I believe in you, Shishiro. Shishiro, Shishiro!
1億！
100 million!
いけるか？いけるか？
Can she do it? Can she do it?
いける、いける、いける！
She can do it! She can do it!
いけるか？カブに全振りするわ。
Can she? I'm betting everything on the turnip.
1億いったらギリ勝つか負けるかくらいなのかな？
If it reaches 100 million, will it be a narrow win or loss?
ねね、1億円分買ったよ！
Nene, I bought 100 million worth!
え？1億！？
Eh? 100 million?!
ねね、めっちゃお金持ってたんだね、元々。
Nene, you had so much money to begin with!
いや、ネポラボの上がりが凄かった。
No, Nepolabo's returns were amazing.
あ、そういうことか！
Ah, is that so!
ほないきまっせ！
Alright, let's go!
はい！お願いします！
Yes! Please!
ししろフーズ！お願い、お願い、ししろ...
Shishiro Foods! Please, please, Shishiro...
お、ししらふ行ったな
Oh, Shishiro went.
お願い、プラス、プラス、何でもいいからプラス！
Please, plus, plus! Anything, just be plus!
ししらふプラス250。おおー！
Shishiro, plus 250. Ohhh!
プラス100だ！プラス100！
It's plus 100! Plus 100!
泥棒建設！おー。
Dorobou Construction! Wow.
泥棒かも。何だこれ？
Might be Dorobou. What's this?
100、100、100、100、100！
100, 100, 100, 100, 100!
マイナス30！マイナス30。
Minus 30! Minus 30.
なんで、です？影響なし。
Why is that? Unaffected.
あがれ！あがれ！えっ、まつり、いけ！
Go up! Go up! What? Matsuri! Go!
マイナス36！マイナス36…うそ！
Minus 36! Minus 36... No!
大空！大空…なんてこと。
Oozora! Oozora... Oh my god.
プラスになれ、プラスになったら何だっていい！
Be plus, please. Please be plus. If it's plus, anything is fine.
プラス30。
Plus 30.
ネポラボ！ネポラボ！ネポラボ？ネポラボ、ネポラボ、ネポラボ…
NePoLaBo! NePoLaBo! NePoLaBo? NePoLaBo, NePoLaBo, NePoLaBo...
おー、ネポラボ +136円！一生買えないw プラス136円。
Oh, NePoLaBo +136 yen! Can never buy it! Oh, plus 136 yen.
すごいね、これ、パーセント？プラス50？
Amazing, is this... which one? Percent? Plus 50?
ネポラボ上がりましたね。
NePoLaBo went up.
やばい、まつり死んだw まつり落ちた…おめでとう！
Oh no, Matsuri died! Oh my god, Matsuri fell. Matsuri fell... congratulations!
How is this going to go?
I want to go here though.
The place from before...
Is this by any chance...
How is this going?
Didn't it go out? A lot...
The rich people...
No wonder...
How does that even happen?
By the way...
Oh, it doesn't go down? I see.
Ah, it goes down, but...
Maybe it will be just a tiny bit, I think. Even so, it's fine.
Where is everyone?
Oh, everyone got so rich.
Shall we sell... this?
Oh, it's going down.
Amazing.
Is it okay with that?
You can't buy negative value stocks. It's blocked.
Where is Anya's... Does Anya have a house?
No way, it must be...
How does stocks work?
I can't even use my locker.
Who is fighting now?
Miko is outside.
Who's fighting? I thought you just wanted lasagna.
That's the warrant office, I think.
Oh, Miko showed up out of here, right?
Is she done?
I will eat my food and wait here.
Should I buy stocks and gamble?
The increase range.
What about the dungeons?
I don't think it has that much effect, though.
What, am I eating the rest of my dinner?
So...
Don't eat the carrot yet?
Wait, Miko has a pet?
Another hour left, huh?
Miko's pet looks very mean.
But that's her second pet?
What was dinner? Miko?
Don't eat the other one...
Did Miko buy her egg yet?
He bought her egg yet?
Yeah, what's up?
I have 1 carrot left.
Butter egg. No, butter dog.
CCTV pet?
Anya's home...
He is just standing there, menacingly.
Anya is...
Anya... Let me, let me fix this.
Anya!
Oh.
いいね！
Nice!
待ってたぞ。
I've been waiting.
いいね、いいね。
Nice, nice.
そしてニコ。
And Niko.
ニコちゃんも... ま、ニコちゃんもいいかな？
Niko-chan too... well, is Niko-chan good too?
ニコちゃんも。
Niko-chan too.
ま、ニコちゃんにもっと似合うかも。
Well, maybe it suits Niko-chan more.
ニコちゃん。
Niko-chan.
ニコです。
I'm Niko.
みゃおみゃおできる？
Can you meow meow?
みゃおみゃお！みゃおみゃお！
Meow meow! Meow meow!
あっ、猫だ！猫にゃ！
Ah, a cat! A cat!
お魚！
Fish!
嬉しい！やった！
I'm happy! Yay!
Anya, can you meow meow?
Meow meow, Anya?
みゃおみゃお...
Meow meow...
お魚！
Fish!
ワンワン！
Woof woof!
お魚！
Fish!
ワンワン！
Woof woof!
ちーちゃん！
Chi-chan!
え、骨はないよ、ちーちゃん！
Huh? I don't have bones, Chi-chan!
みゃおみゃお...
Meow meow...
みゃおみゃお？
Meow meow?
みゃおみゃお。
Meow meow.
あ、猫ちゃんだ！可愛い！
Ah, a kitty! Cute!
可愛い、ちーは。
Cute, Chiha.
みゃおみゃお。
Meow meow.
あにゃ先輩の先輩。
Anya-senpai's senpai.
楽しんでるかい、ちーは？
Are you having fun, Chiha?
楽しんでます！
I'm having fun!
二人ともファイターだね。
You're both fighters.
うんうん！
Yeah!
そうです。
That's right.
いなほどじゃないよ。いなは、大先輩。
Not as much as Ina. Ina is a great senior.
ねえ？
Right?
いや、そんな、そんな。
No, not really...
いなは騎士。
Ina is a knight.
いろんな人と喋ってるみたい。
Looks like you're talking to various people.
えー？えー？
Huh? Really?
いやいや、ただ、釣りする人だよ。見て、釣り。
No no, I'm just a fisher. Look, fishing.
Anya 釣り。
Anya, fishing.
Ah! Oh! Ah!
釣られる...
Being fished...
Yes! More, more!
More, more! Yes! Yes! More!
Harder!
Are you doing hard mode right now?
Yeah, I'm doing hard mode.
Are you soloing hard mode?
Yeah.
I mean, that's kind of like the only way you can earn money.
Really?
Yeah, Fighter's Fighter life.
I believe in you.
Wait, how much do you have right now?
Um... It's ichi, hachi...
Ichi, hachi...
No way! You're freaking rich!
Ichi, hachi, ichi, hachi, ichi, hachi...
I'm trying to end with ichi hachi ichi hachi.
Wait, that song sounds like one anime song that I can't recall.
But it sounds like an old anime song.
Old anime song?
Ichi hachi tako hachi, ichi hachi tako hachi...
All right, Anya.
What does... what does the rabbit say?
Oh, almost there.
What does the rabbit say, Anya?
The rabbit...
It craves for blood.
Craves for blood?
Did... have you seen... have you seen the amount that Pekora-senpai is earning?
No.
It's insane.
Wow. That's a different world from us.
Insane. She craves blood.
She's a fighter.
I don't know how she does it.
She's a war criminal.
She craves blood.
I'm glad you didn't say her name because she just walked by.
So many people just walked...
So many people just walked at us.
I didn't see their name.
You know, I see all these things about like the... the what's it, the spears, the bamboo spears and everything.
Uh-huh.
I'm just like... yeah, it's so peaceful in my corner.
I'm just fishing.
It is.
It is, just you.
In another world, I would have been a fighter, but... I felt very low energy.
In another world...
Well, why not as well, as well...
It's still...
It's not too late. There is still an hour left.
Well, less than an hour.
Like 20 minutes.
Uh-huh.
Or 40 minutes, technically I guess.
Yeah, 40 minutes.
Yeah, 40.
40.
Can you carry me?
There is still 40 minutes left.
Carry me through hard mode.
Yes, obviously.
I'm too cheap to afford a shield though.
It's okay. Are you seeing my diamond armor?
Or actually, it doesn't matter if I die, actually, now that I think about it.
I have nothing to lose.
Yeah, if you go, if you go with two people, as long as the other one lives, you can like...
...they just like, the game just keeps respawning you.
Carry me, Anya.
Wait!
I can, I can, is... the dungeon has the archaeological stuff, right? I can finally clear the daily...
...daily...
Oh...
Please, I need a bodyguard while I shovel through the... through the sand.
Oh my god.
Is it... is it night? Nino-Ina, come back!
No, no, I... I live for the brush now.
You're the knight.
You lived long enough to see Nino-Ina come back?
No, you're the knight! You're protecting me.
But my diamond armor?
Yes!
Wait, you don't have armor?
Um, yeah. So, the thing is, with me solo-ing the dungeon over and over again...
...means my armor just keeps breaking, breaking.
Hold on, I have just the thing for you, my knight.
For your services, follow me.
What did you say?
For your services, so that I can get my daily done...
...I shall award you with...
...my own...
Oh, sorry.
Oh, it's okay, I have a bunch of pants.
But yes, you can now guard me.
...while I brush the sand.
Sorry, I don't have a helmet.
Oh, also, um, yeah, I only have diamond helmet.
Okay, let's go.
Okay! Let's go!
Let's go.
Let's go. It's time.
Wait, let me go to the ATM first.
Okay.
The rise of the brush hero.
Now, I forgot my bees, I guess that's fine.
Oh no, I need shield durability.
Is it about to break?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll wait here.
And have a bite of my dinner.
I don't need a shield, Anya is my shield.
I guess.
No, but does she have a...?
...a crush?
Maybe if she ever has an alter ego, it can be a shield.
Omatasen.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey.
You have your sword?
Yes.
But most importantly...
Sasuga!
As expected!
I have my brush.
Okay.
Wait, I think if you, if you want to, um...
...do you need a block? Like some kind of block for that?
I think so, yeah.
Yeah, I think you need to go to the puzzle, the puzzle dungeon.
Oh, is it a puzzle dungeon?
Yeah, you need to go to the puzzle dungeon.
Is it, wait, is it one of those things that alchemists, alchemists do?
I think so. I thought it was at... is it...
...is it a puzzle dungeon?
Yeah, should be there in the puzzle dungeon instead.
I don't think the fighter dungeon has any.
Oh. Then I'll, I'll join you in the fighter dungeon once, just to see what it's like.
The voices in my head are curious.
Okay.
Oh no, it's full!
Oh no!
Well, we can go normal.
Okay.
Yeah, normal is fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
Guard me, please.
Oh my god.
Ooh, mushrooms.
Here...
Here it is.
We dragged the NinoIna...
...out of her retirement!
Oh my god, I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die!
No, you won't.
Oh, the pigs! The pigs give the most money.
Well, beside...
...Golden Yagoo.
Ooh.
You want to make a group VC?
Oops, sorry. Sure.
After we're safe.
Okay.
They will just keep showing up.
Ooh, free bread.
Oh, no wonder you need so much food!
If I knew, I could have been your food supplier.
Oh!
Slimes!
It's the same, right? We just need like...
...the key?
Oh, can't hear me, I think.
Is there a group chat?
Ah! Ah, there you go. Sorry.
Here you go.
I was going to say...
...it's the same as like the easy dungeon, right, where you just gotta find the key?
Oh yeah, but I think...
Well, not I think, the boss doesn't really give that...
...much money in the first place, so it's actually better to just like farm the, the mobs.
Ah...
Yeah, just keep killing the mobs.
Cuz like the boss is not really...
...not really that good, money-wise.
I see.
Unless you want to see the boss, then yes.
Do you wanna, do you wanna fight the boss?
No, I don't have a shield, so I think I'm fine.
Ooh, pigs.
You don't have a shield?
I can give you one.
Do you need one?
Ah, I'm okay for now.
Really?
Yeah.
I have nothing to lose.
Knight NinoIna...
...Ina!
Don't worry, even without a shield, I'll be fine.
So do you just...
...do you just fight until...
...time's up?
Yeah, you just fight.
Ah...
Life of a fighter.
This truly was our solo leveling.
This is all I've been doing...
...by myself, alone.
Alone...
A dungeon on my own.
Okay, if there's ever another event like this, we can coordinate a little better.
Pigs.
What about the Golden Yagoos?
I wanna see a Golden Yagoo.
Yeah, they usually show up a lot. For some reason, they're not showing up at all.
Maybe because it's normal mode, it's not...
Oh! Pigs!
Uh, I don't think...
...I don't think it makes that much difference.
Ina...
Ow! Pigs, pigs.
Rotten pigs, pigs.
Yeah, the pigs give the most money after Golden Yagoo.
So they're really good.
They're really good.
Anya!
Don't die, Anya. Live.
I am barely living.
Protect me!
Knight Ina!
But you're the one with the shield!
Even the shield is not enough to protect me.
I need your power.
We need our combined power...
...to clear this place together.
Oh, my hearts, my hearts, my hearts, my hearts, my hearts!
Ah! I'm cornered!
Ah! Ah!
Oh no, don't die! My knight!
I am live. I am live.
Oh my god.
Thirty more minutes.
Oh yeah, the Wata medal.
Oh!
I can exchange my Wata medals.
I am die.
No! Don't die!
Oh, I am live.
You live!
Oh, Yagoo!
Yagoo!
Get him! Get him! Get him!
They give a bunch of money.
Yagoo!
Get him, get him!
Yagoo, please! Yagoo, please!
Yagoo, please! We're kind of homeless, we need this.
Oh, you're homeless? You could have told me!
No, it's a... it's a reference to the IShowSpeed meme.
Oh.
Please, Yagoo, let us have this.
Oh, slime.
I don't want to be isekai'd as a slime.
Aren't you already an isekai protagonist? I thought this was your post-isekai life.
I retired from my isekai life.
It's like the trope where a hero saves the world in the isekai...
...and then they come back and they're like, "Oh, the world is still dying."
The world became a capitalist world.
It is. There is never a retirement life for an isekai protagonist, you know that, right?
Please, let me be retired.
I just want to fish in the outskirts of town.
Yagoo!
One perfect petal's view...
Yagoo! Yagoo! Yagoo! Yagoo!
Nice, nice, nice.
Yagoo!
逃げるな、Yagoo！
Don't run away, Yagoo!
Yagoo, stop running away!
Oh nice, pigs, pigs, pigs.
Okay, running out of carrots.
Do you want some?
I'm okay, I'm okay. This is good for me.
No!
Okay, I'm going to be paying all the gold I earn as a payment for your protection.
Oh my god.
Ah! Death!
Ina!
Live!
Ah, I live!
No! Hero Anya!
Oh my god.
Live, Hero Anya, live!
Maybe...
Ah, Yagoo, no!
Maybe you shouldn't have asked for protection, because what if I tap you from the back like that, you know?
It's okay, that's what... That's what a hero experiences.
Maybe... That's why my hand...
That's why my hand did that to you.
Oh, you want to be the antagonist in this story?
Well, we need enemies.
It can be arranged.
It can be what?
I mean, why not spicy?
If we're enemies, that means I'm like enemies with like two out of three of the Myth.
But Anya, we're supposed to be perfect partners.
That's true. Oh my god... My memories from my other life!
You have forgotten because you spent countless... countless years in this dungeon alone.
My head... It's trying to remember something, something from my other life, something about...
Remember, Anya, remember!
Oh, Yagoo!
I can't. It's not letting me remember.
Remember Ya-... No, not remember Yagoo.
Remember Yagoo?
Remember Yagoo? Uh, Yagoo? Who is that?
Yag- Yagoo.
Yagoo?
You know that one Re:Zero episode where Rem... Rem forgetting Subaru? That's me right now.
Have you ever watched Re:Zero?
Maybe?
Hopefully I didn't spoil you.
Oh, no, no, no, don't worry.
Yeah, but I'm dead right now.
Chat literally having flashbacks to yesterday going, "No, don't ruin it!"
YAGOOって誰？
Who is Yagoo?
And then cue the ending song, the ending music.
Oh, which one?
It's got to be, it's got to be an insert song, usually.
Stayin'...
Wait, wait, actually.
...alive...
Yeah, yeah.
Stayin'...
...alive!
The ending will change...
Ah, I need to stay alive.
...into an insert song. Oh.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, stayin' alive, stayin' alive.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, stayin' alive, stayin' alive!
Oh my god, it's so fitting because we're trying to stay alive.
Ah! Live! Live!
Oh my god.
Stayin' alive!
Stay alive, NinoIna.
Stay alive, NinoIna, you can't die here.
Ooh, ooh, lapis!
Who's going to take care of your egg if you die here?
The market. The free market!
Wait, did anyone, did anyone buy your egg?
I don't think so.
I spent like 10 minutes clicking the price.
The highest I could make it was plus a thousand.
Yeah, I wish we had like a plus, plus 10,000 or something, at least.
I don't know, cuz I thought Flare would, Flare would buy it or something.
I think that was the plan, but...
Yeah, that was the plan, I thought that was the plan.
She promised, she promised not to sell it.
She promised... Ah!
She promised.
Oh, my... my equipment is broken. No wonder.
Your equipment is always broken.
Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
I was like, "Why did it hurt so much?"
Especially since you're not using, you're not using a shield, too.
Yeah, I was like, "Why does it hurt so much?"
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
It hurts!
Wait, where are the pigs?
Oh, I hear pigs.
Man, I'm surprised you earned so much from just doing this.
Yeah.
I'm impressed.
You earn so much. How much are you, how much are you earning right now?
I have 195k?
Yeah, exactly. So much.
Yeah.
Just smacking mobs.
You're killing the golden Yagos too, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Ah, it hurts, it hurts!
Oh my god.
Oh no, I accidentally...
No.
My... wait, did you get oh... oh I see. One of my armor is broken. Hold on.
Ah! I'm pantsless and I'm shirtless!
That's not good.
No shoes, no shoes, we roll. This is how I roll. No shoes.
I mean, you don't have shoes normally.
No shoes anyway. Yeah, I don't have shoes normally.
I'm safe here.
Feet for free.
Go, go Anya!
Woo!
If you... if we equip the... the enhancement for like with the drop, what was it again, drop bonus?
Uh-huh.
...or something.
Yeah, you know the enhancements?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, if we equip the ones with like drop bonus...
Uh-huh.
...the percentage bonus, you get more money.
Oh...
Yeah.
What is... Oh, golden Yago!
Yago!
Where are the pigs?
They're under me.
They're under you? Upstairs!
Yago, Yago! Yago!
Yago!
Ouch!
I'm pretty...
I don't remember Yago sounding like that.
You know, it would be really funny if they got his like "Sodesune".
Replace the voice. "Sodesune." "Sodesune."
Yeah, I wish, I wish we could have done that. Wait, can you, can you actually do that, I wonder?
Mhm.
Anything is possible in Minecraft.
Yeah, right, exactly.
I also thought the same thing, like, when I first heard golden Yago, I was like...
Hey, what's the chance of this being YAGOO's actual voice?
Voice reveal!
It would have been funny.
Yeah.
So many pigs at your place, why they not come to my place?
Oh, oh, there's one.
Pigs!
They're upstairs mostly.
Mhm, some of them fell down.
They're going for you, I think.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Sorry, I'll be right down.
Okay.
Oh, YAGOO.
Yay!
YAGOO, don't go hikikomori like that, okay?
YAGOO, come back!
I just have to...
No! The pig killed YAGOO! RIP YAGOO.
YAGOO! No!
Revenge for YAGOO! YAGOO!
YAGOO!
19 something to 2026.
I don't know what year YAGOO was born in.
Oh, my shield. RIP.
Ah!
There's a lot of pigs upstairs, by the way, if you need more pig.
Okay. No, they just, they just spawn.
Ah! I need my shield.
YAGOO!
Pigs.
Ora!
3 minutes left.
Oh, perfect time to get rid of all my other coal. As planned...
I shall pay you greatly for your services...
...Sir Anya.
All according to keikaku?
Okay.
Ora!
I'm not hitting them, why?
Ah, ah, oh!
I killed them all, and they all spawn again!
Oh my god, Knight NinoIna, you're as beautiful as the day I remembered you.
Wait, I don't think that's how the saying goes.
As beautiful as... what was it again?
The day...
You're as beautiful as the day I lost you, though.
Yeah, you lost me again.
Oh, I live again! I live, I die, I live again!
Witness me!
This truly was our Re:Zero.
Have pork...
Witness!
That was my ceremony.
Mushroom.
I want this mushroom.
I can't get the mushroom.
The mushrooms?
Upstairs, there's mushrooms. I can't get the mushrooms.
Where are you? Oh, you are at the second floor.
My mushroom...
Stop! Stop bullying me! Stop bullying me!
Don't bully me!
How dare you!
Stop bullying me! Help!
Ora!
Knight NinoIna, help!
Roman, target!
Oh, the pigs love me so much. Oh, I am dead! Ah!
I'll save you!
Pigs! The pigs!
YAGOO, please! YAGOO, where are you?
The archers! The archers!
Please save us!
Ah, 47 seconds!
These archers, you're so annoying.
I mean, they die relatively fast if you crit them, but...
Yeah, they die relatively fast. ...archers are...
But still, archers!
You missed!
I said "you missed" and then... I got squished by the slime. Oh!
Kyuu... go... fu...?
How dare you! I'll avenge you!
The slimes! The slimes! The slimes!
4 seconds!
YAGOO, please! Where...
No!
All our lobby completely...
Time up...
Wow.
So how was that raid, Nino-Ina?
Ah, I got one common...
...enhancement part. Wow.
All right, follow me.
Huh? Okay.
I shall reward you for your services.
Say what?
You may put up something random for 278,940 Yen.
Two hundred...
Exactly.
Oh, is that the money you...
You can buy my books instead! I put some books.
No, no, no, I need this money...
No, I can't put any more stuff...
...'cause I hit the limit of the amount of stuff you can put up.
Okay, I'll buy one of this and then you can put up...
Okay, you can put up 211,264.
No! Buy them instead!
Anya... Ina...
あにゃ、いな。
Anya, Ina.
Hello アキ先輩！ / アキ先輩！
Hello Aki-senpai! / Aki-senpai!
アキ先輩、私の本買いませんか？今売ってるんですけど。
Aki-senpai, won't you buy my book? I'm selling it right now.
本？
A book?
うん。あにゃの本買って？
Yeah. Buy Anya's book?
あにゃの本を...買うとしたら...
If I were to buy Anya's book...
あにゃは、アキが何でもひとつ言うこと聞く券を1000万円で買いませんか？
Anya, would you buy a ticket for Aki to do whatever you say for 10 million yen?
1000万円。何でも。
10 million yen. For anything.
何でもだよ。
She said anything.
リアルのことでいう、何でもひとつ言うこと聞く。
Even in real life, I'll do any one thing you say.
リアルのこともいい？
Even real-life things?
そう。
Yes.
おおお...どうしよういな？いなどうしよう？
Ooo... what should we do, Ina? Ina, what should we do?
1000万円。
10 million yen.
いいじゃない？
Isn't that good?
買っちゃう？
Should I buy it?
買っちゃえ！買っちゃえ！
Buy it! Buy it!
いいじゃない？
Isn't that good?
何でもだよ！
It's for anything!
何でもだよ、あにゃ！何でもって...
It's for anything, Anya! She said anything...
...何でもだよ。
...it's for anything.
1000万円はきついです。すみません、アキ先輩。
10 million yen is a bit much. I'm sorry, Aki-senpai.
あにゃはまだこの世界でトップを取ろうとしている？
Is Anya still aiming to take the top in this world?
え、さすがに無理だと思います。
Eh, I think that's logically impossible.
じゃ、1000万円買ったほうがお得なんじゃない？この...
Then, wouldn't buying it for 10 million yen be a bargain? In this...
ね、いな？
Right, Ina?
ね！
Right!
アキ先輩は狙ってるですか？トップを。
Aki-senpai, are you aiming for the top?
まあまあ、狙ってる。頑張ろうかなって。
Well, I am. I'm thinking of doing my best.
おおお...
Ooo...
なるほど。
I see.
いな、ちなみに、アキせんの何でもひとつ...いなめっちゃ金持ちだから、買ったら、いな？
Ina, by the way, Aki-sen's 'do anything' coupon... Ina, you're super rich, so why don't you buy it, Ina?
いなは...75,912円、だけ。どうですか？
Ina has... only 75,912 Yen. How about that?
7万？
70,000?
7万5千9百12円。
75,912 Yen.
あ、ちょっと7万円では聞けない...いな。
Ah, I can't listen to a request for just 70,000, Ina.
ええ？アキ先輩いいですか？こんなかわいいかわいいいなちゃんのお願いなんですよ。
Eee? Aki-senpai, is that okay? This is a request from the super cute Ina-chan.
いなのことはとってもかわいいし大好きな果んだけど、何でも...
I find Ina super cute and I love her, but doing anything...
そんなにかわいくないですか、アキ先輩？(笑)
Is she not that cute, Aki-senpai?
7万は...
70,000 is...
こんなかわいいかわいいいなのお願い...いいんですか？本当に。
Are you really okay refusing a request from this super cute Ina?
あにゃが1000万円で言うこと聞く券買ううんだったら、いなのお願いも聞いちゃおうかな。
If Anya buys the 10-million-yen 'do anything' coupon, maybe I'll listen to Ina's request.
それだったら...それだったら、500万、500万で済むんじゃないですか？一人。
If that's the case... if that's the case, wouldn't 5 million each make it work?
いや、1000万円からじゃないといけないんですかね？一個の...一個のお願いが1000万円だから。
No, does it have to start from 10 million yen? Because one request is 10 million yen.
ねええ...
Nooo...
...嫌だ。
...I don't want to.
嫌だなの？嫌だ...
You don't want to? You...
買って、買って... / 買ってよ、あにゃ、買って。
Buy it, buy it... / Buy it Anya, buy it.
何でも言うこと聞くよ。肩のマッサージもするよ。
I'll do whatever you say. I'll even give you a shoulder massage.
ええ？
Eh?
せーの、体売ってる！ / アーニャ、悪い日本語覚えちゃダメ。
One, two, she's selling her body! / Anya, you shouldn't learn bad Japanese.
そんな「体売ってる」、ダメなんですよ。
Saying \"selling body\" is a no-no.
体売って...
Selling body...
ダメなんですよ。
You shouldn't say that.
売ってないよ。
I'm not selling it!
なんでも言うこと聞く...
I'll do whatever you say...
おい、1000万で一人にだけ売ろうと思ってないよね？
Hey, you're not planning to sell her to just one person for 10 million, right?
あ、イナ、イナ、イナいない？
Oh, Ina, is Ina here?
イナ？
Ina?
イナ。
Ina.
イナとは、飲み物、いろんな飲み物を一緒に飲みたい共通点があるもんね、イナ。
We both share a love of wanting to drink different kinds of drinks, right, Ina?
はい。
Yes.
ね？
Right?
はい。
Yes.
1回に3種類とか4種類とか、いろんな飲み物を一緒に飲むのが好きだよね。
We love to drink like three or four different kinds of drinks at the same time.
そうですね。
That's right.
うん。
Yeah.
っていう、っていうことで、アキロゼがなんでも好きな飲み物買ってきてあげる。
So, Akirose will buy you whatever drink you like!
イナと会う時は毎回、好きな、その飲み物買ってきてあげる。
Every time we meet, I'll buy you that drink you like.
じゃあ、イナの好きな飲み物は何でしょう？トゥドゥン！
Then, what is Ina's favorite drink? Ta-da!
えーっとね、うわ、何飲んでたっけ？
Let's see... Oh, what was she drinking?
いっぱいあったの覚えてて。うーん。
I remember there were so many... Hmm...
チオビタ！チオビタ！
Tiovita! Tiovita!
No.
チオ... チオビタドリンク。栄養ドリンク。エナジー...
Tio... Tiovita drink? An energy drink... Energy...
ブブー！あー！
Boo-boo! Ah!
チオビタ。チオビタ。チオビタD。
Tiovita... Tiovita... Tiovita D.
私、私、イナ、イナ、私の正解、正解、正解に答えたら1000万くれる？
Ina, Ina, if I get the right answer, will you give me 10 million?
私に1000万くれる？
Will you give me 10 million?
すみません、今日のイナのサービスは終了しました。次の機会にまた会いましょう。
I'm sorry, Ina's service for today has ended. Let's meet again next time.
チオビタ、チオビタ。ドクターペッパー好きそう。
Tiovita, Tiovita... She seems like she'd like Dr Pepper.
あ、わかった。アーニャ、も、も、も。
Oh, I got it. Anya, mo-mo-mo...
絶対チオビタDでしょ？チオビタ。
It's definitely Tiovita D, right? Tiovita.
ブブー。
Boo-boo.
えー。
Ehhh.
え、コーヒー、コーヒー。
Eh, coffee, coffee.
どんなコーヒー？
What kind of coffee?
コーヒー、うーん。
Coffee... Hmm...
カフェオレ。
Cafe au lait.
ラテ、ラテ、ラテ。
Latte, latte, latte.
ブブブブー！
Boo-boo-boo-boo!
残念でした、みんな。
Too bad, everyone.
ブラック！ブラック！
Black! Black!
フラペチーノじゃない？
Isn't it a Frappuccino?
ヨーグルトとブルーベリー。ヨーグルトとブルーベリードリンク。
Yogurt and blueberry. Yogurt and blueberry drink.
いや皆さん、なんでブラックコーヒーがオプションにないんですか？
Wait, everyone, why is black coffee not even in your options?
え！待って、ちょっと待って。本当に思ったんだけど、イナ本当に思ったんだけど。
Wait, hold on. I actually thought of that. Ina, I really thought of that, but...
何でブラック以外の色んなコーヒーが出てたんですけど。
You guys came up with all these other coffees besides black!
いや思った。いやマジでブラックコーヒーね、思ったんだけど、ホロライブ確率的にブラックコーヒー好きな人は少ないから、確率的に。
No, I did. Seriously, I thought of black coffee, but statistically in Hololive, very few people like black coffee.
早口だな。
She's such a fast talker.
だから...
So...
早口。
Fast talker.
だから、マジで！
So, seriously!
I used my brain cell, and then think about the percentage of someone liking a black coffee. And I went for the percentage, or the higher percentage answer.
残念でした。
Too bad.
えー。
Ehhh.
そんな。そんな。
No way. No way.
しくしく。
*sob sob*
次の機会に。
Next time.
うわー！
Waaaaah!
Wait, I must go fulfill my mission.
I will see you at the finals, Anya, soon.
Okay. Bye-bye. / Bye-bye.
時間がない。時間がない。
No time, no time.
は、は、は、どうしよう。どうしよう。ここで、ここでどうしよう。
Ah, what should I do? What should I do? Here, what should I do here?
「発光ってどうすればできるんだっけ？」
\"How do you get glowing?\"
「もう一個、発光を付けたら良くない？」
\"Wouldn't it be better if we added another glowing?\"
あ、これが早い。オッケーオッケー。
Oh, this is faster. Okay, okay.
I just need to get to 50.
How am I going to spend 75,000?
I'm going to leash chickens to the world, I'm sorry. It's the only way.
これ、欲しくないんだ。
I don't want this.
\"Buy something more expensive.\" Oh, right.
Oh, you're right.
光ってる場合じゃない。
This is not the time to be glowing.
Error processing subtitles for this segment.
行動収入プラス ファーマーのショップ売却です
Activity income plus sales from the Farmer Shop.
ファーマーとして一番稼いだ人！
The top earner as a Farmer!
誰だろうね？誰だ誰だ？
Who could it be? Who is it, who is it?
AZKi！え！？おおー！
AZKi! What?! Ohh!
すごい！5,300万！
Amazing! 53 million!
うそだろ？あれ？
No way! Huh?
5,000万超えてる！
Over 50 million!
AZKiちゃんでした。おめでとうございます！
It was AZKi-chan. Congratulations!
すごーい！
Amazing!
そして、ファイターで一番稼いだ人
Next, the top earner as a Fighter.
行動収入とファイターのショップ売却です
Activity income plus sales from the Fighter Shop.
誰だ？誰だろ？
Who is it? Who could it be?
おかゆ！おおー！
Okayu! Ohh!
おかゆも、5,900万！まぁ約6,000万！
Okayu also earned 59 million! So, about 60 million!
稼ぎました！おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
すごーい！ / 2億あった
Amazing! / I had 200 million.
そして、店売りで一番稼いだ人
Next, the person who earned the most from shop sales.
これは、カブとカジノを除く共通ショップ、フリマ等で稼いだ人です
This is the earner from general shops and flea markets, excluding turnips and casinos.
誰だろうね？全然わかんない
Who could it be? I have no idea.
あ、スバル！おおー！
Ah, Subaru! Ohh!
250万！ハチだ！うわ、ハチだ！
2.5 million! It's bees! Wow, bees!
店売り、何売ったっけ？もう記憶ない
Shop sales, what did I sell? I don't remember anymore.
ハチじゃない？ハチか！ハチ売ってくれた
Isn't it bees? Bees! You sold bees.
ハチ？あ、ハチか！
Bees? Ah, bees!
すごーい！250万だ
Amazing! That's 2.5 million.
じゃあ次、最後。一番お金持ってる人です
Next, the last one: the richest player.
こちらは所持金プラス銀行口座ですね。カブ精算した後の値段となります
This is cash on hand plus bank account, after settling turnip stocks.
一番持ってる人！
The one who has the most!
どうだろうね？カブもちょっとここで...
How will it go? Turnips will also be...
え、スバル！やっぱり！
What, Subaru! As expected!
2億5000万！おめでとうございます！
250 million! Congratulations!
カブ！やばすぎだろ！
Turnips! That's insane!
すごい！さすがギャンブラーズワールド
Amazing! As expected of Gambler's World.
おめでとうございます！やばーい！
Congratulations! This is crazy!
大富豪ですね。おめでとうございます
A multi-millionaire indeed. Congratulations.
ということで、まぁ一応ね、あのランキングというよりかは一番稼いだ人、色んな賞ということなんですが
So, this wasn't really a ranking, but rather celebrating the top earners in various categories.
まだまだね、他にもこんなことでも稼いでましたよっていうのは明日の配信で色々発表しますので。はい。
There are still many other ways people earned money, which I will announce during tomorrow's stream.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
はい、今日たくさんいっぱい遊んでいただきありがとうございました。無事10日間ね、はい。
Yes, thank you all so much for playing a lot today. We successfully completed the 10 days.
ありがとうございました！本当に！
Thank you very much, really!
一応ですね、24時以降もミニゲームとかアスレチックやりたい人いると思うので、サーバーオープン長く開いてますので
By the way, since some might want to play mini-games or athletics even after 24:00, the server will remain open for a bit longer.
ぜひみんなでお誘いして遊んでいただけたらなと思います。よろしくお願いします。
Please invite everyone and enjoy playing. Thank you.
あ、そうだ！
Ah, that's right!
何か作ったのがあるから見てほしい。写真撮りましょうか、じゃあ
There's something I made, I want you to see it. Let's take a photo, then.
写真撮っていい？見たい見たい！
Can I take a photo? I want to see! I want to see!
わたちゃんが作ってくれた
Watame-chan made it.
え、すごい！ラーメン！
Oh, amazing! Ramen!
すごーい！ラーメンこんなに飾ってあるの？
Amazing! There's this much ramen on display?
こんなにカブ持ってたの？このラーメンで
Did you have this many turnips? With this ramen
完成してる！ちゃんと揃ってる
It's completed! They are properly lined up.
すごい！すごーい！可愛い！
Amazing! Amazing! Cute!
上から見るのかな？じゃあ写真撮りましょう
Do we look at it from above? Then let's take a photo.
あ、運営さんに写真撮ってもらおうか。運営さんありがとうございます
Ah, let's have the staff take a photo. Thank you so much, staff.
Error processing subtitles for this segment.