(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Wah.
Good...
...morning, afternoon, evening.
It is...
Tako Time.
Wah.
Oh.
I heard you can sell fish now.
Which is good news.
Very good news.
Brilliant news.
Oh! I got a Combat Support Bee 1.
I should have put more bees in yesterday.
Oh, so they... oh!
So I should end the day by adding a lot of honey and stuff in here.
なるほど。
I see.
And now I should be able to... ah...
Ah... All right, all right, let's go buy a whole bunch of honey.
And then we will farm and fish.
どこ行くのころね？
Where are you going, korone?
あははは！
Ahahaha!
お金預けときよ、イナ！お金！
You'd better deposit your money, Ina! Your money!
サンタさん！
Santa-san!
ほーほーほー！
Ho ho ho!
サンタ！
Santa!
ほーほーほー。いい子にしてたかい？
Ho ho ho. Have you been a good girl?
はい！
Yes!
本当にいい子にしてた？
Have you really been a good girl?
はい！
Yes!
プレゼント欲しいね？
You want a present, don't you?
はい！
Yes!
いいよ。じゃ、いい子のイナにはこれをあげようね。
Alright then. I'll give this to you, Ina, since you were a good girl.
やったー！
Yay!
いぇーい！
Thank you, Santa!
Yay!
あははは！喜んでる、喜んでる。
Ahahaha! She's happy, she's happy.
なんかさ、あれじゃない？タコダチあげた方が喜んでくれそうだよね。
Wait, wouldn't she be happier if I gave her a Takodachi?
気合いっぱい！
Full of spirit!
あ...
Ah...
三十。
Thirty.
お。
Oh.
お、宿題。
Oh, homework.
ハチを手に入れる。
Get a bee.
ててーん！
Ta-da!
バイ。小麦...
Bye. Wheat...
え、22円だよ。
Eh, it's 22 yen.
20、20円やん。もう。
Wait, it's 20, 20 yen, jeez.
これとりあえず買いたい。
I want to buy this for now.
パン、パンを売るでしょ？
Bread... selling bread, right?
あ、箱買うでしょ？
Ah, buy a box, right?
はちみつも買っとくでしょ？
Buy honey as well, right?
バレてない。
They haven't noticed.
いいな、忍者。
Ina, ninja...
うわっ！
Uwah!
おはっ、おはようではない。
Morn... it's not morning.
これいいかも。
This might be good.
あ、おっけーおっけーおっけー。
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
17円。
17 yen.
いや、18がよかったかも。Or I should've had 18.
No, maybe 18 was better... Or I should've had 18.
あれ？こんなとこにこれ。
Huh? In a place like this...
あ、りんご is mine, no...
Ah, apple is mine, no...
りんご is mine.
Apple is mine.
Oh, that's right. That's my name, Ina.
That's me, Ina.
Ah, farmer's life for me...
Farmer's life for me...
I thought about it.
And I was like, I need to get a flower.
I had a flower somewhere, right?
Ah, flower.
Ah. That's not a flower?
There you go.
And then, do this...
Aha! There we go.
Farmer's life for me...
今日はですね、BGMをちょっと...
Today, I prepared...
用意しました。
...some BGM.
I got BGM today.
Because I read comments...
...saying my stream is kind of a different genre...
...than everyone else.
So I was like, "Hmm..."
I should just...
...lean into that.
So...
...it is now...
...a slow life stream.
Isn't it nice?
When the whole world is busy trying to earn the most money...
To try and...
...live the most slow life ever?
I think that's an ideal life.
I need an axe.
Oh, let's get more sugar, too.
That's also just life, you know?
You just gotta chill somewhere.
I should also put this shulker down.
Okay. One goal I do have today...
...is to find some chickens.
And to do that, I do need some wheat.
Chickens like wheat, right?
おお。
Oh.
Axe, axe, axe, axe...
Axe.
Na, na, na... I was thinking maybe I should like...
...fence off the farm so that the monsters won't come in and ruin it again.
Oh, the seeds, not the actual wheat? Oh, right, right!
Seeds. They do love seeds.
Where would I find the chickens though? I've seen a lot of sheep, I've seen some cows,
I've seen some pigs. I haven't seen chickens, I think.
Yeah, there are monsters.
Yeah, I do have some.
I guess I'll put it here.
We'll adventure a little bit. Did I make a shield?
I did not. Ah, it's fine.
It's still daytime. We have plenty of time.
We have, we have, we have a combat support bee.
Surely it can help us somehow.
Chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken...
Chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken...
Chicken, chicken, chicken...
Ah, mushroom!
Mushroom!
Mushroom.
Chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken...
Chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken...
Ah, mushroom!
Mushroom, mushroom, mushroom, mushroom.
Where are all the chickens at?
I guess they... chicken'd out. Ahahaha!
I guess I have to go to plains.
This is not plains.
Chicken, chicken, chicken...
Chicken.
Chi-chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken...
Oh, water.
Chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken...
Listen closely, guys. You gotta hear the go-go-go... go-go-go...
Open your ears.
Chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken...
Chicken, chicken, chicken...
Ah! Chicken!
Chicken, chicken...
Come on. Let's go home.
Ah! Chicken!
Come on.
Chicken. Oh.
Is someone living here? Or at least they...
At least they put all the... Ah! Chicken, chicken!
Please, please, follow me, follow me.
Premium feed.
Waiting for you.
Whose house is this?
Where am I?
It's someone's house.
Alright, chicken.
ココココ...
Cluck cluck...
Chicken!
来い。
Come here.
迷ってないし。
I'm not lost or anything.
Chicken, look at me.
Oh, this way, this way, this way. I see the buildings.
Come on.
コトコ... あ、こっちか。
Cluck cluck... Ah, this way?
こっちかな？ こっちじゃない？
Is it this way? Isn't it this way?
まあいつか行けるでしょ。
Well, we'll get there eventually.
Hey hey hey hey hey. Attention, attention please.
待って、大金を手にする... あ。
Wait, getting a lot of money... oh.
イナちゃん可愛いことしてるね。
Ina-chan, you're doing something cute.
ねねちー。
Nenechii.
ファーマーだもんね。パンいっぱい？
You're a farmer, right? Lots of bread?
うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah.
たまご欲しい？
Do you want eggs?
かわいい。
Cute.
どこまで、どこまで連れて行くん？
How far, how far are you taking them?
どこ？ 家どこ？ あ、あっちか。
Where? Where is the house? Ah, over there.
Come on.
That's right.
Yes, yes. Follow me.
Follow me.
ハロー！ ハロー！
Hello! Hello!
喋ってる！
It's talking!
喋って... いやいやいや。
Talking... No, no, no.
喋ってねーよ！
I'm not talking!
あ、スバルさん！ あー！
Ah, Subaru-san! Ah!
喋ってねーよ！ハローとか言ってねーよ！
I'm not talking! I didn't say hello!
ねぽらぼの鳥、鳥になったと思ったら、あ...
I thought Nepolabo's bird actually became a bird, ah...
何やねんその鳥って！
What do you mean by that bird?!
どっちが、どっちが本物のスバル先輩？
Which one, which one is the real Subaru-senpai?
声とかねえから！ どっちがとか！
There's no voice! What do you mean, which one!
右か左か？
Right or left?
あ、どっちかな？
Ah, which one is it?
もう確保してるの、偽スバル。
We've already captured the fake Subaru.
いやいやいやいや。
No, no, no, no.
ねぽらぼ、あ、どうしようか？ 蜂、蜂優先か？ 一端。
Nepolabo... Ah, what should we do? Prioritize bees? For now.
よし、よし。
Alright, alright.
Buy two get one free?
ここ合体させてもいいのか？
Is it okay if we combine these?
じゃあ、こう、こうして...
Let's do this, like this...
あ、にわとり２匹いる。どこからか連れてきて...
Ah, there are two chickens. Bring them from somewhere...
あ、おいでよー
Ah, come here~
あ、夜になっていく。やばい。
Ah, it's becoming night. Oh no.
いや、まずは家の中に、行こうかな。
Actually, maybe I should go inside the house first.
外は危ないから、まだ何も作ってないし。
It's dangerous outside, and I haven't made anything yet.
I haven't made anything yet, so I think it's the safest for the chickens to stay in the house.
あっ！
Ah!
はい、来い。
Okay, come.
来い。
Come.
はぁ、はぁ、はぁ、はぁ、やった。
Haa, haa, haa, haa, I did it.
Make baby. Nice.
Nice.
Do I have wood? Should I make some fences? I think I should make some fences.
Maybe a fence gate.
They can't jump over this, right?
I think.
Oh, you can't jump over it?
Okay, that's good. That's good. That's good news.
They can?
Oh, from the box.
Maybe I can put a slab?
And then...
This way they can't get on it, right?
Right?
Okay. Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, I could also dig down one.
Tiny one might break out?
I guess we're digging down.
Alright, now they can't escape.
Right?
Okay, good.
And then...
I can go like this.
Yeah.
Wait, I have two eggs. I have the ingredients.
I can totally make some pumpkin pie right now.
I can totally make pumpkin pie right now.
I have sugar. I just need pumpkin.
Oh, I can.
I made two.
Oh, the bees.
Sorry, chicken. It's dangerous outside.
And then maybe we can make a proper place for my animals.
Ah, more bees.
Ah, Farmer Support Bee?
Oh, I can do this.
Conduit power...
Speed, jump boost.
Super rare!
I don't know what the jump boost does though.
Oh, what happened here?
Did I forget to plant it?
Woah! The speed!
はやい！
So fast!
Woah!
Ooooh.
Power!
I suddenly have so much in my hands.
Why can't I hold all these carrots?
Uh... Uh...
Here.
And then...
Hehehehe.
I guess you can't really sell pumpkins as is.
You always have to make them into pumpkin pie.
Oh! Oh!
Some of the pumpkin is missing.
What happened?
Oh, it was my mistake.
Wait, where is the... did it break? The hoe?
Oh.
My crops...
Oh, it's in my left hand! Hahaha.
なるほど。
I see.
Uh... Uh...
There's too many!
No! Stop growing! I'm trying to plant here.
There you go.
Okay...
All good, all good.
We got to work on fencing...
And feeding...
...feeding the chickens.
Ah, multitasking.
I'm so weak.
Hah!
So many pumpkins!
Okay, okay, okay, okay...
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
Okay, where are the seeds?
Okay, it's okay.
They can stack, so it's not a problem.
Chickens!
Ah! Egg!
Make baby.
Nice.
Eat, eat, grow. Produce egg.
Pumpkin... I have sugar. Where is pumpkin?
Ah, three!
They need more space? No.
Do they? No.
No.
Good thing there are no animal living conditions... regulations.
They have so much space! They're fine.
There are so many random things in my backpack.
Mushroom! I can put the mushroom in here.
You know, some family bonding time. It's fine.
But I just wonder if there's just...
...so many pumpkins, but not enough egg.
Mm-mm-mm...
I wonder... I wonder...
We are almost full on this.
We do have to go to town sometime.
We would like to have more bee breeding things.
I wonder...
Oh, egg! Eat, eat, grow!
We're fine, we're fine.
Coz you can sell extra bees as well.
It's just, they have a time limit to how... how long it takes for them to breed, so...
I mean, they did add new things you can sell, so maybe I can go check that out.
Like, other than the fish, what is there?
Ah... peaceful life.
Seeds in here, carrots in here...
...this in here.
Oh, almost done.
Can you eat yet? Oh, another egg! Yes, two eggs!
And we can sell the pumpkin pie, our first pie sale!
Eat, eat, grow!
It's honest work.
Wait, I got another one? Okay, I can make one more pie.
Five pies.
Farm support bee... Farm money boost? Another super rare!
Let's go!
Yes, breed, breed.
Okay, I just want to see if that one... one other chicken also grew up yet. Not yet?
Nice.
Grow up soon. Make egg.
All right, we need a chest.
Is this one... Okay.
I mean... Hold on, let me catch a little more fish to see what we can sell.
Maybe there's more things we can sell.
Can you breed the super rares together?
We could. Probably.
But right now I don't have any bees.
Like, I want enough bees to fill up all my slots, and then start breeding extra super rare ones.
Right?
まず...
First...
ハチを...
The bees...
いっぱい...
many...
作って、
I'll make, and
後でレアリティをアップする感じ。
later upgrade their rarity.
Get lots of bees first, and then go for...
super rare or rarer... not fish, bees! Sorry, only thinking about fish.
Okay.
I mean, we might as well wait until the next batch of carrots, and then go.
Mm, so peaceful.
Salmon.
Maybe I'll have some sushi tomorrow. Salmon sushi, mm.
Yeah, I think I'll do that.
Are we done?
Ah, just a little more.
I mean, the wheat is almost done too.
Oh, someone making a base there?
Could it be the BauBaus?
The wheat is almost done.
Oh yeah, I do want to get one Takodachi from... was it the Land Vegas?
They have it.
タコダチ欲しい。
I want a Takodachi.
Need to gamble for it?
Oh!
Aw, it's just a normal fishing rod.
Okay, there's still time on the wheat.
Yeah...
ころねそ...
Korone-so...
Salmon.
Oh, I did get a bow. And I have three arrows. Oh.
Oh! I heard it! The egg!
たまご聞こえた。
I heard an egg.
たまご。
Egg.
One たまご。
One egg.
More chicken.
Okay.
One pumpkin pie, please!
Yay!
I'll be back, my dear chickens.
Oh, I heard it again!
Sound of egg.
すばらしい。
Wonderful.
Pumpkin, pumpkin.
Ah, the slow life is amazing. I like this.
One bee, two bee...
One bee, two bee.
Okay.
Time for the harvest after I put my fish in.
ふぐ。
Pufferfish.
Okay.
Am I getting more money per harvest? I should, cause I have the special bee.
I want to get like a legendary bee.
Oh, I am getting a lot per harvest.
The bees have special skills that you can breed.
Like for example, I have speed, jump boost, and a farming money boost level two.
So technically...
if...
I get a lot of farming money boosts, that means harvesting will just get me a lot of money.
Maybe I'll put these in here.
The red one will be my fishing box.
ほい。
There we go.
So many pumpkins.
Okay...
Okay, we have pumpkin pie to sell...
And then we have...
...this entire box to sell. Okay.
This one should be done by the time we come... Oh.
This one grew faster than I thought.
Then we can check for more eggs. Ah, the cycle.
It's so fast!
Perhaps some eggs? No?
Okay, it's fine, it's fine. I'll come back for you.
I should maybe create a better path to the town. It's a bit far.
Ah, 77k.
They let us sell everything.
一応あのハチがね２万5000円で買いたいんだよ。一応2万5000円を...
Actually, I want to buy those bees for 25,000 Yen. At least for 25,000...
Wait, cooked fish...
I could just cook the fish and all of a sudden it becomes more expensive? I should cook the fish.
Okay.
And then...
Okay, let me sell...
...this first.
まぁでもネザーゲート自体入れづらいんだよ。
Well, but the Nether Gate itself is hard to enter.
Is making bread out of the wheat a... profit?
マイクラ...お城が設置してあるやつはだるいんですけど...
Minecraft... The ones with the castles set up are annoying, but...
There's three... Bread is the worst? Yeah, it takes three wheat per bread.
It's worth it now? Hold on, let me see how much.
Cuz it's 20 per wheat...
Nah, it's not worth it. Just sell the wheat.
Okay, wheat first.
Cooked potato... actually baked potato might be good to cook.
You know if we can find... I mean we know where to get lava, there was a whole bunch of them...
...in the darkness!
なんてこった、もったいねえ！足がないっ！
Oh my gosh, what a waste! I have no legs!
And then if we can find potato somewhere...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! 110k!
鉄を探すんだ！
I'm going to search for iron!
110k. If we focus on bees...
どうも。今日も暗い？
Hello. Is it dark today too?
今日は...大丈夫です。大丈夫？
Today... I'm fine. You're okay?
まだ行ってないんです、暗いところに。
I haven't gone yet, to the dark place.
ほんと？行けない？ / 行ってないんです、まだ。 / ほんと？まだちょっと様子見に行くね。
Really? You can't go? / I haven't gone yet. / Really? I'll go check it out for a bit then.
はい、はい。はい。
Okay, okay. Yes.
いや、でも今日行くのはとても...
Yeah, but going today is very...
Ah, buy container.
Yesterday we went when zombies and stuff didn't spawn, so...
Today if we go...
it might be bad.
Should I get more bees?
Ah, more stonks actually. Yeah, you're right.
What was it, Nepolabo?
Nepolabo HD...
13...
Here, I can buy 2,000.
Okay.
Hmm.
It can only go up, I hope.
Okay, crops should be grown now.
Yeah.
I don't have any flint.
Oh, not flint. Coal.
Two eggs! Two eggs!
Yes, yes, yes...
Many eggs. Oh, one more!
In that short time span?
Oh, maybe I just didn't make both.
I just wanted to be hopeful that the eggs...
eggs would appear more often.
What was the homework again?
I think we have to go get...
Wait, does this mean it's already done?
The yellow highlighted?
Oh, chicken, egg.
Mmm...
Oh, so this is... archaeological materials?
So I have to go to the brush thing?
Have to go buy a brush?
Oh! Another egg! Yes, yes!
All right, you guys keep doing that.
Oh, slow falling.
I'll just slot you in for now.
Oh, three bees! Oh, maybe we need to get more...
more honey.
Because even if we get like less rare bees, we can sell it.
They do go for like 2,000, or like 500 and stuff.
ね、ね、ねね、ねね。
Ne, ne, nene, nene.
It's a mystery...
あ、ななな...
Ah, na na na...
うわ！ふふふ...
Whoa! *laughs*
コードが壊れてる！
The code is broken!
なんかサンタの声が聞こえた気がする。
I feel like I heard Santa's voice.
Maybe I should invest in a diamond pickaxe. Or diamond axe, so it lasts a little longer.
な、なな、な。
Na, nana, na.
I guess the goal is to get a bee that gives me as much... Ah!
...farming money as possible.
All right, I'll be back for these pumpkins.
ん、な、なな。
Mhm, na, nana.
Got so many pumpkins.
Oh, birch sapling.
な、なな、な。
Na, nana, na.
All right, any eggs? Oh, yes!
I don't know...
...for the number of family members here, there seems to be a lack of eggs. Please...
Look at all those chickens.
へへへ...
*giggles*
Pie...
Grow faster. Grow faster.
Produce eggs.
Where'd the string come from?
ん、うーん...
Mhm, hmmm...
We can sell these, actually, can't we?
ふふ... Trying to be frugal here.
*giggles* Trying to be frugal here.
Okay, we're gonna get a diamond axe, we'll grab one of those archaeological... oh...
It's fine, I get it. You guys are a little shy to egg when I'm around.
But I heard it. I heard you loud and clear. Okay.
ね、ねね、ね。
Ne, nene, ne.
Okay, we'll get one of the brushes, and we'll get a diamond axe.
And then... so... then...
Oh, slow falling. Whee! Whee!
カブ、カブ。 カブ。
Turnip, turnip. Turnip.
これもしかして、今アルケミストと...
Is this perhaps, right now with the Alchemist...
ネコラボホールディングスする？
Are we doing Nekolabo Holdings?
どうする、みんな？ 買っちゃったからな、４万持ってる。
What should we do, everyone? Since I bought it, I have 40,000.
ノーマルはこれから出てくるし。 今日は合計６千万売買できるよね。
Normal ones will appear from now on. Today we can trade a total of 60 million, right.
お、みこち、どこ行くの？
Oh, Mikochi, where are you going?
カブなう！
Turnip now!
Wait, wasn't cake...?
Oh... oh...
I don't need pumpkin for cake.
Brush, brush.
おら！カブの時間や！カブや！
Hey! It's turnip time! Turnips!
20,000... たかい。
20,000... That's expensive.
But it does last a long time.
あったー！ | いえーい！
Found it! | Yay!
ドロボウ建設... | 確かに、確かに。 | やめてね。
Robber Construction... | True, true. | Please don't.
Dorobou Construction...
Robber Construction...
おー！ハラサキさん！ | 34！
Oh! Harasaki-san! | 34!
ハチカ？ | んな建設！
Hachika? | What kind of construction is that?!
I wonder if I can go find some watermelon.
お！プラス100%！ | おー！
Oh! Plus 100%! | Oh!
90円。 | でも割れてんだよな。
90 yen. | But it's split.
全部割れてんだな。
They're all split.
We do have stocks. Why doesn't it show up in...
...in the chat?
Please, please, please. Please, please.
My stocks... my stocks...
No, we hold! We hold!
Yeah, 100%...
...だってもう...
...because...
え？らーめん？
Eh? Ramen?
どこから来た？このらーめん。
Where did this ramen come from?
Ah! Eggs!
らーめん、らーめん...
Ramen, ramen...
いや、なんかお腹空いた。
Yeah, I'm kind of hungry.
お腹空いた。
I'm hungry.
ご飯食べるの忘れた。
I forgot to eat food.
らーめん、らーめん...
Ramen, ramen...
Oh, we need more bees. Soon, soon.
Oh right, I forgot to buy honey.
Oh! Speed!
It would be nice to find some watermelons.
'Cause the melons grow so fast, and then you can get melon slices.
I can replace the pumpkin with melon.
But where would I find melon?
Where would I find a melon?
Jungle?
Is there a jungle nearby? It would be nice.
And then... this...
Ha! Two eggs. Only two?
Grow faster, children.
I don't think they sell melon, no?
Uh! Farm Money Boost! Yes! Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, another.
Okay, buy more honey.
How much honey should I buy? Like 20? 40?
But the boss... the boss is pretty easy.
Okay, like, yeah, we have the shoes now.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! You guys are so strong!
Look at you! Look at you with your diamond... with your diamond shoes!
He has the same outfit!
Oh! It's matching! Matching!
Matching shoes!
Matching shoes?
Eh? Wait, Anya matches too!
Matches! Matching!
Matching shoes!
Oh, this is so romantic.
Ina, have you went to the dungeons or Nazotoki?
Oh, not today.
Oh... Oh, what you're doing today?
Farming.
Farming?! Oh...
You're so dedicated!
Yeah. I adore you!
Maybe, maybe you can spare a few bees?
A bee or two?
Um, not on me, though, unfortunately.
Oh! You don't have any bees on you right now?
Wait, how do you sell stuff?
I have this, though. It's Koronesuki, right?
From Santa.
Whoa! Yellow also looks like... wait, you have that?
Yeah!
Wait, you too? You too, Mococo?
Really?!
We also both have Koronesuki!
Oh! How? How did you get it?
Can you...?
You can get rid of the Koronesuki?
I can also sell my Koronesuki for 1,000,000,000 Yen!
Wait, did you guys get a Takodachi?
Not yet.
Oh... Can you sell the Koronesuki for it?
I didn't... I didn't get it.
I got that from Santa for being a good kid.
Oh...
Oh, and you're gonna sell it away?
You're passing on the Christmas magic to us?
Of course, of course!
Spread the joy.
Joy to the world!
Koronesuki to the world!
Yeah!
Ah, can we do it? Can we sell the Koronesuki?
Don't sell it! That was a present!
Oh, don't sell? Oh...
Let's go, Mococo.
Where do you even use the brush? Do you use it on like sand?
Is that where you use it?
にゃにゃにゃにゃにゃ〜
Nya nya nya nya nya~
Sand or gravel?
Oh, we have some sand.
Any chick- Any eggs?
No eggs?
Ah! No! No! No!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Don't escape! Come back, I have seeds.
What happened? How did they escape?
Is there too many of them?
What happened?
やばい、やばい。
Oh boy. Oh boy.
Alright, that should be good enough for now.
Phew.
That was close.
I mean, we can dig on the ground and make a coop under- under- underground.
That's an option.
Maybe they are not happy with their working conditions.
An honest farming here.
Phew.
Man, life is tough.
Where are they gonna start a union? Hope not!
I wonder what other skills...
Forgot some spots.
...what other skills the bees have?
うーん…
Mmm...
Okay.
Maybe go search for a jungle?
Ah...
Maybe...
I think we'll find some sand and stuff...
...and do the alchemy.
There's a little bit of sand over there.
Any eggs?
One?
One single egg amongst all of you?!
One single egg?
You're slacking.
Get two, three, four... Oh! Oh! Oh!
Now we're talking.
Now we're talking here.
All right, all right.
One more? Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, I just don't have sugar. That's fine.
All right, all right.
狭い...
It's cramped...
Well, well, well, working conditions, huh?
Working conditions, huh?
Oh, I guess I already have... I can break this shovel.
Please, please, no pushing, no pushing.
Trying to help us all here, okay?
狭い...
It's cramped...
Oh, please, oh, please.
I'm trying to do you a favor here.
Ah! Sorry!
All right, all right.
Yeah, leave that one.
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me!
Excuse me, please get off the platform.
Excuse me, off the platform, please.
Off the platform!
There we go. Ah, some peace.
Oh, some eggs over there. I see it, I see it.
I'm trying to help you guys here, okay?
So you can live...
...in a more broader space.
Oh, there's a hole there.
I need more wood. I guess I can use this.
Maybe I should make ladders?
Kind of efficient, though, but...
Oh, now you start laying more eggs.
Maybe it was a problem.
Maybe they did need more space...
...and a better working condition.
I hope this is to your liking, chickens.
Very cozy, thank you.
Yes, yes.
Nine eggs.
I see an increase in production.
I shall return again for a better yield...
...next time.
Oh.
Excuse me, you're not supposed to be here.
Maybe a trapdoor is...
...needed.
For extra protection.
Ah.
I didn't know they could climb ladders.
Are they that smart?
Ah, the pie production has increased...
...a lot, which is great news.
Great, great news.
Triple security.
No chicken shall escape.
Ooh, combat bee. I don't really need that.
Okay, maybe we'll buy another...
...bee...
...thing... breeding.
I'll sell this bee and then...
...buy another breeding thing.
Yes.
And then, once I get a little more super rare bees, I'll breed those.
If we can have one of the breeders be the super rare breeding one...
...and Alchemist higher level, skills maybe?
Okay.
I wanna eat ramen.
Mmm, delicious.
Oh, I got two gold hearts.
I still got to dust some of the sand blocks.
So we must breed the bees first. Wait, actually...
...I guess it's a common bee. Oh, wait, I forgot to sell the bee. Oh, it's alright, it's okay, it's okay.
One... one extra bee.
Can I place it on top? Oh, I can't.
Let me try it on a normal sand block here, though.
Ah!
Mmh, mmh.
[考古学者(ブラシ)が開放。アルケミストLv.3以上が必要]
[Archaeology (brush) unlocks at Alchemist Lv 3 or higher]
Alchemist level 3 or higher!
Suspicious sand or gravel.
I mean, I can re-spec once.
But hey.
I didn't use my level-up ones today, so I could put it into Alchemist.
Whoa...
Mmm...
Yeah, reset is once a day.
So... arena?
Special mission: Monster Hunter. Okay, okay.
Ah, bee slots. That's true.
Oh.
So many Skill Manuals.
Hold on, let me look at the manual here.
えーっと...
Let me see...
I can read.
I think the max points do increase...
...yeah, it increases tomorrow.
I mean, it doesn't...
I think you can still do the daily quests the day after, so maybe I'll wait.
So maybe I'll wait.
Healing power of friendship.
明日やろう。
I'll do it tomorrow.
ばうばう！
Bau bau!
ころね先輩が元の、いつものボリュームになってる。
Korone-senpai's volume is back to normal.
ばうばう！ばいばーい！
Bau bau! Bye-bye!
Mmm...
まだある！パンがいっぱいだ！
There's still more! I have so much bread!
Oh, we have pie.
収穫、じゃなくて...
Harvesting... wait, no...
Two thousand!
あれ？
Huh?
ビーツってどこにあるんだろう？
Where are the beetroots?
Beetroot...
あれ？骨粉...
Wait, bone meal...
106かな？
Maybe 106?
10...
あ、すごい！めっちゃ稼げるやん！
Wow, awesome! You can make so much money!
骨粉のやつ消えとるねこれね。あれ？
The bone meal one is gone, isn't it? Huh?
骨粉のは？
What about the bone meal?
骨粉、何個いる？
How many bone meals do you need?
周回用じゃなくて...
Not for farming...
Since we're here, though...
Maybe we can go see what's up here, in this mysterious building.
Oh, slow falling.
Ow, my damage.
Oh...
Do, do, do...
Medal...
Oh!
Takodachis!
Medal...
1,000... How many can I get?
Mascot...
Two big...
Two big medals.
100 Wata Medal.
We need medals to play the games, I'm assuming. Hold on. Instructions...
Press T, place your bet...
Ah, I see, I see, I see.
Win 405.
や、やって...
Well, I'll...
やってみる。やってみる。
I'll try it. I'll try it.
Lose... Lose...
What does it mean?
Win 3,888.
Is that the last person... what they won?
Oh.
Wata Medal...
I have to change to gambler?
Oh.
One.
Four.
Higher.
Ah!
Yes.
Oh.
Low.
Ah!
Yes.
Ah...
Now I have eight.
Coins...
One.
Low.
What are the chances?
One.
Low.
Yes.
High.
Low.
Nine... All in!
High.
Takodachis...
Wait for me, Takodachis.
I must go before the eggs... eggs... they're gonna disappear.
Takodachis, wait for me...
Wait for me...
Takodachis...
It's okay, we will... we will get you home.
All right.
Eggs...
One egg...
One egg!
There's no way, in less than 5 minutes.
Oh, eggs!
You guys are so good before, what happened?
All these chickens and one single egg?
Two eggs.
Where did the dead bush come from?
I don't know if I should increase the number of chickens that much.
Dolphin's Grace.
Ah! More money boost! Yes!
Hmm, which one do I replace?
Are these common ones, right?
I mean, I'll save the rare one.
Slow falling?
But speed is okay.
You need to be nearby for the extra spawn?
I did hear the eggs now.
Like two more.
Oh, three more.
Well, I guess I just have to be a bit closer, huh?
Oh, yes!
Yes!
Maybe funnels are okay, or the...
What's that thing called?
The thing that collects eggs.
Hoppers.
Let me re-read the rules.
Yeah, I need to go get a lot of iron then. There's not really...
...iron, unless I go get it myself.
Oh! I can buy iron?
Okay, I don't think I need any more chickens, to be honest.
I don't want to lag the server.
Pumpkin...
I mean, I think my farm is close enough for the eggs to spawn.
I just have to spend a lot more time near my farm.
I'll put the extra bees in here.
Nyan, nyan, nyan, nyan, nyan, nyan, nyan...
Yeah, I think the town is a little too far for eggs to spawn.
Oh, bees!
Nyan, nyan...
Also makes me curious, how much can I actually make by just doing...
...farming and fishing.
And breeding of bees.
I think if I can get
one more breeder, we can dedicate that one to be breeding like the rare bees, see...
...to see what it does.
It needs higher skills.
Nya.
Nya nya nya nya nya nya.
I do wish there was a way to sell these pumpkins...
...other than just, just pumpkin pie.
A pie stand.
Hehe!
Yeah, it would be nice if I could find melons.
But to go on an adventure to get melons is another...
...another problem.
Oh, here's lots of eggs though, actually.
Ten.
Eleven.
Now we're talking!
No, you can't sell raw pumpkin. That would be nice, but...
...you cannot.
It's like, the thing I'm worried about with hoppers though is...
...the fact that...
I guess it might be a bit different because, um, like the bees, the ones that I left in the...
I want that one. In the... the hive and stuff, they were done when I came back, which...
...I'm not too sure...
...if that's intended or not.
I'm getting a lot of eggs though. More improvement.
Yes! Yes! Help me KFP!
We will show them how much money slow life can make.
Oh, another one.
Yes, with your cooperation...
...we will make lots of pie.
That's a lot of pie.
See, by the time we're done with the pies, now we're back here.
And everything's grown.
So we harvest.
And then we gather the eggs.
And then we make the pie.
And then we harvest.
We gather the eggs...
...and then we make pie.
Rinse and repeat.
Oh, did I... did I make wheat for all of this? Oops!
Forgot about the carrots.
Oh, we do have to make a trip to...
Maybe we'll do all carrots for one.
Oh, it's just not grown yet.
All carrots.
Let me check the bees.
Ooh, Haste... it's just a rare, though.
Ah... oh, glowing.
Speed, conduit power, glowing. What does glowing do?
Maybe I can replace one.
It makes you glow, that's it? Haha.
I mean, this one also has glowing.
Haste, Jump Boost.
Oh, I hear you, I hear you.
Maybe I'll start selling the common ones.
Keep the rares for now.
Grab egg.
Ten eggs.
Lovely, lovely.
Ah, another.
All right, all right.
Oh, another! Please lay eggs when I'm down there.
Pie... Oh, 45 pies.
Oh, and another.
And another!
Ooh, I feel I'm going a little crazy with all these chicken noises.
Ah, busy life.
Okay, I think we should go...
...go to town and sell.
I'll put this here. Sell the bees. Okay, okay.
Ah... ah, what a life.
Ooh.
High jumps.
Whee!
This wasn't the slow life I imagined.
I'm still very hungry.
パン売れる？
Can I sell bread?
100、200... ちょっと計算できない。300くらい。
100, 200... I can't calculate it. Around 300.
おおー！
Ooh!
パン要るのでは？
Don't we need bread?
美味しいパン... I haven't had bread in a while.
Delicious bread... I haven't had bread in a while.
Okay, sell all the carrots first.
ただいま。
I'm back!
このゴミどうしたら...
What should I do with this trash...
あ！イナちゃんだ！
Ah! It's Ina-chan!
あ、どうも。
Ah, hello.
タカミンはフリマでハチ売ったりしてる？ - いや、まだ...
Is Takamin selling bees at the flea market? - No, not yet...
どうなんだろうね。フリマ見るかな、みんな。
I wonder. Does everyone check the flea market?
結構なんかハチ2万5千円とかで売ってる人いたけどね。
Though there was someone selling bees for like 25,000 yen.
ね。
Right?
And wheat...
普通に売っちゃおうかな... 養蜂箱買って...
Maybe I should just sell them normally... Buy a beehive...
あ、ビビちゃん！ - はい！
Ah, Vivi-chan! - Yes!
ビビちゃん、フリマでハチ売ったりしてる？
Vivi-chan, are you selling bees at the flea market?
フリマでハチ売ってない。 - 売れるかな...
I'm not selling bees at the flea market. - I wonder if they'll sell...
すうごいファーマーの人たちだ。
What an amazing group of farmers.
そうそう... ハチをね...
That's right... The bees...
フリマで売るか、こっちで売るかどっちの方がいいんだろうって...
We're asking whether it's better to sell them at the flea market or here...
いやでもフリマちょっと買ってくれる人いなくないですか？
But aren't there not many people buying at the flea market?
そうなんです。
That's true.
あとハチが2万5千円とかで売れて...売れてて。
Also, bees are selling for like 25,000 yen...
2万5千円... 高いな。
25,000 yen... That's expensive.
Maybe I should leave some in the bank, cause what if I die, I will lose half of my money.
あ！え？え？なに？なに？
Ah! Eh? Eh? What? What?
Raid?
行こうよ！みこもまださん... ずっともう養蜂とさハチやってるんだけどこっちとらは。
Let's go! I've been doing beekeeping and bees this whole time over here.
I need to go buy... I need to buy a shield.
I don't wanna die.
ぷらぶるで... ぷらぶるいっぱい買っちゃったよ。
At Puraburu... I bought a lot of Puraburu.
いないいない、いいな... いないいないいいな... - AZKiちゃん。
Ina is not here, how nice... Ina is not here, how nice... - AZKi-chan.
AZKi-senpai is dangerous. The raid is coming.
来とる来とる！
It's coming, it's coming!
Raid? Raid?
Anya?
Is that... Anya?
Yeah, you see... you see the ominous...?
Yeah.
Can I hit you?
I know what's about to happen.
You're a fighter, right? Protect me! Protect this... weak farmer!
Who's weak? Look at you, fully geared.
No, I'm so weak.
No, you're not.
I'm so weak.
You're the legendary... legendary farmer, Ina... Ina, I've been your fan.
I'm a huge fan!
Yeah, I'm a huge fan of you.
Aww...
How do you... how do you keep yourself so dedicated to your farming?
Well... well...
Well, I do have a whole song about farming.
Oh?
Because farming is all about bees, right?
Yeah.
And then I have a song that goes "Ichi hachi..."
So, you know... to be a dedicated farmer, you need to have an entire original song dedicated to farming.
I want to be like you. How can I be like you?
Well, you can start by becoming a farmer, but fighter... fighter is good too. I had my origins as a fighter, as well.
What do I need to be a farmer like you?
Oh, you just need...
One hoe, and a dream. And maybe a seed.
Oh...
What do you... what do you do farming? I mean, obviously you guys farm, but like, is there like a place where you guys farm?
You just farm. Like Minecraft.
Yeah, where do you... where do you do it?
Just outside the town, anywhere. Anywhere. You can start anywhere.
Even if you have a tragic past, you can... you can set all that aside and you can have a new start in the farm.
Oh my god, you're right. You're right. Oh my god, eight seconds left!
The raid!
Protect me, Anya! Anya! Anya! I'm scared! I'm scared!
え、なにこれ？！
Wait, what's that?!
ハトタウルスが来た！
The Hatotaur is here!
怖い、怖い！
Scary, scary!
ラーメン食べるのがいい
It's better to eat ramen.
おらおらおらおら！いけそういけそう！
Ora ora ora ora! Looks like we can do it!
おらおらおらおら！
Ora ora ora ora!
おいおいおいおいおい！
Oi oi oi oi oi!
おいおいおいおい！
Oi oi oi oi!
ええええ？
Ehhhh?
フレンドリーファイアあります？
Is there friendly fire?
やばい！
Oh no!
フレンドリーファイア...
Friendly fire...
It's friendly fire!
ひっせー！
Watch out!
ファイターの一撃で誰かを殺害する可能性がある
There's a chance a Fighter's blow might kill someone.
おら！おら！
Ora! Ora!
痛い痛い痛い！
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
人殺しそうだよね
Seems like they're gonna kill someone.
あー！
Aaah!
味方、最悪だけど殴りやすいな
Teammates are the worst, but they're easy to hit.
おいおい！
Oi oi!
おら！
Ora!
おらおら！
Ora ora!
やばい、動けん
Oh no, I can't move!
Probably shouldn't have potato salad.
Yeah, we got an onigiri and about 5 different bread.
Some of us are just laughing and getting hit...
...by the members more than the boss!
おお！
Oooh!
踊り上手！
Good dancer!
何、何、何？
What, what, what?
狙われてる、動けた！
I'm targeted, I can move!
死んじゃう、死んじゃう
I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die!
面白いから
Because it's funny.
命が！うっせぇ！
My life! Shut up!
おっ、命が、命が...
Oh, my life, my life...
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Hang in there, hang in there!
ファイターの人倒したら、めっちゃもらえるの？
If we defeat the Fighter, do we get a lot?
ファイターの人、えい！えい！
Fighter, take this! Take this!
おらおらおらおら！
Ora ora ora ora!
やばいやばいやばい！
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
頑張れ！死んじゃう！
Hang in there, I'm gonna die!
おおおー！
Oooooh!
よいしょ！おらおらおらおら！
Heave-ho! Ora ora ora ora!
もうちょい！もうちょっとだ！
A bit more! Almost there!
おらおら！
Ora ora!
おらおらおらおら！
Ora ora ora ora!
Yay!
びび、びび？
Bibi, Bibi?
びびちゃん？
Bibi-chan?
やったー！
We did it!
うれしいー！
So happy!
報酬、報酬ある？
Reward, is there a reward?
報酬ないの？
No reward?
報酬ないの、これ？
No reward for this?
報酬、何もないな
Reward, there's nothing.
びび！殺された、うさぎさんに！
Bibi! I was killed, by the rabbit!
びび大丈夫か？
Bibi, are you okay?
なーんだ、守っただけ？
Aw, man, we just defended?
I love how you were like...
...right as the second wave, or the enemy appears...
...you just ran?
Sorry, my... my Fighter blood, it... it called to me!
That was so funny, like...
何があったんですか？
What happened?
何が起きた？
I'm sorry, "there's an enemy, I must defeat them!"
I was like, "Oh, I got teleported, and I must fight."
みなさん、おめでとうございます！
Everyone, congratulations!
えっとですね...
Well...
みなさん、あの...
Everyone, um...
あの、ハトタウロスおめでとうございます！
Um, congratulations on Hatotaur!
はい、えっと、無事倒せた皆さんにちょっとご褒美がございます！
Yes, well, we have a little reward for everyone who successfully defeated it!
おー！やったー！
Oh! We did it!
うちらがいない間に何か終わってたんだ
Something ended while we weren't here?
逆じゃね？入ってない
Isn't that the opposite? It's not in.
大丈夫です。皆さんに効果あるんで
It's okay, it affects everyone.
えっ、いいの？
Oh, is it okay?
何ですか何ですか？
What is it, what is it?
えっと、レイドを無事クリアできたので、
Well, since we successfully cleared the raid,
次の今から回すカブシルーレットが、特別版になります！
the next turn on the Stock Roulette we're about to spin will be a special edition!
おおー！
Oooooh!
今からじゃあカブ回すか。10時台の。
Shall we spin the stock now? The 10 o'clock one.
今、はい、今カブ回しますね。
Now, yes, I'm going to spin the stock now.
おおー！
Oooooh!
ネポラボホールディングス、いけー！
NePoLaBo Holdings, go!
最近やばかったね / わくわく
Lately, it's been crazy, hasn't it? / I'm so excited!
ということで、特別版ルーレットになります。
So, this is the special version roulette!
特別版ということで、良いのになってるんじゃないですか？
Since it's a special version, it should be good, right?
ししろんフーズ、ピー！
Shishiro Foods, spin!
え？ ゼロしかない？ / ゼロしかないじゃんこれ！
Wait, are there only zeros? / There are only zeros on this!
プラス50円！
Plus 50 yen!
ドロボウです！ / がんばれがんばれ！
Next is Dorobou! / Go, go!
あれ？お？
Oh? Huh?
プラス75円！
Plus 75 yen!
えー、ウナ電鉄！
Next, Una Railway!
プラス100円！
Plus 100 yen!
あ、ごめん、間違えたこれ。
Ah, sorry, I made a mistake.
これ、ウナ電鉄の次、大空なんだけど、ごめん、間違えた！
After Una Railway is Oozora, but sorry, I made a mistake!
大空を105円に戻してからやらせていただきますね。
I'll put Oozora back to 105 yen and spin again.
ちょっと大空は後で回すんで、ちょっとお待ちください。
I'll spin Oozora later, so please wait a bit.
先にネポラボ回しますね。
First, let's spin NePoLaBo.
100！100！100！ / プラス100円！
100! 100! 100! / Plus 100 yen!
Oh my god! 100! Plus 100!
ネポラボ... Sell.
NePoLaBo... Sell.
うわ、もう2000いけたんだ。
Oh, I could've sold 2000 more.
Whoa! Sold!
4000持ってるの？
You had 4000 shares?
Daily trading limit reached... Oh, what to do?
うわー、どうしようかな。
Wow, what should I do?
買い増しとこうかな。
Maybe I should buy more?
Now what...
Let's deposit 400,000.
Maybe I should buy a... what was it? / Withdraw 30,000.
Farmer... Shop. Wait, I'm going to...
Fine, let's just buy one.
売りました。Whew...
I sold them. Whew...
あくちゅ、ごめん...
Achoo! Sorry...
Oh, money boost. Money boost is good.
Farm yield boost.
Oh, yield boost is good too.
Okay, we do have two rare bees.
These aren't stackable.
Wait, did I put that... there?
And then I'll breed these two next. Oh, maybe I should breed these actually.
Let's see what I get.
あ、いなちゃんのハウス。
Ah, Ina-chan's house.
あ、いいじゃん。
Ah, nice.
Oh.
I didn't say anything when I muted, by the way.
I was gonna go boil some water for noodles, but...
...I ended up not.
Oh...
I think I have enough wheat. Maybe...
...maybe I'll just go carrots because they're sold at the same price.
It's just easier to do the same crop.
And carrots are better yield, yeah!
We shall be carrot farmers.
Actually, let's go make some...
Let's go make some pumpkin pie. Carrot and pumpkin pie.
Although the most money I made was from stone.
16.
Woah!
やるじゃん！
Not bad!
Oh, not enough sugar. That's a first.
I need to go collect some sugar.
素晴らしい。
Wonderful.
Oh...
Okay, do I have everything?
Ta-ta-ta-ta...
Oh, I heard it.
Ha!
Oh, they grow so fast.
Ta-ta-ta-ta...
Whoa!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Enough sugar... Oh, that's a lot of sugar.
Let me go grab more... grab more eggs.
Oh God.
Eggs, please.
Nya-nya-nya-nya tamago...
Nya-nya-nya-nya eggs...
Come on, I heard it.
I heard it. The eggs?
All right, I'll come back for you. I'll come back for you.
Wait, what? Am I out of pumpkins? Oh! I'm actually using up the pumpkins!
Nya-nya...
Should I also make this into carrots, too? I think I should make this into carrots, too.
I have enough wheat and seeds.
Nya-nya...
I wonder what the reward for the...
Oh, the carrots...
What's the reward for the homework of Day 2 is? Cuz we got a free...
...free beehive yesterday.
Why are people leaving etc. so often? It's because the dungeon, I think, is in a different server, technically.
So every time they go into the dungeon, the battle...
...they disconnect and reconnect again.
Oh, the carrots!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's halfway through.
15! Nice.
Okay, I'm gonna go boil some water real quick...
...so I can actually eat before it gets too, too late.
I'll be right back.
はぁ！
Whaaa!
The water is boiling.
Oh, oh, you pushed me into a corner. How dare... Oh, chicken eggs!
すばら... Oh! So many eggs suddenly!
Wonde... Oh! So many eggs suddenly!
Oh!
Oh! Eggs, eggs everywhere!
Nice. I don't know if you can hear the water boiling.
Like, great... Great job, friends. I need more.
More sugar, too.
And the carrots are done.
Too busy.
Ah! Oh! Oh!
Oh, it gives four bees!
なるほど。
I see.
What happens if we breed two rare bees?
Oh, wait. Maybe I'll... umm... farm yield boost one.
Jump boost bee?
Oh, I could breed these two.
Okay, I can go sell these.
I'll leave the rares for now.
Ooh.
Maybe, maybe we will become the bee breeder.
Another path has opened.
It's meant to be. We even have a theme song.
It's meant to be.
Oh, Fire Resistance. Okay.
おちついてるよー！おちついてるよー！
I'm calm! I'm calm!
Excuse me... Oh.
What are they doing?
I wasn't seeing what they were doing.
I didn't see what they were doing.
あそこやな。
Over there.
They leave a trace wherever they go.
Oh, I can probably go sell these after.
Tat-tat-tat-ta.
Tat-tat, tat-tat-tat-tat.
Leave it here. Don't need this, don't need this.
I'll leave it here. Don't need this, don't need this.
Oh yeah, I can make so much more...
...pumpkin...
...pies right now. Look at all these eggs I have!
Hehehe.
Oh, pumpkins outside.
Oh, the pumpkins are outside.
Hm, hm, hm...
We're making so m... so many pumpkin pies. I choked on my spit.
I'm so happy, my plan is working.
I'm gonna be a farmer.
Yeah. Na-na, na-na-na-na.
I totally forgot about the water!
Okay, after I... I harvest and plant everything,
I shall... I shall eat my noodles.
Or pour the wa—
Actually, I should pour the water while...
...while I harvest.
It cooks, and then I can harvest, and then I can eat, and then I can harvest. Yeah.
Farmer's life for me~
All right, three minutes, guys, three minutes.
You gotta let me know.
Or my noodles are gonna be noodles without soup.
Maybe I should go do some of the minigames too.
Oh, it's full.
But I can totally fill the rest of my inventory with...
...the... more carrots.
We got to sell soon.
Ooh... very nice.
Yes, yes, yes.
I feel like the closer I am, the more eggs they lay.
Please!
Ladies, ladies...
Oh my, oh my.
All right, we good? We good?
Hey.
Nice. We almost have two full stacks.
Noodles are done?
Are the noodles really done? Okay, I'll... I will eat here.
いただきます。
Bon appétit.
Where is my text?
Ina muted eating real quick, thank you.
Okay, be right back.
[On-Screen Text: INA MUTED EATING RQ TY]
INA MUTED EATING RO TY
Ina is muted while eating. Right back, thank you.
INA MUTED EATING RQ TY
[On-Screen Text: Ina muted, eating real quick, thank you!]
うまい！
Yummy!
I have the soup left, but... um, I finished the noodle.
スープは残ったけど、麺は食べました。
The soup is left, but I ate the noodles.
よし...
Alright...
うまい。
Sweet.
I'm out of pumpkins.
おお...
Oh...
Farm money boost level 2... haste...
We can sell all of these.
バウバウ！
Bow wow!
バウバウ？
Bow wow?
Are you guys done for the day?
We're almost done, oh...
We're gonna make the most money today. I won the lottery.
It should be... a little more eggs for more pie. I think we're gonna make...
...our first full carrot run.
Where's the... did I get it? Okay.
Two stacks of pumpkin pie.
おっ...
Oh...
Good? Okay, okay.
Almost three stacks. Okay, and then we'll go... full box of carrot.
And a little more than that. And also bees.
Oh, I forgot to plant.
No, I don't wanna have more chickens cuz it might lag.
あぁ...
Ah...
And then while we're there, maybe we can try some minigames.
Wait, we should still get the pumpkins cuz we get money for harvesting them.
And they grow pretty fast.
No automation is allowed.
That would make it quite unfair.
Did I miss one?
Let's see.
I did.
にゃ、にゃ、にゃ...
Nya, nya, nya...
お？
Oh?
Did I destroy one by mistake? I did.
Wait, it wasn't me.
Was it... was it...?
Was it accidentally me? Might have been me.
Pumpkins grow fast.
Suddenly almost 100k.
ああ！
Ah!
My carrot!
Yeah, some are growing back as soon as I cut them, like this one.
おお！
Oh!
As soon as I'm done with the pumpkins, all of a sudden...
...it's time for the carrots.
Water breathing.
Slowness and water breathing.
So-so.
Common, so I can sell this one.
Hopefully...
Hopefully, one of these yields another super rare.
And we can breed that again.
Okay, what's the plan here, Ina?
I think we might be able to get a full stack of pumpkin...
...pies, so let me get some eggs.
One more round of carrots...
...and then we go to town.
And then it should be around time...
...for kabu.
Pie...
Uh, I just need some sugar.
Wow, such efficiency.
Actually, it's not that efficient, but I would... I would like to believe that it is...
...for the sake of my sanity.
You'd think...
...possibly get to 1 million today?
Feel like if I try hard, um, might be able to.
Still have one more hour.
今日、100万いけるかな？ いけると思う。
Today, can I make it to 1 million? I think I can.
がんばれば。
If I work hard.
Hmm.
I believe.
I feel like I'm currently getting quite a bit of money just from farming, ね？
I feel like I'm currently getting quite a bit of money just from farming, right?
え？また？
Huh? Again?
Hehe, I got more money saved, though.
Hehehe.
Ah, Vindicator...
Battle content seems kind of fun, too.
な、な、な、な、な、な、な...
Na, na, na, na, na, na, na...
Now that I'm done with the carrots on that side...
...now carrots on this side are done.
終わんない。
It's never-ending.
Okay, for now, leave this here. Oh, we got three stacks and five...
Okay, how about I get this...
...this carrot...
...plant it, and then go.
Oh, bee. Oh, eggs.
Oh.
Yield and money.
And another yield and money. Okay, let's see if I can improve any of them.
Farm, hmm...
Yield and boost. Yield and boost.
Ah.
Okay, and then maybe...
I'll put these here, because I know...
...super rare ones are actually expensive too.
See how much...
Let's see how much more I can earn now.
Oh!
Whoa!
I think my farming business has grown!
We can even buy another hive... wait actually, three hives.
Yeah, we can buy another hive.
The bee-siness is growing.
Alright, alright, let's go sell before...
...before... let's get more honey too.
Here.
Actually, it's been a while since we collected eggs.
Let's do that first.
Oh, oh!
Okay.
We'll leave the eggs in one of the chests.
Okay, okay, okay.
So many distractions, I know.
Maybe we should've built our house a bit closer.
値段見てみるか
Let's see the prices.
Mm-hmm.
パンプキン、300円
Pumpkins are 300 yen.
Hmm...
お、イナ先輩じゃん
Oh, it's Ina-senpai!
Bibii!
ビビー！イナ先輩、ファーマー儲けてますか？
Bibi! Ina-senpai, are you making money as a farmer?
うん、なんとなく
Yeah, kind of.
え？なんとなく？何が儲けてますか？
Eh? Kind of? What's making you money?
何が...
What is...
何、えっと、ファーマーの何が美味しいですか？
What, uh, what's profitable about farming?
あ、美味しい？うーん...
Ah, profitable? Hmm...
うーん、今、私はニンジンとハチやってるかな保存する
Hmm, right now I'm doing carrots and bees.
ニンジン？
Carrots?
ニンジン早いし、なんかハチのスキルで...
Carrots grow fast, and with the bee skills...
うん
Yeah.
お金高くなることもあるし
...sometimes you get more money too.
へえー！
Whoa!
ニンジンなんや
So it's carrots.
えっ、小麦...
Eh, wheat...
カボチャ作ってました、ビビ
I was growing pumpkins.
カボチャは、えっと、パンプキンパイ
Pumpkins are, uh, pumpkin pie.
そう、作って、でも卵がなくて、めんどくさい、作るの
Yeah, I made it, but I don't have eggs, so it's a hassle to make.
あ、そうそうそうそう
Ah, yeah yeah yeah yeah.
ねー
Right?
ええ、そういうことか
Ah, I see.
うん、頑張ってね
Yeah, do your best!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much!
Okay.
Ah.
Uh.
I still have a lot to sell.
えー、Combat Support Bee, Common.
Uh, Combat Support Bee (Common).
で、Farm Support Bee, Rare.
And... Farm Support Bee, Rare.
And... oh yeah, I was gonna cook the fish.
カボチャ？うーん。スイカ売るのって、スイカ売れないでしょ？でも。
Pumpkin? Hmm... Can we sell watermelons? Ah, you can't sell watermelons, right?
That was what I was...
...gonna do.
Cook the fish.
Oh, from Shulker you can do that?
そう、そう。あれ22、23じゃなかったっけ？もう終わった？
Right, right. Wasn't that 22 or 23? Is it already over?
まだだよ。まだだよ。できない... そっかそっか。
Not yet. Not yet. I can't do it... I see, I see.
これは半分、株買わないと。
This is half, I have to buy stocks.
行きます。今日、最後。
Here we go. Today's the last one.
ししらフード。
Shishira Foods.
ぷるぷるぷる...
Purupurupuru...
Oh, cap.
Oh wait, I can sell the bee. / おおー！130！
Oh wait, I can sell the bee. / Ohh! 130!
おおー！どんどん上がる。
Ohh! It keeps going up.
198... / 泥棒建設、次行きます。
198... / Dorobou Construction is next.
あ、プラス50円です！
Ah, it's plus 50 yen!
おおー！
Ohh!
着実に高くなってる。
It's steadily getting higher.
I'm becoming so rich.
下がれ！下がれ！買いたいから下がれ！
Go down! Go down! I want to buy, so go down!
おおー！
Ohh!
プラス30%！めっちゃ上がってる！めっちゃ上がってるじゃん、大空！
Plus 30%! It's going up so much! Oozora is going up so much!
200超えた。すごい悩む。いいね。すごいな。
It went over 200. This is really tough. Nice. Amazing.
200か。
200, huh?
あ、ああーー！ / ああーー！
Ah, ahhh! / "Ahhh!"
クリック... ああーー！1回だけ買うのです。
Click... Ahhh! You only buy it once.
これ可愛い。
This is cute.
オッケー、これでいいでしょう。よし。
Okay, this should be good. Alright.
これで買えない。今何円になった？
I can't buy with this. How much is it now?
おおー。来た来た来た。はぁ... いや、これネポラボ売りすごい悩むな。
Ohh. Here it comes, here it comes. *sigh* Man, I'm really debating whether to sell Nepolabo.
結構、見極めないとやばくない？
Isn't it bad if we don't judge it carefully?
これが上限か。所持数20？
Is this the limit? Amount held is 20?
暴言吐いてるところ売り切れちゃったよ。
It sold out while I was spitting abuse!
すいません！すいません！
Sorry! Sorry!
ていうか、20... あ、ネポラボ下がってる！
Wait, 20... Ah, Nepolabo is going down!
あ、下がってる？買い時買い時。買った。
Ah, it's down? Time to buy, time to buy. Bought.
24円だとな、悩ましい。まあ、20なら。
24 yen is tough. Well, if it's 20.
いや、大空建設の株いつ売るべきだと思う？
Hey, when do you think I should sell Oozora Construction stocks?
Farming. Okay, one more hive.
And then replenish the honey. And then back to farming.
お、もう一匹作っちゃう？
Oh, I'll make another one.
Slow Falling...
Actually, I think you can put hoppers for the bees. They did say that.
Otherwise, um...
it's not gonna...
こっちも可愛い。
This one is cute too.
あ、どうしよう。
Ah, what should I do?
Yeah, it gets stuck after four bees, yeah.
Ooh.
Too rare.
I only have eight.
I'm not sure if...
Yeah...
Like, if... I don't think it carries downwards, so...
Okay, bee related stuff here.
Alright, I was gonna...
Should I go grab some wood? There's a lot of wood.
Hoppers only allowed for bees, I feel.
That would be the only exception.
And I'm pretty sure it's only for...
Let me read.
Okay, both beehives and hatcheries...
can have hoppers.
Placing automation tools other than hoppers on beehives and hives is prohibited.
So we would technically have to...
do a three-three formation...
into the hoppers.
Okay, how about...
Oh, oops.
You know what...
Ah, maybe I should go get iron first.
How many would I need? Three? Cuz I think starting tomorrow we can have five.
But today the limit is three, starting tomorrow, the limit is five hives and apiaries.
I need iron.
I have a little bit. I have like seven that I haven't smelted yet.
It's not much.
We'll start with the iron.
I have the iron ingots for 10 hoppers.
They do not sell iron, cuz you're supposed to go hunt for them, or dig... or mine for them.
Okay, while that's doing that, let's do farmer things.
How much time do I have? 15 minutes?
Ideally, we set up three hoppers tonight, cuz I think...
...we could get some bees while server is open...
...without anyone there.
Oh, maybe we can use the flea shop actually. Let's see if anyone put up iron there.
There must be some... I feel like I saw some yesterday.
Flea market! I forgot!
Okay, and then...
One, two, three, four... Okay, chest.
I need to make one more chest.
Oh wait, anything automation other than that is prohibited.
Okay... okay, okay, okay.
Um, how about since these two are empty...
That was close.
これはどう？
How about this?
My brain has stopped. But...
For now, since these are common bees...
...we'll do this.
We'll get that going.
We're gonna grab some chicken...
...eggs.
Don't worry, the pathway can be...
...redesigned.
This, daijoubu.
This is fine.
Okay.
We need more sugar and basically everything.
Oh. I wasted an egg.
Ah. Sadness.
Oh, more eggs.
Pumpkin.
I just need sugar. Okay.
Pumpkin pie.
More sugar.
I should probably make more...
...let's say...
...straight sugarcane...
...easier access.
Oh, fish done.
One more fish.
Okay, I might make a short stop to sell some stuff.
Like the pie, the cooked cod...
Ooh!
Right now we can get you and you...
...get that going.
And another round of...
...carrots.
Ah, harvest.
Farmers are the busiest of them all.
No time to rest, gotta farm.
Going backwards is easier.
At this rate, it's probably better to get rid of the pumpkin and just do all carrots.
You might be right, but at...
...the same time, I don't know. That means I can just get rid of all the chickens too, no?
Just carrots all the way. But carrots actually don't yield like...
...that, that much, you know?
Which one harvests more? The carrot.
The thing about the pumpkin is that I can't...
...sell it on its own.
That's the biggest problem.
The harvesting is more work than selling.
Pumpkin itself gives more coins, that's true.
So it does synergize with better bees as well.
Ah...
And then we can use the pumpkins, I guess, to make...
...pumpkin pie as an extra thing.
And the pumpkins grow really fast, that's the thing.
So...
It does end up being quite a bit of money, just needs some active grinding.
Like, I can do a thing where I just...
...keep only...
...farming pumpkins.
And then I would return to the beginning, and the pumpkins would have grown already.
Like look, I did like one round of pumpkin harvesting and the carrots are basically all grown.
Oh...
Like look, look at how much kabocha there is.
Like look, look at how much pumpkin there is.
Uh...
See?
Need more pumpkin.
I mean, the yield is not bad right now.
It's just, good news.
Okay, now what?
We'll go sell. We'll see if someone has... wait, we can fill this carrot.
I think.
And probably sell these too.
Actually, we'll leave... this one.
Now, that's the pumpkin strat, is to have a pumpkin field so big, that once you make one round, it... the beginning has already regrown.
So then, you just endlessly farm pumpkins.
Did I pick that up first? Guess I did.
Whoops.
Oh wait.
Carrots, ca- ca- carrots.
Okay.
Grab egg.
I might not even need the fence anymore.
Okay, I'll leave the eggs in here.
にゃー、にゃー、にゃー...
Nya, nya, nya...
Conduit Power...
Water breathing.
Okay, we'll sell these two.
Okay, we gotta go sell, see if they have any iron, and then we'll come back.
The minigames not yet? A farmer's life is busy, okay?
It's serious business.
Okay.
Okay...
Oh, a full sell.
No, it might be better to sell the bees.
あ、それでちまちま...
Ah, so bit by bit with that...
Like, a full stash of carrots is like... one bee.
Mhm, mhm.
Pumpkin pie isn't bad. It just takes a little longer.
ありとー。ありがとう。
Thanks! Thank you.
結構何人かいないときついかもしれない。でもあれ3人だよね。
It might be tough without several people. But that's for 3 people, right?
3人...
3 people...
Let's go check flea market. Flea market.
Oh, 163.
Oh, lava.
And combat bees...
Broken elytra.
ないかも。
Seems there's none.
Oh, I have to go mine for our own.
持ってない。最初のさ、クリア報酬でも...
I don't have it. Even with the first clear reward...
Oh.
いや、これって...
Wait, is this...
痛いなー。
Ouch.
あれシュルカーボックス置けないの？これ。
Huh, can't we place Shulker boxes here?
え？
Eh?
あ、置けた。
Ah, I could place it.
あれこれ普通のピッケルで壊せる？
Huh, can this be broken with a normal pickaxe?
Ah, got them.
いやでもこれって、誰の...
But wait, whose is this...
誰のじゃないよね？
It doesn't belong to anyone, right?
たまたまに、ここにある...あるのね？
It just happens to be here, right?
ね？
Right?
いやでも、インゴット、ない。
But wait, there are no ingots.
うう。
Ugh...
60万くらい稼げた、一回で。
I earned about 600,000 in one go.
こう、一周ね。 え、謎解き？
Like, one round, right? Wait, a riddle?
いや、できないわ。
No, I can't do it.
おおー！
Ooh!
マネー！
Money!
いや、鉄って、どこでも、あるからね？
Well, iron is basically everywhere, you know?
暗い。
It's dark.
でも大丈夫、今日は持って、持ってきた。
But it's fine, I brought them with me today.
今日は暗くないぜ。
It's not dark today!
え、遠い。
Wow, it's far.
これでいいんですか？みなさん。
Is this really okay, everyone?
あ、コメント止まってる？止まった。ちょっと待って、イン...
Ah, is the chat frozen? It froze. Hold on, in...
おし！
Alright!
たまたま。止まっちゃうんです、よ。
It just happens sometimes. It freezes.
いや、あれ持って...持って来なかったなー。
Ah, I didn't... bring that with me.
あ、スーン！
Oh, soon!
あ、来た...かな？
Ah, here it is... maybe?
いやもう、こんなに少なくなった？
Wow, is there really this little left?
あんまり必要ないわ、ラピスは。
I don't really need lapis lazuli.
うーん...
Hmm...
うーん
たいまつ...じゃ勝てるー
Torch... so I can win!
お？
Oh?
いや、ここで、ここで戻ろう。
No, let's go back from here, here.
ここで戻る。
Going back from here.
いや、ちょっと怖いわ。
No, it's a bit scary.
おっ。
Oh.
やっと。
Finally!
いや、これ、これだけ？
No, is this... is this all?
いや、ゼロよりはいいんですけど、but there's nothing...
No, it's better than zero, but there's nothing...
でも、もっとあると思った。
But I thought there would be more.
いや、あきら...
No, give up...
あきら...
Give...
あきらめないよ！
Don't give up!
あきらめないの、お前！
Don't you give up!
あー、よかった！
Ah, thank goodness!
もっとあった！
There was more!
いぇーい！
Yay!
ここで、まわるー。
Let's turn around here.
57だったっけ？
Was it 57?
いや、もう45か。
No, already 45?
え、なんでここにこれが？
Huh, why is this here?
I didn't bring a shovel.
The one time I didn't bring a shovel...
Make a wooden one? But that's just a waste of wood.
Aha!
Yeah, 34...
Ugh...
Torches.
Mmm, gravel.
Phew...
いや、まぁ、暗くなったら今は...
Well, now that it's getting dark...
大丈夫だから。
It should be fine.
大丈夫かも...
Maybe it's fine...
まぁ、リスナーさんも慣れてるんでしょう。暗い、暗いのに。
Well, the viewers are probably used to the darkness by now.
Even if we run out of torches, maybe it's fine. We're used to it.
Oh, coal! Ah...
You have answered my calls! You do not want to be dark, I see.
暗いのそんなに嫌いだったか？
Did you hate the dark that much?
Oh!
暗いのは、いいんだ。
The dark is fine.
32.
Oh...
45だったら戻れる。いや、戻れるかな？道。
If I have 45, I can head back. But can I find my way back?
忘れたかも。
I might have forgotten.
And maybe lost.
That's why whenever I dig, I place the torch on the left.
So if... if I have the torches to my right...
Oh!
Iron.
And I'll know my way out.
Ah.
いや、ここちょっと危ない。
Actually, this place is a bit dangerous.
Ah! Peka peka stone!
Ah! A shiny stone!
Pek... Peka peka stone.
Shi... Shiny stone.
ここにも、peka peka stone があるわ。
There's a shiny stone here too.
なんだと？！
What?!
52!
でも、なんか、もっとある気がする。
But I feel like there are more.
あるかも、peka peka stone.
There might be more shiny stones.
Ah!
Ah, 15 minutes.
いや、どこまで行くの？
No, how far does this go?
いや、ちょっと怖い。
No, it's a bit scary.
あ、でももっとある。
Oh, but there's more.
ええー... あ...
Eeeh... ah...
もうちょっと戻りたいな。
I want to go back a little bit.
見てよ。
Look at this.
なになにこれ、ひゃあ！
What is... what is this, whoa!
なになにここ...
What is this place...
ちょっと覚えとこ。
I should remember this.
でも15分以内に戻らないと。
But I have to go back within 15 minutes.
I must return within 15 minutes.
どこだっけ？ここ？
Where was it? Here?
いや、ここ？
No, here?
いや、ここ...
No, here...
いや...
No...
いやー！
No way!
もっと down?
Further down?
ここ？
Here?
あ...
Ah...
ここだっけ？ここ？
Was it here? Here?
いや、違う。
No, that's wrong.
いや、いや、いや、ま...迷...迷ってはない。
No, no, no, I'm... I'm not lost.
どこから来た？
Where did I come from?
上？下？
Up? Down?
いや、ここ、ここで...
No, here, here...
ここ...
Here...
いや、いや、いや、いや、いける、いける、戻れる、戻れる、絶対に戻れる。
No, no, no, no, I can do this, I can go back, I can go back, I can definitely go back.
は、は、は、は...ここやばいって、やばいって。
*pant pant* This place is bad, it's bad...
マーキングしないと...
I need to make some markings...
おけ、おけ、ここで、こ...あい、あい、あい、あい、あい...
Okay, okay, here, and... aye, aye, aye, aye, aye...
ひゅうー！おっ！
Whew! Oh!
I can't believe I missed it.
大丈夫、大丈夫...
It's okay, it's okay...
もう、無事に戻ったらおけ。
Once I return safely, I'll be fine.
もぐもぐ
*eating sounds*
よし。
Alright.
いやー...いっぱい取れた。
Whew... I got a lot.
はぁ...
*sigh*
あ... あ...
Ah... ah...
あ、みんないる。はーい。
Ah, everyone is here. Hello!
にわとり...
Chickens...
Is she asking if I'm raising chickens?
あ、はい。
Ah, yes.
Is it too many?
Ah, she wants egg?
Ah, she wants eggs?
We need to cook the iron.
Eggs are in high demand? Is that why?
Oh, maybe I should sell eggs at the...
にわとり...もっ...もらう、もらえたりする？
"Can I... have... some chickens?"
...とか感じ？
...something like that?
Oh, trade. Oh, 交換？Ok desu!
Oh, trade. Oh, exchange? Okay!
Ah, chickens!
You may have a new leader soon.
The lucky one shall be chosen!
「今どこいる？」
"Where are you now?"
イナの家にいます。
"I am at Ina's house."
But the question is, how do I get you out of here?
Fishing rod... 出来る？
Can I do it with a fishing rod?
む、難しい...
M-Difficult...
Or... Or, I offer Egg Gacha!
Wait, 16 eggs has good rates, right?
Ah, coordinates.
えっと...
Let's see...
えっと... えっと...
Let's see... Let's see...
Someone write down the coordinates, I can't tab!
み、な、み、げ、ー、と、で...
S-o-u-t-h g-a-t-e...
あ、オッケーオッケー。
Ah, okay okay.
です。
Yes.
Maybe I'll go find her.
しゅば しゅば！しゅば、しゅば しゅば！
Shuba shuba! Shuba, shuba shuba!
しゅば、しゅば、しゅば。
Shuba, shuba, shuba.
How much should I do the 16-egg gacha for, though?
Yeah, I'll have to set up the egg stuff tomorrow.
あ、これって売れないから、フリーマーケット…だっけ？
Ah, since we can't sell these, is it only for the flea market?
What is that miko for?
5k per stack?
Yeah, I'll, I'll do 5k for a stack.
I don't know where she's lost.
Where is Miko-senpai's house?
しゅば しゅば！しゅば しゅば！
Shuba shuba! Shuba shuba!
しゅば しゅば！
Shuba shuba!
5k per egg? I should have sold some eggs at the flea market.
しゅば しゅば！
Shuba shuba!
しゅば しゅば！しゅば、しゅば！
Shuba shuba! Shuba, shuba!
お！おお！イナ！イナ！
Oh! Oh! Ina! Ina!
あ、スバル先輩！
Ah, Subaru-senpai!
イナ！イナ！イナの家どこだ？
Ina! Ina! Where is Ina's house?
ここ！あの、ここ向かって、ここデス。
Here! Um, facing this way... it's here.
あ、ここ！ここか！
Ah, here! Is it here?
ここか！なんかアメジストで可愛いね。
Here?! It's cute with the amethyst.
イナ！ニワトリもらえますか、ニワトリ。
Ina! Can I have some chickens? Chickens.
ニワトリ、ちょっと出るのが難しくて…なんか、卵はどうですか？
Chickens are a bit hard to get out... How about some eggs?
あ、卵めっちゃ欲しくて！
Ah, I really want eggs!
はい！
Yes!
卵、16個？
16 eggs?
え、欲しい！ちなみにイナの欲しいものある？
Eh, I want them! By the way, is there anything Ina wants?
I shall sell the tamago.
I shall sell the eggs.
Oh...
It'd be really fun to do like tamago gacha where...
It'd be really fun to do like an egg gacha where...
Hmm... but then... hmm...
Yeah, to sell the eggs, and then whatever chicken they get out of it, they can keep. Oh.
Oh.
Hehehe...
A new business. I'll think about it.
I didn't realize chickens were in such high demand.
Hahaha...
I guess since all the farmers, they can make pumpkin pie and cake, which is literally needing eggs, so...
I'll think about it. I'll think about it.
Okay.
Well, thanks for watching today. I hope you guys have a...
...wonderful...
...rest of the morning, afternoon, evening.
And I shall see you tomorrow.
Probably. Okay.
Take care! Bye-bye!
Wah!