(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Title: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
The concert will be starting soon.
[Notice: The concert will be starting soon.]
Attention For Visitors
[Notice: Attention For Visitors]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Title: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
二人の活動をこれからも楽しみにしてます！！
I'm looking forward to both of your activities from now on!!
ライブ開催おめでとうございます！ 素敵な公演になりますように！！
Congratulations on the concert! Hope it's a wonderful performance!!
公演まで、今しばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a while.
Attention For Visitors
[Information: Attention for Visitors]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Information: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
2人も、ずっと応援してるよ！ FIGHT〜！！
I'll always be rooting for you both! Good luck!!
LAでのライブ開催おめでとうございます！！
Congratulations on holding the concert in LA!!
素敵なライブを楽しみにしています！
I'm looking forward to a wonderful concert!
公演まで、今しばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a while.
Attention For Visitors
[Information: Attention for Visitors]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Information: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
DRAWN TO DAWN
TAKANASHI KIARA / NINOMAE INA'NIS 1st CONCERT
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
DRAWN TO DAWN
TAKANASHI KIARA / NINOMAE INA'NIS 1st CONCERT
開演まで、いましばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
演出の都合上、フラッシュ等の強い光が点滅する場面があります。
声を出しての応援が可能です。
[Attention] Please be aware of flashing lights.
Cheering loudly is okay.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Merchandise] 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演まで、いましばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
演出の都合上、フラッシュ等の強い光が点滅する場面があります。
声を出しての応援が可能です。
[Attention] Please be aware of flashing lights.
Cheering loudly is okay.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Merchandise] 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Fan Messages
[Fan Messages for "Drawn to Dawn"]
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis 1st Concert "Drawn to Dawn"
The concert will be starting soon.
開演まで、もう少々お待ちください。
[The concert will be starting soon.
Please wait a little longer for the start.]
Attention For Visitors
開演中、まぶしい光の演出がありますので、ご注意ください。
声出し、応援はOKです。
[Attention For Visitors:
Please be aware of flashing light effects during the performance.
Cheering and supporting is OK.]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
グッズ販売情報 第2弾
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Merchandise Information Part 2]
The concert will be starting soon.
[Visual Text: The concert will be starting soon.]
Attention For Visitors
[Visual Text: Attention For Visitors]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
[Visual Text: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
KIKKERIKIIIIIIII!
Thank you all so much for coming to Takanashi Kiara and
Ninomae Ina'nis' first concert, Day 2, Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara and next to me is...
WAH!
Yeah! Good morning, afternoon, evening everyone!
This is Ninomae Ina'nis! WOO!
That's right, it is finally time to start Day 2!
Is everyone hyped!?
All right, before we kick things off, of course,
we have some important safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of recording equipment
are strictly prohibited during the performance.
However, if you are watching from home, screenshots are allowed.
Please take lots of screenshots!
Yeah, スクショはOKですよ！
Yeah, screenshots are okay!
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
Unless you're smoking hot like me!
Mm, where have I heard that one before? / Someone said that yesterday!
If you start unfeeling- feeling unwell at any point,
please don't push yourself.
Just reach out to the nearest staff member for help.
And drink water!
For everyone's safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This, once again, no matter how hyped it is,
includes moshing, diving, sitting on shoulders,
jumping excessively, or throwing objects toward the stage.
Climbing onto the stage, intentionally blocking the aisles,
or rushing toward the front is also not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting,
erratic lightstick movements, or any extreme motions
that might interfere with the experience of those around you.
Be considerate.
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or the venue staff,
you may be asked to leave the venue.
Yeah, please keep in mind that the venue, organizers,
performers, and staff cannot be held responsible for any accident,
equipment damage, or trouble caused by failing to follow instructions.
I- you stumbled over the same words!
It's hard, okay? I'm trying my best here. I can't read!
Additionally, any cost for damage resulting from ignoring these rules
will be the responsibility of the person involved.
There are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today,
and you might appear in the footage or photos.
These may be used for promotional purposes later on, so please keep that in mind.
And finally, just like yesterday, the concert will be in two parts.
There's a part for Wawa and there's a part for me, so please look forward to both of them!
And yeah, that is it for the rules! Woohoo!
The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Have fun! Have fun! See you soon! Bye bye!
DRAWN TO DAWN
[Title: DRAWN TO DAWN]
[Title: Drawn to Dawn]
Enlightened by the powers that be
The ruler of a world run on insanity
It's clear to me they still can't see
I'm just a normal girl
Empowered by the ancient one's call
We're gonna be pun-stoppable, we're not a cult
Nonsensical and nautical
Adventures lie in wait (Give me a one, ayy)
1, 8, タコ達
1, 8, Takodachis
Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina (Woo)
俺のInaの世界線
My Ina's worldline
守るためにタコになろう (Oh, でしょう)
Let's become Takos to protect (Oh, right)
1, 8, タコ達
1, 8, Takodachis
Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina (Woo)
いいタコになりますように
May I become a good Tako
Insanityで踊りましょう (Oh, でしょう)
Let's dance in the insanity (Oh, right)
Think of all that you can be
We're talking evolution, leave it all to me
Maybe just touch of purple ink
What'cha think?
It's a song you can't ignore
The ancient ones are calling you to be so much more
Just put your hand in mine and be reborn
In a blink
Tell me what those legs are for
(俺のIna運ぶためです)
(To carry my Ina)
You could use six more
(感謝感謝 ありがたい)
(Thank you, thank you)
We could all get matching ears
(They aren't really ears though, eh?)
Sleepy eyes to fight your fears
(例えばイナいないの世界 alright)
(Like a world without Ina alright)
Listen to my song, am I striking a chord with you?
Stringing you along, so don't let me get bored of you
80 million strong and we've still got some more to do
Everybody shout, "world domination!"
Can I bank on your emotion? do I have you invested?
Your unwavering devotion isn't all I've requested
Do you care? Are you aware that you're my dearest creations?
おやおやおやおや
Oh, oh, oh, oh
A cute little Takodachi found its way here
Experimentation might be necessary
Takos, we have to cook
(いいタコだちの作り方)
(How to make a good Takodachi)
ひっくりかえして丸くして
Flip it and make it round
モロモロ回して こぼさずに
Spin it all around, without spilling a drop,
そっと分かりと 中フワフワ
Gently understanding, a fluffy feeling inside,
得ったならそう 全て愛しいただき
If I've got it, then yes, I'll take all your love.
The powers that be
The rule of the world run on an insanity
It's clear to me, they still can't be
Just a normal girl
Empowered by the ancient ones' call
We're gonna be unstoppable, what other cause?
Nonsensical and mythical
Adventures lie in wait
Let's talk about the future to be
Rewriting all of history, in emergency
With cookies as our currency
The paths can't be concealed
Ineffable the nature must lie
Or up for some Takoyaki, we'll eat 'til we're done
No doubt about it, multi-dimensional
Welcome to my world!
イナイナイナ
Ina Ina Ina
イナイナイナ イナイナイナ
Ina Ina Ina, Ina Ina Ina
オレのいいな 世界征服
My "Ina" world domination
まるごと たこ焼きになろう
Let's all become takoyaki!
そんなご馳走 いればいい
It would be nice to have such a feast
夢をまた いいな 好き勝手
Dreaming again, "Ina," doing as I please
味わう
Savoring it
Our place of never ending fun
I want the world side by side, let's explore 'til I'm done
そう イレるご馳走 いればいい
Yes, it would be nice to have a feast to put in
いつも俺だ いいな 直視が
It's always me, "Ina," looking straight at it
Our place of never ending fun
I want the world side by side, let's explore 'til I'm done
私のもの、そう私のもの
Mine, yes, it's all mine
洗脳... 数百年の財宝
Brainwash... treasure from hundreds of years ago
この船に眠る
Sleeping within this ship
Hey everyone! Get ready to rev things up for Day 2!
Are you ready?
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
古びた伝説は
The ancient legend
呪われた幽霊船に
On a cursed ghost ship
続くよどみの航路
Following the stagnant sea route
そこに富が残る
There, wealth remains
海賊の夢があるのなら
If there is a pirate's dream
ただ 立ち向かうでしょう
Then you'll just stand and face it, right?
産め仲良よ 若き盗人よ
Give birth, my friends, you young thieves
命を持って 後悔に返してやろう
With your lives, I'll pay you back in regret
やまない
Unceasing
雨の弾丸で
Under a barrage of rain
狂おしいほど この瞳焦がす
Burning these eyes almost to madness
攻めの炎 覚めぬ色彩
Flames of attack, colors that never fade
あららう 方的なのなら
If it's destined, one-sided...
私のもの、そう私のもの
Mine, yes, it's all mine
奪ってみろ 命の証を
Try and steal it, the proof of my life
あなたの求める すべてを
Everything that you desire
輝きは 爪錆びついて
The radiance is rusted over by claws
それでもドロ 目に染みつくなら
But if the mud still stains your eyes
泡沫と共に
Along with the bubbles
沈め
Sink down
暗い今 独り吠える
In the dark now, howling alone
毒蛇の中 海賊の秘宝
Amidst the venomous snakes, a pirate's treasure
散れ 笑う
Scatter and laugh
満月の金銀珠玉
Gold, silver, and jewels of the full moon
七つの身の宝具に
Within the seven sacred treasures
たかる 召し共よ
My throbbing summons
小賢しい 富を狙う
Cleverly aiming for the wealth
愚かのみ あの意志知らず
Only the foolish remain unaware of that will
騒がし 墓標を
A noisy gravestone
船に当たる 黒い魂の群れ
A flock of black souls striking the ship
影の底で 忍び寄る亡者の渦
At the bottom of shadows, a vortex of creeping dead
まるで かの閉じた箱
Just like that closed box
手放したいわ 諦めたいわ
I want to let go, I want to give up
悪夢の中から 逃げられるのにまだ
Even though I could escape from this nightmare, I still...
掴んでる よっぽど思い得たら
...keep grasping on, if I think of it enough
私のもの、そう私のもの
Mine, yes, it's all mine
自分自身を 信じ込ませてしまって
I've made myself believe in it
縛り付けて 待って 気づいた
Bound tight, waiting, I realized...
群れの出口 永遠の回帰
The exit from the flock, an eternal recurrence
目を覚まして あなたの奥から
Wake up, from deep within you
連れ出す貴船よ
The ship that carries me away,
出航して
Set sail!
私のもの
Everything is mine,
また私のもの
Once again, it's all mine.
数多の薔薇 打ち放てたとしても
Even if countless roses were set free,
枯れない魂まで
Until it reaches my undying soul.
魔の友情 永遠の美貌
Devil's friendship, eternal beauty.
そんな幻影を歌っていたいでしょう
I'd want to keep singing of such illusions.
手放して翼ついた
Letting go, wings have grown.
さあ行こう 夜明けに舵を向けて
Come, let's go! Steer towards the dawn.
曰くをも焼き落とした船
A ship that burned away even its history,
希望だけ残していく 神は乗らない
Leaving only hope behind, no gods aboard.
空へ
To the sky!
風に吹かれて 誰も気付かぬよう
Blown by the wind, so that no one notices,
区別がつかない モノクロの世界
I can't tell them apart in this monochrome world.
色を足しても 何も見えなくて
Even if I add color, I can see nothing,
まるで私は 息を止めていた
It's as if I had been holding my breath.
もういいよ 遠くても
It's alright now, even if it's far,
叶えたい 私は
I want to make it come true.
この世界をも 抱きしめていたいのに
Even though I want to embrace this whole world...
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
描き続ける意味は
The meaning of continuing to paint
この胸に 輝いている
is shining within this heart of mine.
Story
溢れることに 意味などないけれど
There's no meaning in things overflowing, but
拾い集めた 欠片失うの
I'm losing the fragments I've gathered up.
そして夜は その冷たさを
And then the night, with its coldness,
溶かして手を伸ばした
thawed as I reached out my hand.
もういいよ 遠くても
It's alright now, even if it's far,
届けたい 私は
I want it to reach you.
不器用でも 抱きしめていたいのに
Even if I'm clumsy, I want to embrace you...
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
心込めるのは
The reason I put my heart into it
この空に 描き出していく
is to paint it out into this sky.
Story
そして夜は その冷たさを
And then the night, with its coldness,
溶かして手を伸ばした
thawed as I reached out my hand.
もういいの 遠くても
It's alright now, even if it's far,
叶えたい 私の
I want it to come true, my
この世界を 言葉で包んだ
I've wrapped this world in words.
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
色を足していく
I'll keep adding colors.
この胸に 今輝いて
Now, shining within this heart...
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong,
壊れかけてもいい
it's okay to be breaking.
この心は 大空に羽ばたいて
This heart will flap its wings into the vast sky.
響くように
So that it resonates,
塗り替えてゆく 彩と
I'll repaint it all with colors.
Woo! Hello everyone!
It is Day 2 of "Drawn to Dawn"!
Yes, yes, welcome to Day 2 of Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis's first concert, "Drawn to Dawn"!
Are you guys enjoying the show so far?
Ah, you know, um, I was really...
I want to talk about Tako Tako first because...
Yesterday, I heard you guys sing along to the instrumental...
and I was like, "Uh, I feel bad for not singing on Day 1."
But, you know, I knew I was opening for, you know, Day 2...
so I couldn't have thought of a better song to open than Tako Tako.
So I hope you guys had fun singing it! Thank you again!
And of course, I sang two of my Senpai's songs...
um, Sencho's Dead Man's Chest and Hoshimachi's Palette.
I specifically... (stammers) I specifically wanted to choose their songs because...
um, they're, you know, Senpais that I really look up to and...
I always feel like my journey here wouldn't have
been possible if I didn't discover my Senpais many, many years ago.
And I always, you know, wanted to pay respect
to the path they paved for us so, yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed it!
I'm so nervous again!
Yeah, and um, you know, I of course didn't really tell you guys
specifically what penlight colors to use...
but I knew that you guys would get my message because we share a brain cell, right? Right?
And yeah, so, well, um, now going by the different setlist...
because we, you know, have different setlists for Day 1 and Day 2...
so, you know, going by the process of elimination, we have a couple of songs from my new EP left.
Actually, who here bought my EP?
Yay! Thank you so much! I hope you were lucky to get an autograph...
I tried to sign as much as possible but, you know, sometimes you can't be lucky.
Thank you, thank you! But yeah, I want you guys to have even more fun than before today.
I mean, you always have fun, so that's good, but...
yeah, you know, sing along, have fun...
and I always think that a live stage is where not only me performing is creating...
the performance, but you guys as well, you really help, you know, help everyone...
with that special experience. So let's create an unforgettable memory together today, okay?
Anyways, um, I would also like to shout out to those watching at home...
and at the live viewing in the cinema. Hello, hello to you again!
And also, the lovely, lovely girls doing a watch-along right now...
Hi guys, thank you, IRyS, Bae, and everyone else doing the watch-along. Thank you, thank you!
Um, you know, I'm always amazed by everyone's support, um...
and really without the support of Holo EN members as well, like, I wouldn't have had the confidence to stand here today.
Thank you, I love you!
And of course, I would like to remind you guys about the hashtag for today's concert as well...
#TakoToriFirstConcert, as usual, post your thoughts about it, post the screenshots...
No videos! No videos! Post the screenshots, and you know...
Moona and I, whenever we have time, we've been checking the hashtag...
and of course, after as well, I want to hear what you guys thought about the live, so yeah!
Thank you, thank you! And unlike yesterday...
first MC means I unfortunately have to bid farewell to those watching the sneak peek on YouTube.
I'm sorry! But if you want to keep the party going...
head to the streaming site via the description, the comment...
I don't know where the comment is. Yeah!
But I know that some of you guys won't get a chance to see my new outfit that I revealed yesterday...
so I thought maybe... maybe you guys can help me transition into the new costume here...
so that even those of you watching on YouTube can see it.
Everyone on YouTube and Chiamise can see.
All right, so I'm going to count down from three. Count down with me, okay?
And then I will switch into the new outfit for you guys to see.
Ready?
Ready? Give me a "wah" if you're ready!
All right, all right. All right, here we go.
Three!
Two!
One!
Ha!
Ta-da!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
All right, it's time to move on to the next song.
And I think this song also fits the starry stage perfectly.
Not that one yet, but...
But this one is from one of my favorite franchises,
so I hope you guys listen.
Anyways, the song will fit the starry stage perfectly.
Please give it a listen.
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
[Text: The sneak peek part of the show has ended.]
Thank you for watching.
[Text: Thank you for watching.]
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The land of my roots,
and the sun ablaze.
The colors of dawn
and a ray of light that shows the way.
I shine
bright for you.
A picture frame holding dreams,
and the waxing, waning moon.
Through the tranquil night,
a tender glow ripples upon the water.
Your light
is what makes me shine.
Two sparkles reflecting each other
melt into one,
and with it comes a dawn yet unseen.
As though to ink
the first lines of a
new story.
The land of my roots,
and the sun ablaze.
The colors of dawn
and a ray of light that shows the way.
I shine
bright for you.
A picture frame holding dreams,
and the waxing, waning moon.
Through the tranquil night,
a tender glow ripples upon the water.
Your light
is what makes me shine.