(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
本公演は間もなく開演いたします。
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
演出等での光の刺激にご注意ください。大きな声での応援もOKです！
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
演出等での光の刺激にご注意ください。大きな声での応援もOKです！
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
[Attention for Visitors]
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
[ファンからの応援メッセージ]
[Congratulatory Messages from Fans]
The concert will be starting soon.
[Attention for Visitors]
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
[ファンからの応援メッセージ]
[Congratulatory Messages from Fans]
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors:
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors:
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
キッケリキー！
Kikkeriki!
Thank you all so much for coming to Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis'...
...first concert Day 2, Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara, and next to me is...
Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone!
This is Ninomae Ina'nis!
That's right, it is finally time to start Day 2!
Is everyone hyped?!
Hype, hype, hype, hype!
All right, before we kick things off, of course, we have some important safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
However, if you are watching from home, screenshots are allowed. Please take lots of screenshots!
Yeah, スクショはOKですよ！
Yeah, screenshots are OK!
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
Unless you're smoking hot like me!
We heard that yesterday...
We said that yesterday.
If you start feeling unwell—
And... unfeeling well...?
If you start feeling unwell at any point, please don't push yourself.
Just reach out to the nearest staff member for help,
and drink water!
For everyone's safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This, once again, no matter how hype it is, includes moshing, diving,
sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively, or throwing objects toward the stage.
Climbing onto the stage, intentionally blocking the aisles, or rushing toward the front is also not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting, erratic lightstick movements,
or any extreme motions that might interfere with the experience of those around you.
Be considerate!
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or the venue staff, you may be asked to leave the venue.
Yeah, please keep in mind that the venue, organizers, performers,
and staff cannot be held responsible for any accidents,
equipment damage, or trouble caused to—
...bleh bleh bleh... caused by failing to follow instructions!
So did you stumble over the same words?
It's hard, okay? I'm trying my best here! I can't read!
Additionally, any costs for damage resulting from ignoring these rules will be the responsibility of the person involved.
There are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today, and you might appear in the footage or photos.
These may be used for promotional purposes later on, so please keep that in mind.
And finally, just like yesterday, the concert will be in two parts.
There's a part for Wawa, and there's a part for me, so please look forward to both of them!
Yeah.
That is it for the rules.
The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Have fun!
See you soon! Bye-bye!
DRAWN TO DAWN
Enlivened by the powers that be
Governing the world round and round on an as-needed basis
It's clear to me they still can't see
I'm just a normal girl
Empowered by ancient ones' call
We're gonna be unstoppable, we're not at all
Nonsensical and mythical, a tension-lightening wave
Let's give them a 1-8!
1! 8! Tako da! 1! 8! Tako da!
Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina!
Sing with me!
タコだちの世界を守るためにタコになろう！
To protect the world of Takodachi, let's become Takos!
1! 8! Tako da! 1! 8! Tako da!
Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina! Ina!
いいタコになりますように
May you become a good Tako,
皆騒ぎて踊りましょう
everyone, make some noise and let's dance!
Never mind what you could've been
We're talking evolution, leave it all to me
Maybe just a touch of purple ink
What do you think?
It's a song you can't ignore
The ancient ones are calling you to be so much more
Just put your hand in my hand and be reborn
In a blink
Tell me what those legs are for
脳のイナが暴れだすのです！
The Ina in your brain is running wild!
You could use six legs more
いつも感謝ありがたや！
Always grateful, thank you so much!
We're all that's matching here
えりえりいっちょ！
Eri eri iccho!
So keep your eyes to fight your fears
イナイナイナイナ！
Ina Ina Ina Ina!
Am I listening to my song, or am I striking a chord with you?
Stringing you along, so that I'm making a follower of you
80 million strong, and we've still got some more to do
Everybody shout...
WAH! To the nation!
In an ocean of motion, do I have you in my possession?
I don't wanna hear you say that you're not in at your best yet
If you're wavering, devotion is all I request yet
So is it clear to you, that you're my dearest creation?
Oya, oya. A cute little Takodachi found his way here.
Well, well. A cute little Takodachi found his way here.
Experimentation might be necessary.
Takos, we have to cook!
いいタコダチの作り方
How to make a good Takodachi
ひっくり返して丸くして
Flip them over, make them round...
ころころまわして こがらしに
Spinning round and round, in the cold wintry wind,
ちょっとばかり なかよくふわふわ
let's get along just a little, fluffy and soft.
いったらそう、すべていただき
Once I say so, yes, I'll take it all!
Like the powers that be
The ruler of the world run on insanity
It's clear to me, you still can't see, I'm just a normal girl
Empowered by ancient ones' call
We're gonna be unstoppable, when horror calls
Nonsensical and comical, adventures lie in wait
Let's talk about the future to be
Rewriting all of history and our destiny
With cookies as our currency, this priestess can finally heal
In Tako's domination, once more we'll fly
Or obstacles we'll tackle, yeah, tabehoudai!
No doubt about it, dimensional, welcome to my world!
1st! Tako-tako!
2nd! Tako-tako!
Ina! Ina! Ina, Ina, Ina!
これいいね
This is nice,
世界征服も
even world domination.
守るために 強くなろう！
Let's become stronger to protect it!
So, colorfully eating, but
Only world domination is what she can...
Our priest of never-ending fun
I want the world on fire, but first, I want a cookie, and I'm done!
So, colorfully eating, but
Only world domination is what she can...
Our priest of never-ending fun
I want the world on fire, but first, I want a cookie, and I'm done!
So, colorfully eating, but
Only world domination is what she can...
Our priest of never-ending fun
I want the world on fire, but first, I want a cookie, and I'm done!
私のもの そう 私のもの
It is mine, yes, it is mine,
数千 数百年の財宝
a treasure of thousands, hundreds of years
この船に眠る
sleeping on this ship.
Hey everyone! Get ready to clap... for Day 2! Are you ready?
古びた伝説は
The old legend is
呪われた幽霊船に
on a cursed ghost ship,
続く夜の航路
the voyage continues into the night.
そこに富が残る
Where the wealth remains,
海賊の夢があるのなら
if there's a pirate's dream,
ただ従うでしょう
you'll probably just follow.
雲の間を行く
Passing through the clouds,
若き乗組員よ
oh young crew members,
命を以て 航海に帰してやろう
I'll return you to the voyage with your lives!
止まない雨の弾丸で
With a rain of endless bullets!
狂おしいほど
So crazy that it
この瞳焦がす
burns these eyes,
生命の炎 薔薇の色彩
the flame of life, the color of a rose.
洗う 宝石の名なら
If it's the name of a washed jewel...
私のもの
It is mine,
そう 私のもの
yes, it is mine!
奪ってみろ
Try to steal it,
命の証を
the proof of life,
あなたが求める すべてを
everything that you desire!
輝くは すべて錆びついて
The shining things will all rust away,
それでもなお 目に焼き付くなら
but if they're still burned into your eyes,
うたかたと共に 沈め
sink down along with the bubbles.
暗い海 一人堪える
Enduring alone in the dark sea,
愚かな海賊の悲報
the tragic news of a foolish pirate.
風は笑う
The wind laughs.
満月の金銀宝飾
Gold and silver treasures under the full moon,
七つの海の宝玉に
at the jewels of the seven seas,
群がる 獣ども
the beasts gather round.
連れ出す舟よ
O ship that carries me away,
祝福して
bless me,
嵐の向こう
beyond the storm.
進むのなら 朽ち果てたとしても
Even if it decays as we move forward,
枯れない 魂まで奪わぬよう
so that even my undying soul will not be stolen.
永遠の美貌 そんな幻 どうだっていいでしょう
Eternal beauty, such an illusion doesn't matter, does it?
手放せ 翼はついたから
Let go of it, for I have grown wings.
さあ行こう 夜明けに舵を向けて
Now, let's go, steering the rudder towards the dawn.
風に吹かれて 誰も気づかぬよう
Fanned by the wind, as if no one notices,
区別がつかない モノクロの世界
a monochrome world that cannot be distinguished.
色を足しても 何も見えなくて
Even if I add color, I cannot see anything,
まるで私は 息を止めていた
as if I had stopped breathing.
もういいよ 遠くても 叶えたい 私は
It's alright now, even if it's far, I want to make it come true...
この世界 惑いも 抱きしめていたいのに
Even though I want to embrace the hesitations in this world,
夢のキャンバスに 描き続ける意味は
the meaning of continuing to paint on the canvas of dreams...
この胸に 輝いている ストーリー
is the story shining in this heart.
溺れることに 意味などないけれど
There is no meaning in drowning, but...
拾い集めた 欠片 失うの
will I lose the fragments I've gathered?
そして夜は その冷たさを 溶かして手を伸ばした
And so, the night melted away that coldness and reached out its hand.
もういいよ 遠くても 届けたい 私は
It's alright now, even if it's far, I want to reach you...
抜け出す 涙も 抱きしめていたいのに
Even though I want to embrace the tears that escape...
夢のキャンバスに 心込めるのは
putting my heart into the canvas of dreams...
この空に 描き出していく ストーリー
is the story I will draw in this sky.
そして夜は その冷たさを 溶かして手を伸ばして
And so, the night melted away that coldness, reaching out its hand...
もういいの 遠くても 叶えたい 私の
It's enough now, even if it's far, I want to make it come true...
この世界 言葉で包んだ
my world wrapped in words.
夢のキャンバスに 色を足していく
Adding color to the canvas of dreams...
この胸に 今輝いて
now shining in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 壊れかけてもいい
It's fine if I'm not strong, it's fine if I'm breaking,
この心は 永久に羽ばたいて
this heart will flap its wings for eternity.
響くように 塗り替えていく 私色
I'll repaint it in my own colors so it resonates.
Hello, everyone!
It is Day 2 of Drawn to Dawn!
Yes, yes. Welcome to Day 2 of Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis' first concert, Drawn to Dawn!
Are you guys enjoying the show so far?
Yay!
Ah, you know, I was really...
I want to talk about Tako Tako first because...
...yesterday, I heard you guys sing along to the instrumental...
...and I was like, "Ah, I feel bad for not singing on Day 1."
But you know, I knew I was opening for, you know, Day 2...
...so I kind of thought of a better song to open than Tako Tako.
So, hope you guys had fun singing it! Thank you again!
And of course, I sang two of my senpais' songs...
...Senchou's Dead Man's Chest and Towa-senpai's Palette.
Oh, I specifically... I specifically wanted to...
...choose their songs...
...because they are, you know, senpais that I really look up to.
And I always feel like...
...my journey here wouldn't have been possible if I didn't discover my senpais many, many years ago.
And I always, you know, wanted to pay respect to...
...the path they paved for us.
So, yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed it!
I'm so nervous again!
Yeah.
And, um, you know, I...
...of course, didn't really tell you guys specifically what penlight colors to use...
...but I knew you guys would get my message because we share a brain cell, right? Right?
Yeah! So, well...
...now going by the different setlist, because we, you know, have different setlist for Day 1 and Day 2...
...so, you know, going by the process of elimination...
...we have a couple of songs from my new EP left. Actually, who...
...bought my EP?!
Yay! Thank you so much!
I hope you were lucky to get an autograph. I tried to sign as much as possible, but...
...I knew, you know, sometimes you can't be lucky.
Thank you, thank you! But yeah, I want you guys to have even more fun than before today.
I mean, you always have fun, so that's good, but, yeah!
And, you know, sing along, have fun, and...
...I always think that a live stage is where not only me performing is creating...
...the performance, but you guys as well. You really help...
...you know, help everyone with that special experience.
So let's create an unforgettable memory together today, okay?!
Yay!
Anyways, um...
...I would also like to shout out to those watching at home and at the live viewings in the cinema. Hello! Hello to you again!
And also...
...the lovely, lovely girls doing a watch-along right now. Hi, guys! Thank you! Bae, IRyS, and everyone else...
...doing the watch-along, thank you, thank you!
Um, you know, I'm always amazed by everyone's support...
...and really, without the support of HoloEN members as well, like, I wouldn't have had...
...the confidence to stand here today. Thank you, I love you!
And of course, I would like to remind you guys about the hashtag for today's concert as well: #TakoToriFirstConcert, as usual.
Post your thoughts about it, post the screenshots, no videos! No videos!
Post the screenshots, and, you know, whenever we have time, we've been checking the hashtag, and of course, after...
...as well. I want to hear what you guys thought about the live, so, yeah!
Thank you, thank you!
And, unlike yesterday...
...first MC means I, unfortunately, have to...
...bid farewell to those watching the sneak peek on YouTube. I'm sorry.
But, if you want to keep the party going...
...head to the streaming site via the description, the comment... I don't know where the comment is.
But I know that some of you guys won't get a chance to see my new outfit that I revealed yesterday, so...
...I thought, maybe, I'll do something... um, maybe you guys can help me...
...transition into the new costume here...
...so that even those of you...
...and on YouTube, teammates can see.
All right, so I'm gonna count down from three. Countdown with me, okay?
And then we'll switch into the new outfit for you guys to see.
Ready?
Ready? Give me a "one" if you're ready!
All right, all right, all right.
All right, here we go!
Three, two, one, ha!
Ta-da!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
All right, it's time to move on to the next song.
And I think this song also fits the starry stage perfectly.
No, not that one yet, but...
...this one is from one of my favorite franchises.
So I hope you guys listen.
Anyways, the song will fit the starry stage perfectly.
Please give it a listen.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The free portion of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!