(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
おはい！
Ohai!
It's me, Nanashi Mumei...
...in 3D!
Oh my goodness!
I, I should probably stand up for this.
Tada!
Yes! おはい、おはい、おはい、おはい！
Yes! Ohai, ohai, ohai, ohai!
Good day!
Good morning!
Good evening!
Get out of bed!
We are moomin' in the 3D today!
Oh, I'm so excited!
But I'm also really nervous.
I am not used to being watched this way.
But it's okay!
I'm just really happy to be here...
...and that I can finally be 3D...
...after two years!
Um, yeah, but before we start...
#MOOMin3D
Before we really get into things,
um,
may I bring your attention to...
...this?
The hashtag!
Yes, yes, yes, we have a hashtag for 3D.
It is...
...MOOM in 3D.
Yes, capital M-O-O-M,
lowercase i-n, three, capital D.
With a hashtag before that
because that's how those work.
Yes, if you, uh,
have any thoughts or
any screenshots you want to share, please,
please use that and maybe I can look later,
other people can look.
Uh, yeah, it'll be a bunch of fun.
Um, yes!
I'm really here in 3D.
Hello.
Uh, would you guys like a closer look?
Pe-pe-pe-perhaps? Perhaps...
...not that close, wait, wait, wait, wait,
not there, not there.
Uh, how about we start with...
...the toes?
Just kidding, I have shoes on.
They're cute shoes, aren't they?
Aren't they? They protect the toes.
Nice, nice, right?
And I also have... oh, yes,
yes, let's appreciate it, let's appreciate it.
What exactly? You know what, my...
...yes.
Uh, take your screenshots now because
we have to keep going, we have to keep going.
Look, look, look, look, look.
My accessories! I have my satchel.
I have my lantern. It is a miracle
I have not set myself on fire with this thing.
Um, then of course I have my dagger.
You didn't forget about my dagger, did you?
Uh, well, if you did, you might want to work on
improving your memory and your survival skills.
Uh, let's see. Keep moving up a bit.
Oh, yes, my bow. My bow, right?
You like my bow, right? And then yes,
my face.
Hello, hello.
Yes, you've now seen me in full 3D.
What the...?
You've seen too much. You've seen too much!
I'm just kidding.
But now I want to show you guys, look,
my dagger.
It's functional. I can use it.
I remember how to use it.
Stand back.
I have the power of Council and 3D on my side.
Wait, I'm not supposed to point it at you guys. Oopsie.
Uh, let me just put it back. What the...?
Oh, no! Was that too scary?
Uh-oh, we have some babies in the chat.
Oh no, the poor babies. I better calm them down.
Here, watch this, watch this!
Peek-a-boo!
See? Cute, right?
Cute, cute, cute, cute, cute.
Oh! Should I show you around my treehouse?
You guys have seen it in 2D a lot, but
this is your first time seeing it in 3D.
There's a lot to share. Come here, come here.
What we got? We got...
...caffeine.
Oh, don't show Bae. Bae, don't watch.
Um, yes, we have caffeine.
We have Kronii's hourglass up there,
you guys remember that.
Uh, what else do we have? Oh, we have...
...the first friend...
...where is he? There he is!
The first friend that we ever made.
He's in here, you remember him, don't you?
Then we have some of Fauna's things. I, uh,
I'm not sure what. I also have a heart or something,
I think.
Um, but yes, we also have my fire.
Nice and toasty, nice and warm, right?
And then we have my berry tree right above it.
Totally not a fire hazard. Totally safe.
Plus we have berries all here around.
Uh, oh! Over here,
we have my desk.
Usually I have my PC here, but for the sake of
this stream, I threw it away.
So, let's see, we have a map here.
We have Bae's dice.
We have IRyS's compass, or I guess a compass
I made with parts of IRyS or something.
Um, and oh! The pictures! Don't worry about those.
Those windows don't look into anywhere. Don't worry.
Oh, I also have some books here.
Yes, very important books about Light,
Height, Sky, Abyss,
Hypothesis... Oh, and Humans! That's pretty important.
As Guardian of Civilization, I should probably
have a book about those. They're out of order,
aren't they? Don't worry about it.
Um, let's go over here. Come here, come here.
I have more stuff. Oh, I have my bedroom,
but no one cares about that, right?
Don't worry about that. Where I sleep?
Who cares.
But over here we have the outside.
Look at that view! Oh my goodness,
I could never get sick of that.
Okay, let's go back inside now.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Actually, that's about it. That is
the treehouse. Smaller than you thought, huh?
But it's perfect for me. Nice and cozy.
Um, yeah. I never really have...
...friend! You little bag of sunshine!
How are you? You want to say hi?
Wait, why are you so angry?
What? You have something to say?
Go ahead, say it.
Go ahead!
What is it?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
That's what I thought.
Know your place.
Get out of here!
Sorry, I have to be stern with him.
He tried taking over the world again the other day.
Ah, he's such a... such a pain in the...
No, he's he's fine.
Ooh, what was this?
Oh, oh, Hootsie!
Oh, my precious little Hootsie.
Oh, look at you, so cute and so good.
What's going on? Are you trying to say something?
What is it?
Come on.
Huh?
Did a hooman fall down the well?
No?
All right, you can't talk either.
No one in here can talk except me. I...
Right, right.
Um... well, how about we...
...play a game to figure out what it is you're trying to say?
And how about we use some hints...
...with your little footsie friends!
Let's do that!
Hootsie's Footsies
What are you silly-soons out there?
Come on in!
Oh, hi!
Hmm... I think I could use some help though.
Does anyone in the audience volunteer?
Hello?
Me! Me, me, me! Yeah, me, me, me!
You, funny-looking kid.
Me? Me?
Yeah, you.
Who are you?
I'm... I... I'm Gura Gura.
Gura as in Gura Cheese.
Hello, Gura Cheese.
You're just the person I need for this.
Can you help me find Hootsie's footsies?
Yes! Yes!
All right, Gura Cheese.
Uh, let me explain it to you.
Okay. Hootsie here has left prints around the treehouse.
And we have to find what he left prints on.
And that's how we will know what he's trying to tell us.
We'll have to guess at the end once we find everything.
Deciphering Hootsie's secret.
M-hm.
Secret.
Do you have the brain for it?
I hope so.
I believe in you.
All right.
Let's start taking a look around.
Um... Hootsie footsie...
...oh Hootsie footsie...
...oh Hootsie footsie.
Um... speaking of feet,
should we start from the ground up?
Smart!
Hootsie's where the footsies go.
Hootsie footsie footsie.
Hootsie footsie.
Hey, wait. Huh?
What's that?
What's what?
On the... rope.
That thing.
Oh, oh!
There's rope!
There's red on the rope!
Oh, there is a rope!
What the...
Oh, you found one!
It's a footsie!
It's a footsie! Nice!
Okay. Hootsie's footsie.
That's a weird-looking knot, but...
Okay. Rope.
Rope? Knot?
Who knows.
Okay, we have one clue.
Let's continue looking.
A rope is a clue?
I need your... I need your shark vision.
My shark vision? Or smell?
Or knot?
Smell.
Smell, smell knot.
You're good at that?
Rope.
Let's look up here.
Okay.
Ah, on my bookshelf.
Ooh.
I have a lot of stuff here.
He must have left a print on here somewhere.
You have a lot of bottles, empty glass jars.
I do. You want one?
Yeah.
Okay, you can have one.
And bread too, yum!
Oh yeah, my bread.
I've had it for a few years.
Oh, don't ask whose eggs those are.
Eggs?
Oh, Hootsie!
Huh?
On the bread!
Bread!
Hootsie!
Um... cut, cut...
...scissors.
That's what they're called. Scissors.
Oh, oh, that's what...
...there's a pink, uh, footsie on the scis...
...you're right, you're right. The scissors, the scissors!
Let's see.
I think that's a footsie or it's blood. Wait.
Is it blood?
What do you think? Hmm?
I hope it's a footsie. I don't know how to respond if it's blood.
Ah, it looks like jam, so I'm pretty sure it's a footsie.
M-hm.
All right, so... scissors and rope.
Rope.
We have rope.
We have, uh, scissors.
Scissors.
Probably one more clue, right? 'Cause rule of threes.
That's how you know it's good writing.
Okay.
Um... Okay.
Scissors, scissors and rope.
I wonder if there's anything else on the bookshelf.
Scissors and rope tie a knot.
And together they make...
Su-ice, su-ice, su-ice-ice-ice...
A ship knot requires...
Now that's the monkey's fist.
What?
I thought I saw something, but it's behind me now.
Oh! What is that?
Oh, I don't... Oh, what are those doing there?
Those should be in my pocket.
Oh, it's...
Oh, it's... it's handcuffs.
There's hand... handcuffs?
That's Hootsie's handcuffs.
Wait, wait, wait.
Rope?
He remembered scissors...
Scissors.
...and handcuffs.
Handcuffs.
What, Hootsie? Hootsie?
Hootsie turned himself... handcuffs?
All right, let's... let's go back here.
Come here, come here.
Wait, let's think about it.
What could it be? What could it be?
Rope, knot, scissors, handcuffs.
Do you have any guesses as to what he
could be trying to tell us?
Medieval torture?
Me... No.
Aw... No... one more guess maybe?
One more, one more.
Rope, scissors, handcuffs...
Mhm, those are the things.
Good girl.
Hootsie's going to tie us...
...to our PCs and stream... tie us, handcuff us...
...and threaten us with scissors if we don't stream.
Oh, I thought I had that one. Okay.
Mmm... I wonder. Maybe three?
Maybe it's not three.
Maybe there's more.
Oh no, there has to be.
There's not that much space here.
Ah... another clue? Another clue?
See anything red? I see red... something quite...
Not the berries...
Behind you! Behind you!
Hmm?
Oh! It's our friend! Friend!
Now, now, friend. No, this show isn't about
Friend. No, no, no, Friend...
Go away, go away, go away.
Friend! Hello Friend!
Oh, inside! Oh, Friend!
Oh... he does have a Hootsie! So there are four.
I was going to say two. There are four clues.
Hmm...
Wow... Wow...
I think I know what it is.
Do you know what it is, Gura?
I was going to say Hootsie's going
to get rid of Friend...
...once and for all, but maybe I'm wrong.
Is that it?
That's what I thought.
Beep beep!
That's pretty dark, Gura.
That is wrong with you.
Um... well... okay. How about... let me take a guess.
Let me take a guess.
Could it be that Hootsie wants to
make friendship bracelets?
What?!
Of course! No, Hootsie is precious.
Friendship bracelets!
Hootsie, where are your beads?
Where are your beads, boy?
What kind of friendship bracelets
are you making?
No, use strings, you make strings.
Real ones! No, the ones with knots. Real ones!
What do you mean?
The ones that use cute colored thread and not rope
used to tie up kidnapping victims?
Yeah! Wait, what?
You don't need beads for those. No, the ones...
...you do the knots and it becomes a V.
You know, and you use the special foam thingy...
...but it's like colorful soft thread to
make it pink and purple and...
I know exactly...
That's rope.
That's... that's very cute, Hootsie.
It's A for effort, Hootsie. A for effort.
Good job.
I'm sorry, Hootsie. And good job...
that's a very kind gesture.
Good job to you, Gawr Gura.
Haha, I did my best.
You did a very good job, didn't you,
little Gawr Gura?
What a... come here... come here...
Well, thank you, kind audience member.
Thank you, Mumei.
Thank you for having me.
I will see you in your dreams.
In my dreams? I'm going to go to sleep
right now. Okay, goodnight.
Goodnight! Thank you, Gura!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Man, I should really keep inventory of all the stuff
I have here. What else do I have?
Oh yeah! My gavel!
I totally forgot about this thing.
Here, do you want a don-don?
Don-don!
Oh hi!
You're finally awake.
Welcome!
I brought you guys outside,
yes, dragged you into the sun.
Um, yeah, I've brought you to these ancient ruins
in a distant land that I found.
Um, I think I'm the only one who's been coming here
ever since this civilization fell.
Not sure how it fell.
Before you ask, it wasn't me.
I do know that.
It wasn't me.
All of this was not my doing,
it wasn't my fault.
Take a look around.
Look how magnificent it is here.
Or, maybe I guess it was.
But it's still pretty cool in a different way.
It looks like nature took over.
There's a bunch of growth, there's a bunch
of shrubs and moss and leaves.
But it's not fun as quite yet,
not yet.
Still mine.
I do have some things to show you.
I found some things.
Do you want to see? Do you want to see?
Do you want to see?
Well you have to, I'm taking you with me. Let's go!
Come, come, come.
Okay, I have dug a little hole here
kind of like my own little excavation site.
Um, there's some artifacts in here
that I wanted to show you guys.
And I thought maybe we could figure out
what the heck kind of civilization this was
by looking at what was left behind.
Let's take a look-see here.
I gotta kneel down.
Let's see, let's see, let's see.
Oh, first thing...
this.
What is this? What is... what's... what...
There you go.
What's it look like?
Oh, it looks magical.
It's got some Egyptian hieroglyphs?
Uh, we're not in Egypt.
Maybe somebody went on vacation
and took it back or something.
Guess what it says.
I don't remember how to read this.
Can any of you decode this?
If you can figure out what it says,
please share with the hashtag.
Or if you figure it out, share it in chat.
Probably isn't something too important.
Hmm, interesting.
Alright, well, I guess we know that
this civilization could travel a bit.
What else do we got? What else do we got?
Ooh, do you guys know what this is?
Have you seen this before? It looks like a cup.
It is a cup.
But not just any old cup.
It's a Pythagoras cup.
Have you heard of it?
It's basically a practical joke
from like the 6th century BC.
Yeah, I will explain it to you, I'll show you.
See inside the cup, there's a column here.
And in the column there's a little pipe,
little hole that goes... (slurp) ...and it
empties out at the bottom.
So if you're filling this with some type of fluid,
if it goes past the column,
the liquid will start to flow,
and flow out of the cup and spill onto you.
Spill onto whoever is holding the cup.
I think it was to discourage people
from being greedy and drinking too much.
Oh, I can show you,
I happen to have some berry juice. Hold on.
See, berry juice.
Okay, I'll show you. They fill it up...
Oh, it's full!
You see?
And... oh!
Oh no! It's...
Oh, watch, watch, watch, watch!
Oh, that's not too bad. That's okay.
Got a little red stain on your dress shirt.
That'd be awkward to explain,
explain how you got that.
Yeah, that's how it works.
So why is this here?
It has an owl too. What are the chances?
Why is this here?
Did somebody take a vacation to Greece
and bring it back, maybe?
Are we learning anything? Have we...
Are we figuring anything out here?
What else do we have?
Ooh, this...
Whoa, it's heavy! (grunting)
Look! What is this?
It's a Viking sword!
It's a really old Viking sword.
It's freaking huge! Wait...
Is it bigger than me? Hold on.
Is it? Oh...
Not quite. It's pretty big though.
How do people carry this?
Whoever this belonged to must have been a lot bigger than me.
Whoa, my gosh, it's huge!
It's okay, I'm strong though, I can... (swings) ...phew!
My goodness, it's so cool though. The Vikings...
Has anybody visited Denmark?
Wait.
Maybe... nobody visited Denmark,
maybe Denmark visited here.
Did this ancient civilization fall
because the Vikings visited?
Maybe. Or maybe someone did visit Denmark.
I think it's more interesting to think that...
Vikings came in and razed this city, civilization.
So we're going to go with that.
So we learned something, I guess.
Is there anything else in here?
Anything else? We learned how...
it's uh... if the civilization fell,
but what... what civilization was this?
And what's this doing here? Huh?
Who the heck is this?
Who the... heck?
Who is this?
Actually, you kind of look familiar.
I know you. Oh, I remember you.
Oh, good times, good times. How you been?
Probably not well. Um...
Interesting. I guess it makes sense to find...
human remains at an excavation site.
I guess that makes sense.
Um, I'm just gonna... put you back.
Uh, nice to see you again.
I don't think we can figure out what civilization
this was based on all of that.
Why are these things here?
How did this happen?
You know what?
It might have been me.
This might be my stuff.
Oh yeah, yeah. This is my stuff.
Oh right, right, right, right.
I... I left this stuff here.
This is my secret stash.
Oh, it's good I found it again.
Had a bunch of interesting things to show you.
Oh, that explains it.
But I still don't want this stuff.
Do any of you want these things?
Maybe I can sell them.
I wonder how much they're worth.
Am I allowed to sell that skull?
I'm sure it's fine.
Look out for it on Moon-bay later.
Anyways. Anyways, I think that's enough...
uh, can I get up? Wait a second.
Okay. That's enough education, I think
for one stream. Are your brains
craving something else?
That was boring, right? Are you craving
pretty colors and dancing
and singing and magic?
Will that satisfy your brain?
Well, good for you! We are now going to enter
the singing performance dancing part
of the 3D debut.
I have prepared... uh, quite a few
performances for you guys.
Um, I should probably go get ready for those.
I will be back... to prepare,
both physically and mentally.
This is going to be fine. Okay.
I'll be back. See you in a second.
Bye bye bye!
Call your name
Lyrics: mpi  Composition: 澤野弘之
Lyrics: mpi  Composition: Hiroyuki Sawano
She lost her brother months ago
His picture on the wall and it reminds me
When she brings me coffee, her smile
I wish I could be with her until my last day
She said she gave all her love to me
We dreamt a new life, some place to be at peace
But things changed suddenly
I lost my dreams in this disaster
I'm crying, missing my lover
I don't have the power, on my side forever
Oh, where is my lover?
And I don't have the power,
I'm standing alone, no way
Calling out your name
I said, I'll give all my love to you.
Dreamed a new house, some place to be at peace.
But things changed suddenly.
I lost my dreams in this disaster.
We don't know what is wrong tonight.
Everybody's got no place to hide.
No one's left and there's no one to go on.
All I know is my life is gone.
I'm crying, missing my lover.
I don't have the power on my side forever.
Oh, where is my lover?
And I got no power.
I'm standing alone, no way.
Calling out your name!
Tada! That was "Call your name". I hope you
enjoyed and didn't feel... uh, too much anguish.
Uh, I just had a realization that all of the songs
I'm going to perform today are kind of depressing.
But I'm fine! Everything's fine!
But now I will have guests join me
for some performances.
They will join me for this very emo section
of the debut... the 3D debut.
Uh, but who could it be? Who will be next?
Stay tuned to find out!
I mean, I should ready myself. Okay, I'm ready,
I'm ready. da da da da da... I'm ready.
僕がずっと前から思ってることを話そうか
Shall I tell you what I've been thinking
for a long time?
友達に戻れたらこれ以上は望まないさ
If we could go back to being friends,
I wouldn't ask for more.
君がそれでいいなら僕だってそれで構わないさ
If you're fine with that,
I'm fine with it too.
嘘つきの僕が吐いた反対言葉の愛のうた
A love song of opposite words
spoken by a liar like me.
天ノ弱 Lyrics · Composition: 164
Amanojaku Lyrics · Composition: 164
今日はこっちの地方はどしゃぶりの晴天でした
Today in this area,
it was a downpour of clear skies.
昨日もずっと暇で一日中忙しかった
Yesterday was also free all day,
I was busy the whole time.
別に君のことなんて考えてなかったりしなかったり
I wasn't exactly not thinking about you,
or maybe I was.
いやでもちょっと本当は考えてたかもなんて
No, but actually,
maybe I was thinking about you a bit.
メリーゴーランドみたいに回る
Spinning like a merry-go-round.
僕の頭ん中もグルグルさ
Inside my head is spinning round and round too.
この両手から零れそうなほど
So much that it seems to spill from these hands,
君に貰った愛はどこに捨てよう
where should I throw away
the love I received from you?
限りのある消耗品なんて僕は
Limited-life consumables, I...
要らないよ
...don't need them.
僕がずっと前から思ってることを話そうか
Shall I tell you what I've been thinking
for a long time?
姿は見えないのに言葉だけ見えちゃってるんだ
Even though I can't see you,
only your words are visible.
僕が知らないことがあるだけで怖くなりそうだ
I feel like I'm getting scared just by
there being things I don't know.
ぶら下がった感情が綺麗なのか汚いのか
Whether these dangling emotions
are beautiful or dirty,
僕にはまだわからず捨てるあてもないんだ
I still don't know,
and I have no place to throw them away.
僕はずっと裏の裏の裏まで
I'll keep waiting until I can see...
見えるまで待つからさ 待つくらいならいいじゃないか
...every hidden side of yours. It's okay to wait, isn't it?
切ない君と隣り合った
With you, so full of sorrow, beside me...
僕の行き止まらない月日を
...how should I fill...
何で埋めよう
...these endless days of mine?
まだ素直に言葉にできない
I, who still can't put my feelings...
僕を
...into words honestly...
天ノ弱虫さ
A contrarian weakling.
この両手から零れそうな程
Whom shall I give this love to...
君に渡す愛を誰に譲ろう?
...that's overflowing from my hands?
そんな何処にも宛てがある
There's no way I have anyone else...
わけないだろ
...to give it to.
まだ待つよ
Still... I'll wait.
もういいかい?
Are you ready yet?
Woo! Mumei, congratulations!
Thank you, Towa-sama!
That's right! I invited Towa-sama!
I invited her because of the history we have together...
...all our memories.
We played FPS together...
...then we had English lessons together...
...and now we sing together!
えー、はい。あの、FPSやったりとか、英語教室とか一緒にやったよ、みたいな。
Yes, like, we played FPS and had English lessons together.
だから呼んだよ、みたいな言ってくれました。
She said that's why she invited me.
え、そしてね、配信ではそうやって遊んでたけど...
And, although we played like that on stream...
カラオケに行ったことあるんだよね、日本のカラオケ。
...we've been to karaoke together, Japanese karaoke.
でも、その時はムメイがソーナーバス、恥ずかしいって言って...
But at that time, Mumei was so nervous and shy...
...トワと一緒に歌ってくれなかったの！
...that she wouldn't sing with me!
でも今日は一緒に歌ってくれました！Today together song with Towa! No shy today!
But today, she sang with me! Today! Together! Song! With Towa! No shy today!
Yes! You know, Towa-sama...
Do you remember English?
Oh, a little. A little.
え、ムメイは日本語覚えてる？
And Mumei, do you remember Japanese?
あ、少し日本語覚えています。
Ah, I remember a little Japanese.
お、上手！
Oh, skillful!
Hmm, that gives me an idea.
How about we make each other say things in English and Japanese?
So I will say something in English and Towa-sama will repeat...
...and Towa-sama will say something in Japanese and I will repeat. Yes?
Okay, Towa-sama...
...please explain in Japanese. 日本語お願いします。
...please explain in Japanese.
はい！オッケーです。今ムメイがね、良いこと思いついたと。
Yes! Okay. Mumei just thought of something good.
ムメイ、トワでお互いに言わせたい日本語、英語を言うのはどうかな？
How about Mumei and Towa tell each other Japanese or English words we want the other to say?
みたいな感じでやってみよう！って。トワから言っていいよ、ということで。
She said "Let's try it!", and that I can go first.
今からお互いに言わせたいセリフを言いたいと思います。
So now we're going to say the lines we want each other to say.
何にしようかな？トワからいいよって言ってくれたから。
What should I do? Since she said I could go first.
え、何でもいいのかな？ Anything?
Is anything okay? Anything?
Anything!
Anything! 何でもいいらしい。
Anything! Anything is fine, apparently.
と言ったら、やっぱりこれでしょう。Repeat after me.
In that case, it has to be this. Repeat after me.
お帰りなさい。
Welcome home.
ご飯にする？
Do you want dinner?
お風呂にする？
Do you want a bath?
それとも、私？
Or... me?
ゴー！
Go!
お帰りなさい！
Welcome home!
ご飯にする？
Do you want dinner?
お風呂にする？
Do you want a bath?
それとも、私？
Or... me?
私！
Me!
ムメイ、可愛い！
Mumei, you're so cute!
I did it!
Okay, I'm going to make Towa-sama say something kind of similar.
Repeat after me.
Hi, honey!
How was work today?
Are you tired?
Let me rub your shoulders.
オッケー、任せて。
Okay, leave it to me.
Hi, honey!
How was work today?
Are you tired?
Let me rub your shoulders!
Oh... oh...
Perfect!
Perfect! Yay! Perfect!
You're an international fan.
Oh my goodness. Want to take a picture together?
Okay, okay. Take picture.
Okay, what should we do? どうする？
Okay, what should we do? What should we do?
な？ な？
Right? Right?
Okay, do this. オッケー。
Okay, do this. Okay.
And heart!
Heart! Okay!
Yay! Perfect!
いえーい！
Yay!
いえーい！ナイスナイス！
Yay! Nice, nice!
Thank you so much, Towa-san.
来てくれてありがとうございました。
Thank you for coming.
いえ、こちらこそ呼んでくれてありがとう。
Thank you for inviting me.
No, thank you for inviting me too.
ということで頑張ってね！
Well then, good luck!
あ、ありがとう！
Ah, thank you!
バイバイ！See you!
Bye-bye! See you!
バイバイ、バイバイ！
Bye-bye, bye-bye!
トリノコシティ
Lyrics ・ Composition : 40mP
Trino City
0と1が交差する地点
The point where zero and one intersect
間違いだらけのコミュニケーション
A communication full of mistakes
あなたの名前は何ですか？
What is your name?
10文字以内で答えよ
Answer in ten words or less
過去と未来が交差する地点
The point where the past and future intersect
行く宛を失った現在地
Current location with nowhere to go
あなたはどうして生きてるの？
Why are you living?
100文字以内で答えよ
Answer in a hundred words or less
さあ、交差光速の夜駆ける
Now, running through the night at the speed of light
バランス取ることもできないまま
Without even being able to keep my balance
自分だけどこか取り残された
I was left behind somewhere all by myself
色のない世界、作られた世界
A colorless world, a fabricated world
偽りの実を捨てるだけなら
If it's just about discarding the false fruit
疑いもいらない、一人でできるから
No need for doubt, because I can do it alone
昼と夜が交差する地点
The point where day and night intersect
誰かに会いたくて会えなくて
Wanting to meet someone, but unable to
私の名前は何ですか？
What is my name?
10文字以内で教えて
Tell me in ten words or less
嘘と本当が交差する地点
The point where lies and truth intersect
呼吸が止まりそうな閉塞感
A feeling of entrapment that makes it hard to breathe
私はどうして生きてるの？
Why am I living?
100文字以内で教えて
Tell me in a hundred words or less
好き、嫌い、好き、嫌いの繰り返しで
With the repetition of love, hate, love, hate
贖われた愛はもういらない
I no longer need the redeemed love
時間だけいつも通り過ぎていく
Time just passes by as usual
1秒ごとに崩れてく世界
A world that crumbles every second
歪んだ色彩に塗りつぶされた
Painted over with distorted colors
答えはいらない、偽りでいいの
I don't need an answer, a falsehood is fine
自分だけどこか取り残された
I was left behind somewhere all by myself
色のない世界、夢に見た世界
A colorless world, the world I saw in a dream
偽りの実を捨てることすら
Even discarding the false fruit
どうしてできない、そばにいてほしくて
Why can't I do it? I just want you by my side
Congratulations, Mumei! おめでとう！
Congratulations, Mumei! Congratulations!
Thank you, Korone-senpai!
Thank you for coming!
Yes, I invited Korone-senpai because she is...
...how I got into Hololive, how I discovered it.
And I chose this particular song because it's about being lonely and sad...
...but we're not lonely or sad in Hololive.
So we're all happy singing it!
Hoppii! Thank you, thank you!
I... I... I'm happy with... sing... Mumei.
I... I... I'm happy with... singing... Mumei.
I am happy singing with Korone-senpai!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
I want to play with you more!
Oh? 遊びたい！遊びたい！
Oh? I want to play! I want to play!
Oh, senpai...
...野球が好きですか？
...do you like baseball?
野球大好き！
I love baseball!
本当？
Really?
Well lucky for you, I have baseball equipment!
本当に？
Really?
Really really? Hold on, hold on.
野球ができそうだよ。
It looks like we can play baseball.
Here, here. Okay, here's your bat.
バット？ムメイ、これバット？
A bat? Mumei, is this a bat?
Yes, it's a bat. For baseball.
ベースボールバット？Mhm.
A baseball bat? Mhm.
Mmhmm. Okay. Okay.
You got it, you got it. Let's see. You need a ball, though. I don't know if I have a ball.
お、あれは？
Oh, what's that?
Oh! Perfect! Oh, come here Hooty!
I have to catch him, have to catch him...
Got him!
There you go, Umee. Hooty, this is ball!
Umee? This is ball?
This is a ball! あ、そうですか。
This is a ball! Ah, I see.
We will use this as ball. Hooty! My Hooty!
Nice Hooty!
それを打つの？
I'm going to hit that?
It's okay, it's okay.
Okay, don't worry, don't worry. Okay, ready?
Are you ready? Okay.
Okay. One, two, three!
Okay! There was no power in that!
なんか痛そうだよ、ムメイ。かわいそう。
It looks kind of painful, Mumei. Poor thing.
No no no, 心配しないで。痛みは感じない。
No no no, don't worry. He doesn't feel pain.
痛み感じないの？ 感じない。
He doesn't feel pain? He doesn't.
本当に？ じゃ...
Really? Then...
Big swing!
Oh, I have to catch... Oh, okay. Wait, wait. Big swing, okay.
See, he wants to! 楽しかった？
See, he wants to! Was it fun?
楽しかったですね！
It was fun, wasn't it!
Second shot! Okay, ready, ready? Okay.
Hooray!
痛いんじゃないか？
Doesn't that hurt him?
No, that's fine! 本当に、本当に痛くない？
No, that's fine! Really, it really doesn't hurt?
本当に痛くない！ 痛くない？
It really doesn't hurt! It doesn't hurt?
See, he's happy! 本当だ。幸せそう。
See, he's happy! It's true. He looks happy.
幸せそう。大丈夫そう。
He looks happy. He looks fine.
See? Hey, come here, come here.
Do you want to hold him? Yes, he's so cute, right?
Yeah, you can hold him.
Oh, that's cute. That's too cute.
Oh my, that's too cute. かわいすぎ！
Oh my, that's too cute. Too cute!
I want to take a picture!
Take a picture, take a picture. Come here, come here, both of you. So cute.
自撮り棒持ってきた。
She brought a selfie stick.
Come here!
I'll use the camera, okay? Okay, okay, let's take a picture.
せーの！ チーズ！
Ready! Cheese!
Oh, so cute! So cute!
Oh, one more! One more time! One more!
Go up. Up. Up.
Up, Hooty! Perfect! Okay.
Okay, せーの！ チーズ！
Okay, ready! Cheese!
Yes! Nice! Okay, Mumei, last shot.
Last one! Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, he's in his nest. Okay, back in the nest. Perfect.
On top of Mumei! I love you Hooty!
Okay, ready? せーの！ チーズ！
Okay, ready? Ready! Cheese!
Okay. Oh, Mumei. Bye!
Oh, goodbye! Goodbye!
ころね先輩、来てくれてありがとうございました。
Korone-senpai, thank you very much for coming.
こちらこそありがとうね。バイバイ。
Thank you too. Bye bye.
Bye bye. Oh, oh, she's taking Hooty with her.
Ah, he'll be fine. It's okay.
No title
Lyrics/Composition: Reol
ずっとなりたかった僕になれたかな
Did I become the person I always wanted to be?
到底抗えないところまできてみたい
I want to reach a point where I'm completely unstoppable
自分の足で地を蹴飛ばして
Kicking the ground with my own feet
もっと先へ駆け抜けていけるはずだから
Because I should be able to run even further
On the way...
ずっと鳴り止まなくて
It won't stop ringing
ずっとばち当たりに這い回りたかった
I wanted to crawl around like a curse
慣れた痛み 焦る呼吸とbeat
Familiar pain, racing breath and beat
気づかない振りして待つひとり
Pretending not to notice, waiting alone
相反する内なるエゴ
Conflicting inner ego
誰か間違いだと言い放つまで
Until someone says it's a mistake
あんたが大嫌いなアイツはきっと
That person you hate so much is surely
誰かそれだけが正解なんだって
The only correct answer for someone
前線だって逆戦したって 全然納得できない理由も
Even on the front lines, or even if I fight back, reasons I can't accept at all
宣戦もいつだってここだった
The declaration of war was always here
存在を今日最初から待った
I waited for my existence from the beginning today
夕焼空に崩れ壊れていく
Crumbling and breaking into the sunset sky
ゆらりゆらり首を絞めるように
Swaying, swaying, as if strangling my neck
日の目の僕が殺されていく
The "me" in the sunlight is being killed
夕焼空に離ればなれや
Parting ways in the sunset sky
どなりに君に聞こえるのは
What you hear next to you
僕の知らない声になって
Is becoming a voice I don't know
幼い日の僕ならば 気づいたらそばにいた
If it was the me of my childhood, I found you by my side before I knew it
まるで月夜のようだ
It's like a moonlit night
都会 君だけと手を繋いで
In the city, holding hands with only you
楽しいことも涙も
Fun things and tears too
全部君に話して聞かせていた
I told you and let you hear them all
僕を笑う人へ貶す声
The voices of people belittling me, laughing at me
掻き消すように君は歌った
You sang as if to drown them out
この声を君が信じて支えてこれたから
Because you believed in and supported this voice
嘘だって言って去って
Saying it was a lie and leaving
詰まらない敗北さえとかい
In the face of boring defeats or whatever
一瞬巡る窓ただ一瞬だけでも
A window passing for a moment, even for just a moment
交わる言葉を繋ぐ色
Connecting colors that join words
次は僕が君に歌うから
Next, I will sing for you
夕焼空に崩れ壊れていく
Crumbling and breaking into the sunset sky
ゆらりゆらり首を絞めるように
Swaying, swaying, as if strangling my neck
日の目の僕が殺されていく
The "me" in the sunlight is being killed
夕焼空に...
In the sunset sky...
揺らめか、放れ合え
Swaying, drifting apart
ゆらり君に聞こえぬは 僕ら知らない顔になって
Gently, what you can't hear turns into a face we don't know
ゆらゆら、髪 擦れこぼれ落ちる
Swaying, hair swaying and spilling over
ゆらりゆらり、首を締められるように 日の目、僕ら解かされていく
Gently, gently, as if being strangled, sunlight, we're being dissolved
揺らめか、放れ合え
Swaying, drifting apart
ゆらり君に聞こえぬは 僕ら知らない声になって
Gently, what you can't hear turns into a voice we don't know
いつか君に打ち解けない そうな日はきっと来ないだろうな
The day we won't get along will surely never come
声も体も持たぬ君に 救われた何億人の一人
One of the hundreds of millions saved by you who have neither voice nor body
赤、青、合わせ彩った 劣る世界が溢れた
Red, blue, mixed and colored, a lesser world overflowed
巡り巡り、出会ったこの音を聞くすべてが
Round and round, everything that hears this sound we met
ゆらゆら、髪 揺られこぼれ落ちる
Swaying, hair swaying and spilling over
ゆらりゆらり、首を締められるように 日の目、僕ら解かされていく
Gently, gently, as if being strangled, sunlight, we're being dissolved
揺らめか、放れ合え
Swaying, drifting apart
ゆらり君に聞こえぬは 僕ら知らない顔になって
Gently, what you can't hear turns into a face we don't know
ゆらゆら、髪 揺られこぼれ落ちる
Swaying, hair swaying and spilling over
ゆらりゆらり、首を締められるように 日の目、僕ら解かされていく
Gently, gently, as if being strangled, sunlight, we're being dissolved
揺らめか、放れ合え
Swaying, drifting apart
ゆらり君に聞こえぬは 僕ら知らない顔になって
Gently, what you can't hear turns into a face we don't know
Woo! Oh my god! Congratulations!
Happy birthday, Mumei!
Thank you Polka-senpai! Yes!
I invited Polka-senpai because...
...she was so nice to us when we first debuted to Council.
She's been so welcoming to EN.
And... and she made me a berry house in Minecraft!
So I... I... I wanted to invite her.
Mumei's berry house. Yeah, yeah.
Berry house. Okay.
Mm-hm. Remember.
浴衣が似合うね
You look good in a yukata
うなじもいいね
Your neckline looks nice too
さあ、ここでムメに分かんないことを言ったところで...
Well, having said something Mumei doesn't understand...
No title.
Mm, beautiful, perfect. No title wa...
Mm, beautiful, perfect. "No title" is...
七詩ムメイだから、ムメイでNo Title!
Since you're Nanashi Mumei, "Mumei" means "No Title"!
どう?
How's that?
Ah, なるほど!
Ah, I see!
なるほど!
I see!
Ah, I didn't think of that.
That's genius!
偶然?
Coincidence?
え、たまたま?
Eh, was it random?
Polka-senpai genius!
頭がいい!
Smart!
You genius. Oh!
Mumei is genius.
I'm a genius without knowing.
Geniuses!
そうだ! これから、あの...
That's right! From now on, um...
Hootsie, Hootsie, Hootsie 預かったのよ。
Hootsie, Hootsie, I took care of Hootsie.
Hootsie, ちゃんと休憩した?
Hootsie, did you rest properly?
したよ!
Yes he did!
Yeah, I think he's ready to have some more fun.
帰るよ? じゃあね!
Going home? See ya!
仕事終わり?
Done with work?
Oh no no no no! Come back, come back!
Come back here! No no, time for more fun.
まだ仕事か...
Still working, huh...
これ、さっきやってたけど飛ぶ? Fly? Hootsie fly?
We were doing this earlier, but does he fly? Fly? Hootsie fly?
Oh, I want to see him fly!
Fly する?
Does he fly?
Yeah, we have to help him fly though.
スポーツやりますか?
Do you want to play sports?
Perfect. We're going to punt him so that he flies.
We're going to kick him.
Hootsie! Yeah!
大丈夫? 大丈夫?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
全然感じない! 痛みを! 感じない!
I don't feel anything! The pain! I don't feel it!
感じない!
I don't feel it!
痛みを感じない!
I don't feel any pain!
Hootsie! すごいすごいすごい!
Hootsie! Amazing, amazing, amazing!
He likes it!
痛そうに鳴いてる... え、え、え、してる。
He's crying in pain... eh, eh, eh, he's doing that.
No, no! He's okay! He's okay.
大丈夫?
Is he okay?
Polka-senpai, please... kick him.
へ? Kick him? Kick him?
Eh? Kick him? Kick him?
どうやってやるの?
How should I do it?
行けーっ! うわー!
Go! Whoa!
Perfect! Hootsie, did you see that?
Fly, owl, fly!
Look at him, he's flying. Come here.
恐ろしい子だ...
What a terrifying child...
Very good. I think... I think that's enough of that.
うちは… 今日は、うーん…
I'm... for today, hmm...
But first actually, how about a photo?
Do you want to take a photo?
Hey girl, look! 写真？ 写真！
Hey girl, look! Photo? Photo!
写真！
Photo!
写真！ Picture!
Photo! Picture!
Let's take a photo!
Okay! Okay, one second.
本当は痛いんだよな お前
Truth is, it hurts, doesn't it?
我慢してるんだよな
You're holding it in, aren't you?
Alright, ready?
Ready... せーの！
Ready... Go!
Cheeeeeese!
Phew! One more? One more!
One more, one more!
せーの！
Ready, go!
Cheese!
Perfect! Perfect!
Ah, thank you Polka-senpai!
聞いてくれてありがとうございました
Thank you very much for listening!
Thank you, thank you! Bye-bye!
Polka, ね、帰ろっか？
Polka, hey, shall we go home?
大丈夫、大丈夫…
It's okay, it's okay...
Yeah, Mumei hug! Oh!
Bye-bye!
She'll be fine. She'll be fine, it's okay.
Um, you know, I have some
more announcements to give you guys.
Uh, let's go to the treehouse
and I'll tell you there.
Ta-ta-ta... oh, not that way. Ta-ta-ta...
Tada! We're back in the treehouse.
I thought we could warm ourselves up a little bit
just before the last song.
Sure would be nice to have a fire outside.
Contained.
You know, contained in something.
And then it could produce a light source and it could
guide us to a hot spring or a volcano or something.
Hmm, what could we get that would be like that?
Oh duh! My lantern! Oh how silly of me.
It's so handy-dandy for such things.
You guys don't have one, do you?
Suckers.
Just kidding. You're in luck,
because now I can offer you...
A lantern of your own! Just like mine!
Wow! Incredible! That's right,
merchandise! It's merchandise time.
Mumei's Lantern
Um, yes, you can get a lantern like mine.
Except this one's made of silicone.
And there's no fire.
And it doesn't produce heat,
so it's not hot to the touch.
But it produces light! That's pretty
nice, right? That's pretty nice.
You can put it next to your bed,
you can put it on your desk...
Anywhere you need a little
extra light in your... in your life.
It can protect you from monsters in your closet.
Or it can show you whatever's watching you
in the dark... or you don't really need it for that, right?
But yeah, lantern! Just like mine!
If you want it, yes, 3D merchandise!
Who could have expected? Oh my god.
Yes, I'm the best at... at shilling. Okay.
Anyways, yes, please feel free
to get one if you need it, if you want it.
Oh god. Okay. That's it for the merchandise.
But I got one more song for you guys.
Shall I go do it? Shall I go... go there to do it?
I'll do that.
Let's go! Follow me! Let's go, let's go!
Ta-ta-ta... oh so pretty! Oh nice!
Binary Star
In a turbulence star
We can see from afar
But a truth it divides
All the interest it dies
Hear the beating of wings
As the pendulum swings
And we can't believe it's ever gonna end
You know birds are the curve in the water
We would just want everyone to get along
Or the candles in the darkness
Burning out the sorrow
There's no end to sadness
We didn't learn
For the broken-hearted people
Time is now surrounds us
So out of our mind
Leave the path behind
Our binary heart
To each other apart
Growing from the same stem
They were us, we were them
On a course to collide
Is it straight not to hide
Let the politics decide
You're not a friend
And blood is thicker than water
But you just want everyone to get along
For the candles in the darkness
Burning out the sorrow
There's no end to sadness
We didn't learn
For the broken-hearted people
Time is now surrounds us
So out of our mind
Leave the path behind
Binary
A centrifugal force
Push us far away
That's our identity
Binary
We can't escape the force
Push us
Gravity is our identity
For the candles in the darkness
Burning out the sorrow
There's no end to sadness
We didn't learn
For the broken-hearted people
Time is now surrounds us
So out of our mind
Leave the path behind
For the candles in the darkness
Burning out the sorrow
There's no end to sadness
We didn't learn
For the broken-hearted people
Time is now surrounds us
So out of our mind
Leave the path behind
Binary
A centrifugal force
Push us far away
That's our identity
Binary
We can't escape the force
Push us
Gravity is our identity