(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Once upon a time... in another world.
A girl was studying...
PAVOLIA REINE INTRODUCTION MOVIE
PRODUCED BY MERRYWEATHER MEDIA
...at an academy of magic.
[A FEW YEARS LATER]
Who can show me a blue illumination spell?
Oh come on, you should all know this by now!
Pavolia Reine.
Yes!
Amazing work, Miss Reine!
Amazing, Reine!
Teach me!!
How did you become so good, Reine?!
Oh, it's just a lot of studying!
Can you share us your routine?!
Sure!
Every day, I wake up at 5am.
I take a shower,
do some exercises,
and make a cup of tea!
Then I go through just 4 or 5
spellbook volumes before class.
Oh no...
That's kinda hard...
It's not that bad once you get used to it!
I bet you're gonna score perfectly
on the potions exam today.
Potions?
Exam?
Oh no.
How could I forget!!!
Ah. It's marked as pancake day.
PANCAKE DAY!
Why did I remember pancake day
and not the potion exam?!
I guess 4 hours of sleep is catching up to me...
Well! Whatever! I'll do my best!
POTION 101
A Beginner Guide to Potions & Alchemy
Potion Exam
3:00 - 5:00
I speed-read through all 6 alchemy
and potion brewing books I had...
I can do this!
And... you may all begin!
A bit of this... and a bit of that...
Wait...
Miss Reine, is your potion quite alright?
Yes, teacher! It should be...
I added in unicorn hair,
and a dash of cinnamon.
A dash of cinnamon?! No!!
That's a portal potion, Reine!!
Wha-?!
Did my memory get jumbled?!
Everyone, get to the back of the classroom!!!
Why did I try to
speed-read the entire compendium?!
NOOO!!!
REINEE!!!
Nooo!!!!
Huh? Where am I...?
What strange buildings...
I sense it... magic...
Who're you?
...A zombie?
Bukalah gerbang keajaiban
Open the gates of wonders
Bentangkan sayap, ku melaju ke dunia baru
Spread my wings, I'm heading to a new world
Mentari tlah tiba
The sun has arrived
Kini sudah saatnya
Now is the time
Tantangan yang dinanti-nantikan
The long-awaited challenge
Sang putri merak
The peacock princess
Tertiup angin
Blown by the wind
Tak sengaja berpindah dunia
Unexpectedly moved worlds
Di tanah yang tak dikenal
In an unknown land
Misteri berlalu-lalang
Mysteries passing by
Kumpulkan tekad
Gather the determination
Gapai harapan
Reach for the hope
Kan kurajut satu mimpi baru
I will weave a new dream
Bukalah gerbang keajaiban
Open the gates of wonders
Bentangkan sayap, magic kan kau saksikan
Spread your wings, you will witness the magic
Lebur duka mari berdansa
Melt away the sorrow, let's dance
Kutunjukkan
I'll show you
Biru tak terlupakan
An unforgettable blue
Kilau hanya untukmu
A glow just for you
Mentari tlah tiba
The sun has arrived
Semangat yang membara
A burning spirit
Di dunia yang silih berputar
In a world that keeps turning
Sang putri merak
The peacock princess
Tak sabar menanti
Can't wait
Esok seperti apa yang tiba
What kind of tomorrow will arrive
Di tanah yang tak dikenal
In an unknown land
Setitik cahaya terang
A speck of bright light
Kuatkan hati
Strengthen the heart
Lekas berlari
Run quickly
Kabulkan mimpi
Grant the dream
Kan kurajut tanpa rasa ragu
I will weave without any doubt
Bukalah gerbang keajaiban
Open the gates of wonders
Lukiskan warna dalam berjuta angan
Paint colors in a million dreams
Sukacita tiada tara
Unparalleled joy
Kau saksikan
You'll witness it
Sinar biru menjulang
A towering blue light
Genggam erat tanganku
Hold my hand tightly
Hari-hari kulewati
The days I passed
Bersamamu di sini
With you here
Tawa canda, suka duka kubagi
Sharing laughter, jokes, joys, and sorrows
Dari rajutan mimpi
From the weave of dreams
Kini ku tak sendiri
Now I'm not alone
Dengan dirimu slalu menerangi
With you always shining
Bukalah gerbang keajaiban
Open the gates of wonders
Pemandangan yang tlah kau nanti-nantikan
The scenery you've been waiting for
Lebur duka mari berdansa
Melt away the sorrow, let's dance
Kutunjukkan
I'll show you
Biru tak terlupakan
An unforgettable blue
Kilau hadir untukmu
The glow is here for you
あの青空のせいだ
It's because of that blue sky
君の笑顔
Your smile
きらめく
Sparkling
雨上がりの午後
In the afternoon after the rain
絶妙な視線
An exquisite gaze
痛いくらいにドキドキした
My heart raced so much it hurt
いたずらに風が吹く
A mischievous wind blows
めくるページを
The flipping pages
隠した途端に
The moment I hid them
世界中がぐるぐる回る
The whole world spins around
気付かれたくない自分に
To the self that doesn't want to be noticed
今以上になれるかな？
Can I become more than that?
溢れそう 泣きそう 駄目だよ
It's about to overflow, I'm about to cry, I shouldn't
あの青空のせいだ
It's because of that blue sky
キミも同じであれと願う
I hope you're the same
この恋はどこまで
How far will this love go?
終わらせたくない想い
These feelings I don't want to end
打ち明ける勇気が
The courage to confess
出せる日まで
Until the day I can find it
まだまだこのままで
Staying like this for a bit longer
ねえねえそうじゃなくて素直になれない
Hey, hey, it's not like that, I just can't be honest
眩しいShine mirage 二人のラインたぐり
Dazzling shine mirage, pulling our lines
寄せたなら would you be mine?
If I draw closer, would you be mine?
妄想する物語
A story I'm imagining
そうスルーするだけの恋のループ
A loop of love where I just look away
気づかれたくないのに
Even though I don't want you to notice
今以上になりたいんだ
I want to become more than we are now
溢れそう 泣きそう どうして
Overwhelming, about to cry, why?
あの青空のせいだ
It's because of that blue sky
両手で日を遮って
Blocking the sun with both hands
俯いたこの恋はどこまで
How far will this love, looking down, go?
終わらせたくない想い
These feelings I don't want to end
だんだん大きくなる
Gradually growing larger
影はキミと二人であれ
May the shadows be of us together
夜になると
When night falls
すぐに会いたくなるよ
I immediately want to see you
綺麗な星の光
The beautiful starlight
それより明日がいい
Tomorrow is better than that
ずっと隣にいさせてほしい
I want you to let me be by your side forever
あの青空のせいだ
It's because of that blue sky
キミも同じであれと願う
I hope you're the same
この恋はどこまで
How far will this love go?
終わらせたくない想い
These feelings I don't want to end
打ち明ける勇気が
The courage to confess
出せる日まで
Until the day I can find it
ちょっと待ってて
Wait just a moment
ラララ…
La la la...
この恋はどこまで ラララ
How far will this love go? La la la
打ち明ける勇気を
The courage to confess
ラララ…
La la la...
WHOA! Whose 3D showcase is this?
Whose 3D showcase is this?!
You guys are right!
Attention, please! I'm Pavolia Reine from hololive ID Generation 2!
Berhatian! Sang putri merak yang tertiup angin, aku Pavolia Reine dari hololive ID generasi 2!
Attention! The peacock princess blown by the wind, I am Pavolia Reine from hololive ID Generation 2!
Attention please! ホロライブID二期生 パヴォリア・レイネです！
Attention please! This is Pavolia Reine from hololive ID 2nd Gen!
Welcome to Reine's very, very special tea party!
Oh, before we start, please do tweet with this hashtag...
...this hashtag, #PavoliaReine3D!
My child, please tweet!
Because I would like to hear your kansou and opinion about the live!
Because I would like to hear your impressions and opinions about the live!
So what are you waiting for? Tweet right now!
Or later, if you want.
ツイートしてください！ぜひぜひね！
Please tweet! Definitely, okay?
Tweet!
Awas kalau nggak.
Watch out if you don't.
So, そうですね。 I started off with two songs.
So, that's right. I started off with two songs.
2曲連続歌いましたね。 最初は「Gate Open: START!」と...
I sang two songs in a row. First was "Gate Open: START!" and...
...「あの青空のせいだ」! Both are Reine's original songs!
..."Ano Aozora no Sei da"! Both are Reine's original songs!
YAY!
Ah, but oh no!
What am I gonna do? I gotta clean!
But before that, let me show you guys...
...show you guys the model!
How do you think I look?
WHOA! No, you don't see anything!
Shh! Camera, camera, camera!
Okay, YAY!
WHOA! You don't see—
Yeah! Nice, right?
Oh, Reine's back! Oh my god, for real!
Reine... Mmm! Yeah! You don't see anything...
...except me in my very clean room!
YAY! Clean room!
Okay, but for real though...
...what am I gonna do?
The 3D showcase, the private tea party is today!
But my room is still a mess!
Oh no! どうしようね。
Oh no! What should I do?
今日お披露目だったのに 部屋はめちゃめちゃダーティーですね！
It's my showcase today, but my room is super dirty!
NO! I've got some guests coming too!
What do I do? What do I do?
I guess I gotta get cleaning, huh?
Hah...
Oh well...
Ah...
Oh, I don't want to do this, but...
Wait just wait a little bit okay?
ちょっと待ってて。
Wait a second.
これから掃除します。So that...
From now, I will clean. So that...
よいしょっと。
Heave-ho.
Wait.
いしょ。
Heave-ho.
ああ。
Ugh.
Oh, and this one...
This one's like the heaviest.
うおー！
Whoa!
But it's okay.
We're putting this aside.
So the camera, it won't be...
Okay.
ふー！
Phew!
I did a lot of cleaning right?
めっちゃ掃除...
Did a lot of cleaning...
めっちゃ掃除した。
Did a lot of cleaning.
And because, uh...
you know, I'm feeling a little bit thirsty now.
掃除終わったからね。
Because I finished cleaning.
喉が...
My throat...
ちょっと、ちょっと...
A little, a little...
喉が乾いたんですね。
My throat is dry.
はあ。
Phew.
So now...
I'm gonna drink a little bit.
Let's drink.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
Oh!
じゅー！
Pouring sound
えっ、あわわわわ...
Eh, bubbles bubbles...
あわ、あわ、どうしよう、どうしよう、これ。
Wait, wait, what should I do, what should I do with this?
Oh my god.
Ya, kurang lebih lah.
Yeah, more or less.
Ya, maybe.
Ya, I think okay lah.
Yeah, okay.
I think...
I think that was perfect.
ばっちりですね。
It's perfect.
はい！
Yes!
Everybody,
for you!
Welcome to Reine tea party.
And it's time to...
乾杯！Cheers for the tea!
Cheers! Cheers for the tea!
Tumpah semua anjir.
It all spilled, damn.
Okay.
And now, apa namanya?
And now, what's it called?
Because we already done with the tea,
I'm now energized.
We can clean more.
Excuse me.
よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
And it's time to clean.
Let me get the broom.
Broom, broom... Broom, broom, broom, broom.
Tada!
I have the broom.
Where is the gomi?
Where is the trash?
Oh my god. Okay.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
Go!
よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
あれ？
Huh?
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
Yeah, gimana sih?
Yeah, how is it?
Aduh.
Ouch.
Iya, iya, gimana?
Yes, yes, how?
Iya.
Okay, okay.
Okay, goal!
Eh belum.
Eh, not yet.
Goal.
GOAL!!
We got it!
Yay, yay, yay, yay!
And then we buang the gomi.
And then we throw away the trash.
ふー！
Phew!
That was so tiring.
はあ。
Phew.
And then, ah, but that's not done.
Not done yet because...
I have a magic trick to show you.
Tada!
It's the hataki magic.
It's the kemoceng magic.
Ready to cleanse your soul.
うっ、うっ、うっ！
Ugh, ugh, ugh!
Yes.
Time to clean.
ふー！
Phew!
Well, you know what?
Look at this beautiful cityscape too.
You guys like this place so much right?
But this is not all.
You know?
Because I still have the bedroom to clean.
まだね。
Not yet.
はあ。
Phew.
まだクリーニング、クリーニングが必要。
Still need cleaning, cleaning.
部屋があるから。
Because there's a room.
Let's 掃除 the bedroom.
Let's clean the bedroom.
Okay?
掃除 to the bedroom!
Cleaning to the bedroom!
I'm here!
This is... this room might be familiar for you guys.
Of course!
And in here,
we have the spicy, spicy,
spicy, spicy...
brankas tuh apa dah?
what is a safe called?
And the hat,
and well, my spare clothes.
Spicy.
So we can't show the contents of this one in this stream, okay?
しーっ。Okay?
Shhh. Okay?
I'm gonna clean that.
And there's uh...
this too.
We got the fishing rod.
Fishing rod.
And we can clean this too.
Many, many, many things.
ああ、いいですね。
Ah, it's nice.
In here... fishing, fishing...
And then we go to this very, very
special place... chu chu chu,
my PC.
And oh, this is my... my desk mat with a...
specially drawn by Anya Melfissa.
And "Love me, love me" also.
Look, it's Holoro Desk Mat. Would you buy this?
I think this is very nice,
but too bad it's exclusive for me and me only for now.
Whoo!
Okay.
Okay. I think... that's enough cleaning, right?
Let's just take a little break.
Ah... ah...
Atatata...
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Whoo!
Ah, I'm satisfied.
And I think now it's time for someone to visit.
あの娘も呼んじゃおうかな。
Maybe I'll call that girl too.
Say it with me. Three, two, one...
Tatang!
Tatang! Oh!
Many, many Tatang!
Tatang!
Oh, look at these Tatangs. OMG.
I've just cleaned this room.
さっきお掃除したばっかりなのにね。
I just finished cleaning, too.
Oh my God. Well, let's pick up one, okay?
Many, many Tatang. Yay!
Hello!
Tatang!
Tatang! Yay! Look at this. Whoo!
Tatang was lost, but he is here.
He comes to my 3D showcase! OMG.
こちら, come here. Wow.
Over here, come here. Wow.
Oh, ading jatuh. Many, many Tatang falling.
Oh, one fell. Many, many Tatang falling.
Oh my God. So yeah. Well...
Whoo! Tatang. Please.
A Tatang, Tatang. I want to... I need to clean this room.
So, room, please. Tatang, I like it that you're... ini.
So, room, please. Tatang, I like it that you're... this.
I like it that you're falling down, but I need to cleaning. Okay?
So we can... we can move on to the guest segment, right?
I've got a lot of special guests today actually.
そうですね、ゲストパートに行きましょうか。
That's right, let's head to the guest segment.
Yeah. Tatang! Tatang! Let's come back later.
Whoo! Shoo shoo. Thank you. Thank you Tatang.
We'll play again later.
そうですね、今日はスペシャルゲストがたくさん来るよ。
That's right, many special guests are coming today.
And... where is the special guest, I wonder?
Mana ya? Tamu nya?
Where are they? The guest?
Oh! Looks like somebody's already here.
Oh, let's set the room up so we're ready for them. Okay?
部屋も準備するね。
I'll get the room ready too.
行け！チェンジ！
Go! Change!
真夏は誰のモノ？
Lyrics: 畑 亜貴 Composition・Arrangement: 原田 篤
Whose midsummer is it?
Lyrics: Aki Hata Composition/Arrangement: Atsushi Harada
赤い太陽のドレスで踊る
Dancing in a dress of the red sun
私のこと見つめているの
Are you staring at me?
目を逸らしたい でも逸らせない
I want to look away, but I can't
あぁ 情熱で焼けたい
Ah, I want to burn with passion
トキメキ以上のリズム
A rhythm more than excitement
今宵 知りたくて
I want to know tonight
いつもより大胆な
Bolder than usual
言葉を呟いた
I whispered the words
自分の気持ちなのに
Even though they're my own feelings
全然 分からなく
I don't understand them at all
理性がいま指令
My reason is now giving orders
コントロール不可能
Impossible to control
正体不明の恋が 届いてしまった
An unknown love has arrived
恥ずかしく思うけど
I feel embarrassed, but...
もっと知りたいの もっと知りたいの
I want to know more, I want to know more
いけない 夢だと気づきながら
While realizing it's a forbidden dream
赤い太陽のドレスで踊る
Dancing in a dress of the red sun
私のこと見つめる瞳
Eyes that gaze at me
目を逸らしたい でも逸らせない
I want to look away, but I can't
真夏は
Midsummer is...
真夏は誰のモノ？
Who does midsummer belong to?
あなたと私のモノにしたくて
I want to make it yours and mine
心が止まらない季節に
In a season where my heart won't stop
初めて胸の扉が
For the first time, the door to my heart
開いてしまいそうよ
Seems about to open
You knock knock my heart
ためらいがちのステップが
My hesitant steps
熱く変わる頃
By the time they turn hot
いつもならあり得ない
Usually impossible
衝動に戸惑うの
I'm bewildered by this impulse
あなたの手に
In your hand
私の手を
My hand
重ねたら何かが始まる
When they overlap, something begins
オーレイ！花火が照らす横顔
Olé! Your profile lit by fireworks
きっとこの日が来ると予感してた
I surely had a premonition this day would come
もう戻れない
Can't go back anymore
戻りたくない
Don't want to go back
真夏に誘われて
Lured by midsummer
あなたと私の夏にしたくて
I want to make it yours and my summer
心が止まらない季節よ
It's a season where my heart won't stop
甘く切ない香りで
With a sweet and painful scent
不意に泣きたくなる気がしたの
I felt like I suddenly wanted to cry
近付いたり離れたりの
Approaching and distancing
ドンステ！頭シビれてる
Don't stop! My head is tingling
ここにいてよ
Stay here
もう怖くないの
I'm not afraid anymore
何もかもが
Everything
紅い太陽のドレスで踊る
Dancing in a dress of the red sun
私のこと見つめる瞳
Eyes staring at me
目そらしたい
Want to look away
でもそらせない
But can't look away
真夏は誰のモノ？
Who does midsummer belong to?
あなたと私のモノにしたくて
I want to make it yours and mine
心が止まらない季節
A season where my heart won't stop
初めて胸の扉が
For the first time, the door to my heart
開いてしまいそうよ
Seems about to open
You knock knock my heart
ああ 情熱的に
Ah, passionately
抱きしめて
Hold me tight
Waaaah!
And that was Manatsu wa Dare no Mono?
And my guest was Kiara!
Kikiriki!
Holo holo holo holo! Oh, already high!
Hololive English no Takanashi Kiara desu! Hi! Yay!
I'm Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English! Hi! Yay!
I was invited to my little bird Kouhai's showcase! So exciting!
Thank you for being such a strict... yeah yeah yeah.
We had only one dance lesson together where there was no teacher.
So I took the yakume, the position of the teacher.
So I took the role, the position of the teacher.
And when Reine was on the floor taking a break, I was like...
Reine get up!
Nooo!
You have to dance!
Get up! Go!
We have no time! We have the studio for two hours only!
I want to review the floor instead.
Oh oh, this floor...
is very nice.
Yeah, we can review this floor.
What do you think about the sound?
Well, I mean, it should be wood. Do we hear the wood?
(Taps floor) It doesn't seem to be wood.
Reine, we knock knock the floor.
We knock knock the floor!
It's mystery flooring, but it's 10 out of 10.
10 out of 10! Bird approved.
I think to you, every floor is 10 out of 10.
It is, as long as it's cool enough to lie down on.
Oh my god, really quickly! We have to do some cute poses, okay?
Okay okay okay.
I want to do this. (Aww/Ohohoho)
Screenshot time!
Use Reine birthday hashtag, it's somewhere up there.
It's up there!
And I want to do a hug.
Ah, yes.
Ojo-chan! Gyu gyu gyu!
Ojo-chan! Squeeze squeeze squeeze!
And let's do back-to-back, like a shoot pose.
Shoot pose?
Like secret agent. Secret agent.
So! Hu! Hu! Na!
Yes!
So Ten-chan, you still have some stuff to do, right?
Yes! Thank you so much for coming!
I'm very very happy to be able to dance with you!
Me too! Let's do more soon!
Of course! Yay!
Okay, okay!
Bye-bye! Have fun!
And next song is...
...Love Me Love Me.
ずっと君の隣
Always by your side
じっと見てるばかり
Just staring intently
相合止まない雨
The rain of mutual love that won't stop
世界に二人きりのように
As if it's just the two of us in the world
永遠刻むように
As if carving eternity
心臓 今この手に
My heart, now in this hand
どんな痛みさえも
No matter what kind of pain
愛のカタチ
Is a form of love
運命に結ばれた小指を握る
Holding the pinky finger tied by fate
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise
LOVE ME LOVE ME
ワタシシカイラナイ
I only need me
LOVE ME LOVE ME
キミガイラナイ
You're not needed
ぎゅっと抱きしめたら
If I hold you tight
きっと逃げられない
You surely won't be able to escape
チクタク針が回る
The tick-tock hands are turning
世界に二人きり
Just the two of us in the world
現実壊すように
As if breaking reality
感情押し殺して
Suppressing emotions
どんな悲鳴さえも
No matter what kind of scream
愛のメロディ
Is a melody of love
運命に結ばれた小指を握る
Holding the pinky finger tied by fate
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise
LOVE ME LOVE ME
ワタシシカイラナイ
I only need me
LOVE ME LOVE ME
キミガイラナイ
You're not needed
愛して愛され
Loving and being loved
離れられない
Cannot be separated
You and me
ふたりきりでいい
Just the two of us is fine
Give me your love
願うほど滴る赤い色
The red color dripping as much as I wish
何もかも染めてしまう愛を
Love that stains everything
もっと頂戴
Give me more
ワタシシカイラナイ
I only need me
LOVE ME LOVE ME
キミガイラナイ
You're not needed
LOVE ME LOVE ME
Wow!
Hello, everybody!
Alright, I've got more people who want to celebrate with me today.
今日ですね、他にもお祝いしてくれる人たちがまだまだいるよ！
Today, there are still more people here to celebrate!
And they should be calling anytime soon.
Gak ada telepon gitu kah? Harusnya kayak...
No phone calls or something? It should be like...
Moshi moshi?
Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Angkat cepat! Lama!
Pick up quickly! Taking so long!
Ah, gitu dong.
Ah, there we go.
Hello?
Woi! Hello!
Hey! Hello!
Anjing suaranya kayak gitu!
Damn, the voice is like that!
Kremes-kremes anjir suaranya, woi!
The voice is crackling, damn, hey!
Moshi-moshi!
Hello!
Oh ya, moshi-moshi, apa password-nya?
Oh yeah, hello, what's the password?
Eh... Merrequat Coffee enak!
Uh... Merrequat Coffee is delicious!
Wih! Somad! Dua ratus ribu rupiah! Terbang!
Whoa! Somad! 200,000 rupiah! Flown away!
Yuk bagi, seratus ribu seratus ribu.
Let's split it, 100k each.
Iya bener, bagi dua, biar adil.
Yeah right, split in two, to be fair.
Okay, okay. Risu and Kobo, thank you so much for coming.
Makasih banyak sudah datang ke acaranya Tante Reine hari ini.
Thank you so much for coming to Auntie Reine's event today.
Yoi!
Yup!
Asik!
Cool!
Aku mau ngucapin selamat atas 3D-nya... akhirnya... debut!
I want to say congratulations on the 3D... finally... debut!
Buset, ini Risu lagi mana sih lu, toilet? Masih diterawang suaranya.
Damn, Risu where are you, the toilet? The voice is still crackling.
Wah, ini suaranya diterawang aja ya? Kalian kenalan dulu dong kepada para viewers.
Wow, so the voices are just being sensed, huh? You guys, please introduce yourselves to the viewers first.
Oh ya, halo teman-teman.
Oh yeah, hello friends.
Aku, uh, definitely not in toilet, Ayunda Risu, Hololive Indonesia Gen 1.
I'm, uh, definitely not in the toilet, Ayunda Risu, Hololive Indonesia Gen 1.
Yay! Terus sebelahnya?
Yay! And next to her?
Aku boko-boko-boko-boko Kanaeru at your service,
I'm boko-boko-boko-boko Kanaeru at your service,
kohai kesayangan Pavolia Reine, Putri Merak, Kobo Kanaeru desu!
Pavolia Reine's favorite junior, the Peacock Princess, Kobo Kanaeru!
Asek! Oke! Yay! Oke!
Nice! Okay! Yay! Okay!
Kalau gitu, aku di sini aku mau meminta kalian untuk request-request pose untuk screenshot time gitu nggak sih?
In that case, I'm here... I want to ask you guys for some pose requests for a screenshot time, right?
Screenshot? Apa aja boleh sebenarnya. Baik-baik saja juga seru gitu lho.
Screenshot? Anything goes, really. Just being 'seiso' (pure) is also fun.
Kalau gitu yang seiso dulu ya, yang seiso. Aku tadi tuh ya tercengang-cengang melihat pose Reine dari samping.
In that case, let's do a pure one first. I was just amazed looking at Reine's pose from the side.
Aku mau Reine pose menyamping pegang pinggang.
I want Reine to pose sideways with hands on her hips.
Gini maksudnya? Ayi!
Like this? Ayi!
Kameranya dari samping! Kameranya dari samping!
Camera from the side! Camera from the side!
Wuih, besar sekali!
Whoa, it's so big!
Kayak gini? Oh my God!
Like this? Oh my God!
Aduh, encok! Encok! Ini aduh sakit punggung gitu.
Ouch, my back! Back pain! My back hurts.
Beda aduh beda!
It's different... oh, it's different!
Ini dikretek-kretekin enak kayaknya! Aduh!
It feels like it needs a good cracking! Ow!
Aku! Aku! Yes, yes, yes, what?
Me! Me! Yes, yes, yes, what?
Bobogile... Oi aku, aku duluan apa Risu dulu nih?
Bobogile... hey me, me first or Risu first?
Bebas, bebas, bebas!
It's up to you, up to you!
Ya udah, ya udah. Enggak deh, Risu dulu deh. Apa deh?
Alright then. No, Risu first. What is it?
Ya udah, ya udah, aku ya. Aku ya.
Okay, okay, me then. Me.
Tadi pose di samping tapi tangan satunya tuh nunjuk ke bibir.
The side pose from before, but with one hand pointing to your lips.
Ngerti nggak?
Got it?
Gimana sih?
How does it go?
Tangan kanan tetap pegang pinggang.
Right hand stays on the hip.
Agak korslet nih.
My brain's short-circuiting.
Beda lho.
It's different.
Gimana? Tangan kirinya tuh kayak sst, sst, sst. Diam, diam, diam.
How? The left hand is like 'shh, shh, shh'. Quiet, quiet, quiet.
Oh, oke. Ya gitu deh pokoknya. Ya agak sebisanya ya guys.
Oh, okay. Well, something like that. I'll do my best, guys.
Atahai! Bisa gini.
Atahai! I can do this.
Ih, sias, sias! Way, bangun!
Whoa, sias! Hey, wake up!
Oke lah, boleh lah, boleh lah. Aku deh aku sekarang nih.
Okay then, it works. Now it's my turn.
Pargoy sekarang!
Pargoy now!
Pargoy? Pargoy itu kayak apa ya?
Pargoy? What's pargoy like?
Pargoy itu kayak apa?
What's pargoy like?
Nggak tahu deh, sedapat lu aja deh.
I don't know, just whatever you can do.
Itu buset goyang ngebor! Ngebor!
Damn, that's the 'drill' dance! Drilling!
Tante jangan, Tante!
Tante, don't, Tante!
Olesen! Goyang ngebor!
Generation gap 'drill' dance!
Generation gap! Bisanya goyang ngebor.
Generation gap! All I can do is the drill dance.
Tante jangan! Ya ampun Tante jangan, jangan ngebor!
Tante, don't! Oh my god, Tante, don't drill!
Yes! Ya habis itu pose apa lagi nih?
Yes! So what's the next pose?
Terakhir, terakhir.
Last one, last one.
Yang lain, bentar-bentar nih.
Let's see, wait a moment.
Apa lagi? Lu, lu ini Tante.
What else? You, you do this, Tante.
Pose lari mau entry ke Site A.
Pose like you're running to entry Site A.
Oh ya, oke-oke. Gue bisa banget tuh.
Oh yeah, okay. I can totally do that.
Ayo. Gila sih pakai Vandal, pakai Vandal.
Let's go. Crazy, use a Vandal, use a Vandal.
Enemy Site A! Enemy Site A!
Headshot!
Tidak-tidak, cek corner soalnya ya.
No, no, I forgot to check the corner.
Makasih ya sudah datang.
Thanks for coming.
Makasih ya sudah ngundang kita juga ya.
Thanks for inviting us too.
Ya, aku senang banget. Izin pinjam kolam renangnya ya, bye-bye!
Yeah, I'm so happy. Permission to use the pool, okay? Bye-bye!
Hah? Bye-bye!
Huh? Bye-bye!
Ya udah sih. Paling nanti dicegat satpam.
Whatever. You'll probably be stopped by security.
Thank you Kobo and Risu from Hololive Indonesia for memeriahkan my tea party!
Thank you Kobo and Risu from Hololive Indonesia for livening up my tea party!
Well, but it looks like we got even more guests!
Who do you think is going to show up next?
They're my senpais.
They're my seniors.
Japanese mode.
もしもーし！聞こえますかー？
Hello? Can you hear me?
わー！ハロー！
Whoa! Hello!
Reineー！
Reine!
Holo Indonesia! Congrats!
トワ先輩、スバル先輩、来てくれてありがとう！
Towa-senpai, Subaru-senpai, thank you for coming!
今日は、えっと、English? English? Japanese?
Today, um... English? English? Japanese?
Which language? English or Japanese?
English or Japanese? Japanese only, please! Yes!
Yes, Japanese only でお願いします、please!
Yes, Japanese only, please!
Ok, Japanese only, Towa-senpai and Subaru-senpai desu ne!
Okay, Japanese only for Towa-senpai and Subaru-senpai!
おねがいしまーす！よろしくお願いします！
Please! Nice to meet you!
ね、あの、今回はですね、ちょっとあの、スクリーンショットタイムのために何かあの、リクエストを受けてますよ。
So, for this occasion, I'm taking some requests for a screenshot time.
おー！
Oh!
どんなポーズがいいか、あ、でも、まずね、ちょっとだけマジック。
What kind of pose would you like... but first, a little bit of magic.
マジ？マジ？ちょっとだけ？
Really? Really? Just a bit?
マジック！わー！
Magic! Whoa!
何、何、何？
What, what, what?
クリーニングはたきです！
It's a cleaning duster!
クリーニングはたき！クリーニングはたき！
Cleaning duster! Cleaning duster!
そうですね、このはたきで何かポーズリクエストとかありますか？
That's right. Do you have any pose requests using this duster?
そのはたきでポーズ？すげー難しいんですけど。
A pose with this duster? That's really difficult.
はい、はい、はい！
Yes, yes, yes!
えっと、ママっぽい... はたきでお掃除しながら...
Please say ara ara please.
Um, like a mom... while cleaning with a duster...
Please say 'ara-ara' please.
あのね... あ...
Well... ah...
Cleaning... ah... ara ara...
It's time to お掃除！
It's time to clean!
Yeah! Thank you beautiful Reine!
You're number one! Beautiful! Yay!
イェーイ！ 他にはポーズありますか？
Do you have any poses?
Yay! Do you have any other poses?
Do you have any other?
あ、じゃあトワは...
スバルちゃんをはたきでどっかやってほしいです。
Ah, then Towa...
wants you to swat Subaru-chan away with the duster.
なんでそこなんですか！？
Why does it turn out like that!?
なんで！？
Why!?
スバルクリーニングでプリーズ。
Subaru cleaning, please.
Subaru cleaning?
Subaru cleaning? Okay...
Subaru cleaning! Please be a bird please!
Okay, okay... It is good, cleaning is good, right?
Okay, thank you.
可愛い。
Cute.
可愛い。待って、ちょっと...
はたきで可愛いポーズしてみて。
Cute. Wait, a sec...
try doing a cute pose with the duster.
はたきと一緒に可愛いポーズ。
A cute pose together with the duster.
めっちゃ難しそう。
That looks really difficult.
むずいよ。むずいよ。
It's hard. It's hard.
これ？ これ... これ可愛い？ Cute pose.
This? This... is this cute? Cute pose.
ちょっと卑しいですそれ... あ、違う...
That's a bit vulgar... ah, no...
いいのよ。いいのよやって。思うが...
It's fine. It's fine, do it. As you think...
いやそれやばい！ やばい！
No, that's dangerous! Dangerous!
やばい？ え？
Dangerous? Eh?
いやちょっとなんかもうその...
ボディがすごいナイスバディすぎるわ。
No, wait, like...
your body is just such a "nice body".
ボディしか見てないやん！ ごめん。
You're only looking at her body! Sorry.
内なるおじさん出てるごめん。
My inner old man is coming out, sorry.
やばい... やばすぎる。やば...
Dangerous... it's too dangerous. Dange...
え、どうすればいいですか？
Eh, what should I do?
ちょっと背中みたいな。
I want to see your back a bit.
背中？ 背中...
Back? Back...
うわぁぁ！ Please say ara ara!
Please say ara ara! あ、あらあら！
Whoaaa! Please say ara ara!
Please say ara ara! Ah, ara ara!
You are number one Reine! Thank you!
Okayですか？ Thank you!
Are you okay? Thank you!
Okayですか？ Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！
Is that okay? Thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
ありがとう！ 嬉しい！
今度何かやりましょうね、一緒に！
Thank you! I'm happy!
Let's do something together next time!
おめでとう、レイネ！ またね！
Bye bye! ありがとう！
Congratulations, Reine! See you!
Bye bye! Thank you!
Yay! そして... that was Towa-senpai and Subaru-senpai
from Hololive JP, my senpais.
Yay! And so... that was Towa-senpai and Subaru-senpai
Senpai, senpai... I'm so happy many many people coming.
えーま、and then, some girls from the
EN branch are also here.
Well, and then, some girls from the
ENからも来てくれましたね。
もしもし、hello.
They also came from EN.
Hello, hello.
Yay! Hello! Hello hello!
Oh wait, I need to hide this! Hosh hosh hosh!
Looking good! Shove it somewhere secret!
Secret secret hataki magic!
Yay! Please introduce yourselves,
Gura, Calli, and IRyS!
Not me, I'm not first. Nose goes!
ド、ド、ド、ドモサメです！
I'm Gawr Gura from Hololive English! Yay!
D-D-D-Domosame-desu!
I'm Mori... Kill-a-people, kill-a-mori from
Hololive English! Yeah let's go! Desu-desu-desu!
And I'm IRyS! Hi-RyS, it's IRyS! Hi Reine!
Hi hi! Thank you so much for coming today!
And so what we're going to do is I'm accepting requests
from you for screenshot time. I'll do any pose for you.
Alright, I'll go first. I'll go ahead and make it easy,
rip the band-aid off. Show us your panties.
HO! What!? Calli!
Just do it! Just... What!?
It's what they want to see!
Ah... Hear me out, that's why I was
thinking kicky-kicky-kick.
Calli, is this what you're always thinking?
No, I'm just thinking about the fans! Oh! Whoa!
Whoa whoa! What just happened? I saw the magic!
I've seen behind the curtain!
Suddenly I don't remember anything!
What? Spaghetti beam!
Anyways, what's next?
I want to see a close-up of your ribs.
My this? This? Ribs?
Ribs! Close up! Oh man, and
waki-pai at the same time!
It's a double-decker! That's not even allowed!
My! Whoa whoa!
Gura, how do you not have those? Are those like gills?
Gills? No! Do you have those?
What the hell? Gills?
Okay! Any more requests? I got something
to show you too actually after this.
Surprised.
I want to see you do a bridge.
A bridge?
Yes.
A bridge like "kayang" desu ka?
A bridge like "kayang" (bridge pose)?
Kayang lagi, emang ngerti?
Bridge again, do they even understand?
You have to like, lie down first? This is dangerous.
How limber are you?
I don't know!
(Grunts)
Cameraman!
Nice! So limber.
Cameraman was not really keyed in on the memo there.
Damn it!
No, no more rebroadcast. Sorry, sorry.
We'll get them next time.
I gotta show you something.
Do you know who this is?
Show it, show it.
Mister... Tamboree!
Tatang!
Big old Tatang.
Tatang! It looks like a post office.
My beloved... My beloved Tatang.
And I want to... say a little bit of something.
This Tatang can grow big.
You know Tatang is small, right?
Like your chest?
Hmm? Eh? Eh?
No, no, no. Reine's Tatangs are not small.
Yes. So like if you feel like...
Wait, I'm just going to demonstrate it to you.
What? They're not. Of course they're not.
I mean, you just said they can get bigger?
Oh broke. Tatang's going to get wet.
With this tea! Oh no!
With this tea, you can...
(Gulp sounds) Oh God! I see...
Oh! Whoa! It's like a sponge!
And he's peeing it out right away! It's going right through him!
It's...
Big Tatang! Big Tatang!
So if you guys feel like you want to, maybe for example...
...grow bigger and stronger...
...like have a bigger heart or something...
IRyS needs that. Yeah.
You guys can call me and order this tea from me.
Everybody join the "Royalty".
So if you know, if the tofu has a little problem or something...
Whoa, yeah. I don't specifically need anything like that.
But yeah, I'm just saying... I'm not mentioning any names.
Will it make me grow bigger everywhere?
Everywhere? Of course! Voluptuous Gura coming up soon.
If you take a bath with it every single day, then maybe...
Oh! I'm going to take a lot of tea.
Sounds like my mom telling me to drink milk every day of my childhood life.
Exactly! It's better! Even better!
Oops, where do I put this?
Sign me up.
I don't know what I want to grow, but it sounds cool.
We need stuff like that in our lives.
Of course.
You know. Okay, thank you so much for coming to the call.
Congratulations on your 3D!
You look amazing! You look great!
You look awesome! You look divine!
Beautiful! Keep doing your best!
Yeah, thank you!
Bye bye! Mata ne!
Bye bye! See you later!
Bye!
Yeah, so just call me guys if you need that, yeah.
Anyways, that was great! I'm so happy so many people came to see me.
But I'm not done singing yet. There's still more.
So mada utaitai kara... Eh, fukanjatta.
So since I still want to sing... Oops, I slipped up.
Mada utaitai kara, I'm going to sing someplace else maybe.
Since I still want to sing, I'm going to sing someplace else maybe.
I want to sing in a place...
...where I can sing as much as I like.
And then... So let's... Ido!
And then... So let's... Move!
Chu-ru chu-ru chu-ru pa-ya-pa
Sweetie darling 踊りましょう
Sweetie darling, let's dance
はじける キュピトに
Into a bursting Cupid
生まれかわって 甘い夢
Born anew, in a sweet dream
彩りたいの
I want to color it
グラマラスな 唇
Glamorous lips
ピンク色の 誘惑ね
A pink temptation
ガラスの 向こう側に
On the other side of the glass
うつる 素顔は シュールなデイズ
The face reflected is a surreal day
君だけに ずっと
Only for you, always
見せていたい 心の中
I want to show the inside of my heart
瞳の奥 そばに
Deep in your eyes, by your side
いてほしいよ 月のミラーボール
I want you there, moonlight mirror ball
照らされて
Illuminated
My darling vivid とばしましょう
My darling, let's fly vividly
...safety beauty
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩る My life
Gently coloring my life
ほら
Look
世界は変わる
The world is changing
CHURU CHURU CHURU PAYAPPA
ドラマチックな呪文
A dramatic spell
解けないデジャヴ 見つめたくて
Wanting to gaze at an unbreakable deja vu
カラフルな Sweet story
A colorful sweet story
心深く刻み込む
Etched deep into my heart
小さな闇が訪れても
Even if a little darkness visits
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If I chant the spell of love
そう きっと果てない空
Yes, surely the endless sky
星屑のシャワーが降り注ぐ
A stardust shower will pour down
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう
So let's head for HAPPY STATION
50/50（フィフティ・フィフティ）合わせて
Adding 50/50 together
100%以上の愛
More than 100% love
揺るぎなくここにあると
That it's here without wavering
私を火照らせる
It makes me flush
CHURU CHURU CHURU PAYAPPA
トラブルーらしくと
Like trouble
コンサバティブな自分
A conservative self
君にありのままを
To you, just as I am
伝えてほしいと
Wanting to tell you
願いは
The wish is
セキラララ
Sekirarara
My darling もっと一緒に踊りましょう
My darling, let's dance together more
Secret night 素敵な
Secret night, wonderful
Love songのデコレーション
Decoration of a love song
二人のハートで奏で合わせて
Playing together with our two hearts
My darling ねえ vividに過ごしましょう
My darling, hey, let's spend time vividly
弾ける safety beauty
Bursting safety beauty
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩る My life
Gently coloring my life
ほら
Look
世界は変わる
The world is changing
CHURU CHURU CHURU PAYAPPA
Oh my god...
愛のネタバレ別れっぽいな
Spoiler of love, looks like a breakup
人生のネタバレ死ぬっぽいな
Spoiler of life, looks like death
なにそれ意味深でかっこいいじゃん
What's that? It's meaningful and cool
それっぽい単語で踊ってんだ失敬
Dancing with words like that, excuse me
とぅっとぅる　とぅっとぅる　とぅ
Tu-tu-ru tu-tu-ru tu
神っぽいな
Lyrics / Composition: PinocchioP
God-ish
神っぽいな
Like a god
ぽいじゃん　ぽいじゃん
Like one, like one
神っぽいな
Like a god
もうええぜ　もうええぜ　それもええぜ
Enough already, enough already, that's fine too
逆に昂進してきたら
If on the contrary, it gets advanced
起きね　起きね　夢起きね
Wake up, wake up, dream wake up
景気ええけど非は自演
Business is good, but the fault is self-enacted
Bebebe
Wait wait
神っぽいな　それ卑怯
Like a god, that's unfair
神っぽいな　それ
Like a god, that
I want you want you IQが下がっていく伏線
I want you, want you, the foreshadowing of IQ dropping
邪心ぽいな　それ卑怯
Evil-ish, that's unfair
邪心ぽいな　それ
Evil-ish, that
I hate you hate you 害虫はどっち
I hate you, hate you, which one is the pest?
その髪型 その目つき その口元 その香水 その起こし方 そのメイク
That hair, that gaze, that mouth, that perfume, that way of waking, that makeup
アレっぽいな それ卑怯
Looks like "that", that's unfair
その礼儀 その威厳 その卑屈 そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That etiquette, that dignity, that servility, that charisma, that gag, that sense
神っぽいな それ卑怯 ぽいな ぽいな ぽいな 憧れちゃう
Like a god, that's unfair, ish, ish, ish, I'm admiring it
メタ思考する本質は悔い
The essence of meta-thinking is regret
人を小馬鹿にしたような作意
A design like making fun of people
無為に生き延びるのは難しい
Living on aimlessly is difficult
権力に呑まれて揺らぐ灯り
A flickering light swallowed by power
神を否定し神に成り代わり
Denying God and taking God's place
玉座で豹変する小物たち
Small-time crooks who change suddenly on the throne
批判に見せかけ自戒の祈り
A prayer of self-reflection disguised as criticism
Do you know?
何してんのそれ うぜえ
What are you doing? Annoying
何してんのそれ
What are you doing?
意味がよく分かんない 死ね 無中生有 まじ
I don't really get it. Die. Fabricated. Seriously.
飽きっぽいんだ OK みんな飽きっぽいんだ OK
Fickle, OK. Everyone's fickle, OK.
踊れるやつ頂戴頂戴
Give me someone who can dance
きっしょいね きっしょいね それきっしょいね きっしょいね
Gross, right? Gross, right? That's gross, right? Gross, right?
逆にファンになってきたじゃん
I've actually become a fan now.
ちっちゃいね ちっちゃいね 器ちっちゃいね ちっちゃいね
Small, right? Small, right? Your capacity is small, right? Small, right?
出した手引っ込めてご苦労様
Thanks for your hard work pulling back your hand.
かっけえ...
Cool...
God...
神っぽいな それ 卑怯 神っぽいな それ 卑怯
God-ish, that's unfair. God-ish, that's unfair.
条件公約遵守してくたばっていく感じ
The feeling of complying with conditions and pledges then dying.
ヤケっぽいな それ 卑怯 ヤケっぽいな それ 卑怯
Desperate-ish, that's unfair. Desperate-ish, that's unfair.
愛執 愛執 エピゴーネンの日
Attachment, attachment, day of the epigone.
そのタイトル その絵 そのストーリー その音楽 その歌 そのメロディ
That title, that art, that story, that music, that song, that melody.
あれっぽいな それ 卑怯 あれっぽいな それ 卑怯
Like that-ish, that's unfair. Like that-ish, that's unfair.
その名言 その意見 その批評 そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That quote, that opinion, that criticism, that charisma, that joke, that sense.
神っぽいな それ 卑怯 ぽいな ぽいな ぽい 憧れちゃうわ
God-ish, that's unfair. -ish, -ish, -ish, I'm starting to admire it.
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる... ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
Tu turu tu tu turu... -ish, right? -ish, right?
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる... “神”
Tu turu tu tu turu... 'God'.
愛のネタバレ 別れっぽいな
Spoiler of love, it seems like a breakup.
人生のネタバレ 死ぬっぽいな
Spoiler of life, it seems like dying.
すべて理解して煩った
Understanding everything, I became troubled.
無邪気に踊っていたかった 人生
I wanted to dance innocently, life.
マリン先輩、ありがとうございました！
Marine-senpai, thank you so much!
レイネおめでとう！お披露目呼んでくれてありがとうね。
Congratulations, Reine! Thank you for inviting me to your showcase.
一緒に歌えて楽しかったよ。
I had a lot of fun singing with you.
わー！マリン先輩大好きですー！
Wow! I love you, Marine-senpai!
マリンも大好きだよ。またね。頑張ってね。バイバイ！
I love you too, Reine. See you later. Good luck. Bye-bye!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
やー、嬉しいな。
Man, I'm so happy.
えー、それじゃあ、そろそろラストの曲なんですが、
Well then, it's almost time for the last song,
その前に、CMです！
but before that, here's a commercial!
Attention please! Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Are you by any chance a MERAKyats who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck! My name is Pavolia Reine,
and I'm going to be here explaining briefly what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership. (That is mine, by the way.)
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights,
which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging
by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties,
which also means membership-exclusive streams
in which we can have various talks, play games together, and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
Like what, you might ask?
Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it is...
...SAFETY IS GUARANTEED GUARANTEED...
...development training in which we aim to build a community of people who like living dangerously.
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
Illusion Night
Kiss me ふらつかないで
Kiss me, don't stagger
Tell me 甘い言葉で
Tell me with sweet words
Give me 君のすべてを
Give me all of you
今この幻想で
Now in this illusion
ただつながる時間 委ねていてね
Just surrender to the time we're connected
声を枯らすくらい 心臓で叫べ
Shout with your heart until your voice goes hoarse
今更恋なんて思わない 変わりはいくらでもいるわ
I won't think of it as love now; there are plenty of replacements
熱く燃えるほど愛おしくて 騒がしい街へ
So dear as it burns hotly, to the noisy city
また夜が明けて
And the dawn breaks again
まだまだ終わらない Show time ほら踊り明かそう
Show time isn't over yet, hey, let's dance the night away
クラクラしちゃうくらいに 見つめてね
Stare at me until you feel dizzy
Take me 深い夜まで
Take me until the deep night
Touch me 気の向くままに
Touch me as you please
Trust me 夢いざなう 飽きるまでずっと
Trust me, I'll invite you into a dream, forever until you're tired of it
...にして二人きりなら
...if it's just the two of us...
強く生き続けることを称えよう
Let's celebrate our strength to keep on living.
優しい私は昼の祝い
The gentle me is a blessing of the day.
さよならは必要ないから
Because there's no need for goodbyes...
構わないでね
...don't worry about me.
いつか戻るから
Because I'll return someday.
正直な気持ち知って　私をもっと止めて
Knowing my honest feelings, stop me even more.
曖昧にしないで　他は要らないでしょ
Don't be vague, you don't need anyone else, right?
心繋がる場所で　強く感じたら
If you feel it strongly in the place where our hearts connect...
声を枯らしてでも
Even if your voice goes hoarse...
心臓で叫べ
...scream with your heart!
今更恋しいなんて思わない
I won't think I miss you now.
愛してるなんて言わないわ
I won't say I love you.
代わりは誰もいないから
Because there's no one else like you.
熱く燃える炎を通して
Through the hotly burning flames...
騒がしい夜の中　二人だけの世界で踊ろう
In the noisy night, let's dance in a world just for the two of us.
邪魔するものは何もないわ
There's nothing to stand in our way.
さよならは言わせないからね
I won't let you say goodbye.
心地好い夢へ
Into a pleasant dream...
続く Illusion Night
...the Illusion Night continues.
まだまだ終わらない Showtime
The showtime isn't over yet.
ほら踊り明かそうや
Come on, let's dance the night away.
クラクラしちゃうくらいに
Until we get dizzy...
弾けてね
...let's have a blast!
Whoo! Thank you so much for today everybody!
みんな今日は本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for today, everyone!
But...
Ah, so yeah, that was Illusion Night.
And how did you like the collab song? Whoo! The duo! Nice.
Oh, and before I end things, I have an announcement.
そうですね、最後はアナウンスメントがありますね。
That's right, there's an announcement at the end.
グッズ！Merch! グッズがあります！
Merch! Merch! We have merch!
まずは、こちらですね！
First, here it is!
Yay! Whoo! Oh my god!
Sweet Tonjok Hoodie!
Sweet Tonjok Hoodie
Sweet Tonjok Hoodie, a hoodie just for you.
Well, look at that! The front part, the front part...
...there's an illustration by Yomozaka-sensei!
And look at the sides, look at this!
Sleeve design has "Salam Merahyats"!
Sleeve design has "Greetings, Merahyats"!
Perfect for the Merahyats who want to have a Tonjok identity! Pew-pew-pew-pew-pew-pew!
The size of the hoodie is one-size-fits-all, so you don't have to worry about size...
...and the material is cotton. Yummy yummy.
Ah, and the goods will not be on sale immediately...
...it will be on sale in the Holoro 3D collaboration on July 29th.
グッズは、7月29日にセール始まります。
The merch will go on sale on July 29th.
いえーい、楽しみにしててね！
Yay, look forward to it!
And, I also have a very big announcement to share.
そう、えー、大切なお知らせがあります。
Yes, I have an important announcement.
Then, take a look!
PAVOLIA REINE
NEW ORIGINAL SONG
Produced by MARDIAL
Pavolia Reine's first ENGLISH X INDONESIAN ORIGINAL SONG
COMING SOON
はい！そう皆さん、楽しみにしててね！
Yes! So everyone, look forward to it!
And don't forget to tweet with the hashtag #PavoliaReine3D...
...ご感想 waiting, waiting しますね！
...I'll be waiting for your thoughts!
Please tweet dengan hashtag ini!
Please tweet with this hashtag!
And so, we've reached the end of the night.
Thank you so much everybody for watching Pavolia Reine's 3D showcase!
見てくれて、本当にありがとうね！
Thank you so much for watching!
それじゃ、えー...
Well then...
...We say, SALAM MERAHYATS!
Bye bye! Yay!
After waiting for so long, the time to celebrate and cheer has finally come!
There are still so many things to see and experience in the story of Pavolia Reine,
and I am forever grateful to have you all be part of it.
I will always treasure the memories we have, and I'm excited to make new ones! - Reine