(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.3",
"generated_at": "2026-07-05T00:45:30.489443",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 16,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Mom: Jenna Roehrs
Jay: Gemma
Hey, why were you tickling my Raora?
No, I wasn't!
Raora already loves me, plus first come, first served!
What are you even talking about?
No, she's mine! Mine! Mine!
Mine!
No, she's mine now! Don't take her! No, it's mine!
Raora's mine now! No, mine! Mine! Mine!
Mine! Mine! Mine!
Jay, what on earth are you playing over here?
The jealousy game!
The jealousy game?
And shouldn't you play something more appropriate for a five-year-old?
Mom, I'm five, and this is what five-year-olds do.
And I thought this was funny.
Oh, you and Daddy are definitely having a conversation about this later.
All righty, it's time for your favorite thing: Justice!
Justice! Justice!
Jay, what do you like so much about...
...Justice.
They make lots of trouble.
What?
Oops, is that...
Justice! Justice! Justice!
How to Protect Justice!
Members of Justice...
...are expected to possess strength...
...sound judgment...
...and an unwavering sense of justice.
In this training video...
...you will learn the fundamental skills and exercises required of every Justice member.
Now, join us and say it together:
For Justice!
The first training is a body search.
Conducted immediately after securing a subject...
...even the slightest oversight can lead to serious incidents or the destruction of evidence...
...making this one of the most critical police procedures.
Can Justice keep their emotions in check under any circumstances...
...and carry out a precise body search to completion?
(La la la la...)
Stop, ma'am! No further, no further is policy...
...and I'll be conducting a body search.
Come here, madam. Yes, body search you here.
If you really insist. / Over here, over here, over here, ma'am.
Okay, okay. / Do you have any electronics, tablets, laptops, devices...
Turn around here, ma'am.
Arms up! All right, straight arms, there we go. Wonderful, wonderful, all right.
What is this?
Oh, you know, it's a Chattini! You see my Chattini?
They're always hungry and they really want some food, so sometimes I always have an emergency cucumber.
Emergency rations, I see, I see, I see. We can't have that on this person, I'm sorry.
...conducting the body search.
Stop right there! Hands up in the air!
I didn't do anything wrong!
Do I have your consent to do a body search on you? Do I have your consent?
No, no! I didn't do anything wrong!
Okay, let us see. Let us see what you have here.
I didn't do anything wrong! On what charges?
What's this?
Nothing.
Hey, that's mine! Why did you take that from me?
It's not! We never met before. Why would I take something from you?
No, I can't believe you would steal. You're a thief!
I did not steal it!
You stole it!
It was given to me!
Stand still. Hands up in the air!
No, ah, ah, ah!
What's, what's this then?
There's nothing wrong with having that in my pocket! It's a Grampire Buddy, we're friends!
Does it live under humane living conditions?
Yes, it lives in a nice little shoe box and it's really happy there! So that's why you should not arrest me, Officer.
Okay, okay, I believe you.
What's this?
Wait, a Notomodo? Why do you have Notomodo?
No reason!
Are they friends?
They're friends! He was on a play date, obviously. He came to visit the shoe box, so that's why!
Am I free to go, Officer?
I'm starting to think that maybe, maybe it's okay. Let me see one more time.
Ah, ah! No, no!
What's this?
Nothing! It's nothing!
Can't a girl have some BL in her pocket?
Kimi ni Dunk...
Can't a girl have some hobbies?
Okay, I see. I see.
Can't I read? Am I not allowed to read?
Stop making those noises! What's this?
Another one?
This one is a cat boy. Have you heard of that really awesome manga where whenever they...
Okay, okay. Ground! On the floor!
On the floor? On the floor?
Get down!
Stop making those noises!
What's this?
What's this one then?
So this is the one that I really like. You see these two men right here? One is an Omega, and the other's an Alpha. It's called the Omegaverse.
They don't actually turn into wolves here, it's just called pack dynamics. And one of them is really, really dominant...
...and the other one is really submissive, and then one of them can get pregnant! Do you like... Hello? Are you listening, Officer?
Officer? One of them gets pregnant. It's really, really...
The next training is: Apprehension Training.
This is a critical close-quarters task in the field...
...requiring officers to approach and subdue a target swiftly.
However, unexpected behavior on site can sometimes shake one's judgment.
Can Justice successfully and reliably subdue the target?
Gigi and Raora's Apprehension Training! You have 3 minutes! Begin!
You're going down, criminal scum!
No! No! Ah! Ah!
Put your arms behind your back! Put your arms behind your back!
No, you don't do that!
I mean... Why are they together?
Get her! Get her!
Look at my tail! Look at my tail! That's my pink tail.
Don't fall for it!
Don't you like my tail?
I'm unsure who's winning.
Cute tail!
Hey, Gigi, don't fall for that!
You know, it's kind of hard for me...
You are Justice!
Show me your back!
Kill her!
You have the right to remain silent...
You don't want to hurt me, do you?
You're a criminal, so I'm gonna have to touch you. I'm gonna have to put you in jail.
Why would you put me in jail, Gigi? Oh, stop! Stop!
Apprehend her!
Kill her! Kill her! Kill her! Yes, yes!
Gigi, why would you... Why do you want to touch my tail? Hey! That's my tail!
Show me your tail!
Stop! You're a criminal! You're a criminal! You're a criminal!
Down, Raora!
Don't look! Don't look!
What?
Lie down! Where are you going?
No, you're not going to touch me, right?
No, I would touch you. I will touch you.
I will hurt you. / I don't want to get hurt.
Lie down. Lie down. / No.
Lie down. You're a criminal, you're a criminal, so you have to lie down. You have to do what I say because I'm the police.
I'm a police officer! / Wait, I have something here. Hold on.
Oh, my clothes... My...
Ah!
Get down! Get down! / No!
I'm trying! I'm trying!
Get back on the ground! / Ah!
Oh, you wanna... You wanna be here next to me?
Wait, you want me?! / Ah!
I'm the cop! I'm the cop! / No, you're not the cop!
You're not the cop! You got me...
Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me!
Haha!
I win! Guys, I win! / Okay, okay, okay, that's enough, that's enough.
That's enough! / I win!
That's enough.
I don't know... / That was, that was apprehension. / Who do you think won, Liz?
Did I win? / I don't know. / Wow.
And the winner is... / Wait, this is about... This is about apprehension training, there's no winner.
Okay, so apprehension... Did you do a good job? / I am still free!
In the end, you apprehended her? / Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was... in a very... / I got her in a leg lock and everything! / I think she's corrupt. / You definitely interlocked...
Ahhh! / Hey, hey, hey, hey! / Stop, stop, stop!
Get off! / Get off!
You know what? I... disqualified! Gigi's the winner! / Yay!
Yes, Gigi, well done. You apprehended the... / Yeah, I think you won.
I think I won, too! / You won. / Yes, Gigi. That was really good.
Hey, hey, hey, not without my consent! / Okay, okay.
[Suspect: Elizabeth / Officer: Cecilia]
Elizabeth and Cecilia, apprehension training! / You have three minutes. Are you ready?
Oh, one, one second. Here we go.
Flame on! / Wow! / Flame on.
I'm ready. / Flame on! Flame on!
Are you ready now? / We're ready. / Yeah.
Okay. 3, 2, 1, start!
Suspect! Suspect, stop right there!
Aha, ha, ha, ha! I am Evil Elizabeth!
And I have put chewing gum in everyone's hair!
How evil am I?! / How evil!
Hands up in the air!
Oh, oh, oh...
Hands up! / Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh no! Oh no!
Oh no! Oh!
Help! Help!
Help! Help! / Oh my god, Liz, you should kill her. / She's so strong.
An interrogation process where even the slightest inconsistencies in a statement must be detected to get closer to the truth.
Can Justice remain unaffected by the situation and accurately draw out the information?
[Q. Are you good at interrogations?]
Yeah, I'm the best actually. I have a gun, and I know how to use it, so...
Easy! Don't worry about it, I have my ways. I've been here for so long, it's going to be the easiest case of my life.
[Q. Are you good at interrogations?]
No, I don't think so. Because my heart is too pure, and my ass is too fat, and I'm not a gaslighter like Cecilia Immergreen.
I'm not very confident, but I'll do my best.
Well, well, well, little criminal. We are about to begin your interrogation!
Wait a minute! I'm not a criminal! Why me? I haven't done anything. What exactly have I been accused of?
That... That would be the suspected identity fraud, and the unlawful acquisition of personal...
Come on, Gigi! ...of Nerissa Ravencroft!
I don't know anything about that! I'm innocent! Who is Nerissa Ravencroft?
Have you ever seen Nerissa Ravencroft? You know who Nerissa Ravencroft is.
No, I've never seen her in my life.
Blue, black, long hair, red eyes?
If I have ever saw such a maiden, I would call her a princess. She sounds like one.
Well, we have evidence, we have evidence! We have evidence!
Does the name 99_X3_XD ring a bell to you?
Oh, yes. Because 99_X3_XD is me.
Ah! I knew it!
You are the prime suspect in the stalking incident!
Of Nerissa Ravencroft! We have it!
We have it on paper right here, and we have all the chat logs that you put in Nerissa Ravencroft's channel right here.
I don't know, I watch, I watch a lot of virtual entertainers.
Nerissa Ravencroft, I'm outside of your house right now.
Nerissa Ravencroft, I see you from the window.
Nerissa Ravencroft, take off your shirt. Whoa, now.
That was all you! I don't know about that.
I think you are mistaken. I would never speak that way to a princess.
Tell her that we're never going to give her donuts ever again.
And you will never have donuts ever again!
And I will never have... Donuts?! How did you know I like donuts?!
No more donuts! No more donuts!
But, but, if you, if you just confess, we have an in with Nerissa Ravencroft.
Yeah, offer her a good deal. We can give you what you want.
A date... with Nerissa Ravencroft!
Okay, now you guys are in control. Gigi is the bad cop now.
Answer us right now! Answer us right now!
Go crazy, go crazy on her! I'm scared.
Hey, you! Whoa.
A fine woman, it is my lucky day. Chief Raora!
Chief Raora! Oh, Chief Raora! What do you guys think you're doing, huh?
But we were doing what you were saying.
You useless! You don't do anything in this place!
But we were... Why did they hire you, huh? You're so useless!
This person, we have all the evidence, and you still didn't manage to make her tell the truth?!
Chief, we are trying our best, okay? We are underpaid, overworked!
You're embarrassing us in front of the criminal.
Well, maybe you should do better than this! You're not even listening to me, are you?
You never fix our coffee machine! And we never get free time off, Raora! Chief Raora, I mean!
Well, if you work more, maybe you will deserve your coffee machine!
Do you like coffee? No.
Well, what do you want from me? I want it fixed! And you want coffee?! Silence!
You know, one of my favorite virtual entertainers, Cecilia Immergreen, she does not like coffee.
Do you remember what did you do in that record?
Um, I mean, I make up my own stories in my blog.
Well, your own story with Nerissa Ravencroft, by any chance?
Get her, Boss! Get her, Boss! Wow.
You know, Boss, I think you're all put to the test. Yeah, I think you're doing great.
Thank you! Thank you! Thank, thank...
So you do know Nerissa Ravencroft!
I know that her name spelled backwards is Assiren.
How do you know that? How do you know that?
Uh, I know many Nerissas because I'm very popular with the ladies.
Ask her about the photo collection she has in her room.
We have some things that I want to show you, okay? See this paper right here? Are you gonna show me my shackles, please?
No, no, no. These are all the photos we found in your room that you have taken of Nerissa Ravencroft. Do you recognize these?
These photos! Do you recognize these photos of Nerissa Ravencroft?
You took them! We found them on your camera!
I think my mother... we, we were like, we were with Nerissa Ravencroft.
It was not your mother!
Oh...
There's a selfie right here!
Oh. That's you!
Right there! What do you think?
It's you, it's you.
So, what do you have to say? Is that you or is that not you?
I think there's an imposter here.
Is that you, or is that not you?
Tell her about the evidence that we have! The bra was the wrong size...
...so it's not hers, it's from Nerissa Ravencroft because it's also signed by her!
We found a bra in your room!
And it's the wrong size.
I checked your breast size when you came in, and it's not this size.
Not that one! It is Nerissa Ravencroft's.
And it's also blue! Tell her that it's blue. She never wears blue!
And we know you don't wear blue bras. / I do!
No, you don't, because I... I checked. / Are you sure? Are you sure?
I think you guys should arrest... I think you guys should arrest...
Stop it! / Stop it, criminal!
I mean, we can... We can give you more than a bra from Nerissa Ravencroft.
We can give you way more than a bra from Nerissa... / Help me. I need help.
She took the photos. She took the photos.
We are not going to get away with this. / It's me.
That's her. / What are you doing to her?!
What did you offer just now?!
You offered the Nerissa Ravencroft... / I was doing what you were telling me to do!
You offered me? It was all her! / I was doing what you were telling me to do!
I'm going to get away. / What are you talking about?
She was talking about the bra! / She is trying to escape!
We are not supposed to try to find a new victim!
She told me to do it.
What you are doing... why am I even paying you right now?
I always just get yelled at.
It's my first day on the force, and I just really wanted to be a good cop.
And then 99X3XD... we had all the evidence and all...
She, but it doesn't feel like it!
I've never seen such a thing. 99X3XD was just so cunning.
It was kind of attractive, actually. Those long hairs and...
...those curves.
Actually, I should go find her.
Oh, they are totally useless. They can't do anything.
I, I need to find new, new people for this job.
They don't have the guts for this.
Yeah.
But 99X3XD, she said that she likes ladies and stuff.
Maybe she would like me. Maybe she could work with me. Who knows?
Where is she anyway?
They didn't see it coming.
They didn't know I was... well, they didn't know I was 99X3XD.
But they didn't, they didn't crack me one bit.
For I am too good. I am too cunning.
I am... too powerful, as they say.
Can I get out of this?
The next training is firearms training.
What's required is precision and split-second judgment.
A moment's hesitation can greatly impact the outcome.
Can Justice remain unfazed by the situation and deliver highly accurate shots?
Firearms training, let's go!
Let's go!
First, let's go over the rules.
A variety of targets will appear one after the other.
Your job is to quickly decide whether to shoot or hold your fire.
If it's a valid target, take it out with your revolver.
But be careful. Not every target is meant to be shot.
Out of the 10 targets, three are no-shoot targets.
So don't let your guard down!
Okay! Okay, we got it.
What do you mean? I wasn't listening. I wasn't paying attention.
So we should shoot everything.
No! No, we should shoot our targets, not everyone! You should listen to what I said!
Most importantly, shoot your friends. / What?
What? What the freak?!
All right, Cecilia, you're up first!
Just like that! Justice!
Justice! Shoot that!
Shoot that! Shoot that!
Cecilia, are you feeling confident?
Really good. Look at my trigger... Oh, it's not... Oh, yeah, I'm really good.
I'm gonna shoot everything, and I'm gonna win!
Ready, set, go!
Oh, there it is.
Whoa! Yes!
Oh my god, I got it! Crazy!
Oh my god, it's a gnome with magic!
And it's dead! You killed the magic gnome!
With magic fairy mushrooms! Magic fairy gnome?
What is that? It's a pizza!
Shoot the pizza! Pizza!
Pizza is a bad thing now? Wait, are we supposed to shoot the pizza?
Oh! Oh, oh! No! No, no!
She shot it! No, she was just a little girl!
No! She was just a little girl.
Oh! That's a royal...
No! Cecilia!
Oh, she's a killer.
Wait! He's texting while driving!
Good, good. We got rid of a criminal.
That's a criminal right there. Hey, that's my pension!
Oh yeah, shoot that! Shoot her pension! Yeah!
Oh! Oh, oh!
Oh, a tiny jet! Very tiny.
Yes! Nice shot!
Is that... cucumber? No, cucumber!
No! Don't shoot cucumber! Cucumber!
Cecilia! Yes!
Wait, yeah, we...
Don't shoot! He has cookies!
Nice, very nice. Really? I did it!
I shot everything!
Yeah! Woo!
Cecilia's final score is... drumroll...
7 points! 7? Yes! 7?
6, 7. Hey, why 7? 8, 9.
Well, doing it for... Even if I... honestly...
I think the cucumber was a minus, and I thought it was a plus...
...because we want to kill the cucumber so she doesn't have to eat it.
I don't like cucumbers, right. And I think...
...even if I shot the ones that weren't meant to shoot sometimes...
In a crisis situation, you just have to make a decision, even if it's the wrong one.
Shoot. Keep us, keep us.
[Elizabeth]
All right, let's go. Flame on!
Flame on! All right.
Three, two, one, go! Okay.
Shoot it, shoot it, shoot it!
Nice. Oh, she's a cheerleader.
Shoot it, shoot it, shoot her!
Wow, headshot! Headshot!
Wait, is this obviously not...
No, no, no! Don't shoot! She has a bird!
Yeah, that's a nice bird. Oh, yeah.
Haha. Oh, oh, oh! Shoot her!
Why did you shoot yourself? You shot yourself! Why did you do that?
Okay.
A bird! No, that's a bird. Birds!
I love birds. Wait, is she shooting the birds? No, no. Why is she shooting... Penny on the ground?
Oh, my pension! Pension! Pension!
We need it, we need it!
Yes! We need that for justice.
Justice!
My pizza! My pizza! I'm hungry!
Nice! People want pizza.
Okay. Money! Money!
Shoot it, shoot it, we need money!
We need money!
Why?! What?!
We need money! What?! Oh no, Liz.
Oh, kill that! Oh, cute!
Kill it! Kill it! No, please!
It's so funny though!
Wait, what's that? Shoot me! Shoot me!
Nice, nice.
Nice.
So good! Okay, you are done!
Oh yes! Okay, what is my score? Your points are... drumroll...
Nine! No points?
Not nine? Not...
Nine! Nine points.
Nine points! Wow!
Flame on. Flame on. Wow.
[Gigi]
Ohoho!
Your aim is so bad! Wait, Gigi. She just shot us.
No, Liz! How are you feeling, Gigi? Are you confident?
Are you confident? I'm confident.
I'm confident. I'm confident.
Three, two...
...one, go!
Oh! Oh, cute!
That was on purpose! How could you? So cute!
That's not real, the guns are not real.
Money, money, money! That's money!
That was money! That's not real.
Yay, money! Yay, money! Okay.
Keep shooting.
Oh, money, money, money! Money, money, money!
We need money. Oh, cute.
I had to kill her. Yes! Yes!
That was just a baby. Kill the baby.
Oh, the jet! I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it.
Kill it! It's so tiny! Yeah! Yay!
No, that's bad!
Oh! Oh! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! No! No! No! Kill it! No! Kill it!
I can't... I can't hit it.
They're gone...
Gigi, you're lucky. You're lucky.
You're so lucky right now.
Oh! Oh, no!
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
I can't kill it! I looked into its eyes and I can't kill it!
I looked right into its eyes, and I couldn't do it!
Pizza!
Yay! Good job!
No more pizza. No more pizza diet. No more pizza for...
Whoa, he's stealing your cookies!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
It's not a real gun! My gun doesn't work!
Oh, he's texting and driving!
Oh my god, we have to put him down!
Okay, I think you're done!
Okay, you've run out... You've run out of bullets now. Okay?
Okay, Gigi. Okay, we got it...
Don't shoot us! Oh, no! No! No! No!
Okay!
All right, let's find out what Gigi's score is!
They're real! They're real!
Okay, the final score for Gigi...
Drumroll...
I'm so tired, we...
Eight! You got eight! You got eight!
Yay!
It's your turn, Raora Panthera.
It's me! Yeah, yeah, big cat, means... big gun?
Big gun? Me?
Yeah, yeah, okay, okay, let's go.
Let's... Let's... Let's face the gun...
Uh, it's not real. Don't die, it's not a real gun.
I practice killing that baby.
What do I do again?
Uh, you shoot the targets and you shoot the ones that are bad. Bad targets.
Okay?
Bad ones. Bad, only the bad ones?
How do I know which one is bad?
That's up to you to decide as a member of Justice.
Ready? Ready? I'm ready.
Set... Go!
Get her, get her!
Okay, okay... Ah!
You got to shoot... Shoot that! Aim, Raora, aim! A little to the left, a little...
Raora, you were supposed to shoot this one!
How do I shoot? Yes, it says 'shoot me' in English!
Oh, oh, oh! Texting and driving, texting and driving!
Kill him, kill him! Get him, get him, get him!
Wait, get him! He's...
That guy is menace!
Liz is on for sure. Liz? Liz!
No, don't kill her!
Oh my god, you killed her! You killed Liz!
Kill her! Kill her!
Kill her! Kill!
Kill it! Kill it!
No! What the hell?!
That's so bad! Raora, what are you doing?!
He's stealing the cookies!
Ah! But he's innocent! Yeah!
Why didn't you kill the guy with the cookies?!
Raora, you need to get the next one! Get the next one!
Oh, cute!
No, he's... he's evil! He's stealing... stealing mushrooms!
He does have mushrooms.
Is that... is that...?
Ah! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
Oh, my god!
Oh, dust bunny!
Dust bunny! Get it, get it, get it!
Oh, it's Raora's... get it!
Good job! Good job!
A pickle!
He's jumping really, really fast! He's jumpy!
Why, why, why? Why do we have to shoot it? No, don't shoot!
Yay! Pickle for dinner!
Oh, money!
Money? Do we want money?
Oh, no, we don't want money.
Wait, we have... Gigi texting.
What's wrong with Gigi texting?
Yeah!
That was great! That was... That was...
That was great, Raora! That was great!
That was really good. That was...
Can I kill... Can I kill something else instead? Can I kill some criminals?
Gigi, do you want to save... I'll save the score.
Do you want to know how much it was?
I know! Do you want to know? I know!
Hold my hand, I need to tell you. Hold my hand.
It was... It was... four!
Four! Yay!
You did it on purpose, because there's four of us!
Raora, you're so... you're so clever, pretty.
Justice!
And with that, the training is complete! Huzzah!
And the winner is... the winner is...
All of them! Yeah!
At the loser...
The loser! Loser!
No! The loser...
It's okay, Raora. You're definitely a loser.
I just wanted to make you win because I'm the strongest with my God eyes, so...
Look what's behind my back.
What's behind your back?
You can't do that!
She's mad! She's mad!
Gigi! Gigi!
Cecilia! Cecilia!
No!
The next training is Traffic Enforcement Training.
This duty requires accurately assessing the violation and processing it correctly.
However, in the field, unexpected behavior can sometimes shake an officer's judgment.
Can Justice stay unfazed in any situation and carry out the appropriate response?
We did it, boys! Good job, my goon!
Oh no, cop car behind us!
Oh no!
My goon, goon, do the voice, do the voice!
Okay, boss.
Good afternoon.
Buonasera!
Good afternoon. What's all this then?
You know what? I pulled you over...
That was really cool.
Oh my god, you did it again!
Silence!
Don't act like you don't know anything!
You blew right through the stop sign!
We are just really in our hurry right now!
We are in a hurry!
My husband, he's pregnant!
Right, now. Can I see your driver's license, please?
I... Oh, yeah, see, see? Yes.
Do you have... Do you have your driver's license?
I don't have driver's license.
We don't have time! He's really pregnant!
I am so pregnant.
His water just broke!
Oh my god!
We have to go to the hospital right now, please!
I think they are lying.
We are... We're not... We're not lying.
He's like, really pregnant.
Look how big he is.
I think she is not pregnant, sir.
Excuse me, my husband is really pregnant, he's really big right now.
I'm really big.
Please.
Let me feel the baby.
It's kicking!
I'm kicking right now!
Can you not feel it?
My son! I feel you!
Your heir.
Silenzio!
Silence!
Please.
What do you think? Those two are acting a little bit suspicious.
Suspicious.
Mamma mia!
Oh my god!
Are you alright?
Do you think...
Could it be...
Yes!
See? This is exactly...
...what I was thinking!
What?
My son!
No, no, no, you are stopping us because...
...of my son!
My son!
You are stopping us because I am pregnant!
Yeah, it was the baby! It was the baby!
It was the baby!
There was a horse there.
No, it was my baby! It was our baby!
Our baby.
No, no, no, no, I heard a hoof sound...
No, it's our baby!
...coming from the truck.
Hey, you can't say that about my baby!
Mind if we take a look?
I do mind! No!
Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no! Okay, okay, okay!
Don't look, don't look!
We are just going to take a look at the trunk.
No, please! Please!
You are definitely guilty!
No, you can't! Please officer, stop!
Officer, please! No, don't stop me!
It's the officers!
A horse!
It's a horse! It's a horse!
It's my son!
No, it's our...
Gigi Murin, Cecilia Immergreen...
...you're under arrest.
No, wait! We didn't do anything!
You are under arrest.
No, I can't be under arrest! I have too much to lose!
Yes, you're under arrest! Give me your hand!
No!
You are under arrest officially!
Wait, what? Boss! Boss! You can't leave me! Boss!
Bye-bye!
Yes, yes, yes, we're going to arrest her.
See you later!
No!
We are going to catch her!
Come on, let's get her!
I can't drive!
It's just you and me, baby.
All right, the place is empty.
Got about 10 minutes before the guard's next patrol.
So, this is the YAGO trophy?
The Giga-Mega National Treasure.
I'm going to make a fortune on this.
This is Justice. Is this an emergency?
Help! Help! Please! Please! Can you please help me? Please, is somebody here right now? I don't know what to do! Please!
Calm down and take a deep breath.
Can you tell me exactly what happened?
Uh, calm down. Calm down.
Leave it to us. Leave it to us.
Justice is on the way right now!
Everyone, we have a case.
The Giga-Mega National Treasure has been stolen!
Head to the scene immediately!
The Giga-Mega National Treasure?
You mean the YAGO statue?
Who would even want that? Just let them keep it.
Gigi, that is disrespectful!
It is still the Giga-Mega National Treasure.
We're counting on you.
Fine, I'm on it.
Oh wait! Please! Ah!
The super limited edition sweetie plush drop is in just three minutes!
It's limited quantity, okay?
That... that means I absolutely have to buy it!
Okay, so only two minutes left now.
Just go already!
Ah, no!
Oh my god, the connection! No!
Cecilia, did you get any information?
Cecilia...!
Hold on! Who the hell changed my keyboard layout to Dvorak?!
But I love my presents, Ceci!
This was you?!
You! You absolute piece of sh*t!
You absolute garbage can!
When I get you, I'm going to...
Cecilia, every second counts here.
I know, I know.
All right, found a backdoor on the palace server.
Cracking the encrypted protocol with brute force...
...enforcing the security patch overdrive on the mainframe.
Fine, I'm in!
The suspect is a woman dressed entirely in black.
Height looks around 168 centimeters.
She really likes people wearing helmets.
Ah, she's fleeing north!
If you move now, you can still catch her.
You all heard her.
Let's move out and apprehend the suspect!
For Justice!
Raora, what are you doing? You're not even driving!
You don't know how to drive a car? Put your foot on the gas pedal!
What? What?
Wait! Wait, wait, wait! What?!
There's a horse right in front of us!
There's no freaking horse!
Oh my god, there's a horse. A horse is right there!
No way, it's a real horse!
Oh my god, how are we supposed to get out of here now?
We might be able to...
But we missed... Oh no! Oh, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Horses like vegetables, right? I think there's a cucumber in the trunk.
What? A cucumber? In the trunk?
Hold on, Gigi Murin. Why do you have a cucumber in your pocket right now?
Gigi Murin, you know I hate cucumbers!
You know why.
What? You...
Gigi Murin, you know I hate cucumbers!
Why do you have cucumbers right now?!
Eww, get out of here!
You know where I'm going to put that cucumber?
Where?
Get out of here right now! I don't want to see that cucumber! Eww!
What about for the horse?
No!
What about for the horse? Oh, you hate me!
Don't you freaking hate me? You hate me!
So you hate me? So you hate me? Just say it!
Tell me you freaking hate me! You hate me!
You know how I feel when you tell me that you bring cucumbers, and I hate cucumbers!
And I hate... I hate the taste, I hate everything about cucumbers!
We talked about that many times, and now...
Haaah... those two are away with the fairies.
Cecilia!
Do you have any updates on the suspects' location?
Mmm, so close... hehe.
Cecilia?
Wait, wait... one more...
Cecilia!
Cecilia Immergreen! Noooo! I missed!
Look what you did, Liz! You ruined my perfect score!
I was so close! Aaaaah!
Not you, too!
Ah... did I fail them as a mother?
My heart breaks as their big sister.
I've done everything in my power to look after those three.
Those three wild, eccentric little sisters...
...and guide them to this very day.
I gave them my all!
Oh... what did I do to deserve such cruelty?
Where did I go wrong?
Where did my guidance stray away from the path?
Oh.
You're still... still there, huh? Huh? Yeah.
We're sorry...
Promise I will be a good girl.
Big sister... Big sister, big sister...
Ah... it's just allergies. I'm not crying. You're crying.
Thank you, big sister. I love you, big sister.
Happy ever after.
Justice, just like that.
Justice, get, get, get...
Huh?!
Guys! Everyone!
It's the thief who stole the Ultimate Justice Statue!
We're going to kill them.
What the freak?
Hey, you! Hold it right there!
Because of you, I missed out on a limited edition spaghettini...
...and I didn't even get to eat my delicious pizza!
How are you going to take responsibility for this?
That sounds like a 'you' problem. Go eat your pizza now.
Oh, by the way, there's a shop nearby famous for its cucumber pizza. It's to die for.
Ah! Cucumber pizza?!
Yeah. Ewww.
Even I've had it before. Absolutely exquisite.
Now, this is... aaaah... this is such an insult!
Impossible!
It's okay, it's okay, Gigi. Relax, relax, relax.
Doom!
Doom?
Justice Shopping! Whoaaa!
And now, it's time to introduce Justice's 2nd Anniversary Merch!
Yay!
First, take a look at this!
The Premium Acrylic Message Board!
Whoaaa!
We spoke with someone who actually used it.
Oh, you want to meet...
You want to talk about the premium acrylic message board?
Ah yeah, yeah, sûr! Oui oui!
Ah, this artwork is so cool! I love it so much!
Ah, using acrylic instead of paper was such a good choice!
And it makes it feel really special. And the foil stamped replicated messages...
...that's honestly the best part! I can't stop looking at it!
It just looks that much good, you know? Oui oui.
Ah, please support Justice and buy their merch! Oui, thank you, merci!
Wow! That's some pretty high praise!
We've still got lots more merch to introduce! So let's move on to the next item! Here it is...
Embroidered Patch Keychain!
So cute!
The illustrator behind this artwork is none other than Raora Panthera! And guess what? We've received a special message directly from her!
Tada! This is Raora Panthera, the artist behind the embroidered keychains! Ciao!
You know, I'm... I'm so happy I got the chance to draw for my Justice girls!
Creating something for my friends always feel really special, and... and I hope, I hope you're gonna love them as much as I do!
Yes, yes, yes! And you know, they took all my adorable illustrations and turned them into those cute embroidered keychains.
And, you know, since they're... since they're keychains, you can attach them to your bag and take them with you wherever you go.
Yeah! A little bit extra cuteness for your everyday life!
So make sure to pick one up! And trust me, the cuteness is guaranteed!
Yes! Look at that, they're so cute! Adorable!
What a wonderful piece of merch! Anyone would love to have that one in their home! Including me!
Oh right! Let's move on to the next piece of merch! Take a look at this... The Medal-Style Badge!
Cool!
We caught up with Justice's leader, Elizabeth, to get her thoughts.
Hmm? You want to hear about the badge?
Of course, my sweethearts, my Justicers.
This badge was designed with the image of law enforcement and authority in mind.
The weighty, prestigious look fits Justice perfectly, don't you think?
I think it looks absolutely... fan-tabby-dozy! It looks fantastic! Very cool.
Anyone who strives for justice should definitely get their hands on one.
Oh, and it also comes in a beautiful display box, so it's perfect for displaying and admiring as well.
I hope when you guys look at your... your medal or wear it, that you will remember how... us, Justice, are...
...so proud of you all, and we all really appreciate you so, so, so much. So I really hope that comes to mind every time you wear or look at this medal.
Mwah!
And that was a message from Elizabeth!
And now, for the final item we're introducing today! Here it is... The Double-Zip Patch Hoodie!
Wow!
We spoke with a fan who actually got their hands on the merch!
Wait, a Justice show?! Oh, oh my god, oh my god, I'm so excited!
You want to hear my thoughts on this merch, as the biggest Justice fan in the world...
...that has nothing to do with Justice, I'm just a random fan passing by?
Of course! Ask me anything!
[Question: What do you think about this item?]
Oh, I absolutely love the design! The patches inspired by all four members of Justice are so cute and stylish!
And I love how each one of them reflects their personality.
And, and the logo and text on the back gives it such a cool, premium look! It's the kind of hoodie that instantly makes you think...
...'Mmm, yes, this is Justice!'
[Question: How is it when you actually wear it?]
Oh, it's amazing! The brushed fleece lining makes it super warm and comfortable!
Not only does it look great, but it's also really practical!
And the fact that it comes in both L and LL sizes is fantastic!
I think a lot of fans will appreciate having different size options. So make sure to buy the Justice merch, okay?
Wow! Jolly good! Now, that's a passionate fan!
And that's it for Justice Shopping!
JUSTICE SHOPPING!
So, how was it?
It was awesome!
Oh, and what did you like the most?
The horses!
Oh, the horses.
And there's just this new flash!
We interrupt your regularly scheduled programming to bring you this breaking news.
We have just received an exclusive update from Justice, the global guardians of peace.
Rumor has it, a brand new track from the iconic four-piece is about to drop at any second.
I repeat, new music from Justice is imminent.
Do not touch that dial.
We will be right back with the world premiere.
This is Ouro Kronii, signing out.
Yeah
Are you there?
You're a SUPER GIRL
(JUSTICE JUST LIKE THAT)
(JUSTICE GET GET THAT)
If you're feeling trapped, send out a signal right above!
We'll find you, set you free then you can sign up for the club!
Danger, fun fun fun
Soul shine like the sun
(Minna happiness, Minna happiness)
The frig? I'm big! My strong strong muscle
They see me run, it's no miracle
You are shining SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL
I'm the SUPER!
Hey! DUPER!
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
SUPER DUPER!
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun <3 it
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit
I'm the SUPER!
Hey! DUPER!
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
I always want a pizza, stack those fries up to the sky
You lot say whatcha think about us hittin' town tonight?
(JUSTICE!)
Feeling happy time, no sad, say bye bye
(MOTTO MANIAC! JUSTICE JUST LIKE THAT!)
So stomp, stomp, stomp your feet to this beat
Cuz we are space, no no gravity!
You are shining SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL
I'm the SUPER!
Hey! DUPER!
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
SUPER DUPER!
I know you're feeling so super bad
You don't have depression, you're just super sad
We are change the world, that's hope!
If you doubt, hope you explode!
Justice loud, Justice proud
And we keep telling you!
WE ARE SUPER!
We are SUPER!
Hey! DUPER!
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
SUPER DUPER!
Justice we are Justice, make the baddies go boom!
Come on, come on, baby, rocket ship to the moon!
I'm the SUPER!
Hey! DUPER!
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
And that was \"SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL\", our brand new song!
Yeah!
And just like that, our second anniversary stream is coming to an end.
So what did you all think? We'll start with Raora this time.
Who, me?
Yeah, you first this time.
Ah, it was really fun, it was amazing!
I can't believe it's been already, what, two years?
I know!
Ah, thank you so much you guys as well for being...
...the best, the best companions ever, you know?
Yeah! I'm so grateful to you guys.
And thank you to Just Chat for supporting us since two years now!
It's insane, thank you!
Thank you, Just Chat! Thank you!
Woo! Oh!
Thank you very much, everyone, for...
And hello! Oh, sorry! Oh, sorry.
Let's do it, Cecilia! Do it with green!
Thank you very much for being here today, everyone!
Thank you for today! Stage of Justice! Yeah!
Please keep supporting us and listen to our song!
Stream Supernova Super Girl! Yeah!
All right! Elizabeth is about to speak!
What I think? I think the stage is very cool. Look at the stage! Wow!
And look at this amazing team. I couldn't ask for a better team!
I love you girls! I love you all very much! Aww!
And Justiaz, we love you all very much too. Thank you so much for supporting Justice!
Thank you so, so, so much! I love you so much!
So many kisses! Justiaz is so spoiled! Okay, Gigi...
(Kissing sounds) Are you eating that? She's eating that! Oh my god!
Thanks, Justiaz, for partying with us for... two years! Two!
I didn't even know Raora could count to two! Hey! Really, really!
But we made it to two years! Yeah! Thank you for partying!
Please stream Supernova Super Girl!
And learn the... The chants!
Learn the chants! For some reason, maybe you should learn the chants.
I wonder if there is a lyrics somewhere...
...for you to learn when we go... Supernova... Super Girl!
Or... Minna happiness!
Minna happiness! Yeah!
We all feel like super girls because of you guys. Thank you so much! Yes!
And don't forget to grab the merch! Purchase our merch!
Yes, thank you, thank you, thank you all so much for celebrating with us today!
Please keep supporting Justice, please, going forward as well.
Now then, let's all say goodbye together with our own chant! Yay!
Are you ready? I'm ready.
Justice... just like that!
Justice... get, get, get down! Woo!
Minna happiness!
Minna happiness! Bye-bye!
Stay tuned for the premier of Justice's new MV "SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL" right after this!