(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.3",
"generated_at": "2026-07-05T23:53:18.109243",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 16,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive English 4th Concert -Serendipity-
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Concert Merch Sales: Acrylic Stand
Concert Merch Sales: Button Badge & Acrylic Panel
hololive English 4th Concert -Serendipity-
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Concert Merch Sales: Acrylic Stand
Concert Merch Sales: Button Badge & Acrylic Panel
Greetings CC, my fated rival.
Greetings Ina, my distant rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Whoo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made...
...post about them with #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay! Thank you, AmiAmi, for supporting our rivalry!
And for supporting Serendipity! Be sure to check out our booth at...
...Anime Expo!
Yay!
Hey pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me!
All 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round 1 USA locations nationwide...
...starting this September!
So come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
[On-Screen Text] The concert will be starting soon.
[On-Screen Text] Attention For Visitors
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stands, Button Badges & Acrylic Panels
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stands, Button Badges & Acrylic Panels
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show begins.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Last Writes
(Shiori Novella / Mori Calliope)
AutoFister
(Gigi Murin / Cecilia Immergreen)
BloodRavens
(Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame / Nerissa Ravencroft)
A-D-V-E-N-T
Everyone, let's light the fire!
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire / Higher, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire / Sparking up like wildfire
Never ever have I ever / Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Take the chance and with my lighter / Start the fire
Come burn me out
I'm not a secret
All those carousel stories wearing me down
Step out of the system
Break out, give it everything
This is our time
We are destined to shine
Hello, brand new world
Would you welcome the light?
And free us from the night
Fire, fire, light the fire / Higher, higher, as you desire
United beating hearts
Jump into the flame of life
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump into the end of time
次元の向こう側連れて行ってあげる Rebellion
I'll take you to the other side of dimensions, Rebellion
I know that I can still be / The future of this story
I know that I can be free / The one and the only
They tell me that I'm crazy / I'll never let them stop me
With this, our perfect...
Time to get this party started
Never ever have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Fire, fire, light the fire
United beating hearts
Jump into the flame of life
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump into the end of time
次元の向こう側連れて行ってあげる Rebellion
I'll take you to the other side of dimensions, Rebellion
Jump into the flame of life
それぞれのステージへ
To our respective stages
Jump into the end of time
奇跡の向こう側連れて行ってあげる Rebellion
I'll take you to the other side of miracles, Rebellion
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Higher, higher, as you desire
Time to get this party started!
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below, takin' you all be—
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below we go
They think they want it? (Huh?)
They wanna ge- get down
We take 'em down, down, down
Queendom in the borderline
Run it, no surprise
You ain't gonna win but you can try
Told ya, you got no luck
End up in my lineup, listen, listen
Run, oh, hide and scream out, already locked ya up
Fool's games you always play
Call me corrupt, won't hear anything
Aiming my sight down right on your heart
Throwin' the keys out, shut down, I- I- I
Jump!
Love!
Up!
Below!
Justice!
Up!
Go!
Above!
Standin' on the edge, don't know me, unpredictable
Typical, you got nowhere to go
Show you somethin' real, my level, no you'll never know
As above so below, you should know
And we got it!
Run in the light, oh, my dio
What's wrong, what's right?
Rushin' in a fantasy
Wanna be disease
Sure that you won't ever make it out
Eyes follow now, do it, do it
New target locked on it now
Enemies? Girl, I lost count
See your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop, it's just the start
It's just the start!
Get down, get da-ra-da
Like it like that? Run it like that
Get down! (Get down, down, down, hey!)
Takin' me up, up, up, let's go
Goin' above, go below
Told ya, you already know, don't ya
Run in the light, oh, my dio
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night, oh, my dio
Come take a bite
Never ending, endless sky
As above, so it goes below
...now, don't worry, we've just begun.
We rise!
Yeah, we rise! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Standing on the edge
normally unpredictable, typical of you
Got nowhere to go
Show you something real
On my level, no, you'll never know
Half of the soul, go below, you should know
Just that level of unpredictable, beautiful
Just...
Look at, look at!
Next level, almost criminal
Half of the soul, it goes below
준비
Ready
다 쓸고 갈게, what's your shade?
I'll sweep it all away, what's your shade?
Players, they all complain
Why me? No, not again
Shout loud, ta-ta-ta, bang!
인과관계, throw the dice
Cause and effect, throw the dice
누가 날 만족시켜? Satisfaction
Who can satisfy me? Satisfaction
The broken and bruised, I got something to prove now
Abrakadabra, let's go, watch as they clash as they fall
끝까지 가보자고, 나는 내 멋대로 해, hey!
Let's go to the end, I do what I want, hey!
Double up, double up, only to lottery, we do, alright...
...we hit that high
Snake, I'm a snake, oh
Come on now, don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라
Burning up hot
Move all day, all night
Don't turn it off, can't stop, won't stop breathing
Who said the sky's the limit? Show them that we're in business
We are the young, efficient snakes, eyes never lie
Fly high with pride and leave our fears behind
지켜봐, 우리 둘이 만들어낼 party
Watch, the party we two will make
불합리하게 얽힌 safari
Unreasonably tangled safari
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me, 기꺼이 받아
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me, gladly accept it
Go go go, blindly, acting all naughty
사정없이 흔들어 재껴, 흔들어 재껴
Shake it mercilessly, shake it up
Shake it off, what goes around
Shoot your mouth, will come back down
Ready to fight, ready to scream it
Abrakadabra, let's go, watch as we're whipping it up
거칠지 않은 이 짓, 대들 수 있으면 play
This isn't rough, if you can stand up, play
Freeze up, demons, believe in the beating, just waiting...
...ee, we hit that high
Snake, I'm a snake, oh
Come on now, don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라, move all day, all night
Burning up hot, move all day, all night
Let me hear you alive! Let's make some noise!
Go!
We go hard!
위험을 삼켜, 전부 내 걸로 만들어, let's go
Swallow the danger, make it all mine, let's go
We go hard!
I want it all
죽지 않아, 전부 골라
I won't die, choose them all
맞서 싸워, 시작이야
Fight back, this is the start
끝까지 달려가
Run to the very end
We'll hit that high
Snake, I'm a snake, oh
Come on now, don't be shy
같이 전부 달아올라 이렇게
Burning up like this together
멈출 수 없어 같이 dance, dance, dance
Can't stop, let's dance, dance, dance together
Don't be afraid of losing, it's just a new beginning
Look at the clouds we're clearing, sometimes it takes a villain
Look at the clouds we're clearing, sometimes it sometimes takes a villain
Snakes, eyes, the time is now
Fly high with pride and leave our fears behind
Cut you off at the ties
This'll be the only battlefield that can tell of lies
Ego is enormous, so put the camera down and face it
They went and got complacent
Come and run with me
You say you stand for nothing, no one else can relate
Just know the company you keep is in the business of hate
Are you...
Right away, right away, close together now
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Go on, shoot, shoot, shoot, oh baby, what a mess
Ricochet, ricochet
You can think about me any time, any time
So get your street fight, this is trench war!
I'll make you mosh, mosh, mosh till you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision
Let them wonder what they're missing in the front row
Now here we go!
Seen a white line, it's a call to arms
We've become the wicked, the hunger-driven, make a decision
As you look here for permission to riot, you got it raw
Think about it for identity, click-clack, now you're alone
めらめら めらめら
Mera mera, mera mera
Stand for nothing, play the coward, stand for someone, you'll devour
It's a step and tread, the threat, the quest, the endless, yes, the next success!
めらめら めらめら
Mera mera, mera mera
Stand for nothing, play the coward, stand for someone, you'll devour
It's a step and tread, the threat, the quest, the endless, yes, the next success!
めらめら めらめら
Mera mera, mera mera
Let me say this, WOAH!
狙う獲物 隙 この子に決めた
I've chosen my target, the moment I saw an opening
角度調整 角度微調整
Angle adjusted, micro-adjusted
飽きたらポイから Please send me business
Once I'm bored I'll throw it away, so please send me business
Decide, special is the scarlet, risk
Yeah, bite, bite, bite it, chips are stacked
We're some lovely animals, till we crack
最高！ 最恐！ 隠したアイデンティティ
The best! The most terrifying! Hidden identity
集まったこの高感度のフィーリング
All of these high-sensitivity feelings gathered
Always starving! 時間の無駄無駄
Always starving! A waste of time
ヤダ！ ヤダ！ I can tell you're not a friend
No way! No way! I can tell you're not a friend
全部、ごちそうさまです
Thank you for the feast
ごちそうさまです
足りない！ 足りない！
Not enough! Not enough!
舞台消すなら 脳裏、脳裏
If the stage is gone, it's in my mind
全部奪うなら 総取り、総取り
If I take it all, it's a clean sweep
圧倒的、優位、軽々、登る 見下してやるわ
Overwhelmingly superior, effortlessly climbing, looking down on you
めらめら めらめら
Mera mera, mera mera
最高！ 最恐！ 張り付き 剥がそう
The best! The most terrifying! Stick it on, rip it off
アンプ、エフェクター、シールド、接続
Amp, effectors, shield, connected
全部、OK？ レッツゴー！
Everything OK? Let's go!
Yeah, check, check, testing when you are out of ideas
Yes, yes, I'm the one that's not impressed
全部、最低！ 先手を取り、払え！
Everything's the worst! Take the initiative and banish them!
もっと、光って、波に乗れ！
Shine brighter, ride the wave!
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
I gotta tell you, I never lied to you
Never would I lie to you, believe me, not yet
Why should we take control?
My primal ways of a bull terrier
It's a territorial, after-life battle
Underestimated every single word
They can aim but it doesn't make a difference at all
Got a million different enemies that can never be calmed
Walking up to a battle when you know that you've won
Here's a motivation, watch it all burn!
I gotta tell you, I never lied to you
Never would I lie to you, believe me, not yet
When the thunder crashes down
When the world breathes under my pressure
There'll be no one to save
Where is your precious human will to survive?
Was it just empty words for your grief?
I'll reach inside this soul and all that remains
Is delusion and decay
How's a king to live this way?
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
Lately I realized I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know, do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree
Oh, hey
I can feel the rain wash over...
...wash over us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice...
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
And I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side, my heart is beating in double time
In every moment, you make me feel alive, it goes like...
I can feel the rain wash over us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice...
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
And I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hahaha, oh my god, haha!
Hello, hello!
Hi! Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello!
Hi, hello.
Hello up there!
Hello down there!
Hello, みな!
Hello, everyone!
Hey, who are you?
Mmh, hi there, darlings! This is Hololive English -Advent- Devilish Diva...
...the one, the only...
...Nerissa Ravencroft!
And with me...
Ah... Oh! Ahahaha!
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue...
...also known as the Scarlet Queen, the Harbinger of Order, Leader of Justice...
...I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you... lovely!
Woo! Ah!
That was so fun! Yeah!
Wow! What a setlist so far, huh?
I know, we're starting off really strong!
We had...
Snake Eyes, Snake Eyes!
Woah, woah, oh my god!
And we had Mori...
...rocking it out! Seriously!
And then Kronii coming in with her new song, so good! Yeah, such cute dance moves!
And we had Advent and Justice, of course!
Yes, yes, did you enjoy?
Did you enjoy?
Couldn't hear you! Did you enjoy?
Yeah, hello!
Wow, you know what? We didn't have solos yesterday.
No, no. So, we must be having them today, right?
So excited!
Oh, yeah. For mine, I want to practice something, okay? Oh, okay, go on.
A little chant from Great Exardia. So when I go "Oggy Oggy Oggy", you go "Oi Oi Oi"!
Are you ready?
Okay, here we go!
Oggy Oggy Oggy! Oi Oi Oi!
Perfect! Completely... "Compiki"!
What about you? Any sneak peeks about your solo?
Mmh... would you guys really like a sneak peek?
Well... I think I have to remind you all...
...no matter how you identify, no matter what you are, you in this audience today...
...are my wives!
Can I hear it from my wives?!
What the freak?! Everyone here is your wife?! Yes, including you!
So, if I ask you to sing along, you have to, all right?
You've got to!
Oh, yeah, that's my hint.
Does it give it away? Maybe a little.
You know, we're singing, and I was thinking that we'd like to hear you...
I sing too.
Hehehe...
You guys know I like harmonies?
Yes. So we're gonna split you into different notes, okay?
So we have...
...you guys over here.
...you guys over here,
...and all of you at the top!
So, we're gonna start off with you guys here.
Yeah. We want you to hold this note:
Ah~
Ah~ Perfect!
You guys: ah~
Up there: ah~
All right, everyone together!
Ah~
Woo! Beautiful! Beautiful!
Oh my gosh, we have a choir!
So good!
We've got to do that more often, that was cool. Yeah!
I like hearing you all sing for us.
Ah~ Hey, that reminds me of a song, doesn't it? You know, that- that first note? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah~ You know, something like...
Three, two, one...
It's wondrous...
Somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me
Embracing Serendipity
Whoa, that was great, wasn't it?!
Yeah!
Harmonizing, yeah!
And...
It's wonderful harmonizing with you, and I just want to say...
...thank you so much for being my friend.
I love you!
Ahhh!
Anyway, oh...
We're gonna sing together!
I got too excited! I got too excited!
I'm just too happy! I'm so happy!
Me too! Woo!
Weee woo wee woo wee woo...
Oh, I spammed too fast. There we go.
Anyway...
無料配信は、次の曲で最後になります。
The free stream will end with the next song.
ライブの続きは、ぜひ配信チケットを買って見てね！
To see the rest of the live concert, please buy a streaming ticket and watch!
The YouTube free sneak peek is only until the next song, which is...
...a duet!
If you want to continue watching, click the link in the description and get your tickets now!
All right, everybody. After three, we all say Serendipity. Got it?
Yeah! Ah, thanks so much! We love you guys so much!
We love you!
All right, here we go! Three, two, one...
Serendipity!
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, become a legend!
青い風がいま
The blue wind now...
胸のドアを叩いても
...knocks on the door of your heart,
私だけをただ見つめて
but you only look at me,
微笑んでいるあなた
smiling at me.
そっと触れるもの
Gently seeking something to touch,
求めることに夢中で
you are completely absorbed,
運命さえまだ知らない
not even knowing your destiny yet,
いたいけな瞳
with those innocent eyes.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう
But someday you will realize,
その背中には
that on your back,
遥か未来 めざすための
you have wings...
羽根があること
...to fly toward the distant future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A cruel angel's thesis,
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
will soon fly out from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
With a surging, hot pathos,
思い出を裏切るなら
if you betray your memories...
少年よ 神話になれ
Become a legend, young boy.
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
もっともっと盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get more and more excited!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Back to you, princess!
ずっと眠ってる
Still sleeping,
私の愛の揺りかご
The cradle of my love,
あなただけが 夢の使者に
The morning that only you
呼ばれる朝がくる
Are called by the messenger of dreams is coming.
細い首筋を
On your slender neck,
月あかりが映してる
The moonlight is reflecting.
世界中の時を止めて
I want to stop the time of the whole world
閉じこめたいけど
And lock it away, but...
もしもふたり逢えたことに
If there is a meaning
意味があるなら
In our meeting,
私はそう 自由を知るための
I, too, want to know freedom,
バイブル
A bible.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
The thesis of a cruel angel,
悲しみがそしてはじまる
And then sadness begins.
抱きしめた命のかたち
The shape of the life I held in my arms,
その夢に目覚めたとき
When I wake up from that dream,
誰よりも光を放つ
Shining more brightly than anyone,
少年よ 神話になれ
Become a legend, young boy.
人は愛をつむぎながら
People spin love
歴史をつくる
And create history,
女神なんてなれないまま
While never being able to become a goddess,
私は生きる
I live on.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
The thesis of a cruel angel,
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
Will soon fly out from the windowsill,
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
With the surging hot pathos,
思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く
Embrace this universe and shine,
少年よ 神話になれ
Become a legend, young boy.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[On-Screen Text] The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.