(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.3",
"generated_at": "2026-07-05T02:27:18.552581",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 16,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. / Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors / Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. / Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors / Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Greetings CC, my fated rival.
Greetings Senpai, my distant rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Woo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made...
...post about it with #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay!
Thank you AmiAmi for supporting us!
...rivalry.
And for supporting Serendipity...
Be sure to check out our booth at...
Anime Expo!
Yeah!
Hey Pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me!
All 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round 1 USA locations nationwide,
starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
[注意事項] 公演中のフラッシュライトにご注意ください。大声での声援は可能です。
[Attention] Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK.
【グッズ情報：第2次販売】
[Merch Info: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
【グッズ情報：アクリルスタンド】
[Merch Info: Acrylic Stand]
【グッズ情報：缶バッジ／アクリルパネル】
[Merch Info: Button Badge / Acrylic Panel]
【ファンメッセージ＆ファンアート】
[Fan Messages & Fan Art]
間もなく開演いたします。
The concert will be starting soon.
【来場者の皆様への注意事項】公演中のフラッシュライトにご注意ください。大声での声援はOKです。
[Attention For Visitors] Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
【グッズ情報：第2次販売】
[Merch Info: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
注意事項：公演中のフラッシュライトにご注意ください / 声援はOKです
Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering is ok
コンサートグッズ第2弾販売
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
Sing our blue again
Continuing this odyssey
We'll start this new refrain
Brimming with memories
And when the clouded skies become bright
Let's reunite!
What's up, everyone? Welcome to hololive English 4th Concert, Serendipity!
Wow! And we're back!
Let's kick off the show with a Myth Medley!
Ready? One, two, three!
Showtime baby, I would say
Today's breakfast was slightly delayed
Revving up the engine, is it really enough?
Stomach rumbling endlessly, why?
Take it easy, what did we learn?
Set a fire in the hearts when the PC burns, ah
Optimistic, focus on a quick fix
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks
Growing stronger than ever and never saying die
And I'm aware it's ironic, but where's the freaking lie?
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers to senpai
Not losing to you young people, in our hearts...
...a myth that's priceless in all!
Spanning new dimensions
We can bring another mystery to light
Blending our ascension, dancing inside
We ignite!
Join us while we're celebrating in the myth that we're creating
There's another story waiting
Through this world and beyond
Our distant dreams have brought us here
A strong, unyielding bond
Guiding us endlessly, will bring us moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on
And though these winds may scatter us
We'll keep this promise
When the moment's finally right
We'll always find a way to reunite!
One, two, three!
Light up, let's begin!
We'll start stage right and shuffle on in!
The crowd is ready, let's steal the show
We're jumping with joy, let's go!
Fortunes of self so cute, the band
Will keep on entertaining hand in hand
It's our greatest moment yet
A spectacle they'll never forget!
We'll party from dusk to dawn
The show will go on and on!
Tell them that we're here to stay
And spread the news from Tokyo to Broadway!
Gleaming spotlight
Get together, we'll be boogying all night!
Beaming so bright
Now we're feeling alright!
Since the day we met, we've fallen and going strong
And we'll keep moving right along!
So keep on dancing, move your feet
Nothing can stop us, we're perfect, complete!
In harmony, no matter where we go
Like it's meant to be, don't you know?
We're gonna feel so alive when it's our street
Ready to put on another show!
There's an answer out there somewhere
And the muses whisper truth or dare
In the hazard of a tilted world
But no one's keeping score
Stay course and be tenacious
Since the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, go all in
I'll play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
And we'll turn in the betting ring
These outcomes are spun in golden string
And through this tangled thread
I see what's up ahead
Our lives trace
A thread of fate
We got to try our luck
And spin the wheel
La la la la-la-la-la
I've always been this way
Oh, yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on
Our threads unbroken
Cord, life, by flex and string
Casting lives together
At the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I spin back round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
Black, white, or is it black or red?
I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance
A daring dance
I win this game of fate with my own hands
La la la...
I'm taking fate into my hands
Oh, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Blazing fire!
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
Tension rising to the top, won't look back, I'll never stop
Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot
It's your fault, baby
Fever burning up inside, it can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
Come on and come on, I wanna confess, baby oh baby, I'm gettin' obsessed
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter, gonna be wanna be ready for more
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over!
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire!
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch, it's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm bearing my soul
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play, a dangerous game
Got your fire running through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
Give me your love, give me your attention, shaking me, making me, making me crazy
And tear it all away until you're mine
Drivin' me crazy, tellin' me, tellin' me, what do you mean?
Caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over!
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire, love, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire, love, burn for my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire!
Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump!
Blazing fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fueling my delusion
I want you burning for me
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me closer if you dare
Fire, love, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire, love, burn for my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire!
Gigi Murin
[On-Screen: Gigi Murin]
Cecilia Immergreen
[On-Screen: Cecilia Immergreen]
Autofister
[On-Screen: Autofister]
1, 2, 3, go!
Gigi Murin! Cecilia Immergreen!
And we are...
Autofister!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Excuse me, foreigner, can you point me to the bathroom? The lines in LA are so long.
Ah, Moment, ich passe... Uh, uh, uh... Aufpassen, aufpassen, aufpassen! Ah, you want me to speak German? Oh!
Ah, one moment, I'll... Oh, watch out, watch out, watch out! Ah, you want me to speak German? Oh!
On this day, our connection close
Can keep it within your memory
Oh come on, you're supposed to hold
And let our random madness, let's run this story!
Take our hand, let's fly away
Break a leg, now challenge the day
Quick, before your time is up, give in
And be our playmate!
Punch, slap, jump, our dreams away
Love yourself, don't be afraid
Find just one solution, give in, release all the hate!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, matte!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, wait!
Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Autofister!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, matte!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, wait!
Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, come and play!
Come on, LA! We want to hear you shout!
Say something, Gigi! Oh my god, why won't you say something?!
Say say something, Gigi, wait...
Oh come on, can you keep our hope
To lose your heart in reverie
Best no way to divert this trope
So laugh, and run, and let's run this story!
Take our hand, let's fly away
Make a way, now choose the day
Quick, before your time is up, give in
And be our playmate!
Punch, slap, jump, our dreams away
Love yourself, don't be afraid
Live up your ambition, come on, let go of expectations!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, matte!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, wait!
Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Ceci, Autofister!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, matte!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, wait!
...or rather.
One, two, ready, go!
Take a hand, let's fly away
Turn around and let us play
Find just one good reason, come on
Join in our sacred adventure
Fly away
La, la, la, la, la
Come on, let's play!
Yeah!
Hahaha!
Hello, hello!
Hello!
Welcome to Hololive's very first...
...and chat's greatest tweet:
"My butt's too big for this seat!"
Ah!
Wow, look at it, it's so big and juicy! How impressive!
Hello, everyone!
It's me, Cecilia Immergreen!
And me, Gigi Murin!
And together, we are...
Autofister!
Well, LA, we wanted to do some LA call-and-response!
So I'm going to say something, and you cheer if you like it, okay?
Okay?
The beach!
Woo!
Hololive in LA!
Sitting in traffic!
Whatever.
CCGG in LA!
Yeah!
Okay, everybody, excited to be here at Hololive...
...Serendipity? Serendipity!
Please all stand. It is the 4th of July weekend...
...for the flag...
Please stand up, everyone!
Oh, say can you see...
...by the dawn's early light...
...what so proudly...
Okay, okay, okay, shut up, shut up, shut up! That's enough!
That's enough, enough, enough.
Enough with that chit, okay.
How about we do a CCGG chant?
How do we...
Oh, no, no, no! Not yet, not yet, not yet!
USA? No, no, no!
No, no, no, not yet!
Okay guys, since you are standing, we want you to do our chant of our chorus...
...plus... Stomping!
...stomping to the beat, okay?
So, the left side, we want them to be green...
...and this side... Green!
Orange!
Green! Orange! Do it now!
Quickly!
Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect!
Orange, good.
Okay, okay, okay, stomping...
...and you stomp...
...and then we say CCGG, CCGG.
Yes, yes.
CC!
GG!
GG! Madness!
CC!
GG!
GG! Autofister!
CC!
GG!
GG! Madness!
CC!
GG!
Come let's play!
一緒に... together.
Together... together.
Everyone together really fast though.
Show, impress us, okay? Okay?
Are you ready? Are you ready? Okay.
CC GG CC GG CC GG Madness!
CC GG CC GG Autofister!
CC GG CC GG Come let's play!
Woo!
Really impressive, guys! That was really, really good.
Maybe America is awesome.
USA! USA! USA! USA! USA!
Yeah, they freaking love us again...
...in America!
In America. Well...
For those at home...
...this is sadly the end of the free section.
So please... Boo!
There's one more song, actually. The song after this.
Oh, oh, one more song. One more song. One more song. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
But there's the tickets... for the streaming ticket down below, so please check them out.
In the description. Check out the streaming tickets, okay?
Autofister gets to do this today, okay?
And...
無料配信は次の曲で最後になります。
This will be the last song of the free stream.
ライブの続きはぜひ配信チケットを買ってみてね！
For the rest of the live concert, please buy a streaming ticket!
買ってみてね！
Please buy it!
All you freaking haters.
All you freaking haters, okay?
Don't hate us. Don't be a freaking loser.
Don't hate us. For the very last part...
...since this is the very first MC, we want you to be as loud as possible, okay?
We will become a bowling ball and a bowling pin,
and we need you to chant "Serendipity", right? Okay?
Keep chanting until we leave, okay?
Keep chanting until we're gone!
Don't stop until we're gone!
Don't stop.
Okay. Well, one time together, everyone!
Serendipity!
I'll be your exit route
pound the gavel and sentence me to doom
even though I'm just doing what you do
decide which lies become the truth
no, you never really thought about it that far
judging me when I can see you've got the same scars
that's the price that I pay, it's a deep mark
come, pick your sacrifice
nail me to your crucifix
nothing else can fix this
so I'll take the blame
see yourself reflected and not corrected
one request, it's:
don't be gentle
don't be kind when you
murder, murder, murder the martyr
poke their eyes out
leave them blind
one request, it's -
hypocrisy
I've seen what you do in private things
all your friends yeah they know what you really think
to your glory, the masses keep on singing
point at me in a hurry
pick a scapegoat for the new controversy
even when I'm buried, hidden, silent, you'll be wary
please dear god show them mercy
nail me to your crucifix
nothing else can fix this
so I'll take the blame
see yourself reflected and not corrected
one request, it's:
don't be gentle
don't be kind when you
murder, murder, murder the martyr
poke their eyes out
leave them blind
break me now
take me down
me down
one request, it's -
I see your sins
and they're in your soul
consume and ignore
decay to your core
I'll never win to you
but within you'll -
break, break, break, break
and when I -
you will -
and in your hands, the hammer pounds the nail in
don't be gentle
don't be kind when you
murder, murder, murder the martyr
poke their eyes out
leave them blind
one request, it's -
do you love me?
again, again, again
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！