(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Well, you might be wondering how I got here.
It all started on my debut, one year ago.
Hmm, hmm, hmm...
Ah!
Ouch... Ah...
Wait, wait, wait, wait... are you going to play your entire debut video?
No, but I have a three-hour video essay prepared.
But no, you don't have time or budget for that.
What?
Let me fix this.
Kronii, no!
Ah, oh man, I wish I had 3D.
Oh? Oh?
Huh?
Aah!
get flashbanged haha
Spin to win!
Ah, my ankles...
Ah, my ankle!
Hello everyone, it's me, Cecilia Immergreen from Hololive Justice!
Spin to win! Yay, I'm 3D!
Oh my god, I'm so nervous, I'm so excited!
Hi everyone! Hello tous, hello everyone in chat! Hello, hello!
It's me, and I was just born out of this egg.
Non-canon, by the way.
Today we'll be going on a beautiful adventure...
...and maybe having some guests.
And actually, our very first guest is right here on my shoulder.
Who could it be? It's Ototori! Yay!
Oh, he's so cute!
Yeah, this is our very first guest today. I wonder who else is going to come today.
Maybe, maybe some people?
But Otomo, what are you doing? Wait, you're so cute!
What do you want, Otomo? Huh? What is it?
Uh, can I say no?
Wow, okay...
So Otomo has just said... I don't know if you can understand him, he has a very weird dialect.
But he just said that since it's been a year since I crashed that car, we're supposed to learn how to drive.
Do you guys want to go learn how to drive? Huh? Should we do it?
I guess we should do it, Otomo. Okay.
I think... I wonder what we should be doing next.
Okay, let's see, guys. Here are options. Please vote in chat!
a) find a driving teacher
b) ask otomo what to do next
First, find a driving teacher,
or ask Otomo what to do next. Maybe he has a better idea.
I'm thinking, I'm thinking. But yeah, while we're waiting for the poll to end,
maybe I can show off a little bit. This is what I look like!
Finally, you can see me from the back!
Ah, this is my bow, my pretty bow! Yay!
Okay, A, B... no, you don't have to type it into chat, you're going to have to put it into the poll.
Okay, is the poll good? Shall we see? Oh, not yet.
Okay, yeah, the bow, and then if you look closely you can see that everything reflects...
...everything that's made out of metal.
And Ototori is here too, of course, not forgotten. Never forgotten!
And Otomo is very cute.
Oh, the poll is over, it's done! Okay, which one won?
A! Find a driving teacher. Okay!
I think I know exactly where to go.
Wait, but I forgot, if we're going to drive, I'm going to have to take off the skirt...
...because it's very stiff and I can't sit in it.
Let's do that real quick.
Excuse you, back off, Otomo, back off!
Ta-da!
This is what I look like without the skirt on!
Ah, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Okay, let's go this way!
Let's find a driving teacher!
Hmm... Huh.
According to the Otomo, this is where I'm supposed to go.
But no one's here. Huh?
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa! Be careful!
Danger, danger! Oh my god!
Hi everyone!
What are you guys doing here?
Oh, actually a little Otomo told us...
...that you were really bad at driving.
No! No! No!
That's a lie. That's fake.
But anyway...
Very big galaxy brain Ririka...
...and Biboo...
...and Sora-senpai...
...will tell you how to drive! Yay!
Can you guys drive?
Sure! We're the best!
I totally have a license... No I don't. But it's fine.
Okay, I think if you guys are teaching me...
...I have nothing to worry about. So, let's do it.
Okay! Well, if you're ready, please get on the vehicle.
Your noble steed.
So what do I do?
Um, you do the you turn the you go... Wait! Whoa!
Cece! Are you okay? Are you alright?
Wait, wait, no, no, no, I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
Guys, don't worry.
No, it's okay.
Oh, but that could've gone better I think.
So let me show you how it's done! Yay!
Okay! We'll call this the practical task.
Get hit and you'll go boom! Holokart Time Attack!
Our racing course is ready! Look, look!
The rules are simple.
The four of us will compete to see who has the fastest time...
...completing the course while avoiding the obstacles.
The course starts with two cones.
Feel free to dodge it, or just knock it down if it's in your way.
Then you'll enter the barrel zone!
Dodge them like a pro!
And then finally, you aim for the perfect park at the finish line...
...to clear the course.
Yay! Simple enough, right? Easy, easy, easy!
But, but! If you mess up or hit anything other than the cones...
Total explosion!
Uh oh!
And it won't just explode.
Each explosion adds a penalty of three seconds to your time.
So, try not to risk it.
Or risk it, or do it fast, it's totally up to you.
I don't want to die! Nooo!
Okay, I'll go first and show Cece how it's done! Yay!
I'm so nervous.
Okay, pre-race interview.
Sora-senpai, is there anything you would like to say?
I'll do my best and have fun!
Okay! Yay!
Ready?
Okay.
Okay!
The Holokart Time Attack starts...
NOW!
GO!
And she's on the race! She goes to the first loop!
Okay!
Let's see if she can finish. Oh!
Okay, Sora-chan... Sora-chan, she's going fast!
Okay, the last loop is the start.
Keep going, Sora-chan! Okay!
Go, go, go! Go, Sora-chan!
She's got this! She's so safe! Oh!
That's on the straight! The last burst is so difficult!
Now the finish line! The finish line!
Go get it!
Yeah! Goal! Yeah!
Good job!
That was explosive!
Yeah!
Okay, now we are checking the final time. So...
in the meantime, how was it? How did you think?
Ah, I think I did great!
Yeah!
Okay, let's look at the time!
Oh! One minute and three seconds!
Yeah! That's actually really good!
And you got one explosion, so three seconds is added.
But very fun! Sora-chan! Yes, Sora!
Good job! Good job!
Okay, okay, okay, who's next?
Who will be our next challenger?
Hey, I'm going!
Okay, Iroha-chan, step up to...
the starting line right here.
Yeah, yeah! Alright, Iroha-chan,
is there anything you would like to say to the audience or Senpai or anybody?
I will show you my Holo-Monkey style! Nice driving!
Yeah!
Alright, Iroha-chan, are you ready?
Sure! I can!
Okay, she sounds very, very sure about herself.
Let's see, let's see if she can put her skills to the test.
Alright, the Holokart Time Attack starts...
NOW!
Okay, okay, okay, you got this!
Ganbatte!
Good luck!
GO!
Stay away! Go away from me! No!
I don't want to die! No!
No! Stay away! No!
Ah! You did it!
Yeah! I'm alive! Yes, she's alive!
Good job!
Alright, that was really good.
We're checking the time now, but let's hear it. Are you okay from the challenger?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
I will never drive. I might kill someone.
That might be, that might be for the best, you know?
Yes, I have to be your Sensei and Senpai.
Alright, Iroha-chan, your time...
Yes! Wow! One minute and nine seconds!
You received five explosions, so five penalties,
a total of fifteen second penalty.
So that means I was worse than Sora-chan Senpai.
You were, but you hit the stuff so you're silver.
Yeah, yeah!
Our next... next contestant!
Yay!
It's my turn now.
Hehe.
It's Biboo's turn.
Anything you'd like to say?
I will win.
She's gonna lose.
No, she's so good. Have confidence.
Yeah, you're good at gaming, so maybe driving is also very good.
We'll see.
Okay. Start now!
3... 2... 1... Go!
Biboo, go!
Go, go, go!
Oh, it's... oh-oh!
Biboo!
What?!
Go, Biboo! Go, Biboo!
What?! Final lap already?
Oh no!
Aaaah! No!
Yeah, that was really good!
Yay!
You okay? How was it?
I win! I win! I win! I win!
Just checking the time of how long it was.
Let's see, let's see...
Maybe I shouldn't drive either.
Everyone's my teachers. Only Sora-chan so far has driven safely.
Oh wait, time is coming. Oh wait!
Oh, so finally, you were 1 minute and 11 seconds!
FINAL TIME 01:11
So that means you were the latest.
Oh... oh...
You got four times explosions, so that means 20 seconds added.
Dang it! Oh well, whatever.
Anyway, I still had the time of my life. It was a blast!
No battle, please.
Well, for our last challenger, we have prepared for you a special course because you are our student, right?
Since you've already seen this, you have an advantage going last, so we're not going to give you that advantage.
Oh, okay.
Here it is!
Oh! Wow! It's Justice! It's Justice!
Yeah, Justice 3D was not in our budget, so we have cutouts. Thanks, guys.
Also, just so you know, this is your driver's practical, so you're going to have to beat our average time.
And our average time was 1 minute and 8 seconds!
Rule: Driving test cleared if average time is faster than 1:08!
I got this. Okay, watch... watch me.
It's okay. Guys, don't worry. Easy, easy, easy. Easy.
This is what I've been training for for the last 10 minutes. Don't worry about it.
Okay, I'm ready.
Anything you'd like to say before the race?
Spin to win! Spin to win!
Yeah, you should be spinning as much as possible.
Yeah, I should be spinning. Thank you. Okay, let's go.
Any advice for Cece-senpai? Okay, advice?
First, never slow down! Okay.
Second, go faster!
Whoa, okay, go faster. Faster!
You can do it!
Okay, the Holokart Time Attack starts... now!
3... 2... 1... Go!
Go, Cecilia, go! Show us your driving skills!
Go go go go go go go!
Don't look! Whoa!
I'm so good! Whoa!
Okay, okay, okay, okay...
Okay, now for the finish!
You have to park! Park!
Yeah!
Good! Good!
Are you sure you should be teaching us?
Maybe I should be teaching you guys!
What do you think your time was?
Faster than ours or not? 20 seconds!
20 seconds! A little bit more than that.
But how do you feel after the race?
Invigorated.
I feel like I learned so much today.
Were we good teachers? Were we?
You especially, IRyS!
All times coming!
Your time is... 56 seconds! Oh my god!
You only got one penalty! Oh my god!
Wow, Cece, you... pass!
Congratulations! Such a great job!
Thank you! Our driving spot also...
Here we go!
O-nice!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for teaching me! Bye-bye!
Hope you enjoyed! Bye-bye!
Come on! Wait, I want to go too!
Wait, wait, wait, let's go!
Bye-bye! I want to get in a car!
Wait, wait!
Wait, what are we doing?
Going on a drive.
We need a third.
Ah, you're right.
IRyS!
Let's go!
One, two, three, let's go!
Lost hope in love, I thought I'd never understand
Couldn't help it when you took my hand
Roads I ignored before, you left me wanting more
Destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead
Neon lights fly by, is it fake or reality?
Not sure of much but know I'm ready
Soaring these streets make me complete
Full throttle, come give me your all
Engine's not keeping up with the beat of my heart
Just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last till the sun's up
One, two, three, let's go!
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line mark the end but we'll...
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up
And don't look back again
Carbonated love
One, two, three, let's go!
Took a bet on love, it's better than I could've dreamed
Look at what we've done, we're too extreme
Pour me your favorite drink, so much until we sink
Down to the bottom, don't wanna miss a thing
The track we're on might crash, oh what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring old avenues
Race through the night, my guiding light
Sparkling, I'm right here with you
Engine's not keeping up with the beat of my heart
Just can't get enough
just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
only us, make it last
Till the sun's up
One, two, let's go!
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach a line, mark the end, but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up
and don't look back again
Carbonated love
Come overflow my cup, I'm empty without you
Make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm the fool
Another night of bliss, speed up, let's make it new
Love me despite the way I'm crazy just for you
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach a line, mark the end, but we'll
Let's go!
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush, we shouldn't don't give up
Fire it up again
Time is up, not enough, fill it up
and begin
Carbonated love
Wait! What?!
Huh?
Wait! Where'd it go?!
It's... it's your fault!
Hehehe. Losers.
Oh! Otomo, you took IRyS's place!
Wow! Amazing!
Can you... can you even see the road?
Wait, wait! Eyes on the road! Eyes on the road!
No, no, don't worry guys. It's fine, there's no cars here.
There's barely any cars, so really it's completely fine.
But yeah, do you see?
Do you see how much I learned in such a little time?
Do you feel safe, guys?
Do you feel next... safe next to me in this car? Hmm?
What? What are you saying, Otomo? Do... is it safe here? Huh?
Hmm... Yeah, I think so. Whoa!
What's that? Otomo, look!
Can you... Otomo, jump up and look!
Oh! I had turned this off for today because I didn't want it to disrupt...
you know, my special day.
But I guess since we're in the car, it makes sense that...
that Otomos would fall from the sky.
Yeah, every membership, a gift membership...
gives a little 'plop'. It's like a birth.
Wow, the circle of Otomo life. That is so beautiful. Wow, that's incredible.
I wish I could see you, Otomo, but you're so small.
I wish you could see the road and be impressed with how good I am at driving, you know? Wow.
Hehe, you look so cute. Wait, can I pet you?
Pat-pat-pat. Pet-pet-pet. Otomo.
Okay, okay. Well, anyways, I hope you are impressed by my driving today.
Yeah, I really do hope so.
But I think... I think that's too...
I think that's enough Otomos, because otherwise I'll struggle with seeing the road.
Okay, that's enough.
Okay, okay, you can stop now.
No! No! Ah! Hey, stop, stop!
Stop it! Stop! No, no, no! Stop!
Stop! It's enough! Stop! Stop!
That's too many! Stop, stop! Ah!
Ah! I can't see! Get rid of those!
Ah! I can't see! I can't!
I can't see! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
What... what?
Where... what is this?
Where am I?
Whoa...!
It's so pretty in here! Wow!
Wait, I think I want to match...
...this aesthetic a little bit better.
Let me get my skirt back.
Ta-da! Wow!
Otomo?
Otomo! Otomo! Oh...
There you are, you little...!
This is your fault!
How dare you fall on top of my car and make us crash!
You stupid little...!
Why did you do that to me with all your friends, huh?
What did I ever do to deserve that, huh?
You know what? This is your fault as well!
How dare you make me crash, you little...!
I worked so hard for this!
I worked so hard today, and you...!
No, okay. No, it's okay.
Come back up. Come back up.
Come back up, you baby. It's okay.
Anger's not the right answer.
Otomo is shaking, I guess...
I guess you must be really afraid.
Okay, I'll take a step back. I'm sorry.
Anger's not the right answer right now.
We are trapped in this beautiful world, and maybe...
we're gonna have to find out
what we're supposed to do here.
Otomo, do you have any ideas?
Music
Huh? Oh, of course!
How did I not think about that?
This is the inner clockwork world of our minds!
Both you and me, Otomo, or just me, I'm not sure.
Emotions
He doesn't know either.
Okay, so what we have to do here, apparently, is...
Otomo wants to learn how to feel emotions.
Otomo wants to be human.
I do understand a lot of emotions...
...with all my time on Earth.
And I think my favorite emotion of all time is...
JOY!
So, let's teach Otomo some joy, shall we?
What's the most joyous thing in the world, guys?
Of course! Music!
Playing music with others!
So, let's play some music, shall we? Yay!
Flashbang!
Oh? Why do I have...
...why do I have my violin? Huh, that's weird.
Cece! Hello! Hi!
Oh my god, all of you here! And with instruments!
Does that mean that my dream of having...
...a school band is finally coming true?
Yeah! Let's join her!
Okay, okay! Shall we play a song together?
Yeah! Let's do it!
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to keep watching the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to get that dream in my hands
それぞれ 違った
With our own different...
ココロで 走れ GO
hearts, let's run, GO
どこを見ても真っ暗な
No matter where I looked, it was pitch black
場所に芽生えてた
But a tiny hope sprouted
ほんの小さな希望に
In just a tiny hope,
この瞳奪われた
My eyes were stolen.
不安で揺れる心を
I tuned my heart that was shaking with anxiety
上手くチューニングして
I tuned it well...
ほんの小さな勇気を
And squeezed out a little bit of courage
振り絞っていたよ
Squeezing it out.
諦めの文字
I delete the words 'give up' and move forward
デリートして進む
I delete them.
苦しいときも
Even when it's hard,
もう私は ひとりじゃないから
I'm not alone anymore.
だからもっと夢追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dreams even more
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像 越えてく
I'll show you a world
世界見せてあげる
that goes beyond your imagination.
アクセスしてみたい？
Do you want to try accessing it?
後悔なんてそうさせない
I won't let you regret it.
Whoo!
Yay! Thank you so much, guys!
Oh? Look. Otomo?
So cute! Wow!
Is that a gear of emotions?
Oh my god!
Is it gonna learn? Whoa!
What? Oh!
She learned joy! Joy! Happy!
Thanks to you guys, thank you so much!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Gotta go. Come on.
Okay, you can go now. Okay, bye!
Yay!
Okay, let me put this away for now.
I'll get it back in a second.
That was so much fun!
What did you think, guys?
Oh, Otomo, did you learn how to be happy?
Are you happy now? Yeah?
So cute! That was so much fun! Yay!
Okay, that's enough.
That was like a dream come true for me...
...to play with everyone together,
so I'm really happy about that.
Wow, dreams really do come true...
...in this clockwork world, huh?
...I don't make the rules.
But yeah, ultimately laziness is
when you don't do anything.
Oh, you have deadlines? Eh.
Oh, oh you have really important things to do?
Procrastinate!
Oh, things are coming up in your calendar?
Eh, forget about it.
Everything's messy and it's the worst
it's ever been in your room? Eh, forget about it.
Just lay in bed and do absolutely nothing.
Yeah, I think that's really important.
And it's very, very, very important
that you learn how to do that...
...because that's one of the main emotions
of being a human.
Okay, let's see what did the poll result,
what's the poll result?
Hmm... Hmm...
Let's just not do anything.
Wow, Otomo, you're so smart!
Okay, don't do anything!
He's taking it in. Oh, cute!
Oh, that's so—
Wait. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Anyways.
So, what is the next emotion
that we need to learn?
Obviously, what is human if not...
Okay, so we have joy, lazy,
and the next one is obviously...
Hate.
So, no, come back Otomo, it's okay!
I'll tell you a little bit about
the things that I hate.
So, I hate... hmm...
Okay, okay, okay, listen. I hate coffee.
I hate raisins. I hate green peas.
I hate olives on pizza.
I hate when something stops working...
...and suddenly starts working again
when you turn it off and on again.
I hate long queues. I hate waiting.
I hate... um, when I can't sleep at night.
I hate when the pillow is too warm
and the blanket is too warm...
...but then you take off the blanket
but then it's too cold...
...and then you have to put the blanket back on.
And I hate when they make updates
for programs and websites
that are absolute downgrades!
Okay, okay.
And you know what I also hate, Otomo?
The fact that I prepared a lot of stuff
for today, but you,
and you made it so that I crashed
as I came into this world...
...and now I can't prepare it—
I mean, show it to you.
But maybe I should show you anyways.
Okay, I'll show you.
I'll show you anyways.
It's fine. I mean, this is a circular stage.
Okay Otomo, please listen.
蕐薇の誓い / Music: 光宗信吉
Bara no Chikai / Music: Mitsumune Shinkichi
Yay!
That was Bara no Chikai
from Rozen Maiden OST!
I love it, I love that OST,
it's one of my favorite OSTs.
Uh, what? What? Huh?
Oh, sorry. I just got a message. Oh.
Oh, apparently I read the poll wrong earlier
and it was actually "You decide"!
My bad, guys!
I decide what to do next!
You know what I decided?
I decided that we're gonna look at this beautiful stage!
It's so warm!
Oh my god! Well...
This looks so cool though!
Where did all the fire come from?
I guess from our rage.
So Otomo, did you learn how to be...
...I mean hate, hatred?
Did you learn how to be hateful?
Look!
He's lit! Oh!
Whoa, Otomo, whoa!
Don't say that!
No, don't listen to him, don't listen to him!
No! No! No, we're gonna get demonetized!
No, no, no, no, no!
Okay, okay, okay, just ignore him.
Okay, I've gotta talk a little bit louder
so you can't hear him cursing.
Okay, well, this is a really cool stage
and everything, but it's way too warm.
Shut up!
Okay, this is way too warm, so I think
we're gonna have to turn it back. How about that?
And since this is the inner clockwork of our
clockwork world of our minds...
I can turn it back with just a spin!
Turn it back! Whee!
Ah, it's way nicer.
Whoa, look, so pretty!
Now that's so nice.
I'm so excited!
And it's green! Everything's green,
just like Cecilia Immergreen from Justice!
Yay!
Okay, well, what do we have next?
Oh, another emotion, shall we, Otomo?
Because obviously it's four emotions because
there's four people in Justice.
So the best number in the entire world is...
Four! Four Justice!
So, Otomo, I have one song prepared for you.
And for you. I worked really hard on this one.
It's a little bit scuffed, but that's okay.
You know what? That's okay.
Please listen and watch as I perform my next song.
薔薇獄乙女
Lyrics: 宝野アリカ Music: 片倉三起也
Baragoku Otome
Lyrics: Arika Takano Music: Mikiya Katakura
豹のように美しくわたし
Beautiful as a leopard, I am
着飾るは闇の毛皮
Adorned in a fur of darkness
谷間の百合 踏みつけても
Even if I trample on the lilies of the valley
あなたの場所に向かうため
It is to reach your place
牙を立てる果実の甘さは
The sweetness of the fruit I sink my fangs into
結ばぬ実の不実の夢
Is the dream of the unbearing fruit's faithlessness
交わりましょう
Let us intertwine
生きてるのか 堕ちてるのか
Whether I'm living or falling,
わからなくなるまで
Until I can no longer tell,
わたしを視て 悶え深く
Watch me, as I writhe deeply,
溺れ乱れ満つ地獄
Drowning in this overflowing, chaotic hell.
魔女の爪を 証の骨
With a witch's claws and bones of proof,
きしりと響かせ
Letting them creak and echo,
これが愛か 憎しみなのか 答えは必要ですか
Is this love or is this hatred? Is an answer necessary?
ああ 掴み取った心臓
Ah, the heart I've snatched
あなたの凍りの檻の中
Within your cage of ice
闇の中で 生き返るわ
I will come back to life in the darkness
哀しみだけ飼いならしても
Even if I tame only sadness
装うは蝶の微笑
What I wear is a butterfly's smile
足首を解く綺麗な鎖
The beautiful chains that loosen my ankles
奈落の扉に繋がり
Are connected to the doors of the abyss
舌でなぞる鍵穴の先は
Beyond the keyhole traced with my tongue
血の味に 湿る小径
Is a small path damp with the taste of blood
進みましょうか
Shall we proceed?
抱いてるのか 抱かれるのか
Whether I'm holding you or being held
わからなくなるほど
To the point where I no longer know
薔薇獄乙女
Baragoku Otome
紅に咲いて薔薇地獄
Blooming in crimson, a rose hell
浮世の月は乱の夜
The moon of this fleeting world is a night of turmoil
欠けてはまた満ちる
Waning and then waxing again
これが恋でも 裏切りでも
Even if this is love, or betrayal
屍は同じでしょう
Our corpses will be the same
嗚呼 絶えに絶え尽くしたモノから
Ah, from things that have completely ceased to exist
その上に色を添える
I add color on top of that
逃げてるのか 追ってるのか
Are you running away, or chasing?
分からなくなるまで
Until you can no longer tell
私を見て もっと捕らえて
Look at me, capture me more
燃えて紅蓮 薔薇地獄
Burning in crimson, rose hell
生きたいのか 墜ちたいのか
Do you want to live, or to fall?
もう分からないけど
I don't know anymore, but...
これが愛で 苦しみならば
If this is love and suffering
終焉が欲しかったさ
I wanted the end
嗚呼 奪いとって その心
Ah, snatch away that heart
檻に変わりゆく わたしの
It's turning into a cage, my...
身体の中 閉じ込める
...trapped inside my body
Yeah!
What did you think, Otomos?
Oh, claps!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you!
My, that was me and my sho- ballet performance.
My, that was me and my short ballet performance.
So, Otomo, what did you learn?
This emotion... it was... obsessiveness!
Yeah!
Because when I get into new things, I get like really obsessed with them...
...and it's really a lot of fun.
Oh, what's with your facial expression?
What's... whoa!
Otomo? Otomo, are you okay?
Oh... AHH!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
No, Otomo! No!
Why are you so big?
Hey, hey, hey! Stop, stop, stop! Not again!
Hmm... he's going crazy.
Okay guys, don't worry.
I got this. I can protect you.
Because this is what we're fighting for!
This is what justice is for!
So... FOR JUSTICE!! HAAA YAH!!
Wait, wait! No, you should come with me!
Come on, let's run, let's run!
Oh, oh, you... you don't want to?
Are you so scared?
Can't come with me? It's okay.
I might not be able to help this Otomo...
...but I can sure help you!
Haya! Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Come on, let's run!
Oh no, you're limping. Come on!
Now Loading...
Again?
What the...
Where are we this time?
Ah! A stage!
Hello Otomos! Hi!
Oh my god, it's an idol stage!
So pretty!
Ah, so excited!
Oh...
（笑い声）
(Laughs)
私の車が！
My car!
うそ！　そんな！
No! No!
二人でいろんなことを乗り越えてきたのに
We've gone through so much together.
どうしてこんなことに……
How could this happen...
待って！　水鉄砲だ！
Wait! A water gun!
助けてあげるから！　助けてあげる！
I can save you! I can save you!
嫌だ、こんな終わり方させない！
No, no, I won't let it end like this!
あ、意外と簡単だった。
Oh, well that was easy.
あ、待って。　待って、何か見える。
Oh, wait. Wait, I see something.
あ！　みんな、見て！
Oh! Look, guys!
私の……私のグッズだ！
It's... it's my merch!
これが私の3D記念グッズ！
This is my 3D merch!
オートモポーチと……えっと……オートモ靴下です。
It's an Otomo pouch and... um... Otomo socks.
それで、ポーチの中に靴下を入れられるんだよ。
And then you put the socks into the pouch...
7つ買えば毎日違う靴下が履けるし、
And then you buy seven of these so you have socks
for every day of the week.
これも7つゲットすれば、一石二鳥だね！
And then you get seven of these too because
it's one... two in one!
靴下が2つだから、一石三鳥かな？
Technically I guess three in one because it's two
socks...
そう！　だからぜひチェックしてね！
Oh yeah! So please look out for these!
このコラボの後に発売される予定です。　やったー！
They're gonna be releasing after the... um...
just collab. Yeah yeah yeah!
それから、これも……これも持ってるよ！
And then I also have... um... I also have this!
私の1周年記念グッズ！
My anniversary merch!
あと3日間だけ買えるから、ぜひゲットしてね！
It's available for three more days,
so please go get it!
すごく可愛いよ。　こっちは親切なオートモで……
It's very cute. Here's a very helpful Otomo...
こっちは完全な悪、悪、悪のオートモです。
And here's a completely evil, evil, evil Otomo.
興味があったらぜひ買ってね。
So yeah, please, please get them if
you're interested.
概要欄にあると思うけど、どうかな？
Please check them out. I think... um...
maybe in the description, I'm not sure.
さて！　せっかくこの素晴らしいステージにいるんだし、
Okay! So obviously, now that we're here on
this beautiful stage...
歌を歌わないとね、そうでしょ？
We're gonna have to sing a song, shall we?
でも！　歌の後に、もう一つ重大発表があります！
But! After the song, there's one more HUGE
announcement!
だから、歌の後まで待っててね。　すごく楽しみ！
So please, uh, wait for after the song as well.
Yeah, I'm very excited!
よし！　私のオートモ軍団、準備はいい？
Okay! My army of Otomos, are you ready?
次の曲、いくよ？
Are you ready for the next song?
よし！　レッツゴー！
Okay! Let's go!
私の3Dに来てくれて本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to my 3D, everyone!
ありがとう、スター！　マネちゃん！　オートモ！
Thank you, Star! Thank you, Money-chan!
Thank you, Otomo!
Intergalactic Bound
作詞: CircusP　作曲: 雄之助, CircusP
Lyrics: CircusP Music: Yunosuke, CircusP
C'mon, I feel like there's something about this song
It's like we knew how it'd go all along
So put down your worries and raise your cups
There's nowhere to go but up
Lots of thumbs with a rhythm from New York to Japan
Know you'll never be alone
At first glance we're miles away
But our hearts are connected through these soundwaves
Nothing but up, up, up! (yeah!)
Cut through the clouds
We're never coming down
Jump! (jump!) Jump! (jump!)
Without a doubt
Nothing but up, up, up! (yeah!)
Intergalactic bound
If you're oldy or fresh on the scene
Come put your lights up, we'll make a wave of green
Bridge the beginning, was all here and now
Just take a deep breath and let me hear you shout
Let's groove with the static in the air
A breakthrough that can bring us anywhere
It's your move, so take the lead
From the crowd to the stage, what sights can we see
Nothing but up, up, up! (yeah!)
Cut through the clouds
We're never coming down
Jump! (jump!) Jump! (jump!)
Without a doubt
Nothing but up, up, up! (yeah!)
Intergalactic bound
A thousand little voices sing
It's a fiesta from now on
With our playthings always by our side
To help us make this song
Through the dark of the night, I know we will be alright
Through
Whoa-oh, whoa-oh-oh!
Intergalactic Bound! Whoa-oh!
Whoa-oh-oh! Intergalactic Bound!
Yay! That was... Intergalactic Bound! Yay!
I hope you liked that. I really like that song, so I'm really happy. Yippee!
Okay, okay. And now for the... grand announcement! Yay!
I've been working on this for a while and... yeah.
So today, maybe you've seen it already, there's a waiting room up for it.
I wrote, composed, and produced my first original song...
with the help of Ethero, who's also an amazing producer.
So please, wait a little bit longer so we redirect to it...
and then you can listen to it. Yeah!
It's called "Wind Up". So... um, yeah. Very nervous. I hope you like it.
But, um, thank you very much for coming to my 3D showcase today. It was a lot of fun.
And, um, yeah. Thank you very much to staff, Money Town, and everyone...
and all the Otomos... wait, I wanted to do one thing.
They love me. Okay.
Thank you very much. Okay, wait, let me give you a hug.
Mmm.
Okay, okay, that's enough. Back off, back off, back off. That's enough.
Okay, well. Thank you so much Otomos! Thank you everyone! Thank you for watching my 3D.
Um, maybe we should take care of the fire, huh?
Because otherwise, if we don't take care of the fire, there might be a forest fire, you know.
Also, don't forget, tomorrow is Raora's 3D! So you better watch that one as well, okay?
Otherwise, you know what's gonna happen.
Don't worry, I know exactly... I know exactly... oh, my knee.
I know exactly what to do to take care of this fire. Okay.
Pshhh. There we go. Easy, easy. Oh.
Pshhh. Oh, easy, easy. Oh.
I'm too tired for this. I'm too... stop...
oh, whatever. Goodbye.
Dearest Otomos! Thank you! Thank you for always supporting me...
for believing in me and cheering for me throughout all this time!
It's already been a year and I couldn't have asked for a better community...
than the one we've built together. You know, I'm always bad with words...
but I just want to say that I am forever grateful for how much joy you bring me.