(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-21T23:15:05.214763",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
お気に召すまま
[Title: As You Like It]
淡々 言葉を吐いた
We spat out words indifferently...
あんな思い出に泣いたのは
...and the fact that we cried over such memories...
今日で終わりにしないか
...shall we put an end to that today?
1, 2の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal,
ユーアンドミー手を取り合ったのは
the reason you and me joined hands...
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイズ 1
...was my courageous action in Phase 1.
立ち止まんないでいいんだからね
It's totally fine if you don't stop.
空々しいな この人生
How empty and hollow this life is.
できないなんて 言わないでね
Don't tell me you can't do it...
言わないでね
...don't say that.
今更なんて 言わないでね
Don't tell me it's too late now.
僕ら今さあさあ輪になって
Now, let's gather in a circle...
回り始める
...and start spinning around.
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Gradually growing to hate it, but falling in love with it anyway.
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, I just don't know, even during my inner meeting...
どんどん 中に寄って でも離れてく
...we draw closer and closer, yet drift apart.
ぱっぱっ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Moving to the beat, we start dancing.
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Hating it so much, but falling in love with it anyway.
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, I just don't know, from here on out too...
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
...keep shaking my heart! Yeah!
大正解なんてないのさ
There's no such thing as a perfect answer.
じゃあ一体どこに向かえば
So, where on earth should we head...
物語は終わりますか
...to bring this story to a close?
1, 2の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal,
ユーアンドミー手が触れ合ったのは
the reason you and me, our hands touched...
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイズ 2
...was my courageous action in Phase 2.
畏まったって 意味ないんだって
There's no point in being so formal.
恥ずかしがった 夢にバイバイです
Let's say goodbye to those embarrassing dreams.
この先ずっとよろしくね
Please treat me well from now on...
よろしくね
...okay?
君と今さあさあ交わって
Now, intersecting with you...
目を逸らし合う
...we avert our eyes from each other.
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Gradually growing to hate it, but falling in love with it anyway.
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, I just don't know, even during my inner meeting...
どんどん 様になって 崩れ落ちてく
...slowly taking shape, only to crumble down.
ぱっぱっ 触れる前に 消えてしまうの
Poof! Disappearing before we can even touch.
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Hating it so much, but falling in love with it anyway.
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, I just don't know, from here on out too...
わかりあえるまで僕たちは
...until we can fully understand each other.
今更なんて 言わないでね
Don't tell me it's too late now.
僕ら今さあさあ輪になって
Now, let's gather in a circle...
回り始める
...and start spinning around.
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Gradually growing to hate it, but falling in love with it anyway.
ねえねえ わかんないや 自分会議も
Hey, I just don't know, even during my inner meeting...
どんどん 中に寄って でも離れてく
...we draw closer and closer, yet drift apart.
ぱっぱっ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Moving to the beat, we start dancing.
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Hating it so much, but falling in love with it anyway.
ねえねえ わかんないや この先もずっと
Hey, I just don't know, from here on out too...
僕の心をシェイクシェイク いえい
...keep shaking my heart! Yeah!
Wow!
Oh my God!
Did you see us?
We're so cute!
All four of us are so cute together!
I loved the concert!
Yay!
We should do more...
This is where the money's at!
Yeah, the money's in the concert!
It was so nice to see everyone perform.
More concerts! More music!
If only there was a concert that was coming up.
Ah, if only. If only there were tickets available right now for a concert.
Yes, for a concert.
Serendipity...
I wonder where that word came from.
Wait, what if we invite even more people?
But if we invite more people, it won't be a concert anymore.
Because when there's more people, they start fighting.
You mean drama?
Drama... Drama!
Wait, that's good! If you get too many girls in a room, drama happens.
And that sells!
People love seeing girls fight.
Sometimes there's just too many girls, you know?
And yeah, and sometimes they just can't get along.
But that makes for good television.
We should film them.
Let's content farm them.
FOLLOWING UP ON THE HOLOLIVE-ENIANS
LOS ANGELES
GINA'S CONDO
Oh my God, girls. If you want to hang out with us, you have to step up your bag game.
Like, where did you even get your bag from? It looks budget.
You don't even recognize the bag I carried today?
Oh, you... next time, we're going to have to take you to, like, Bonella.
Bonella?
Yeah.
I own that company.
What? You own Bonella?
I own the sister branch of Bonella.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, what are you cooking?
Oh, it's my newest recipe. It's a zero calorie...
Oh shit!
Oh my God!
Oh my God, what the fuck?
What happened?
Are you going to pick that up?
Don't tell me what to do.
You literally threw it on the ground.
No, I didn't.
You literally did it. You can't accidentally throw something on the ground.
No, I didn't. You put it there.
I put it there?
You put your ass in my stupid kitchen, you bitch.
You absolute cunt!
I did not do that.
You literally did.
Don't always make shit up. I watched.
This always happens.
Did you see her do that?
Did you see that?
Oh yeah, I saw that, sis. I saw you throw...
I saw you throw a frying pan, Celine.
No, excuse me?
Yeah, so I was making this totally delicious zero-calorie option...
dinner for everyone because I know that everyone needs to lose a little weight for the party tomorrow.
And I just can't believe that she would do such a thing. Have you seen Celine? She's a total fucking bitch.
That food is going to be nasty, and you know it.
She's always on these, like, health trips, but it doesn't do anything for her figure.
Come here! Don't tell me what to do!
Come here! You're not my mom!
Look, look at it. You threw that on the ground.
I've never seen that in my entire life.
You've never seen that in your entire life? I've never seen that in my entire life.
You bought this for me for Christmas!
I would never get you something for Christmas.
What? You got it for me for Christmas! No, I don't know what you're talking...
You always do this!
Someone hold me back! Hold me back! Hold me back!
Hey, hey, hey! Leave her!
Leave my friend alone!
It's okay, it's okay, don't cry. You're going to ruin your mascara, girl.
Oh my god, so dramatic, so dramatic.
How dare you! She is crazy!
This is crazy! She is crazy!
Shut the fuck up! Who even are you?
I don't know why the fuck I'm here.
Who's crying?
I was just here to, like, promote my music, and, like...
all of these, you know, really rich girls here. I'm so honored to be here, honestly.
But I don't know what the fuck went on. Like, what the fuck?
I think it's the water. There's something in the water.
I don't even know why Irene was here.
Who invited her?
She's sexy.
Why are you always so dramatic?
Me, dramatic?
Why do you always make shit up?
You live for the drama!
You are fake! You are fake!
The only thing about me that's fake is my tits!
Don't talk to her like that!
You [beep]!
Yeah, her tits are fake.
I would know, I paid for them.
I was really insecure about my chest, so, you know, I got it...
Well, you know, Daddy paid... No, wait, was it Gigi?
Oh my god, I forgot about that!
I owe her. She's the best.
It's fine. Are you okay?
I'm not okay. I'm literally not okay.
Did you see what she did to me?
I saw. That was unbelievable.
Our food! I was looking forward to that.
I was on a low-calorie option!
Excuse me, like, you should stop acting like that, you know.
How old are you?
Excuse me? Don't talk to her like that.
I can talk to her any way I want.
No, you talk to me! You don't talk to her!
Oh my god, shut up!
Oh my god, Gigi always has my back, girl.
I know she'll throw down with me.
Are you getting my good side?
Make sure you get the right angle.
This is for TV, right? Yeah, check me out.
Anyway...
Cecilia is a [beep]!
I don't know what kind of problem she has with my girl Gigi, but...
...if she continues with this, we're gonna have to throw hands.
She better catch me outside, how about that, if you know what I mean.
I think she needs a wake-up call.
Bijou is such a follower. She doesn't have a single thought in that empty head of hers.
If you were to take her head and rattle it, it would sound like a baby rattle.
You guys are so loud, we're gonna get a noise complaint, and it's gonna be so embarrassing for you because...
The only noise complaint we'll get is when you're in your bedroom!
What? What does that mean? Bedroom?
You know what? Well, at least this apartment isn't under my name, so you're gonna get in trouble.
I will send you to jail! My daddy is a lawyer!
Oh, well, you know what? My daddy owns your daddy.
He might be under your daddy, but he's a lawyer! Lawyer!
I think your daddy is under my daddy in more ways than one.
Do you see what she's doing to me, Bijou?
Oh, so you have a problem with German accents?
You're so... too many... oh my god, you!
Don't touch her! Don't touch her ever again, you understand?
Oh my god, who do you think you are?
She threw herself on the ground! She did nothing!
She pushed me!
Raora threw herself on the floor, I saw it happen.
She is just... so dramatic.
That Raora is a pick-me.
Kind of a [beep].
I'd pick her though.
Have you seen her thunder thighs?
Dang, I wanna... I wanna bite that. Don't tell her though!
Cut that out! Cut that out!
Quella stronza! Ma m'ha toccato quella [beep]!
That bitch! She touched me, that [beep]!
Sempre con quella [beep]... Se mi tocca di nuovo...
Always with that [beep]... If she touches me again...
...io non ce la faccio più! Basta, ho finito.
...I can't take it anymore! That's it, I'm done.
Raora is so sweet. She always got my back.
Sometimes she falls down though, but, you know, it helps for my cause, so it's okay.
Shut up! You are the problem, and you are a danger to society!
A danger?! Excuse me?!
Watch out, watch out! Get out of the way, you're gonna ruin her outfit!
Yeah, seriously!
Stop! Stop touching each other!
This is getting a little too far, I think.
Gigi, I got you, girl. I got you.
Get up. Get up right now, you're ruining our outfit.
Anyway, guys, I'm kind of hungry. Do you want...
Oh, I'm for food! I came here for food and networking.
I was making a new low-calorie recipe because you really need to slim down.
Oh, oh! I was fighting for you!
If you were cooking, I guess everyone's going to lose their appetite.
I don't want it anymore.
I thought Gigi was trained by a Michelin chef.
I was!
No, she's just... she always makes up this shit.
Namaste, namaste, namaste...
Oh, I can expect something so nutritious.
It's really nutritious.
How dare you try to ruin our perfect five-star meal!
It was really delicious. We made a really good choice.
Five stars! You ruined Thanksgiving!
You know what? She can do whatever she wants! And you are no one...
Well, I can say whatever I... I lied.
Leave her alone, Rachel. Leave Bijou alone.
So what are we here for, anyways?
Dinner! Dinner! Dinner!
Do we get to actually eat?
Yeah, we're going to eat. That's right. We're going to eat!
We're going to eat! Oh my god!
Anyways, I want to go back to the kitchen and I'm going to finish cooking.
Yeah, where you belong!
You little...
Hold her back! Hold me back! Back off of her!
Abuse! Animal abuse! Animal abuse!
Are you okay, girl? Girl, are you okay?
Animal abuse? Animal abuse here?
Just because your dad is a lawyer, doesn't mean you can do whatever you want! Oh, the forks, not soup again.
Make me look good in the edit, okay?
Check them out!
I feel like that was too many swear words.
I think they said too... there's too many beepings in there.
Yeah, it was almost like Morse code.
They didn't even censor "fuck".
Or "shit". I just... I don't know...
Please stop. I would never swear on your channel, by the way.
Yeah, you're so sweet. That's really nice of you.
I would never fucking do that. That's so messed up of someone to do. Really fucked up.
Yeah, I just wish they would have edited that out, you know? I'm really uncomfortable right now.
I'm only five minutes old. I'm not allowed to hear those words.
I'm just really scared. It's also, I don't think we're going to make any money because it's not going to be allowed to be aired.
They'll demonetize our channel.
What if... what if we have a show, but instead of like real people, it's scripted?
Oh! And then we can make sure there's no curse words in it. We'll take them all out.
Yeah! We'll script it. It can still be drama, right?
Ooh! But just no...
No cursing, please.
Please, no cursing on our channel.
[タイトル：HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH]
[Title: Half a Fortnite Away from Death]
PREVIOUSLY ON: HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH - THE TALE OF BEAVER AND THINKER.
TWO UNLIKELY SURVIVORS FIND EACH OTHER IN THE MIDDLE OF THE APOCALYPSE, AND ALTHOUGH WARY, THEY'VE COME TO FIND COMFORT IN EACH OTHER'S PRESENCE.
HAUNTED BY THEIR PAST, AFRAID OF A FUTURE THAT MAY NEVER COME, WILL THEY EVER BE ABLE TO OVERCOME THEIR STRUGGLES AND REACH MUTUAL UNDERSTANDING IN A DYING WORLD?
FOR MORE INFORMATION, PLEASE WATCH SEASON 1 FIRST AIRED ON JULY 3, 2024.
So have you thought about it?
You just... you always say things,
but in reality, you... I love you.
No, you love your wife. She's dead now.
You don't even remember...
Even if she's dead,
that doesn't mean she's not there anymore.
And I've been thinking about it because I'm the Thinker.
What are you even? I'm the Beaver.
Oh man, if I was a beaver, I'd be eating so good right now! Because I have wood. Look at my wood! Check it out.
Oh, pretty impressive wood.
So you will want for nothing. I can provide for you.
But you... you love your wife! You don't understand!
But still, she was your wife.
The past seven days... that we've learned to survive.
You just want me for my body. You're not interested in my mind.
I want you for your mind! I want you! No, no.
No, you have to understand... You're wrong! No! No, please!
It doesn't have to be like this.
Check out my wood! Look at my wood!
No, I don't want to look at your wood! Ah! Oh! Oh, please! No!
I don't want your wood! I don't...
But you'll be so full. No, ew! Ew, put that away!
Look at my wood! Look! You don't even want me for my mind. You want...
Aaaah!
A skeleton! Run away, run away! I'll protect us!
I mean, I mean, Beaver. I'm the Beaver! I'm not Gigi, I'm Beaver! I'm the Beaver!
Beaver, be careful!
Oh my god, where'd you get that weapon? I've never seen you use that before.
Yeah, I've used... I bought it from that one pawnshop owner, remember?
Oh yeah, the guy. With the one eye. With Wawa-mi? No.
You still want me? No.
Watch out! Watch out!
That's so cool!
Oh my god, that skeleton is so cool! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, she's just... It's too strong!
It's too strong!
It's just so cool!
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
Someday the light of love you lit within your eyes
時を超えて
will transcend time,
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
and surely destroy one of the dreams
確かに一つ壊すだろう
of a world racing towards destruction.
躊躇いを飲み干して
Now that you've drunk dry your doubts,
君が望むものは何？
what do you desire?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
At the end of this path of selfish yearning,
儚い明日はあるの？
will there be a fleeting tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic
古の魔法のように
I saw in my dreams when I was young,
闇さえ砕く力で
with the power to destroy even darkness,
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to see you smiling.
怯えるこの手の中には
In these trembling hands,
手折られた花の勇気
I hold a broken flower's courage.
想いだけが頼る全て
I rely on my feelings alone.
光を呼び覚ます
A wish...
願い
...that will wake the light.
いつか君も誰かの為に
Someday perhaps you, too, will desire
強い力を望むのだろう
power for another's sake.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
On the night when love captures your chest,
未知の言葉が生まれて来る
unknown words will spring forth.
迷わずに行けるなら
If I can follow my path without wavering,
心が砕けてもいいわ
I care not if my heart shatters.
いつも目の前の哀しみに保存
To stand against the sadness
立ち向かう為の
that's ever before my eyes,
呪文が欲しい
I wish I had a spell.
君はまだ夢見る記憶保存
For you, dreams of memories,
私は眠らない明日
for me, a sleepless tomorrow,
二人が出会う奇跡を
but I'll continue to fight for
勝ち取る為に進むわ
the miracle of our meeting.
怯えるこの手の中には
In these trembling hands,
手折られた花の刃
I hold a broken flower's blade.
想いだけが生きる全て
I live for my feelings alone.
心に振りかざす
A wish...
願い
...held aloft in my heart.
囚われた太陽の輝く
Where a captive sun shines,
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
back when I loved books about wonderlands,
願いはきっと叶うと
that told me all my wishes would come true...
教えるお伽話を信じた
...I believed those fairy tales.
静かに咲き乱れていた
The quietly blossoming
古の魔法を優しく
ancient magic gently whispers to me,
世界を変える力が
'In your hands is the power
その手にあると囁く
to change the world'.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let's dream a neverending dream
君と行く時の中で
in the time I have with you.
想いだけが生きる全て保存
I live for my feelings alone.
命を創るのは
My wish...
願い
...'To create life'.
They brought them back to kill them off?
They killed a main character? Like, not... it's not a big cast!
It's literally just two characters.
I can't believe that you would have a finale of a show years ago,
and then you would do a reunion episode to kill the main character!
It's so...
Stupid!
Oh my god... Well...
These writers don't know what they're doing!
We should trash this idea. This is a terrible idea.
You know what? Not my canon. Not my canon.
This is not my show.
No, no. This is just a cash grab. I hate it!
Okay, okay...
You know what else is a cash grab?
What? What?
The Autofister merchandise!
If only we had someone here that can tell... tell us about it.
Is this... is this thing on? Okay, great.
Mina-san! Hey everyone, it's me, Mori Calliope
from Hololive English Myth, coming here to you today
to ask you to please purchase this merchandise...
...the Autofister Net merch set!
Ever wanted a Gremtomo keychain? Or a Gimimi or Cemimi?
Or better yet, an acrylic stand with Autofister on it?
Noise of enthusiasm!
Oh, wow!
For the low, low price of 99.99... [beep]
Sorry, sorry, sorry... This can be yours!
This can be yours!
And if you purchase now! Double exclamation point.
I will say this one super awesome word out loud!
Pregnant silence.
League of Legends.
Wait, okay, I see what's on there. That's three words.
I'm not saying that.
Did you check the script beforehand?
This was a bad idea, this is a freaking bad idea. I don't know why I agreed to this.
League of Legends, thank you, and buy the merchandise!
Oh wow, thanks Calli!
She loves us. She loves our merch.
Yeah!
Grow up, non-stop, try track, giga
Ready... Let's go!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
身体も魂のマスマティクス
Both body and soul mathematics
惑わされんのもっと驕って プライドがすべてじゃない
Don't be fooled, show off more, pride is not everything
凝り固まる思考を気取りで
Pretending with stiffened thoughts
高みの見物ばかりじゃつまんねえ
Just watching from a safe distance is boring
ほら もっと
Come on, more
間違って上等
Making mistakes is fine
退屈に手をかけて
Lay hands on the boredom
待てない やっぱ あたしは
I can't wait, after all, I am...
こんなところじゃ終われない
I can't end in a place like this
うるさい 気が触れそう
Shut up, feels like I'm losing my mind
ごっこ遊びも 芝居も さようなら
Goodbye to role-play and acting
ずっと このまま なんてさ
Like staying this way forever...
いらないんだよ
...is impossible
脱 脱 達しようぜ どんなになる？
Let's escape, escape, escape, what will happen?
有無も言わさぬ 感覚を分け合って今
Sharing the undeniable sensation right now
ぱっ ぱっ ぱっ 変わる時代
The changing era
悪い言葉ばかりじゃないでしょう
It's not all bad words, is it?
覚悟
Preparedness
罪も
Even sin
罰も
And punishment
すべて
Everything
超える愛で
To transcend with love
一気にやり返すわ
We'll pay them back all at once!
Yeah!
Show hands, あたしたちの番
Show hands, it's our turn
緑の合図にばっか染まってね
Get dyed in nothing but green signals
サーブ、レシーブ。つまんなくなったら漏れなく降格
Serve, receive. If it gets boring, demotion is guaranteed
悪魔に売るソウルとかだめなんですか？
Is a soul sold to the devil not allowed?
飽くなき亡者にドランク
Drunk on insatiable dead souls
薬理にコンバット
Combating pharmacology
白旗と愛
White flag and love
ちゅーだんだんBlack dog
Interrupted, black dog
中指立てたくなるような日常
Daily life that makes you want to flip the middle finger
針すぎたインプット
Overstressed input
足りないからHands up and What's up?
Because it's not enough, hands up and what's up?
最低で、待って
At the worst, wait
もつれ合おう
Let's get tangled up
Bring it on!
待ったなし 帰らない
No waiting, not going back
欲しがります 死ぬまで我等
We will keep wanting until we die
いたずらする 街に投げキッス
Blowing a kiss to the mischievous city,
見せつけてやるから ここから
I'll show them what I've got from right here.
覚悟しとけよ D.A.D.D.Y
Better prepare yourself, D.A.D.D.Y.
D.A.N.D.Y ほら大人になるカウントダウン
D.A.N.D.Y, see? Countdown to becoming an adult.
ねえ 痛い痛いな日々に
Hey, in these painful, painful days...
燦々と交わす地雷源
Brilliantly dodging the landmines,
誰も読めない先回りわかるでしょ？
Nobody can predict my next move, you know?
バグも
Even the bugs,
ロスも
the losses,
ズレも
the lags,
すべて
everything,
ツレて
take them along,
生きて
and live,
生き抜いていく強さよ
the strength to survive!
We're going on, we're doing special, let's go!
かったるい態度はとらない
No playing it cool,
言葉ばかりが揺れてる
only words are wavering.
わかるから あたしの美学
Because I know my own aesthetics,
このバイアス 正直な
this bias, honestly...
こぶし一つが
A single fist...
(If you think...)
切り札
...is my trump card!
(We can not...)
がななるラットゥー
Growling rat-tat,
一撃のKO
with a one-shot K.O.!
Oh!
Are you ready? Let's go!
Are you all ready? Everyone grab at home!
Put your hands up!
Come on!
Hey!
こんなもんじゃない
This isn't all I've got!
だってあたしよ 大人になる
Because after all, it's me who's becoming an adult!
酸いも甘いも 見分けて今
Tasting the sour and the sweet, distinguishing them now,
燦々と交わる未来を
in a brilliantly intersecting future,
追うこともないの わかるでしょ？
there's no need to chase it, you know?
期待
Anticipation,
奇奇怪怪
mysterious anomalies,
待ってくれない
they won't wait for us!
連れて行って
Take me with you,
生き抜いて
survive,
超等なタフ
with supreme toughness!
Ah...
I love it!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
それでは皆様 お先にバイバイ！
And with that, everyone, bye-bye for now!
動画 お片付けしました！
I've cleaned up the video!
Hah... Are you thinking...
...what I'm thinking?
I think I am!
Oh my god!
We have to bring this...
...write this down, write this down right now!
We've got to take it to the suits! Yeah!
Oh my god, they're going to love this.
They're going to love it.
They're going to love us.
They love us.
They love us!
This is bad.
This... is... bad...
I'm going to give up on my dreams.
Don't... never give up on your dreams.
Really?
Yeah. I feel like...
...you had half a good idea.
And you had half a good idea too.
And together...
that's a...
whole good idea.
We'll get the funding one day.
Well, thank you very much, everyone that helped us work on all these shows together!
Oh, thank you to all our beautiful, wonderful guests!
And thank you to you, grems and otomos...
...at home...
...watching us...
...today during our TV show!
Um, please sign our petition...
And look at the credits!
And don't forget there is something else...
...coming up in just a few minutes!
Very special!
Right after this, so don't change the channel!
Don't change the channel just yet! Put down that remote! Put it down!
Yes! Gun to your head, put it down right now!
Put down the remote right now! There's something really, really cool...
...coming up right after this!
Yay!
The...
...Autofister Network!