(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
How are you feeling about your upcoming performance tonight?
Amazing.
I feel amazing.
And you guys need to look forward for the upcoming performance tonight.
Yeah!
Can you say something to the viewers of our channel please?
Have fun!
And please enjoy tonight's show as well.
Thank you!
Okay, bye!
How are you feeling about your upcoming performance tonight?
とっても楽しみです。
I'm really looking forward to it.
実はこのメンバーで一緒に歌うのは初めてになると思うので、
Actually, I think this is the first time for this group to sing together,
全員で奏でるハーモニーにぜひぜひ注目してほしいです。
so I definitely want everyone to pay attention to the harmony we'll create together.
Can you say something to the viewers of our channel please?
キケルキ！キアラちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Kikeriki! Kiara-chan, happy birthday!
一緒にライブをすることができてとっても嬉しいです。
I'm so happy to be able to do a live show with you.
なので、見ているみんなも一緒に盛り上がってほしいな！
So, I want everyone watching to get excited with us too!
ということで、最高の生誕ライブにしましょう！
With that said, let's make this the best birthday live!
イエーイ！AZKiでした。
Yay! This was AZKi.
How are you feeling about your upcoming performance tonight?
I feel so excited.
You know, I feel like me and Kiara have a lot of things in common about performance.
So singing and dancing, we're... we really love to doing that.
We really love... um... performs, and also...
um... I think we have... the same taste of genre.
So singing with her and dancing with her in the same stage,
I feel really, really happy, excited and... ah! I can't wait to show you guys!
Can you say something to the viewers of our channel please?
Hello, KFP! I hope you guys enjoy... our performance.
Um... I hope you guys enjoy all the things in Kiara's anniversary.
And don't forget to always support her,
always buy her merch,
and re-loop her song!
Thank you!
Thank you! Bye-bye! Thank you!
How are you feeling about your upcoming performance tonight?
It's always a blast to be performing with Takanashi Kiara,
so I hope you'll be looking forward to it as well.
Can you say something to the viewers of our channel please?
KFP, I hope you're all ready to have the night of your lives!
Thank you!
Thank you so much for coming out today, everyone!
And don't forget to cheer extra loud for the birthday girl, Kiara!
Happy birthday, Kiara! And... for now KFP, bye-bye!
How are you feeling about your upcoming performance tonight?
クールビューティー... ですかね。
Cool beauty... I guess.
かっこよくて美しい僕たちのパフォーマンス、
Please look forward to our cool and beautiful performance!
楽しみにしててくださーい！はい！
Look forward to it! Yes!
Can you say something to the viewers of our channel please?
ハロー！キアラ・チャンネル！アイム、ロボ子。
Hello! Kiara Channel! I'm Roboco.
あー、とっても感情こめて歌って踊ったので楽しみにしててください。
Ah, I put a lot of emotion into singing and dancing, so please look forward to it.
プリーズ、エンジョイ。
Please enjoy.
プリーズ、ルック、アス。
Please look at us.
イエーイ！
Yay!
Yey!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
How are you feeling about your upcoming performance tonight?
How am I feeling about my upcoming performance tonight?
Oh...
I believe we have cooked so hard.
And yeah...
How- how much can I say?
Well, I do believe and I do sincerely hope you guys are gonna enjoy it.
Because me, I have a really good feeling about this, alright?
I'm so, so happy.
Can you say something to the viewers of our channel please?
Ah, I wonder... I wonder what...
You know, you guys... you guys need to... you guys need to keep treating Kiara right, okay?
Keep treating her right, 'cause you know, she deserves it.
And it's her party night today...
...so you guys better shower her with lots of love, okay?
We're here to celebrate as well...
...but ultimately, yeah, celebrate for her. It's her day.
Let's freaking go!
Thank you!
I... Bye-bye! Hope you guys enjoy!
きっけにきーでござる！
Kikkenikine de gozaru!
ホロックスの用心棒、侍の風真いろはでござる。
I'm the bodyguard of holoX, the samurai, Kazama Iroha.
Today's live, so I'm very nervous.
I practiced hard so that I could give a performance...
...that I would not be embarrassed to stand next to Kiara-senpai.
とても緊張しています。
I'm very nervous.
But I'm happy to be a guest performer at Kiara-senpai's wonderful live show.
So we will bring our best singing and dancing.
Please enjoy the show.
今日は楽しんでいってくださいでござる！
Please enjoy yourselves today!
How are you feeling about your upcoming performance tonight?
I'm super nervous and excited to perform with Kiara!
Our performance is going to be mind-blowing!
Can you say something to the viewers of our channel please?
Kiara's amazing, and you guys are lucky to have her as your Tencho!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Bye-ryS!
How are you feeling about your upcoming performance tonight?
Oh you know, I'm just so excited!
I invited all my friends to dance and perform with me today...
...and I practiced so hard, spilled so much sweat...
...sweaty spaghetti, you know?
But I think the result will be really exquisite... divine, perhaps?
Can you say something to the viewers of our channel please?
Oh yeah, um, of course!
Subscribe, like, leave a comment, all of that!
Make sure to share it with your friends!
Thank you!
Yay! Bye-bye!
Enjoy the show everybody! Bye!
瞬く 星の揺りかご
A cradle of twinkling stars
駆けだす台詞を 砂時計に合わせた memory
A memory of words that rush out, timed with an hourglass
聖なる 奏者が集う
The holy musicians gather
審判の言葉に 祈り耳を澄ませ
Listening closely with prayers to the words of judgment
Show me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voices
仇振る言葉 傷を焦がす
Swaying words, scorching the wounds
焔降り注ぐ空に 身を焼き尽くして
Scorching my body in the sky where flames pour down
乱れ咲く 赤い花弁 継承を
Inheriting the blooming red petals
幾多重なる試練も 生き抜いてみせる
I will survive the many overlapping trials
I will never give up fighting until the dawn
半分
Half
Don't break I will never give up
Don't break 願わくしてもう
Don't break, even if I overcome my wishes
消せない強さだ
It's a strength that cannot be erased
時のシルエット
The silhouette of time
舞い上がる大地に
On the earth that soars
目を伏せ
Cast your eyes down
燃ゆる夜明けの中で
In the burning dawn
目覚ます
Awaken
刃交わし吐息が
The sigh of crossing blades
交わした契りは
The vow we exchanged
Eyes on you, neon lights at the break of day
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me away
If I go on what awaits me in the dark
Could you tell me please where I need to go
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, in the voiceless voice
みなぎる決意は
The determination that overflows
影をはがす
Tears away the shadows
焔降り注ぐ空に
In the sky where flames pour down
身をやつして
Exhausting myself
乱れた火花は
The disturbed sparks
紅化粧
Red makeup
天降る死でも
Even death from heaven
生き抜いてみせる
I will survive
Blazing flames show me the path to luminous
And in the next life, I promise I will find you
Kikiriki! Yeah!
We're so back! Welcome to my 4th year anniversary 3D live! Yay!
That was HINOTORI REDSHIFT Remix.
The first time I ever performed this version of it.
Did you like the comeback of the Kikiriki? Kyah!
Well, well, well...
Let me take you through the stage a little bit.
This is our new stage. It looks so luxurious and beautiful.
Wow, so shiny, I know.
Well, we also have a very, or I have a very special surprise
for you guys at the end of this live.
The last song... hmm, what could it be?
It will still stay a surprise, but please still stay until the very end.
And we have many guests too, that you may already have seen or heard about.
So look forward to them!
Yeah! The next song will be a cover song from KIRA,
my song even though, you know, similar vibe to my original songs.
So please enjoy, NICE TYPE!
NICE TYPE
Lyrics: Asteroid Music Team (monii, KIRA)
Music: Asteroid Music Team (KIRA, monii, Johnny R)
It's getting dark, better watch your back
Better pay attention now
A demon on the loose, I'm c-c-cowering for you now
Watching and teasing, make it so easy
To set you at ease, listen
But baby, why don't you give in?
Feeling, you want it, I need it, go get it
Dreaming, believe it, take control
You're just so easy, I'm stuck, I'm greedy
Satisfy the hunger, got you lo-lo-locked down
Still begging for more, sinister allure
Look what you got yourself into after all
Watch it escalate, no more rotate
Voyeur, boy, try if you want
I'll let you come inside my mind
Hold it down and let's go all night
Oh you look so nervous, what's wrong?
Don't be polite
Got you on your knees
I never claimed to be the nice type
I'm touching now, innocent to you
You're looking for the helper, ain't no use
Boy, you should have known
Once I'm done, I'm moving on
One look into my eyes and you're gonna fall
You're mine forever but I ain't yours, no
It only takes a minute to get you all addicted
Can never get enough, no no no
Still begging for more, sinister allure
Look what you got yourself into after all
Watch it escalate, no more...
Try if you want, I'll let you come inside my mind
Call it down, and let's go all night
Oh you look so nervous, what's wrong? Don't be polite
Got you on your knees, I never claimed to be the nice type
I'm not the nice type, nah
Got you like that, oh
Never claimed to be the nice type
I miss you
Didn't want to admit it if I do
Always been close but far away
You go but then you stay
It's always been you
I guess we are different after all
But it's shocking how far apart we grew
So I cut all the ties to play it safe
But you like playing games
It's always been you
And somehow you're still here
This feeling could kill me
Somehow you're still here
And this might take me out, take me down, take me apart
Oh I got it bad, got attached,
my imagination brings me right back to you
Always wanted all, when I fall, I fall hard
Oh baby tell me why, tell me why, tell me why does a heart break
A heart break, a heart...
Tell me why does a heart break, a heart break
Oh baby tell me why, tell me why
It's kind of painful, to tell the truth
I should cry it out, but I don't usually do
Some things don't change though, I'd make them if I could
Cause I don't feel human, I wonder if you would
And it's not even fair, that you're happy with her
And you're so unaware, maybe that's why it hurts
The world stops and the clock keeps ticking, oh no...
Oh I got it bad, got attached,
my imagination brings me right back to you
Always wanted all, when I fall, I fall hard
Oh baby tell me why, tell me why, tell me why does a heart break
Why won't you let me go
I really want to be alone
Right now, delete my number from your phone
I want to be alone
But somehow you're still here
Oh yeah, somehow you're still here, ah-ah-ah
And this might take me out, take me down, take me apart
Oh I got it bad, got attached,
my imagination brings me right back to you
Always wanted all, when I fall, I fall hard
Oh baby tell me why, tell me why, tell me why does a heart break
Oh I got it bad, got attached,
my imagination brings me right back to you
Always wanted all, when I fall, I fall hard
Oh baby tell me why, tell me why, tell me why does a heart break
A heart break, a heart...
Tell me why does a heart break, a heart break
Oh baby tell me why, tell me why
Hoo-hoo-hoo...
Yay!
We can't wait to talk!
I know, right?
Yay!
IRyS! IRyS! IRyS!
Thank you so much for inviting me!
Of course! It's such a rare duo!
I know, right? We had to do it!
I think this is the first time...
Yeah!
That we sang and danced together, like just the two of us!
Did you like it?
Did you guys like it?
Thank you!
Introduce yourself then.
Hi-RyS, it's IRyS from Hololive English Promise.
Yeah.
I and I am just so, so happy.
Me too!
I think I've been in Hololive for like over three years...
...and I just can't believe this is our first time.
Yeah!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yeah, no, I know. It's very special, so...
Yeah, and it was a really special song, too, right?
Yeah, "Why Does the Heartbreak", right?
Yeah, why does the heartbreak, IRyS?
Tell me.
I mean, technically I've never been heartbroken ever in my life.
Oh really?
What about me?
Well, I mean, I might have broken her heart...
...but I've never been broken.
Oh really?
Well, I mean, honestly, when we were doing this dance move...
...this one...
...I was like... (sniffs)
Oh?
I smelled Bae on you!
Liar!
No!
What are you...? Liar!
No, no!
I was alone last night. What you talkin' about?
She's lying, she's lying!
She's a fat liar!
Maybe it was the night before?
Or before?
No, no, no! If you see... I wash my hair every day!
Ah...
It's more like your whole body exudes...
Okay...
Well...
Well, let me let me take a sniff at your hair.
You know.
(Sniffing sound)
Hmm, smells nice.
It smells a little bit like a nice-smelling crow.
Oh, crow?
Maybe like Kronii? No, no, no, Kronii's not a crow.
No, I'm thinking of someone like the Nerizzler.
Nerizzler!
Nerizzler! Well, I mean, okay, honestly, that could be.
Because...
...me and Nerissa, I thought we had, you know, something.
Because she...
I felt like she chose me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You do have something.
Thank you.
But I got a little bit confused because a while ago at the New Year concert...
...she was kissed.
Okay, she didn't kiss her, she was kissed by Shiori.
Uh-huh.
So now I'm really confused because I know she loves Shiori...
...and I'm like, where do I stand with her? I'm so confused.
I mean...
...no, you guys just take your relationship...
...especially when it comes to kissing and stuff, more personal, not in public.
I'm assuming, right?
I don't really know about that.
Did you guys like... did you guys like take a shower together?
No, no!
Huh?
Well, okay, we were in swimsuits.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Anyway, I think I'll clear it up with her...
...because the song after this... Hmm, I think I sense her presence.
Oh?
Yeah, maybe you should talk to her a bit if you're worried.
You know, she's the Nerizzler though, so you know...
...I'm sure she's gone on a like couple dates.
Ah!
No, no, not a couple dates. It's just a group of friends.
What you talking about?
It's just a group of friends.
Well then...
...are you guys ready for the next song?
I am so excited to see that!
Thank you!
Alright, you watch on the sidelines.
Yes.
See you guys!
Next song!
Wee!
GETCHA!
いくつもの九分九厘　主義愛の範疇
Quite a few 99%, within the domain of ideologic love
独りじゃんけん
Rock-paper-scissors all alone
運命と縛り　見ないふり　それも案低
Binding with fate, pretending like everyone else, that's also quite low
Now I know all about you, baby.
I don't want the handbags, the money, or the diamond rings
'Cause guys like you, they all don't care about the little things
まぁ　Anyway　忘れちゃって
Well, anyway, just forget about it
デッドボディ　上がって掘り出したって圏外で
Even if the dead body is dug up, it's out of range
I'm moving on and I'm never ever turning back around
Around, around again now
I'll go higher
And I'll go higher
And you couldn't take me down if you tried
バラまいてた愛取り返して大体だ
Taking back the love I scattered, that's about right
Now I can finally open my eyes
そんで来世も解除　君への返済
And then, cancel the next life too, repayment to you
Get out of my life, boy, I'll getcha, getcha, getcha
放置っぱなしの恋なんで
Since it's a love left abandoned
情弱　駆け引き　捨て去って
Discarding information weakness and tactics
'Cause I'm fine, I'm alright　君なんて大正解
'Cause I'm fine, I'm alright, you are the right answer
Get out of my life, boy, I'll getcha, getcha, getcha
Get out of my life, boy (I'll getcha, getcha, getcha)
Oops, deleted your number
All of my friends used to warn me about you, baby
Thought that I couldn't without you
I got myself, no, I don't need no other
吐息も止まるトキメキさなうなう今
A heartbeat-stopping excitement, right now now
颯爽ステップ　愛嬌振り撒いて　なら　ななな
Dashing step, scattering charms, then na na na
I don't want the handbags, the money, or the diamond rings
'Cause guys like you, they all don't care about the little things
そう、Everyday　蓄えは順調で
Yes, everyday, the savings are going well
撤底打ち勝つ証拠さ　だってバイバイ
Evidence of complete victory, because bye-bye
I'm moving on and I'm never ever turning back around
Around, around again now
I'll go higher
And I'll go higher
And you couldn't take me down if you tried
バラまいてた愛取り返して大体だ
Taking back the love I scattered, that's about right
Now I can finally open my eyes.
今までいない 混じり合った周回
GETCHA MY LIFE BOY I GETCHA GETCHA GETCHA
Never before, a mixed circulation,
Getcha my life boy, I Getcha getcha getcha.
All the lies and every mistake,
all the goodbyes and the heartbreaks.
君がいない世界さえも 望む
I even desire a world without you.
Break!
K-I-G-A and K-I-L-A
You ready?
Getcha out my life boy, Getcha out my life boy
Let's go!
Getcha out my life boy, I GETCHA GETCHA GETCHA
困ってたギザアイディ 没落した価値本意
Troubled Giza ID, ruined value priority,
全勝な生活レンズに流されてく スライダー Out the way
flowing through the lens of a winning life,
slider out the way.
Woo!
もっと愛が溶けてくアイスは 元だけは泡が抜けた
The more love melts, the ice,
only the bottom lost its fizz.
空殻振ってなフレッシュなってなフレッシュ
GETCHA GETCHA GETCHA
Shake the empty shell, be fresh, be fresh,
Getcha getcha getcha.
GETCHA MY 絶対 取り返して 絶体絶命
Getcha my absolute, take it back,
a desperate situation.
Now I can finally open my eyes.
澄んでない全肯定 君への返信さ
Not clear full affirmation, it's my reply to you.
GETCHA OUT MY LIFE BOY I GETCHA GETCHA GETCHA
待ち放しの恋なんで
Because it's a love left waiting,
重過激傷口塞いでさあて
closing the heavy extreme wounds, now then.
今までいない 混じり合った周回
Never before, a mixed circulation.
GETCHA OUT MY LIFE BOY I GETCHA GETCHA GETCHA
Cause I'm finally alright 君がして大正解
Cause I'm finally alright, your choice was the big success.
GETCHA OUT MY LIFE BOY I GETCHA GETCHA GETCHA
気付いたんだ今は Rolling
I've realized, right now I'm Rolling.
止まりたくないんだのみ
I only don't want to stop.
Beat Eater
Lyrics, Music: ポリスピカデリー
Lyrics, Music: Police Piccadilly
分かってんだ 見せられたって
I know, even if I'm shown.
雑の罠に嵌まるつもりなっとんない
I have no intention of falling into a sloppy trap.
当たり前が止まんない 怖いな
The obvious won't stop, it's scary.
もどかしさも正味だい
The frustration is also real.
HELLO 湧いてくる 束の間のジプシン
Hello, a fleeting gypsophila that wells up.
そこからはどう見えてる？ Tell me, jumping
How does it look from there? Tell me, jumping.
どれだけ僕を弄ってくれるの？
How much will you mess with me?
干渉して 心を加速して
Interfere, accelerate my heart.
始まりはどこから？
Where does it start?
それも容赦ないから
Because that's also relentless.
体を支配している 満ち足りた様
The satisfied appearance that dominates the body.
ダーリンダーリン 貪って NEXT TIME
Darling, darling, devour it, next time.
マニーマニー 化けるのさ
Money, money, I'll transform.
何がどうなったって不思議じゃない
No matter what happens, it's not a mystery.
振りを増し 糊塗になって 響き出す
Increasing the pretense, becoming a cover-up,
it starts to resonate.
COME OVER 消えて 噛み噛み
Come over, disappear, biting biting.
あくまで踊っていたいだけ
I just want to dance to the end.
気付いたんだ今は Rolling
I've realized, right now I'm Rolling.
止まりたくないんだのみ
I only don't want to stop.
ヤバい 何となくのみ
Oh no, just somehow.
魅了されてるのみ
I'm just fascinated.
予想より不便で長い航路
A route longer and more inconvenient than expected.
不確かなものに囲まれてんだあれ
Look, I'm surrounded by uncertain things.
そこら中に転がってる堕落
Corruption rolling around everywhere.
妄想だって思いのほか重要
Delusions are more important than one might think.
心に差か 放れた振る舞い
Behavior detached from the heart.
早まったのさ引くに引けないよそう
It was premature,
an expectation I can't back out of.
こんな手に入れて妥協を打ち込め
Getting this in hand, hammer in the compromise.
姿を映して危なかった盤
The disc that was dangerous, reflecting the figure.
アイアイアイ 道は分かれたんだ
Ai ai ai, the paths have diverged.
アイアイアイ それも遠くから
Ai ai ai, even that from afar.
アイアイアイ 全て間違いじゃない
Ai ai ai, everything is not a mistake.
アイアイアイ 哀しみに込めた
Ai ai ai, infused with sadness.
ダーリンダーリン 万更でもない
Darling, darling, not all that bad.
マニーマニー 塗り直すのさ
Money, money, I'll repaint it.
今になればいつだって構わない
By now, I don't care when it is.
色を買い 糊塗になって 溢れ出す
Buying colors, becoming a cover-up, it overflows.
COME OVER 消えて 噛み噛み
Come over, disappear, biting biting.
まだまだ足りてないみたい
It seems it's still not enough.
重なり合う 光だ 耳寄り側
Overlapping light, on the edge of a tip.
どこにも消えないでほしい
I want it to never disappear.
留まる濃い 深い重心だより
Staying dense, relying on a deep center of gravity.
傷付くことも有る
There are also times when things get hurt.
ダーリンダーリン 貪って NEXT TIME
Darling, darling, devour it, next time.
マニーマニー 退屈なのさ
Money, money, it's just boring.
何がどうなったって不思議じゃない
No matter what happens, it's not a mystery.
振りを増し 糊塗になって 響き出す
Increasing the pretense, becoming a cover-up,
it starts to resonate.
COME OVER 消えて 噛み噛み
Come over, disappear, biting biting.
世界は完　完
The world is...
あくまで踊ってたいだけ
I just want to keep dancing
Give it up だ 今は lonely
Give it up, now I'm lonely
止まりたくないのに
Even though I don't want to stop
ヤバい なんとなくなのに
It's dangerous, even though it's somehow...
見透かされてんのに
Even though I'm being seen through
Hey!
Wooo! Yatta! Dekimashita! "Beat Eater"!
Wooo! We did it! We performed "Beat Eater"!
Yeah!
Iroha-chan, welcome!
Introduction, please!
Hello! My name is Iroha Kazama.
Japanese Hololive 6th generation HoloX.
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
Welcome! Yatta! Iroha-chan!
Welcome! We did it! Iroha-chan!
We sang Beat Eater together.
I'm so happy because I really, really love this song.
And when I chose it, I thought I need someone who can dance really well,
which is Iroha-chan.
But then after I already chose you, I realized when I was looking up "Beat Eater" on YouTube...
I found your cover! I was like, eh? She sang this already?!
もうカバーしてる！
You've already covered it!
Yes, そうです！　だから今回誘ってもらえて...
Yes, that's right! So being invited this time...
...とってもとっても嬉しくて。"Beat Eater" so very, very pop and cool song.
...I'm very, very happy. "Beat Eater" is such a pop and cool song.
I love it! So thank you today!
Yes, thank you!
ありがとう！ Live guest, thank you ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Live guest, thank you, thank you very much!
Well, it was a very like dance-focused song, so I wonder what dance move was difficult for you?
やっぱり、サビ。
As expected, the chorus.
サビ？
The chorus?
Tu-tu-tu-tu-tu... そこ！
Tu-tu-tu-tu-tu... There!
Beat Eater...
So waving, so very, very difficult.
Actually I also just like today I finally understood.
今日やっと把握できたと思う。
I think I finally got the hang of it today.
で、rehearsal together, lesson... mm?
And we rehearsed together, had lessons... mm?
Hm? This way? Hm?
Yeah, ってことでやりましたもんね。
Yeah, so we did it together.
For me, there's like, you know when I overthink?
Overthinking, then I like forget how to do the simplest things...
...even though I know that I know it.
So there was this one move... you like step forward...
...and when you step, you like kick the other leg back, right?
And then you put it to the front and we add the hand, right?
So it's like this, but I overthink and I like stumble over my legs...
Step, kick, wave, more, more resource...
So I had to do it a hundred times so that I stop overthinking.
Oh my god! But Kiara-senpai practicing so hard!
Iroha-chan too!
So together, practice together very fun! Yes!
So together, practicing together was very fun! Yes!
ありがとうございました！　楽しかった！
Thank you very much! It was fun!
本当に楽しかった！　ありがとうございました！
It was really fun! Thank you very much!
Let's do it again sometime.
Yes! So singing and dancing, so together, yes!
Also Iroha-chan, very nice English!
No, no, zako zako English! No nice English!
No, no, pathetic English! Not nice English!
マジ助かる、助かる。
It really helps, it helps.
More English practice hard, 頑張ります！
I'll practice English harder and do my best!
Okay! So with that we move on to the next song...
...and the next guest! Who could it be?
Bye-bye guys! See you next song! Bye-bye next guest! Yeah!
い〜やい〜やい〜や
Ya ya ya ya
(Whatever, whatever, whatever)
Lyrics, Music: Neru & z'5
Whatever, whatever, whatever
い〜やい〜やい〜や
くたばってる頭脳　ぽしゃった
My brain is exhausted and failed
この怠惰が憎いな
I hate this laziness
またこうしてベッドで　また寝腐っている
Lying in bed and rotting away again like this
ここ最近　調子悪いな
I've been out of sorts lately
いや　本気はまたまた
No, I'm still not serious
そう言ったのはこれで何度目のセリフだろう
I wonder how many times I've said that phrase by now
無造作な部屋　一人の両目
A messy room, one pair of eyes
隠れ際　机の下で
Hiding under the table
午前二時もせぬ　身なりは三流
Not even 2 AM, my appearance is low-class
お涙はどうぞ頂戴
Please give me some tears
僕らどうせ聖者じゃないさ
We're not saints anyway
だから終止でいいや
So a full stop is fine
ノー・サンキューさ　い〜やい〜やい〜や
No thank you, whatever, whatever, whatever
クリンゼ　一生ナンセンスだっていいや
A whole life of nonsense is fine
ノー・サンキューさ　い〜やい〜やい〜や
No thank you, whatever, whatever, whatever
最低で結構　堂々食っていいや
Lowest is fine, it's okay to be unashamedly proud
よ、センチメンタル相まって
Mixed with sentimentality
一年中のボケ数も
And year-round foolishness
140文字のポエムに放っている
Unleashing it in a 140-character poem
これ外にパッと決まったなら
If this was suddenly decided outside...
いーないーな　もっと当然
It's fine, it's fine, it's only natural
逃げ足だけが　特得の芸
My only skill is running away
エッサホイサ　待つの身
Heave-ho, heave-ho, I'm just waiting
口だけで　ちゃちゃ
Just talk, talk, talk
獲物には　速攻　ダイブ　そう
Diving headfirst for the prey, yeah
嘘も　方便　だって　言うさ
They say lies are sometimes necessary
だから　同情　なんて　いや
So I don't want any sympathy
ノー天気スタイル　いーや　いーや　いーや
Carefree style, whatever, whatever, whatever
ご臨終　一生　ポンコツ　だって　いーや
I'm a failure for life, and I don't care
ノー天気スタイル　いーや　いーや　いーや
Carefree style, whatever, whatever, whatever
最低で　結構　ハッピー　だって　いーや
I'm at rock bottom, but I'm happy, so whatever
ハラ減ったら　ヤル気が失せた
When I'm hungry, I lose all motivation
また　スマホ　いじった
And start messing with my phone again
ただ　こうして　ベッドで　死んだフリを　してる
Just lying in bed like this, pretending to be dead
言葉たら　絵空　口だ
Empty words and pipedreams
なら　どうして　そうしない？
Then why don't you do it?
そりゃ　ボッチで　デブっちの　ヘタレ　だから　だろう
Because I'm a lonely, chubby coward, that's why
また　妄想の　エッチが　バズった
Another dirty delusion went viral
まあ正直　テラった
To be honest, it was amazing
ただ　こうして　ベッドで　僕は　腐っている
Just rotting away in bed like this
ここ最近　調子は悪いが
I haven't been doing well lately
いや本気は　まだまだ
But I haven't even gotten serious yet
もー　どうにでも　なってくれ　お釈迦様
Oh, just let whatever happen, Lord Buddha
ノー天気スタイル　いーや　いーや　いーや
Carefree style, whatever, whatever, whatever
ご臨終　一生　プライド　だって　いーや
Dead for life, I don't care about pride
ノー天気スタイル　いーや　いーや　いーや
Carefree style, whatever, whatever, whatever
最低で　結構　ノーナシ　だって　いーや
I'm the worst, and I'm incompetent, so whatever
ノー天気スタイル！
Carefree style!
明日も　頑張って　と　いーな
I hope I can do my best tomorrow too
ノー天気スタイル！
Carefree style!
だから　今日　まくら　だって　いーや
So for today, even a pillow is fine
(Coughing) Good morning!
We're on stage!
Five more minutes...
Why did we fall asleep?
Oh, such a chill song, though.
How are you? Hello!
Maybe you should introduce yourself?
Myself? Oh, hi!
I'm Ninomae Ina'nis from Hololive English Myth. Hello!
Yeah, okay, I know it's comfortable on the floor. You love the floor.
Five more minutes.
Special floor, right? Floor rating?
The floor... A solid 8.37.
Oh, that's pretty good!
But we gotta leave the floor now.
Yeah.
Guys, it's been so long since we released this as a song cover!
And now we finally, upon popular demand...
Performed it!
Yeah! How long has it been? Like, three years?
Three years. Unbelievable.
Yeah. Have you guys listened to it before? Or are you a newcomer and you never heard it before?
In that case, what should they do, Ina?
Listen to it.
Listen to it! Yeah, it's like pretty far down.
So you gotta go to the videos and to "Most Popular", because it's really popular!
Yeah! Thank you Takotori!
Yeah, Takotori!
Thank you for giving us love.
And thanks for inviting me!
Oh, of course Ina! It's so fun with you!
Oh yeah, we had that, you know, this special dance...
Yeah, speaking of fun, we have this... guys, dance with us!
(Humming)
We're like robots.
No-tenki style.
Yeah, robots, kind of.
But it's like, ah, whatever, whatever, whatever.
Yeah, that's fine.
So, actually, this stage is like pretty like epic and godlike, isn't it?
Oh, I feel like a goddess!
So far the songs haven't quite fit the theme...
...but now in the second part of this, there's gonna be more guests, more songs...
...and they're all gonna fit the vibe more. They're gonna be godlike and epic! Yes!
Godlike. Epic. Yes.
So I'm kind of nervous!
Eh, you can't wait? Well, can you give me some kind of motivation call, please, Ina?
Iya, iya, iya...
(Laughs) Oh, come on! Not "whatever, whatever"!
Okay, okay. Well, just this time, okay?
Okay, okay.
You're gonna join me on the "Oh!", everyone will join me on the "Oh!", okay?
On the "Oh!"? Okay, sounds good.
Here we go.
Takanashi Kiara! Fight!
Oh!
Fight!
Fight! Oh!
Never heard that before. Okay, okay!
Thank you! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Next song!
STYX HELIX
Lyrics, Music: MYTH & ROID
Oh, please don't let me die
waiting for your touch
No, don't give up on life,
this endless dead end
言葉を吐き出す 命零れ落ちてゆくほどに
Words are spat out, as life spills over
盗まれた 芽生えた想いまでも
Even the stolen, sprouting feelings
こんなにあっけなく
So easily
消えてしまうの
They disappear
I wish I was there
Oh, please don't let me die
waiting for your touch
二度と何も失くさないように
So that I won't lose anything again
私を忘れて
Forget about me
始めて Restart
And begin, Restart
No, don't give up on life,
this endless dead end
君を砕くこの悲しみが
May this sadness that breaks you
いつか終わりますように
One day come to an end
For now, adieu
My time is spinning around
Your deep black eyes
I forgot what time it is
And our memories are gone
甘い香り放つ 追憶という名の誘惑
A sweet fragrance emitting, temptation of memories
囚われ 飛ばされて 逃れられず また
Captured, blown away, unable to escape, again
溺れてしまうの
I end up drowning
I wish you were here
Oh, never close your eyes
searching for true fate
何処か消えた あの温もりを
The warmth that disappeared somewhere
追いかけ続けて
Continuing to chase it
見失う Restart
I lose sight, Restart
So, let us try again
from the very first time
きっと きっと そうやって 今も
Surely, surely, even now
虚しい輪を描いている
Drawing an empty circle
For now, adieu again
Fading in
Fading out
I wish you were here
あの日には戻れない
I cannot return to that day
時は強く
Time is strong,
悲しく強く
sadly strong
ただただ進んでゆくだけ
Just moving forward
Restart
No, don't give up on life,
this endless dead end
振り返らない そんな強さを
The strength to not look back
誰も皆 持ってる
Everyone has it,
知ってる
everyone knows it
For now, adieu
And we'll start waiting for a new day
二度と...
Never again...
And we'll start waiting for a new day
君と...
With you...
Oh, please don't let me die
消えないで
Don't disappear
Magia
Lyrics, Music: 梶浦由記
Lyrics, Music: Yuki Kajiura
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
Someday the light of love you'll ignite in your eyes
時を越えて
Will cross through time
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
And surely break one dream
確かに一つ壊すだろう
Of this world racing toward destruction
ためらいを飲み干して
Swallowing down your hesitation
君が望むものは何？
What is it that you desire?
こんな欲深い憧れの
Does a fleeting tomorrow exist
行方に儚い明日はあるの？
In the destination of such greedy yearnings?
子供の頃の夢に見ていた
Like the ancient magic
古の魔法のように
I used to see in my childhood dreams
闇さえ砕く力で
With a power that can crush even the darkness
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to see you smiling
怯えるこの手の中には
Within these trembling hands
手折られた花の勇気
Is the courage of a plucked flower
想いだけが頼る全て
My feelings are all I can rely on
光を呼び覚ます願い
A wish to awaken the light
いつか君も誰かのために
Someday you, too, for someone's sake
強い力を望むだろう
Will surely desire a strong power
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
On the night when love captures your heart
未知の言葉が生まれて来る
Unknown words will be born
迷わず行けるのなら
If I can go on without hesitation
心が砕けてもいい
I don't mind if my heart is shattered
いつも目の前の悲しみに
I always want a spell
立ち向かうための呪文が欲しい
To confront the sadness before my eyes
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are still a dreaming memory
私は眠らない明日
I am a tomorrow that doesn't sleep
二人が出会う奇跡を
As we move forward
勝ち取るために進むわ
To win the miracle of our meeting
怯えるこの手の中には
Within these trembling hands
手折られた花の刃
Is the blade of a plucked flower
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings are all that live
心に振りかざす願い
A wish I brandish in my heart
囚われた太陽の輝く
Where the trapped sun shines
（ハ・ヤ・イ・ヨ...）
(Ha-ya-i-yo...)
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
Back when I loved books about Wonderland
（ハ・ヤ・イ・ヨ...）
(Ha-ya-i-yo...)
願いはきっと叶うと教える
I believed in fairy tales
お伽話を信じた
That told me wishes will surely come true
静かに咲き乱れていた
The ancient magic was blooming silently
古の魔法優しく
Gently
世界を変える力が
Whispering that the power
その手にあると囁く
To change the world is in those hands
終わらない夢を見よう
Let's dream an endless dream
君と行く時のなかで
As I go through time with you
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings are all that live
命を作るのは願い
It's my wish that creates life
Blumenkranz
Lyrics: Rie Music: 澤野弘之
Lyrics: Rie Music: Hiroyuki Sawano
Ich möchte stärker werden
I want to become stronger
weil unsere Welt sehr grausam ist
because our world is very cruel
Es ist ratsam
It is advisable
welke Blumen zu entfernen
to remove withered flowers
Du fragst mich, ob ich mit dir komm'
You ask me if I'll come with you
Du flüsterst mir in mein Ohr
You whisper into my ear
Du fragst mich, ob ich deine Hand nehm'
You ask me if I'll take your hand
Ich hab' keinen Grund, dich abzulehnen
I have no reason to reject you
Du fragst mich, ob ich mit dir komm'
You ask me if I'll come with you
Du flüsterst mir in mein Ohr
You whisper into my ear
Du fragst mich, ob ich deine Hand nehm'
You ask me if I'll take your hand
Du flüsterst mir...
You whisper to me...
Ja, ich bin viel stärker
Yes, I am much stronger
als ich je gedacht hab'
than I ever thought
Fliege höher, laufe viel schneller
Fly higher, run much faster
Vergiss die Wahrheit nicht
Don't forget the truth
Ja, ich bin viel stärker
Yes, I am much stronger
als ich je gedacht hab'
than I ever thought
Ich entferne welke Blumen
I remove withered flowers
Wieso siehst du so traurig aus?
Why do you look so sad?
Diese Welt ist grausam
This world is cruel
es ist traurig, aber wahr
it's sad but true
diese Welt ist seltsam
this world is strange
es ist tragisch, aber wahr
it's tragic but true
Diese Welt ist ein Blumengarten
This world is a flower garden
echt oder falsch?
real or fake?
diese Welt ist seltsam
this world is strange
es ist tragisch, aber wahr
it's tragic but true
Ich möchte stärker werden
I want to become stronger
weil unsere Welt sehr grausam ist
because our world is very cruel
Es ist ratsam
It is advisable
welke Blumen zu entfernen
to remove withered flowers
Ja, ich bin viel stärker
Yes, I am much stronger
als ich je gedacht hab'
than I ever thought
Fliege höher, laufe viel schneller
Fly higher, run much faster
Vergiss die Wahrheit nicht
Don't forget the truth
Ja, ich bin viel stärker
Yes, I am much stronger
als ich je gedacht hab'
than I ever thought
Ich entferne welke Blumen
I remove withered flowers
Wieso siehst du so traurig aus?
Why do you look so sad?
Was willst du von mir?
What do you want from me?
Ich mag wollen oder nicht
Whether I want to or not
ich muss dem Pfad folgen
I must follow the path
ich bin nicht frei von dieser Welt
I am not free from this world
Was willst du von mir?
What do you want from me?
Ich mag wollen oder nicht
Whether I want to or not
ich muss dem Pfad folgen
I must follow the path
ich bin nicht frei von dieser Welt
I am not free from this world
Egal wie hart du auch bist
No matter how hard you are
fliege höher, laufe viel schneller
fly higher, run much faster
vergiss die Wahrheit nicht
don't forget the truth
Ja, ich bin viel stärker
Yes, I am much stronger
als ich je gedacht hab'
than I ever thought
du bindest einen Blumenkranz
you're binding a flower wreath
wieso siehst du so traurig aus?
why do you look so sad?
YAY!
Whoa!
Was that epic or what?
Blumenkranz, I think, is a song that many people wanted me to do for a long time.
And I finally did it!
Whoa!
German song on my live! What?!
Who would believe it?
But this vibe was, I think, really epic and amazing.
Thanks for singing with me, everybody, by the way!
Yeah...
But I have to kind of ruin the vibe now,
because I'm going to advertise to you my merchandise!
It...
I've been here for over four years now,
and I know my anniversary was a few weeks ago,
but this got delayed, as you know,
we're a little bit past anniversary now.
But I haven't shown you my solo anniversary merchandise yet!
So, here we go, it is time!
Ta-da!
4th Anniversary Celebration
Oh, what is this?
Yes, my merchandise is once again kind of kitchen-themed.
Now let's start with number one, the plate! Ta-da!
KFP Plate
Isn't it nice? This is like the main illustration...
...with, you know, a little cute new outfit.
It's like kind of like an apron or like waitress outfit.
I really like it, it's so cute!
And you can eat all kinds of stuff on it.
You can eat pasta or you can eat a burger or some fries or a steak! Yes!
Or maybe some fried eggs. But if you're not really...
...a fried egg kind of person...
...we would go to next...
KFP Egg Cup
...the egg cup! Yes, we have an egg cup!
Where you put in your favorite boiled egg.
How many minutes, guys? One, two? What's your favorite like...?
I don't know how to say it.
Well, I like it like maybe six, seven minutes. Mmm.
But of course, just like that, that's not enough.
We need some salt, and maybe even some pepper.
Do you put pepper on it? I don't.
But for that, I got you covered.
KFP Enhancement Spice Container (Set of 2)
We have salt and pepper shakers! Oh, what's so cute!
They are in the shape of an egg...
...but they're wearing the uniform!
What, the egg gets to wear the uniform? That's new.
But yeah, it's really cute.
It's your choice in which one you put salt and pepper, I think.
But I think there's a more common way to do it.
It's different with how many holes it has.
Isn't it cute?
And last but not least, another kitchen-themed thing would be... Ta-da!
KFP Hydration Station Glass
The glass! Yes, we have a glass!
Wonderful!
Finally a glass, don't break it! Be careful with it.
But in case you break it, maybe get some more.
Maybe get some more of the plates too. Might as well, right?
And after the glass, we have one more thing, a voice pack! Yeah!
Situational Voice Pack "Taking flight with Wawa"
I wrote the script, and I tried my best.
I was writing it on the airplane...
...and the situation is also on an airplane.
So I was like...
Don't worry, it's not a situation that really happened to me.
But maybe, maybe in your brain it really happened...
...just like for me.
I spilled like some tomato juice and so on onto you.
So isn't that kind of spicy? It might be.
It might just be.
Besides that, we have for full set an A5 clear file...
A5 clear folder
...which has the main illustration on it, which I would love to have that.
So make sure to get the full set to support me. I would appreciate it.
And now we're getting into the last phase, guys.
Don't you want to hear some Chimera again? Hmm?
I got you covered.
Last song, everybody. Are you ready?
The song: CHIMERA!
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na...
Oh no!
Down into the abyss unknown
CHIMERA - Lyrics, Music: Asteroid Music Team
Left me bleeding heartless, so alone
A-yo, a-yo, no control
A-yo, a-yo, don't you dare apologize
Turned my back and felt the cold night
Listen up 'cause here's some advice
(Ah-ya-ya-ya-ya) You're out of time, we're out of line
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Ch-ch-ch-chimera-era-era
You got me twisted
(You got me twisted)
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You're gonna hear them all sing
Ch-ch-ch-chimera-era-era
You got me twisted
Don't back it up, don't back it up, keep that aim
I got thoughts that will drive you insane
Come along if you like, we'll have a lot of fun
But I got a lot of fight
I do what I want, make sure you don't forget
An army on my back, I'm sick and sadistic
No living in a lie, pariah in the light
I wanna see the way you bleed
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Ch-ch-ch-chimera-era-era
You got me twisted
Taking the crown now you calling me king
You're gonna hear em all sing
Chimera-era-era-ya
I want it all, so give me some more
Flames burn me up down into my core
Oh you wish I'd stay down but then I just rise
You're not my enemy
Baby you're dead to me
Hear my voice screaming out loud
Don't doubt, yeah!
La la la la la la
Chimera-era-era-ya
La la la la la la, Chimera
Tearing it down do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner (Don't you think so)
Chimera-era-era-ya (Don't you twist it)
Chimera-era-era-ya
Taking the crown now you calling me king
You're gonna hear em all sing
Chimera-era-era-ya
La la la la la la, Chimera-era-era-ya
La la la la la la, Chimera
Hah... Chimera!
That was fun to do that again.
Did you press 4?
Thank you.
So, with the next song, it'll actually be the last song.
But this one is a very special one because
for the first time ever, you will hear my next song, "MIRAGE".
And for this one, what's really special is,
for the first time ever, I'm bringing in
some back-up dancers, back-dancers,
who are gonna join me.
So, please enjoy.
And afterwards, the MV will be released.
So, hopefully everything goes according to plan.
So, please make sure to check that out too
and support my new song...
..."MIRAGE"!
MIRAGE
Lyrics: Asteroid Music Team (monii)
Music: Asteroid Music Team (monii, Johnny R, Ari)
Mirror's reflection, going under.
Confused obsession.
I still wonder if I was made for you,
if I could only see, oh please
Make me up, a new
persona, calculated perfectly for you
Pretending like it's all just
for me? Don't think so
Live life incognito
Oh I ~
play god and yet I'm asking why
You never see what I want, what I need
Oh do you? (No, no)
Follow through, light you pursue but now
Ahh ~
You sold me on a mirage
I tore you up into shreds
I don't even know what to do with this mess
Tell me the cost
Sit, be good, play your part, my mirage
Livin' with regrets, those don't do anything
Better left unsaid
Thought I'd be the king and queen of
newfound paradise
I'm beggin' you to see
I'm you, you're all of me
It seems like everyone wants it
All around and round, running round around,
on and on
This cycle keepin' me captive, escape my way
You say I'm way too fragile
I'm just your perfect idol
Break me, shape me, I ~
You never see what I want, what I need
Oh do you? (No, no)
Follow through, light you pursue but now
Ahh ~
You sold me on a mirage
I tore you up into shreds
I don't even know what to do with this mess
Tell me the cost
Sit, be good, play your part, my mirage
Mi-mi-mimi-mirage you
Spinnin' little lies, new disguise, on and on,
and on!
This mirage I'm lost
Who owns your heart? Mirage
You, you... you make me fall in line ~
You make me... (You, you... you... you...)
No ooh!
Oh...
You sold me on a mirage
I tore you up into shreds
I don't even know what to do with this mess
Tell me the cost
Sit be good, play your part, my mirage
Mi-mi-mimi-mirage you
Spinnin' little lies, new disguise, on and on
And on and on and on
This mirage, I'm lost
Who owns your heart? Mirage...
Yeah...
MIRAGE PREMIERE NOW!