(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ライブ中に重大告知あり！
Important announcement during the live!
3D BIRTHDAY CONCERT ...WITH HUGE NEWS
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Hey Dead Beats! What's up!
Wooooo!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Happy birthday, happy birthday to me!
Hey guys, what's up? Thank you very much
for coming to my very first ever 3D live concert!
I see all you Dead Beats in chat going wild right now. What is up!
疲れてる... バイバイ！
I'm tired... bye bye!
I'm kidding, I'm kidding! It's a joke, it's a joke!
No, we're here to... we're here to celebrate!
Why are we starting off in this room? I don't know,
maybe because I'm nervous as hell
and I want to talk to my friends.
I want to talk to my friends.
友達と一緒に話したいよ。
I want to talk with my friends.
緊張してるからね。
Because I'm nervous.
Because I'm nervous, I'm so... I'm so nervous.
So I thought, I thought... why not do a little
fun game with my friends who have been with me
since the beginning, and afterward,
new friends too that I've made along the way.
Why don't we play a game or something?
So I can calm down before this big concert.
What do you guys think? Is that okay?
Is that okay, Dead Beats?
“Happy birthday, Daddy, calm down now!”
Now? I refuse!
You watch yourself, mister. You watch your...
watch yourself, I'm looking at you.
Don't you tell me to calm down, I'm too excited!
“Dad needs a workout.” I do need to go back to the gym.
But you know what? After today, after today,
I'm gonna be extra strong,
ムキムキ！
and ripped!
Yeah, especially after today's game.
Today's game is gonna require some 3D movement.
I thought, hey, why not, we're 3D today.
So let's... let's do some things in 3D.
Let's do some actions. And maybe, I don't know,
have my friends try to guess what I'm doing.
Maybe that would be cool.
So anyway, that's what I thought. So...
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Let's enjoy a game of charades,
charades, with my friends in HoloEN.
And I have some friends from ID joining,
and also a friend from JP will be here as well.
So let's get the party started! Let's start!
始まります！
Let's begin!
Charades game.
Let's do it.
We've got two different groups of people.
Just so you guys know, we had to split them up.
Too many cool friends. So...
Let's see if we can get them in here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, here we go.
Here we go, here we go.
Oh, who's it gonna be? Who's it gonna be?
Who's gonna be joining us?
By the way, tweet at the hashtag if you want, it's right here.
I want to see your screenshots.
Please, show me your screenshots.
Okay, everyone, come in!
From the first group, please come here.
Wah! Hello!
I heard a wah.
Happy Birthday! / Congratulations!
I hear my friends.
So many friends!
You're so beautiful!
No, stop! I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed! Hazukashii!
I'm embarrassed! I'm embarrassed!
You're so cute!
I'm embarrassed.
I have my friends here today. We've got Sana, IRyS, Bae, Ina and Lui-chan in group number one.
Hello guys!
Hello!
Can I get your jiko shoukai first so everyone knows who you are?
Can I get your self-introductions first so everyone knows who you are?
Congratulations! Thank you, I'm so happy.
Please, first jiko shoukai.
Please, first self-introduction.
You're so cute!
No, stop! Stop!
Stop it! Stop!
やめて！
Stop it!
Man...
No, you don't get to look at them.
So cute! I'm gonna die!
She can't! She can't!
ボコボコにしてやるぞ！
I'm gonna beat you up!
Oh, thank you.
ボコボコに... Thank you, thank you.
Beat you up... Thank you, thank you.
ヤンキーだから...
Because she's a delinquent...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. She's doing it.
Thank you, Pon-zombie, for the words.
Thank you, everyone!
Hey!
Oof.
That wasn't part of the game.
Before we start the game, though, can you introduce yourselves, please? From Sana.
Sana.
Oh, yes! It's Sana Tsukumo...
...from Hololive EN Council!
I am a major Calliope Mori fan!
Not your space, dude? What are you talking about?
Oi, oi!
Thank you, Sana, you're so sweet. How about IRyS?
Hi-RyS! It's IRyS...
...Hololive EN Project HOPE, VSinger/VTuber...
...and I'm so excited for Calli's 3D debut!
And also, Calli's number one fan in Japan! Yeah!
Hey, hold on a minute! Thank you.
I see, I see.
That makes sense.
I love you.
If I could really properly make a heart, I would right now, but...
...it's a little difficult.
Anyway...
Close enough. You get the message.
Thank you, IRyS. How about... how about my little sister?
Lil' sis?
What's up? It's me!
Hakos Baelz! I have infiltrated!
I am her big sister, guys!
It's her birthday, and I wanted to come say hi.
And, oh yeah, I'm from Holo Council. I'm not leaving without a signature...
...on the boob. Okay?
Okay. You'll get one.
You're still bringing up the boob? Okay.
Oh my gosh.
You'll get one, you silly freaking rat.
I'll take a signature on my leg, on my leg please.
Is that what you want? You want a signature?
Yes!
Oh! Thank you! Beautiful!
It's up to you where I sign, so...
Never washing that part of my body ever again. No, never.
How about... how about our favorite taco?
Ina, you want to introduce yourself?
WAH!
Good morning, afternoon, evening! It's Ninomae Ina'nis...
...from Hololive English -Myth-!
The proudest, proudest tentacultist of Calli!
I'm so proud of Calli! Happy Birthday!
WAH!
I love you, Ina! Thank you for coming today.
I'm so happy.
Man, you know I love you, dude.
Gosh dang it, when are we gonna be on the same stage, right?
Gah!
I want a boco-boco fight in the face. Boco-boco.
I want a beating-up fight in the face. Beat up.
And then, who do we have last? We have my favorite kohai.
And then, who do we have last? We have my favorite junior.
お、知ってるね？
Oh, she knows, right?
待ったかね？
Did you wait?
Hi, I am Takane Lui...
...from the secret society HoloX!
Yeah! You're so cute every day.
But, you are so cute more than usual!
ルイちゃん、大好き！大好き！
Lui-chan, I love you! I love you!
Happy Birthday!
Thank you so much, Lui-chan.
ルイちゃんも可愛い。来てくれてありがとう。
Lui-chan is cute too. Thank you for coming.
Thank you for coming.
じゃ、shall we start the game?
Well, shall we start the game?
Yay! Let's go!
頑張ります！
I'll do my best!
Okay, let's go!
First word!
Okay, the audience can see, and I can see, but the girls can't see the word.
Okay, so they're going to guess.
Guess me. Okay.
All right, here's number one.
忍者 (ninja)
Ninja
Oh no... how am I supposed to... okay, hold on.
Karate?
Is that karate?
Martial arts?
Hiding?
Ninja!
Ninja! Ninja run!
Yes! You got it! I'm a ninja!
Once I pulled out the Naruto run, you guys knew.
You guys knew I'm a ninja.
And don't bring up Iroha-chan in my chat, any of you!
J-chat will ban you.
She will ban you. We don't do that here.
She's a samurai!
Yes, Iroha-chan is a samurai.
Not a ninja. Not ninja, okay?
Please remember. Okay!
Now, next word! Let's go!
IRyS
Oh no... okay, this is going to be kind of hard.
Cartwheel?
Levitation?
Singing?
Opera singer?
Hold on, I'm trying to find a way to...
Okay, I hope I don't get in trouble for this.
They're going to beat the shit out of me if I get in trouble for this.
Floating! Levitation!
Titanic?
IRyS?
Descending?
That's right, that's right! You got it!
It's IRyS!
It's supposed to be IRyS! I'm singing...
...and I'm descending.
I tried to get on like a swivel chair...
...but then the chair started moving around, I was like "shit, I'm getting in trouble."
I didn't know descending was that much of a big image.
I mean, yeah, you did descend three times, IRyS.
That's true, three times.
Three times! I had to climb up on something to descend.
Well, that's what I figured out about midway through.
And I was like, "this isn't going to work."
But yeah, nice job!
All right, the last question mark, last question mark.
Question... maybe it's question.
It's supposed to be hard, so let's go!
大盛りラーメンを食べる人
(Someone Eating a Large Bowl of Ramen)
Someone Eating a Large Bowl of Ramen
Oh no... how... okay, hold on.
A circle?
Swimming?
Or eating?
Eating... eating a bowl?
Person at an eating contest?
Izakaya?
Nomikai?
Drinking party?
Slurping soup! Something soup!
Slurping! Ramen!
Person eating giant ramen!
That's right! Yes!
Someone eating a large bowl of ramen! There you go!
Nice job! I was worried about that one.
I didn't know if you'd get the first part...
...but I think I illustrated the large bowl with my impeccable 3D tracking.
やった! (Yatta!) Nice job. Wow, you guys are smart!
Hooray! Nice job. Wow, you guys are smart!
We are smart!
You guys blasted through those three so easy.
We should do this more often when everybody gets a chance to be in 3D someday.
Charades!
Charades party with everyone, yeah!
Please, someday... think about how crazy that would be.
If that was what we did just now and it was so hilarious...
...imagine all of us together!
約束です。(Yakusoku desu.)
It's a promise.
約束です！ (Yakusoku desu!) Promise me!
It's a promise! Promise me!
Pinky promise!
I'll drink a thousand needles.
Oh wow, please don't hurt yourself!
Anyway, I'll see you guys later. Thank you so much for coming!
Thank you! Bye!
またね！ (Mata ne!) Bye bye!
See you! Bye bye!
Oh man, it's so nice to have my friends.
But guess what? They're not the only guests that came today.
No no, we have several more guests...
...that will be joining us in the next group.
Why don't you ladies come on in?
Come here, come here!
Yay! Oh my god!
Oh, jump more? Okay!
Yay yay yay yay yay yay yay yay yay!
Save your energy, Ollie! Ollie!
No, you just want to see them bounce!
Kiara's giving me the good idol advice.
She knows what I need to be doing right now. Sorry, let me calm down.
Yeah, save your energy. You have a whole performance ahead of you, right?
Yes, you are right. Thank you.
There you go.
Okay. Calm.
Discomposed. There we go.
Big breath, big breath. Breathe in...
Oh, big breath. Breathe out.
もっと！もっと！
More! More!
Breathe in... breathe out.
Okay. Be zen. Okay. We're fine. We're fine now.
Okay, who do we have here today?
Oh my gosh, some of my favorite... some of my favorite ladies in the whole world.
Oh my goodness, thank you so much for coming today.
We have both ID and of course EN Myth being represented here.
Please introduce yourselves, first starting from Reine, my fishing buddy.
Yay! Attention please, I'm Pavolia Reine from Hololive ID Generation 2,
Calli's fishing buddy, also a big fan!
Everybody's a fan.
Everybody's suddenly... well, I know you guys have always been supporting me, so thanks. I appreciate it.
Thank you my sweet fishing buddy. Love you so much, Reine.
Dang. And how about... how about... how about my Apex buddy for the two times I've ever played Apex?
We've got K-K-K-K-Kureiji Ollie! Did I do it correctly?
You did it so well! Yes! はい、こんばんは！
You did it so well! Yes! Hi, good evening!
Super Kawaii Zombie Idol ク……ク……ク……クレイジー・オリーです！
Super Kawaii Zombie Idol K-K-K-Kureiji Ollie here!
Calliou-senpai's wife/daughter/mother-in-law. Our relationship is a little bit foggy here, but good to be here!
Eh? Hold on, I didn't get the memo for the... wait, did you say wife? Wife? Hmm?
You proposed to me!
Yeah, but you tricked me!
It doesn't count. Oh, you guys! I've been tricked by Ollie.
Oi, oi, oi, Ollie, you watch yourself.
Next up, we've got Holo EN's number one detective Amelia Watson. Introduce yourself!
Amelia Watson! Hi Calli! Hello everybody!
I'm Hololive Detective Amelia Watson. こんにちワトソン！
I'm Hololive Detective Amelia Watson. Konnichi-Watson!
I'm so happy to be here, Calli. I'm so proud of you. You look so beautiful. Happy Birthday!
Watson, thank you so much. I appreciate that. Oh man, I'm so glad I get to do 3D stuff.
You're also doing really awesome 3D stuff too, so I hope we get to do some fun stuff in the future. やった！
You're also doing really awesome 3D stuff too, so I hope we get to do some fun stuff in the future. Yatta!
I can't wait. I can't wait. Let's do it!
Yeah! And we can't forget about my idol mentor, apparently. Takanashi Kiara! Tenchou!
Hey! Ki-ki-ri-ki! I'm Hololive English's Phoenix and KFP owner, Takanashi Kiara!
And I am apparently a pro for charades because I got the testing prompt within one second.
Oh my god, that is true. That is true. In the beginning there, you immediately knew.
But that was something... that was something that you like know well. You knew that I was pretending to be an idol.
Hold on, that was... that's not because of that. I'm just really good at charades. I'll prove that, Calli.
But it's also... it's also because you are just really, really good at showing those moves, expressing yourself, right?
I have too much fun. I have too much fun in 3D. It's like all of a sudden I see myself like on the screen and I'm like,
Oh man, I want to jump... I won't jump. I won't jump. I'm gonna stay calm.
Please jump! Please jump! Please jump!
Ollie! Ollie! Don't tell your Senpai what to do!
Sorry Ollie, I can't do that. I do gotta save my energy.
Well, shall we begin the game then? Let's go!
Yeah! Let's go!
Alright, first word. Here we go. First word... Oh no. How am I... Okay. Here we go.
寿司職人
Sushi Master
Oh! Oh! Washing your hair?
Making... huh? Pizza? Horse riding?
Oh, you're frying your hair!
No!
Spaghetti? You're cooking? Playing the piano?
No, xylophone? No, drum? What?
It's like you're... you're tying your hair and then you're eating.
Cooking! Cooking!
Close!
Making pizza! Making ramen!
You're tying your hair so like the hair doesn't go... a chef! At a restaurant!
KFP restaurant! Making dough! Making bread!
Okay, okay. Watch this. First... Oh yes, that's it! You got it, Watson! You got it!
Sushi master!
Sushi master! I'm the sushi master.
I guess... I guess my sushi rolling technique, top tier.
Why did you tuck your hands behind your head?
Because I was... you know how...
寿司職人
Sushi Master
...sushi chefs like maybe have like a little
cooking hat or bandana or something?
Ah! Why do you hammer the sushi?
Why do you hammer that?
I don't know, don't you chop the sushi like this?
If you're making like... like Hanamaki or something?
Well at least... at least Amen... maybe that's just a
very American perspective but at least Watson got it.
Anyway.
Oh thank goodness, thank goodness.
I thought that I was going to lose that one.
Number two! Question number two, let's go.
小鳥遊キアラ
Takanashi Kiara
All right. Oh boy.
Oh this one's too easy. I can do this one.
Okay. Watch closely.
Oh... uh-huh.
Kiara! I know, Kiara! Takanashi Kiara!
Yes! I'm Takanashi Kiara!
I'm Takanashi Kiara! Too easy!
All I have to do is pull out the kick and be like...
K-K-K-Kick! It's the Kiara kick!
You do it with a lot more finesse than I do but...
Excellent, nice! I like...
I like that angle, that's good!
Oh thank goodness! Should I try it again?
Yes! Nice, nice! Get the kick one more time,
thank you!
Oh! Thank you! Kiara can do it with her
whole body as much as me!
Oh! Thank you! Yeah!
I probably learned that a lot today.
Whoa! Well, I don't really know what you mean
by that but anyway, question number three!
Question number three, the last,
most difficult question. Here we go.
ホラー映画で最初に死ぬ人
The First Person to Die in a Horror Movie
No! Oh no!
Oh no! This is impossible! Okay, right, hold on.
Okay. Hold on.
Hmm. Think, Calli, think.
What? What are you doing? Mushy?
Oh no! Dead!
G-reaping... Reaping, I think.
Uh, bad guy killing someone.
Close, you're very close!
Murder... a murder... a villain killing someone!
Yes! Villain!
Someone... Stabbing someone! Stabbing someone!
Criminal!
And somebody died!
Uh... Oh no, begging for mercy and died- dying.
Uh... Well maybe if I can use my fingers.
Your fingers, okay. Okay. Okay.
Uh, a tiny ball? No tiny ball.
What number is this?
Two- two. No.
One! Yes! One!
Seven! One! One!
One! One guy stabbing someone! One stab!
One punch! One! Number one!
One! One guy running away?
One guy being killed!
Close!
One guy about to die! Close!
What specifically more about them? Uh...
A murder relationship? One bad guy!
One... I'm going to kill whoever chose this
question. I'm going to kill them!
I think I might lose this one guys. Oh boy.
Reaper... Reper-r-r... Uh... a murderer...
Yes! The murderer! Don't kill me!
Please don't kill me!
No! My friend! Please don't kill me!
I... No! Running for your life!
Rest in peace! Rest in peace!
All my friends are alive and I am dead!
Someone died! Someone- someone died!
People die when they are killed!
I lost this one!
Someone died by being stabbed to death?
Bleeding to death?
That was too freaking specific!
Okay, the answer was 'the first person to die
in a horror movie'!
Aww! How am I supposed to indicate
that I'm the first person?
That's difficult! That's hard but you guys got
it for the most part.
How can you be so specific? Right, I know...
...but you guys got it for the most part.
So you guys did your best.
We all did our best, yeah. Ah, but you know what,
that was fun with you guys, honestly.
Oh man, I'm so glad we got to play
a little game together.
You guys need to get over here too and do
some 3D with me, okay?
Yes! Of course! I'm waiting for you!
Do your best! Do your best, Calli! I will!
I hope you'll keep watching for the
announcement! So excited!
Thank you! I'm excited too! Ah!
Thanks for coming and making time for me.
I know it's really early for some folks here...
...and really inconvenient timing, so thank you
so much for being here to support me.
And if you check out the concert...
don't- don't make me start crying!
Thank you for inviting us! Oh... I love you guys!
Of course we gotta be here for this special
event! Yeah! Bye guys!
Happy birthday girl! Happy birthday!
I love y'all!
It's my birthday! It's my birthday!
I'm gonna kick it like it's my birthday!
Thank you so much everyone!
I'll see you guys soon then, okay? Okay! Bye!
Bye-bye! Goodbye my friend! Thank you!
Bye everyone! See you! There they go.
Well I guess that that means it's time for the
singing portion.
I did get to shake off some of the nerves
thanks to my friends...
...because my heart's been racing today,
but because I got to talk to them and I know
that they're supporting me...
I feel good.
I feel like we can put on a show,
and I'll do my best.
It's my first time really doing this like live,
so I'm trying not to run out of energy.
I gotta take... I gotta take Kiara's idol expertise to heart.
I should know that too, being a rapper as well, but you know, I forget.
And plus, you know, the speakers go boom-boom-boom all the time.
Anyway, let's... let's do a show, alright?
Let's do a show, you guys!
I'll do my... I'll do my best, okay?
Nervous or tired? A little bit of both, but also ready to go.
Let's do this, okay?
Let's go to the stage!
わっしょい、わっしょい、わっしょい！
Washoi, washoi, washoi!
spiral tones
Lyrics • Composition: 律可, Mori Calliope
Lyrics • Composition: Rikka, Mori Calliope
Ah. Imagine, take a look,
it's a change of age,
more an open book that's got a lot to say.
Like a spiral, others say out of control,
but we just keep spinning still for that soul.
Stay committed to the sick vibes, good music,
rhythmic type cruising, proof, isn't it?
But you'll lose it, stuck on yesterday
'cause it only really matters if you play it that way. Uh.
How would you rate this? Add it to your playlist.
Got something to say, but only when your face'll stay stasis.
You ain't gotta be held back by the status quo.
When the odds are stacked, we'll make a badass show.
With our ways with words, blast off to another vista way of the world.
Move fast when we want to run, knock 'em unconscious,
bring 'em back to life and tell 'em, 'Hey, watch this!'
そんな音色で 終われるはずがない
There's no way it can end with such a tone
新しいことに挑むには
In order to challenge new things
いっそ開き直り切るくらいの方が ちょうどいい
It's better to just go all out with defiance
おかしくない？ Don't be surrender.
Isn't it strange? Don't be surrender.
三秒で分からせて
Make me understand in three seconds
止まない It's awesome 拍手喝采
Unceasingly, it's awesome, a round of applause
進化するフロー
An evolving flow
次元を超えて 見失わぬよう
Transcending dimensions, so as not to lose sight
その呼吸を射抜いて
Pierce through that breath
重なり合っていく spiral tones
Overlapping, spiral tones
ここらで勝手な想像 後出しも早々 沸いてそう
Right around here, selfish imaginations are brewing up
揚げ足取り 野暮な呟き
Nitpicking, insensitive mutterings
誰得で寒い もうな、ログ
Who is this for? It's chilling. Already, a log.
簡単に考えりゃいいよ 厄介な心配は無用
Just think about it simply. No need for troublesome worries
ありもしない 後悔なんてナンセンス
Regrets for things that don't exist are nonsense
これで開眼できたら僥倖 最大限ハイファイで
If you can open your eyes with this, it's a blessing. With maximum hi-fi
身体を震わす音の波線 何度だい
How many times have sound waves vibrated your body?
それでも分からないなら
If you still don't understand
拝啓 誠意をどうぞ
Dear someone, please show some sincerity
Notes on ideologies, hella ancient, junk, fond, no apologies,
with your anxious creationists, thankless demolitions imminent.
Waiting for the movement, not just beginning it. First try winging it,
see you have an issue, limitless bringing this sick vibes, tribute's yada you don't say but hey guess what? Your old news done living with your eyes blind shut.
おかしくない？ Don't be surrender.
Isn't it strange? Don't be surrender.
三分で口ずさめる
You can hum it in three minutes
続けて It's awesome 震天動地
Continually, it's awesome, world-shaking
増えていくフロック
Increasing flukes
次元を超えて 見失わぬよう
Transcending dimensions, so as not to lose sight
その期待値を射抜いて
Pierce through those expectations
大人になんてない spiral tones
There's no such thing as becoming an adult, spiral tones
Can't ignore forever.
What could make you better?
Anyway, anyway, anyway, no wonder.
嫌いが好きに変わったって
Even if hate changed into love
おかしくない？ Don't be surrender.
Isn't it strange? Don't be surrender.
三秒で分からせて
Make me understand in three seconds
止まない It's awesome 拍手喝采
Unceasingly, it's awesome, a round of applause
進化するフロー
An evolving flow
次元を超えて 見失わぬよう
Transcending dimensions, so as not to lose sight
その呼吸を射抜いて
Pierce through that breath
重なり合っていく spiral tones
Overlapping, spiral tones
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
Thank you! Thank you everyone!
Thank you so much!
最高です。ありがとうございました！
That was awesome! Thank you very much!
最高ですね！
That was awesome!
すごい楽しかったです、リッカさん、本当に。ありがとう。
I had a lot of fun, Rikka-san, really. Thank you.
ありがとう、聞いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you, thank you for listening!
お疲れ様です、ハッピーバースデー！
Good job out there, and Happy Birthday!
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
Rikka-senpai, I'm so happy.
ついに一緒にやれたね、なんか。
Finally, we got to do this together.
Finally!
ねえ。
Yeah.
ようやく。
At long last.
Yeah, we can perform on the same stage together.
なんか前ね、約束、promiseしてたもんね。
We made a promise before, didn't we?
We promised.
You're right. We promised.
呼んでくれてありがとう、special day。
Thanks for inviting me on your special day.
Of course, of course!
Thank you for coming here on my special day.
And I loved making Spiral Tones together with you.
凄い、えっと、Spiral Tones作るの凄い楽しかった。
It was so much fun making "Spiral Tones."
楽しかった。
It was fun.
ねえ、right. ねえ、良いコラボ。
Yeah, right. It was a great collab.
Right?
Someday, いつか、また凄い素敵な曲作りたいと思います。
Someday, I'd like to make another wonderful song.
あーもう、また作ろう。全部英語のとかね。
Oh, let's make another one. All in English, maybe?
あー、そうね。
Ah, yeah.
An all English song.
An all English song? I wonder... 出来るかな？
絶対出来ると思う。頑張ったら絶対出来るよ。
An all English song? I wonder... Can we do it?
I think we definitely can. We can do it if we try!
Rikka-senpaiの英語、あの、少しずつ上手くなってきて、
聞いたと思います。
I heard Rikka-senpai's English is
getting better and better!
本当に？
Really?
Thank you.
凄い！頑張る、頑張る。
Amazing! I'll do my best.
頑張ってね。
Good luck!
うん。また曲ね、一緒に作ったり。
Yeah. Let's make songs together again...
Please, of course.
ライブも。
And do lives too.
Yes.
全体で頑張りましょう、ホロでね。
Let's do our best overall as Holo.
Yes, let's do it!
Thank you.
And I always support Holostars.
ホロスターズ、いつも応援しています。
I'm always rooting for Holostars.
ホント、ありがたい。
I really appreciate it.
ありがとうございます、本当に。頑張ってくださいね。
Thank you so much. Good luck!
ホロスターズもめっちゃ素敵だと思う。
I think Holostars is really wonderful, too.
いや、HoloEN最高。
HoloEN is the best!
優しい、優しい。
You're so kind!
Thank you my man, Rikka. Thank you so much.
Great singer.
Great singer too, and guitar! 凄い。
Great singer too, and guitar! Amazing!
えー、ギター、全然出来ない私。
I can't play the guitar at all.
全然いい。
That's totally fine.
むずい、むずいよ。
It's so hard!
ラップ、ラップが出来れば。
As long as you can rap!
Thank you!
We have our specialties. 得意、得意なとこ。
We each have our strengths.
まあ一緒にね、色々やれば
Well, if we do various things together...
そうね。
Yeah.
全部いい感じになるよ。
Everything will turn out great.
Right! Combine our power. Nice combination.
ナイスコンビネーションね。
Nice combination.
それが一番だと思う。
I think that's the best.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
ありがとうございます、Rikka-senpai.
Thank you, Rikka-senpai.
ありがとうね。
Thank you.
また絶対やりましょう。See you!
Let's definitely do it again. See you!
See you! Thank you so much!
Goodbye senpai! Bye bye, Rikka! See you!
Gosh, Rikka-senpai's so cool.
Man, what an awesome dude and great musician.
Check out Rikka's stuff, please.
Check out Rikka's channel.
He does a lot of music stuff.
I know that a lot of my Dead Beats love my music
and stuff like that that I make...
So I always have my recommended musicians amongst the
Holo crew, and Rikka's definitely one of them.
And check out the Stars, 'cause they're working
super hard too.
Now then. Since we started off with a guest song...
I figured it's probably time for me to take it on
my own.
But I need a little bit of water.
This always happens at every show I go to.
It's like every single song that I do, it's like in
between, I'm like "Okay, water, water."
It's become a joke, honestly.
Hold on.
But you can't see it. It's the mysterious water
bottle you can't see.
All right.
Oh, by the way, check out the stage!
You see that cool skeleton?
Yeah, this is my special Hololive made-to-order
Calliope Mori stage...
With my cool skeletons with the wings designed
after the "UnAlive" album art by Rei.
Check it. Check out my ガイコツたち。My skeletons.
Check it. Check out my skeletons. My skeletons.
It's like you guys, sitting behind me, supporting me.
Couldn't have skeleton back-up dancers this time,
maybe next time. You'll be watching.
Anyway, shall we go to the next song?
Let's do it. "The Grim Reaper is a Live-Streamer."
The Grim Reaper is a Live-Streamer
Lyrics: Mori Calliope, てにをは / Composition: てにをは
Lyrics: Mori Calliope, teniwoha / Composition: teniwoha
3, 2, 1, swing it!
お騒がせね Ladies
Pardon me, ladies
Dead Beats swinging out, out of control
シャラララララバ
Sha-la-la-la-la-bye
誰も気付かない
No one notices
The variety of life, ha ha, you know?
全方向ランデブー
All-direction rendezvous
Alright, never-missing moon
今あなたの隣に死神がいますよ
Right now, a reaper is right next to you
Yeah, right.
Let’s hit the crosswalk, let’s talk, can you keep up?
You’re kind of 気になり looking like a dose of enough
You’re kind of curious looking like a dose of enough
A petite rendezvous, we’re bound to stray far
I'm the kind to ease your mind,
but take you to the graveyard
Step out to the city, but you don't know me
Take my wits right with me, but they don't know me
Maybe feel like going psycho in the streets
Save that for later, instead I'll make a stylish treat
I go live, go high, so fly, oh my
No drive, this guy, talk about misfire
Leave it to me, spit fire, fitting for cash
I'll never be caught again, right in this office bash
Honestly, I never had life to begin with
And now I got you, double the power to sin with
But not like I'll complain, just laughing, just saying...
晴れ日を上手の手の表裏
Fair days, inside and out of a skilled hand
輝く演者の晴れ舞台
The shining performer’s grand stage
高々空浮かぶは我が調べ
Floating high in the sky is my melody
表はどうか尋ねないで
Please don't ask about the outside
Don't know, don't know, don't know...
お騒がせね Ladies
Pardon me, ladies
Down, down, 歌わせて
Down, down, let me sing
Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la...
誰も気付かない
No one notices
日和見をトハ
The opportunism
今宵には
On this night
Never missing moon
誰かを照らす
Shining on someone
As far as telling horror stories goes
My kind of warfare
Lift the curtain for one hell of a show
And now action!
Transmission live before you
Everything real-time
Just don't forget admission
The soul's still mine
Out on the town again, death in your midst
Right behind you, down below, listen you get the gist
Nobody realizing, they don't recognize me
Fine by me, it's agonizingly disguised, see?
Life now broadcasting, only so long lasting
Rather it's a matter of a right and wrong casting
Fasten your seatbelt fast, or do you need help?
Need that fresh air?
海辺に掻き立てた摩訶
Stirred up on the seashore, a wonder
溶けてゆく日々の中に
In the days that melt away
鮮出し魔法
Vivid magic
上書きしてく素っ気ないし
Overwriting it, blunt as it is
という意味
That's what it means
正解は自分で探してみ
Try looking for the answer yourself
月に裏も表もねえ
The moon has neither front nor back
Have a great night!
私 Show time, ladies...
It's my showtime, ladies...
Down, down, 歌ってる
Down, down, I'm singing
Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la...
誰も気付かない
No one notices
日和見をトハ
The opportunism
今宵には
On this night
Never missing moon
誰かを照らす
Shining on someone
As far as telling horror stories goes
My kind of warfare
Lift the curtain for one hell of a show
And now action!
Transmission live before you
Everything real-time
Just don't forget admission
The soul's still mine
Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la...
Hey! Listen!
今、あなたの隣に... 死神がいますよ。ハハッ！
Right now, by your side... there's a Grim Reaper. Haha!
Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la...
Hey!
もしもしー？
Hello...?
Whatever.
Yeah! Woo! Woo, that had me out of breath there, man.
Let's go.
Oh, oh, oh yeah! Suisei Calliope!
Wicked
あぁもう、どうしようもない
Ah, there's just no helping it
アウトロー　女利
Outlaw onnary
灰色　視界を獲りたい
I want to take this grey vision
勝ち逃げろ今夜今更なプライド
Win and run tonight, a pride that's too late now
Yeah, apostle of consistency on hunt
説教とか勘弁ですわ
Please spare me the lectures
知ったんだよ、うるさいな
I found out, you're annoying
それ、不正直ですよ？どこが？
That's dishonest, isn't it? In what way?
馬鹿馬鹿しいな　前代未聞
How ridiculous, unheard of
ナモン造ったって、バーン！Breathe you have fun
Even if you create such a thing, bam! Breathe you have fun
Roll some whiskey, we just gonna break it
結び付けられた運命の舞台　今上へ
To the stage of destiny we're bound to, now upwards
Ah-eh-ah, 己の正当性戦うの
Ah-eh-ah, fighting for our own legitimacy
Wicked gonna break it, nobody can check me
君と未来のため　見つけてゆくんだよ
For you and the future, I will keep on searching
Shiny shiny star, 轟きそうな
Shiny shiny star, about to roar
Don't try to chick-a-boom, chick-a-boom, chick-a-boom babe
I!
Right now, this world where you get what you give
I'm a girl of a whole lot of adjectives
A couple might say stubborn, rude, heartless
And the craziest, praise me with secrets please, no guise please
I came for to get a lot, now I'm spittin' here with swag
Say burnin' hot, you can start to see the scars
Hit the grind, now we shinin', see how far we've done came
Our shame's in a numbers game, some fun first fame, second win
And stop, 'cause we livin' in the moment and we own it
And K we've done pavin' our way for one aim, top shinin'
Still came with a loaded gun, give it a try
Better pick a direction and run with an alibi
Let me be tonight, maybe you're asleep in the deep
Roll some whiskey, we just gonna break it
結び付けられた運命の舞台　今上へ
To the stage of destiny we're bound to, now upwards
Ah-eh-ah, 己の正当性戦うの
Ah-eh-ah, fighting for our own legitimacy
とても不思議ね　君といる時だけは
It's so strange, only when I'm with you
胸を撫で下ろすの　越してゆく　Save me baby
I breathe a sigh of relief, moving past... Save me baby
他の誰も知らない　私見せたり
Showing a side of me that no one else knows
時が経てばとか　考えていたり
Thinking about things like time passing
声枯れたよ　夢の場所へ
My voice is hoarse, towards the place of dreams
来たのよ　Long long way
I've come a long, long way
Roll some whiskey, we just gonna break it
踏み出せば次なるレベル　近付いたら上へ
If we step forward, the next level, when we get close, upwards
Ah-eh-ah, 己のものさして続けるの
Ah-eh-ah, continuing with our own yardstick
走り続けて　優しさ覚えて
Keep on running, learning kindness
それぞれの幸せ　見分かってくんだよ
We'll come to understand our respective happiness
Just moving, moving on, そんな運命だ
Just moving, moving on, that's destiny
Born to be wicked and we aims to fly
With the angels and devils it's a do or die
Yeah!
Thank you! ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you very much!
Thank you everyone!
すいせい先輩、ハグした！ハグハグ！
I hugged Suisei-senpai! Hug, hug!
Yes, welcome to my stage!
イェーイ！最高！
Yay! This is awesome!
どう思いますか？
What do you think?
あ、空気がうまい！
Ah, the air is tasty!
あっそう！エアうまい！
Ah, right! Tasty air!
嬉しい、なんかちょっと地獄のバイブスあるけど。
I'm happy, it's got some hellish vibes though.
ちょっと怖いと思うんだけどな。
Might be a bit scary though.
Ah, soiri! But yeah, Suisei-senpai likes the hellish vibes.
イェーイ！ありがとう！
や、カリオペとステージで歌えるなんて...
Yay! Thank you!
To think I'd be singing on stage with Calliope...
あれ？え？
Wait, what?
久しぶりだね！久しぶりだね、カリオペ！
It's been a while! It's been a while, Calliope!
Yeah, long time no see, together.
４日ぶりです！
It's been four days!
Yeah, it's been like four days. そうですよね！ Right.
Yeah, it's been like four days. That's right! Right.
ね。で、私のえっと...周年ライブでね、
Right. And, uh... at my anniversary live,
アニバーサリーライブでカリオペを呼びまして。
さっきの『Wicked』を歌いましたね。
I invited Calliope to my anniversary live.
We sang 'Wicked' just now, didn't we?
Yeah, 'Wicked' is Suisei-senpai's song,
and it came out with her new single 'Template'.
And 'Template' was number one on the charts, and
'Wicked' was number two, so おめでとうすいせい先輩！
'Wicked' was number two, so congratulations Suisei-senpai!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Amazing. It's so wonderful. And...
すごい、楽しかったね！
『Wicked』一緒に歌えたの楽しかった、本当に。
It was great, it was fun!
It was really fun to sing 'Wicked' together.
え、でも今日はまだあるんだよね？
Eh, but there's more today, right?
Yes! We have... we have another song actually,
that we wrote together.
Except this time, it's a Mori Calliope
featuring Hoshimachi Suisei song.
A brand new song and it's very important because
after we perform this song,
there's a really, really big announcement.
It's 'the' one.
It's the announcement I mentioned
that's the biggest of my entire life.
So please look forward to it, and it has
something to do with the song we're doing.
So, we're going to do our brand new song.
Yes, it's called 'CapSule'.
Yes! 『CapSule』.
Yes! 'CapSule'.
『CapSule』 with C-A, Calliope,
S-U, Suisei-senpai.
'CapSule' with C-A, Calliope,
そうなんですよ！
That's right!
『CapSule』っていう二人の新しい曲が
出ますよ、皆さん！
A new song by the two of us called 'CapSule'
is coming out, everyone!
なんと二曲目！やったー！
It's our second one! Yay!
So please enjoy! Yes, let's check it out!
Check it out!
And thank you so much Suisei-senpai for coming
to my birthday! イェーイ！イェーイ！
to my birthday! Yay! Yay!
楽しみましょう！ Join us!
Let's have fun! Join us!
Yes, join us. 頑張りましょう！ 頑張りましょう！
Yes, join us. Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
CapSule
Lyrics: DECO*27, Mori Calliope / Composition: DECO*27
冗談ねちゃって a-ha
Just kidding, a-ha
此処ろまたやっちゃった
Done it again here
酸いも甘いも苦いのでも飲み干せば All right
Sour, sweet, or even bitter, if you drink it all up, it's All right
Stand up, nothing’s no sinners,
Man up, this is where it takes off
And even sweat when the going gets rough,
And I’m leaving ‘til the last laugh
間違い探しじゃ致し方ないなきっと
Finding mistakes can't be helped, I'm sure
心七変化って本物のオンボロだ
A heart of seven changes is a real piece of junk
透き通った名前冤罪だね
A transparent name, it's a false accusation
笑っちゃうでも溢れ出すのエモ
I laugh, but the 'emo' starts overflowing
Emotional wreck, but still I'm rockin' hot specs
With every life it marks survival where the mic check
We both not of this world, we both remain a connect
‘Cause when the chips are down, your cards are out,
the Queen’s on the deck
Live on my vibe
終焉は何処でもいいから期待させて
I don't care where the end is, just keep me expectant
Take you higher 貸せてよ
Take you higher, let me lend it
Mistafire 出る炎
Mistafire, the emerging flames
Raise the fire なんない Beat on
Raise the fire, never ending Beat on
Underrated on, it’s encapsulated sun
意地を張り混ぜついてよ
Mix in some stubbornness and follow along
目立たせてカルテじゃ
Make it stand out, in the charts
We want it all 愛しの
We want it all, my dear
Under fascinated us, we can’t be faster because
We want it all and wanna follow stay proud
Without any storm engine can’t get louder
We want it all and wanna fall I'm gone bright
I won't fear at all I'm still among those eyes
ねえ面倒臭いとか言ったらそれは謂わゆる終いじゃん
Hey, if you say it's a pain, that's what you'd call the end, right?
Why should I be trying for a dream that’s a pain
‘Cause death is dying every day, designer up again you know
０から映像まで完タップ仕上がって
どうぞ私の守守歌
From zero to video, it's fully tapped and finished
Here is my lullaby
Mellow doesn’t suit our vibe, steady blowin’ stellar styles,
Still, it’s really keep your eyes on the Mori
それじゃ反省なんて嘘ね
Then reflecting is just a lie, isn't it
ヒットと上下ガチャ
Hits and up-down gacha
回してみて機嫌ガチャ
Try spinning the mood gacha
漁るまで後悔
Regret until you scavenge
What’s the point of feeling sorry?
Just an act I still don’t care
Could maybe lay it down a million times,
I’ll get fine when I can’t get my share
Save it for the night
第内同士で
Among our inner selves
同情を灰にして
Turning sympathy into ash
Death stars shoot across the sky we the bad guys
お待たせしやして修羅場さ
Sorry to keep you waiting, it's a scene of carnage
私九理居左太 可愛いもっと頂戴
I'm the Curator, give me more 'kawaii'
Tarinai tarinai in and out of the spotlight
but still got a couple of parts in us you know
Not enough, not enough, in and out of the spotlight
Take you higher 貸せるわ
Take you higher, I can lend it
Mistafire 出るまで
Mistafire, until it comes out
Raise the fire 街のビート
Raise the fire, the city's beat
Underrated on, it’s encapsulated sun, it’s got
どこへ行っても
No matter where I go
狙い定める
I'll set my aim
もう居ないや
There's no one left
As we wanted
弾む声
Our bouncing voices
Up faster and faster leader we can't be faster enough
We want it all, and when it falls
Stay proud without any storm and you can't get louder
I'm gone by your side, I won't be your salt
Still I'm mourning those eyes
Those eyes...
Mori Calliope x 星街すいせい 「CapSule」 streaming now!
Mori Calliope x Hoshimachi Suisei "CapSule" streaming now!
UNIVERSAL MUSIC GROUP
Major Debut
07.21.2022 at Toyosu PIT Solo concert Coming soon...
(Laughing) Oh my gosh...
You guys are so... You guys are such a surprise...
...and excited. Thank you. Thank you so much everyone.
Yes, uh, the truth is, um, I am now signed to Universal Music.
Um, and I am doing... it's my major debut...
I'm lost for words, I like don't know what to say.
Um, this is like something I dreamed for for such a long time.
Um, honestly, I... I dreamed of doing something like this.
And um... Yeah, I'm not gonna... I won't get emotional right now.
Um, we got a couple things to talk about, so...
But yes, I am debuting from Universal Music.
And I will also be doing, um, a solo live show in July.
My first solo on a real stage in front of a crowd.
In front of all of you guys. So let the Dead Beat Empire continue onward.
And um... and there's a new EP.
Major debut new EP called "SHINGAMI NOTE".
"SHINGAMI NOTE", 死神の音...
"SHINGAMI NOTE", Shinigami no Oto...
...which is kind of a popular... it's like a play on words.
Um, you'll see later when you read the kanji, but, uh...
Thank you everyone, um, who's been supporting me.
And... and yeah, I'm really excited to see where this journey takes us.
But I promise you guys I'll still be me.
I'll still be making the music I want to make.
It's just it's going to be on a larger scale. I'm like shaking right now.
Um, I'm still going to make the music that I want to make and for the world that I want to see.
This is a little corny, but... anyway...
This is like the biggest thing that's ever happened to me in my life.
So and I wouldn't be here if... if you guys didn't love what I do so much and support me...
...and cheer for me and listen to my music and thank you so much.
Yeah. So I want to explain some things.
I want to explain a little bit about the EP and whatnot.
説明しますね。
I'll explain it.
So first, we have of course "CapSule", first major single...
And guess what, it's featuring my beloved singing senpai Hoshimachi Suisei...
...who I respect and love so much. We love Suisei-senpai.
And I could not have chosen a better partner to be involved in my first major single from Universal Music.
Um, and yeah, it's actually premiering after this show.
The MV YouTube premier and digital release.
It's going to be 30 minutes... not 30 minutes... um, more like...
...more like 25 from now on my channel, so please check it out, "CapSule".
Um, yeah, let's go to the next slide. 次に行きます。
Um, yeah, let's go to the next slide. Moving to the next.
Next we've got "SHINGAMI NOTE", 死神の音.
Next we've got "SHINGAMI NOTE", Shinigami no Oto.
If you check it out at the bottom, it's like, you know, SHINGAMI Music Note...
...get it? Right? 'Cause music.
But then also 死神の音, using the kanji for "sound"...
But then also Shinigami no Oto, using the kanji for "sound"...
...which is kind of a popular play on words in Japan. So, um, yeah.
My first major EP. And we have the art done by my fantastic Mama, Yukisame Mama.
You can scan the...
QR code right now to pre-order
it's going to be released on July 20th
July 20th, July 20th
and that will include 'Capsule'. By the way, 'Capsule's art was illustrated by Nardack.
So let's give a big ups to Nardack as well.
But if you guys want to pre-order and I recommend you pre-order cause you get some cool stuff
you can scan the QR code right now.
次に行きます。Next slide.
Going to the next. Next slide.
Because if you order the first press limited edition,
you get the LP-sized set, which is a CD plus DVD plus extras.
It's LP-sized but it's not a record, it's just like the size of a record,
but it's got the CD in it, the Shinigami Note EP CD,
as well as five original LP-sized cover jackets drawn by various artists.
You guys are going to love these art pieces, they're so cool.
And then I also will be doing an interview, 30 minutes, on DVD,
behind-the-scenes of the creation of the EP.
And then also you get a crest badge, honorary Dead Beat crest badge.
So yeah, that's pretty neat. But just so you guys know, these are super limited,
like we only have a certain amount of them,
so if you want it, you may want to try and grab it before it's gone,
because these are not infinite and we are never making them again.
So you may want to grab these as soon as possible if you're interested.
And then we've got the standard version of course including the same songs,
and then we have bonus items depending on each outlet that you use to buy the CD.
So you'll see those items pretty soon when the EP comes out.
It's available for pre-order everywhere but you'll get little bonus items depending on which store you buy from.
So again scan the QR code if you're interested. 次に行きます！Let's go to the next slide.
So again scan the QR code if you're interested. Going to the next! Let's go to the next slide.
And finally! My first solo concert, July 21st, 2022 at Toyosu Pit.
That's the day after the EP drops. I want to see you guys there.
More information coming soon but save the date.
And don't worry you guys if you're overseas and you can't get to Japan, no worries,
because it will be streamed live to you and you will be able to buy a ticket for it.
So please don't worry about that, fans all over the world,
you guys will get a chance to see it, so please anticipate it.
We're working very hard on it and yeah I hope you'll have fun. That's all, 以上です。 That's all.
We're working very hard on it and yeah I hope you'll have fun. That's all, that's all. That's all.
So I figured the next song that I would sing would be...
sort of a celebration of moving on to the next.
I wrote this song to kind of come to terms with me moving on...
...from Japan's underground rap scene and embracing what I have found here in Holo.
And things won't change with me in terms of Holo,
I'll still stream for you guys and collab with my friends and do music collabs with them too.
But when it comes to my original music, Universal's going to be kind of with me throughout the journey.
So don't worry, I'm not leaving or anything. I'm still here.
But things maybe become a little more focused on the music.
Things might change a little bit, but again I don't want you to worry.
I'm really excited about this, so let's rather try and celebrate together,
looking towards a positive future with the next song, end of a life. Let's go.
We’d run right through those nights
I’ll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
There was madness in the meaning, never laughless, we were screaming
At the top of our lungs to the numbingness This city never died
I’ll fly no proof those heights
I’ll never find another chance to say “thanks for saving my life”
I was hopeless, it was stinging, running roadless, we were singing
At the top of our lungs to the numbingness This city never died
What was the root of it all? I couldn't say
Used to jump and then fall, well, getting cliché
We'd shrug it off without complaint, not a sound
No use in trying to find friends 'cause in the end nobody sticks around
It's when you shoved yourself into a crowded place
That you turned around and found yourself in love and outer space
Cue the reckless nights, no strings, laughing at our own dreams
Just what the hell was so funny?
Up the wrong tree, stumble, used to fall and grey heart
Abyss to concrete jungle, singing 'cause it felt right
We mixed the ennui and troubles rhyming art's intent
And though it's history I can't forget the time we spent
Convinced that this could mean another end exists between real and pretend
A twisted ultra fiction where I missed my chance to not ascend
Disappearing into the mist of “never happened”
Is it to me that I can never be a friend?
I let it go
Fade in, fade out, this crazy dream
Without a direction flowing aimlessly
There's nothing left back there for me
Breathe in, but it won't stop the rain
from pouring right through
Those nights, I'll never find my way
back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
There was madness in the meaning, never mindless,
we were screaming at the top of our lungs
To the numinous, this city never died,
but was there ever a soul inside?
Chasing fireflies between the soaring high rises,
left a trail behind to find a waste of time...
Silent finger over words and underpaid,
things a synopsis, a coffin, and cenotaphs...
Yet a thought persists: not optimist
you ought to be afraid,
saw that nothing wrong and right
and songs behind the low-lit shade
Is the world a sadder place
without the words that you evade,
when the ladder fell and shattered
every bar that we had played?
Does it matter in the end,
the sound diminished and decayed,
and your friends grew tired of fantasy
you're wishing they had stayed?
You don't get to say I miss you,
you watched your heroes fade
into the rear view mirror of the villain
you portrayed
Stop the pity party, listen,
you don't get to be dismayed,
you don't get to be emotional,
feel blessed you got it made
The best years of life because
you chose to make a trade,
recollect the days you hoped and you prayed
for this, what is there to miss?
Fade in, fade out,
this hazy dream
Without a direction, roaming aimlessly
There's nothing left back there for me,
pretend it's the end of a made-up story
I know for real...
Those highs, I'll never find another chance
to say thanks for saving my life
I was hopeless, it was spinning,
driving roadless, we were singing
at the top of our lungs
To the numinous, this city never died,
I'll say goodbye to the souls inside
Waking up now to my real life,
let me daydream 'til the next flight
Drowning so long I got older,
now the crowd's gone, is it over?
Is it over?
Thank you so much everyone!
Thank you! Thank you!
Oh my gosh, all the hearts and the claps
in the chat! I saw so many people
being so supportive in the chat, and you guys
are amazing and I love you guys so much!
Thank you so much for being my fans,
honestly, it means the world to me.
And um, and I have some other things
to show you as well.
My birthday merch! Of course I made
goods for you guys, I wanted to make
some really cool merch for my birthday
as well, for my amazing Dead Beats.
So let's go ahead and show them!
Alright, first of all we've got a beautiful
illustration by Nardack to show off the
release of my birthday celebration merch.
We've got a birthday voice and four merch items.
We have a Dead Beat honorary sweater,
my favorite wine glass for konbini wine,
and a "So Gorgeous Your Eyes Will Melt Out
of Your Skull Unalive" poster, and a Holo
Classic Unalive Album Vinyl. And of course,
if you buy everything together
you get a printed letter.
次に行きますね。これは日本語の説明です。
色々ありますよね。
Let's move on. This is the Japanese
explanation. There are various things.
買ってくださいね。よかったらどうぞどうぞ。
Yeah!
Please buy them. If you'd like,
please do. Yeah!
So, uh, we have many, many things here.
色々あるよ。
There are various things.
First of all, we have a Dead Beat sweater.
I designed that skull, I made that skull. Um,
I found a skull, I looked at a skull
and I drew a skull. And then I wrote
"Dead Beat" over it. Um, so hopefully you
feel cool and chill wearing this.
It's a one size fits all, very, very big
sweater. Big comfy cozy sweater.
Then we've got a beautiful wine glass with
a little gradation at the bottom. You can
enjoy your konbini wine with, um, a little
bit of gold Mori encrusted on top of it,
so I hope that you'll enjoy that. And we have
a beautiful poster designed by Ray,
who made my album jacket for Unalive,
my first solo album.
It's the alter version of Calli from the 'UnAlive' MV...
...and it is super amazing. It's the same size as the Your Mori one, so it's super big.
And it's gonna look beautiful on your wall, so I hope you guys will get it.
I'm looking forward to getting a bunch of them and just putting them all over my house.
Then we also have the UnAlive album vinyl. Right now it looks like it's just front and back...
...but it's actually a six-panel vinyl album. So you fold it out...
...and you get to see all of Rei's beautiful artwork in beautiful six-panel glory.
So it's in the same format as the Your Mori album.
Everything can be bought individually this time. And uh, yeah.
If you buy everything together, you get a special printed letter from me with some choice words from your boy and also a signature.
So yeah, here's the sweater. Check it out, front and back.
On the back, you got my little Calliope Mori logo crest at the top.
I designed this skull myself, looking to the side over there.
It's got a really cool neck. Uh, let's go next.
And then we've got my wine glass. This is really cool. I can't wait to drink wine out of this.
It's got my signature on it and everything. Beautiful golden gradient at the bottom.
It's really lovely. Next, we've got the poster.
Check this art out. I die every time I look at it. Rei's work is just like a beautiful, beautiful painting.
So I hope that you guys will enjoy having this on your wall. And next, uh... is there a next?
The album, that's right. We've got the vinyl and it includes every single track from the album.
Check it. Um, but like I said, it's a six-panel, so you'll open it up and there'll be more than just a front and back.
And it's really cool. You guys are gonna love it so much. Um, so yeah.
That's all in terms of merchandise. Please look forward to a special letter from me.
It'll be a printed letter from your boy to the Dead Beats who get the full set.
And so yeah, look forward to that please.
楽しみにしてくださいね。
Please look forward to it.
Please look forward to it. Um, and yeah...
I hope you guys enjoyed my birthday party, but I do have one more song.
One more song to sing to you guys. A song that's very close to my heart, about the world that we live in.
Because from now on, I'm gonna be trying my best with Universal and really, really...
...頑張る from here on out.
...try my best from here on out.
There's a world I want to see, and um, and it's really beautiful.
But things right now seem kind of dark and dreary, you know?
It really seems some days like just the worst days are every day, right?
So um, I would like to continue forward singing songs that have some kind of meaning to me.
Whether they be about enjoying yourself and just having fun, wacky and wild fun party songs, or songs about our world.
This song happens to be one of those more emotional ones.
But let's keep moving forward towards the world that we want to see.
Let's go. Scuffed Up Age.
Scuffed Up Age
Lyrics: Mori Calliope, Camellia / Composition: Camellia
Lost in thoughts, a frost-tipped fray of mind
Honest to God, it's just not our time
Promises flawed by cosmic design
これくらい取ってことない、でも涙のあとは消さない
It’s nothing much, but I won’t erase the traces of tears
Coming of age, the stage doesn't light up
Just right away, they told us it might've
夢はもう諦めました
I’ve already given up on dreams
Cynical mindset, why’d you try? Why not give up and play the bad guy?
分かってるさ
I know it
胸が涙で濡れながら
While my chest gets wet with tears
あなたの元へ急ぐのなら
If I hurry to where you are
崩れ落ちそうな体、抱きしめながら
While hugging my body that seems about to collapse
We choose to know
The struggles of this scuffed up age we’re living in
だからもう
So already
火蓋を切ってこう
Let’s start the fire
この夜は結構似合ってる、あなたのドレス
This night suits your dress quite well
それでも
Even so
あなたは絶対に離さないで、ねえ
You, please never let go, okay?
Can't find a reason to stay, some botched world led astray
Once trusted left to decay
We choose to go on anyway
Lost in thoughts of all with change in pace
Allies and friends hide in more than one face
Not really surprising, why are you compromising?
Horizons and friendships like life’s in the night sins,
Back, so what are you prioritizing?
You are sick of crying?
See I don’t buy it.
But here we are, hanging on, fighting strong, despite it.
儚い冗談は消し切れない
Fleeting jokes can't be completely erased,
目を閉じてしまいたい
I want to close my eyes,
くらい 暗い 空
to the point it's dark, a dark sky.
This cynical mindset why’d you try?
Why not give up and play the bad guy?
分かってないんだ
You just don't understand.
誇りにまみれの街で
In a city covered in pride,
あなたのため生き抜け
live on for your own sake,
私の微かな火で
with my faint light,
照らしたいだけ
I just want to light the way.
We choose to know
the struggles of this scuffed up age
We’re giving it goshani
よかったね
That’s good.
Be real it hurts to grow
Believing in a world of hate is overrated
今でも
Even now,
あなたは美しいのだから
because you are beautiful.
Must be something surreal
and listless dream we can’t heal
This rusty world wound up real
Still want to love the way it feels
May not the city feels that sure, but like
the lights and sights and sounds are treasures.
こんな世界に
In a world like this,
抗って歩く
fighting as I walk,
力なんて
such power,
私にはないけど
I don't have it, but...
Face up this world
can’t kill that peace
So why don’t we turn this scuffed up page
We’re writing in
こんな世界じゃ
In a world like this,
Be real I think we know
この夜明けは is rarely fair
this dawn is rarely fair
Decide your fate
だから
So,
あなたを放してしまわないで
don't ever let go of yourself.
Hey
Tomorrow’s a brand new day
Like all those mistakes
Pass through this rather ruthless… it might be
Rain the question is
Will you bear that pain?
What’s your reason on the stage?
This shining world let us stray
Won't leave it all to decay
I choose to love it anyway
Oh-oh-oh...
We choose to know
the struggles of this scuffed up
page we live in
So don’t give in
Mori Calliope x 星街すいせい 「CapSule」 streaming now!
Mori Calliope x Hoshimachi Suisei 「CapSule」 streaming now!
Mori Calliope
Excuse me, but could you please RIP?
ごめん、失礼しますが、RIP♡
Sorry, excuse me, but please RIP♡
Mori Calliope
Major Debut
えー、みなさん、
Uh, everyone,
You got the rest.
Mori’s in the building
so you know you’re already dead.
Major 1st EP SHINGAMI NOTE シニガミの音 07.20 release from UNIVERSAL MUSIC
Major 1st EP SHINGAMI NOTE / The Sound of the Shinigami 07.20 release from UNIVERSAL MUSIC
...and
07.21.2022
07.21.2022 at Toyosu PIT Solo concert Coming soon...
Why are you still here?
Why are you still here? Go check out the Capsule MV!
It's happening in five minutes!
Five minutes on my channel, go!
Go, go, go, now! Go watch the MV!
Go watch the Capsule MV!
Goodness gracious, bye! Go, go, go, go, go!
Why are you still here? Go!
3D BIRTHDAY CONCERT ...WITH HUGE NEWS
ライブ中に重大告知あり！
Major announcement during the live!