(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Dear Novelites,
I'm sorry to have left suddenly.
Trust me, I didn't want to,
but hopefully I'll be back soon.
If I'm not though, then you deserve to know what happened.
Remember when I mentioned those unsettling dreams I've been getting?
I'm just in this courtyard, but
everything feels off when I'm there.
Like, imagine if you lived your whole life underwater
and then one day you were on the surface.
There's something alien about that place.
And when Dream Me is there,
I'm filled with a sense of being trapped.
It builds and...
well, lately I keep ending up in that courtyard every time I dream,
which has made it hard for me to fall asleep.
I was hoping the dreams would fade
so I could continue with my normal routine.
But since then, they've only grown in intensity.
Finally, I just couldn't take it anymore.
I'd seen that distant castle in my dreams enough times
to be able to write a detailed description of it.
When I did some research,
I found a place just like it in the real world, so I have to go there.
It might seem crazy, but there's something in the corner
of my mind that's pulling me towards it.
And I think if I do it, the dreams will finally stop.
Sorry again for not telling you how bad things have gotten.
The truth is, it wasn't something I wanted to deal with.
I wanted our time together to be fun and full of smiles,
tangents, multiple tangents, non-stop tangents,
and this just kept getting in the way.
So, I'm going to take care of it
and then go back to my happy sugar life.
So, yeah. See you soon!
Present Day
Well, this is the place.
Come on, Shiori. Get this over with
and then you can go back to them.
Huh?
Sigh.
Here goes nothing.
Huh?
What is this place?
Ah? What?
Hey! You! Get back here!
It's just gone now, I guess.
At least it's a nice place.
I was expecting something scary.
It's not too bad.
Then again, I hate the sun.
Got some pretty flowers over there.
Some pretty butterflies.
I wonder who takes care of these though.
Someone has to be a gardener here, right?
He got a big giant castle. Nice.
Wow.
I wonder if that place is inhabited. Hmm.
If not, I'm gonna take that place.
Oh. I feel a lot more complete too, thinking about it.
A little bit more fluid in my motion.
Ah...
Thankfully no one's here to see this.
Huh.
For some reason, my heart feels funny.
It's acting weird.
Not sure why.
I think... not crap.
I think... I think I'm breaking down!
ガ
Lyrics • Music: 鬱P
Moth
Lyrics • Music: Utsu-P
You are blind, have no blood
Just consume soon, soon, soon
You don't know about me, you, you, you
あたし蛾だと知りゃ皆嫌うが あの蝶と何が違う?
If you knew I were a moth, you'd all hate me
But how am I different from that butterfly?
あたし蛾だと知らず皆ガサツに 繭を開く
Not knowing I'm a moth, you all crudely
Open up the cocoon
頭ちゃらんぽらん 下手具不乱不乱
宵のまにまに 裾絡み合い
Empty-headed, staggering about
In the depths of the night, our hems intertwining
蝶々の不乱不乱 闇雲喰らう喰らう
飛んで火に入った 数の自慢ばっか
A butterfly's wild dance, devouring blindly
Just boasting about how many flew into the fire
きれいな羽だけを欲しがってる 撒き散らすscaleは見ない
You only want the beautiful wings
You don't look at the scales I scatter about
You are blind, have no blood
Just consume soon, soon, soon
You don't know about me, you, you, you
ああどうせ 自分一粉 自分一粉まみれ
Ah, anyway, I'm just covered
in my own dust, my own powder
昆虫の身分一粉 身分一粉でブラドメ
With an insect's status, I'm brand-named
by this powder, this status
「あんた蛾なのに頑張っててエライエライ」
"You're doing so well for a moth, good girl, good girl"
「だけど蛾のくせにハッピーそうで不快不快」
"But you look so happy for a moth, how disgusting"
切り抜き動画で孵化を観 感動して動画を消し 颯爽と過ごして
Watching the hatching in a clip, being moved,
then closing it and moving on briskly
正義の瞬間だけしかいらんらん 感傷の涙に溶かしたバイバイ
Only wanting the moments of justice
Good-bye, dissolved in sentimental tears
数あるペインペイン 奴らへの隠蔽隠蔽
生々しさは綺麗にさっぱりバーリーナイト
Endless pain, concealing it from them
All the rawness wiped clean on this burly night
きれいなハンディだけを欲しがってる 実際は違っても美談
They only want the beautiful handicaps
A moving tale, even if the reality is different
You are blind, have no blood
Just consume soon, soon, soon
You don't know about me, you, you, you
嗚呼 所詮 偏見過度の嫌い 過度の美化でパスだね
Ah, in the end, it's just hatred from prejudice
And a pass given by excessive glorification
こちらの身分差分 身分差分でブラドメ
With this status difference, I'm brand-named
by this status, this difference
Why don't you wanna be a moth?
(ちょうちょよちょうちょ 息の根とまれ)
Don't you wanna be a moth?
Why don't you wanna be a moth?
(Little butterfly, little butterfly, stop your breath)
Don't you wanna be a moth?
モスは火に…
Moth to the flame...
Don't you wanna be a moth?
Like a moth...
モスは火に…
Moth to the flame...
Don't you wanna be a moth?
Uh...
Where am I?
Hello?
Anyone here?
Really? Just me...
...in this Halloween-looking town.
Feels a lot different though.
Feeling a little bit more... more powerful, actually.
Hehe!
Even my eyes are glowing a lot more brighter than usual.
Ooh! Look at my shoes.
I can stomp a little bit better now, too.
And my skirt...
I feel like it has a lot more bounce to it.
Hehe!
Ah! I'm feeling great.
But what is this place?
There's eye flowers around here.
You guys look a lot like my Novelites, huh?
My little inky babies.
What else is around here?
Oh!
There's a bookshelf over there.
I guess if I'm hungry, I can eat something here.
Let's see... what do you have?
Eeny meeny miny moe...
...maybe I'll eat you later.
Ooh! A wonderful, glorious castle over there.
It's quite pretty.
And a round, spectacular moon.
Maybe it's the end of the world here. Who knows?
月が綺麗。
The moon is beautiful.
I'm not sure what I'm doing here, though.
I feel like there's something missing.
What's this?
Shiori Novella walked towards the table and examines the weird grooves in it.
She wonders if this could be the key to freeing her from this strange world she's found herself in.
Rissa, are you stalking me again?
Hiya darling! Don't mind me...
...I'm just narrating for you.
What do you mean by narrating, huh?
It's this new side hustle we all got.
We?
The pay is really good!
Yeah! Can you do something please?
You know, so then we can narrate it?
Yeah, pretty please!
We're getting paid by the word, you know.
Uhh...
They have some cue cards we can read too, if you want to hear them.
Yeah! Why don't I read you one now?
This one says, 'Shiori seems concerned...'
...that she can't silence the voices in her head.'
Oh, sorry Shiori. Are we being too loud?
Yeah, there's this thing called a mute button.
I would like you to use it.
You definitely might be going a little loopy, huh?
Oh, I wonder if Shiori's mind created us to protect itself.
Wait, but if we're made up...
...will we still get paid?
Ugh, you guys only care about that?
Ah, don't worry so much about it.
Real or fake, we're your friends, and we're going to help you through this.
And we're not the only ones.
Oh?
What's that supposed to mean?
Is there anyone else here?
You guys!
You came...
Hey! Get off the floor!
No, don't crap over here!
I can't believe it.
No! Jacka!
I can't believe you guys are here.
You're supposed to make this a happy occasion, but I can't believe you start crapping on my floor.
What are you guys doing here, though?
Salt and Pepper.
Shiori followed the Nyakuzas towards the bookshelf.
Books had always been her source of comfort during hard times...
...so returning to them now felt natural to her.
Hey, are there any fan fictions of your oshi in there?
Of course there are!
This is Shiori's bookshelf, after all.
Oh hey! That reminds me of this great manga...
...I read the other day about...
Hey, back to topic, you guys!
By the way, who is your oshi, Shiori?
It's me, right? Me? Me?
What a funny joke. Ahaha!
You know, ever since we started narrating for you, I've had this odd urge to tangent.
I think it's the magic of this realm.
We're all slowly becoming Shioris.
Yeah, how about let's not do that, huh?
It means we better help you out quickly.
I don't think the internet is ready for eight 'bye people'.
Hey, I'm wholesome though!
I'm a wholesome Hololive girl. Hehe!
I can already feel the intrusive thoughts creeping up on me!
Resist, Biboo!
Uh, say, Shiori, I think the Nyakuzas want to tell you something.
What is it?
You guys are pointing at something?
Huh, the Nyakuzas are saying that the books are
full of pages trapped away in your mind.
If you unlock what's within,
you'll be able to go back home,
so go on, take a book.
Already on it!
How about this little one?
Ooh, Shiori grabbed one of the
most powerful books out there.
It contains vast wisdoms about humanity.
But to unlock it, you have to go under
a great and difficult trial.
Was she sure that she was ready?
Kind of trial is this, huh?
Koseki Bijou (古石ビジュ)
Koseki Bijou
Okay, Shiori...
For this book, I want you to act out some memes
or maybe some poses for me.
Come on, even, you know, just two would work.
That's what I think of your memes though, but...
I changed my mind, Shiori. I want you to do three. Yeah.
Three! Three memes!
All right. Just for you,
but you have to be specific.
What do you want me to do?
Hmm, for the first one maybe, you could unleash
your patented Shiori Beam!
My Shiori Beam?
Ah, fine, just for you. Okay.
The... Shiori... Beam!
Oh! Oh, um, ah, ah! That was... that was pretty close!
Uh, can you do it again? Maybe this time shout
something cool like "EXPLOSION!" or something?
I think you're expecting too much from me.
How about we do something else?
Aw, okay fine.
Hmm... Oh, oh, I know!
For the next one, you have a lot of people watching, right?
I want you to rizz up the audience.
Yeah, can you like captivate the camera
and then and then give us your best line?
Yeah, do that. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is this like your secret fantasy, Bibbs?
No, no! Just do it. Just do it. I'm in charge here, okay?
Ah, that's what you want, huh?
But tonight, I'm using you.
Shiori! Bibbs!
What? Wow!
Are you okay there, my girl?
Yeah, yeah, I'm all good.
You're not supposed to be rizzing the rizz-er,
you're supposed to be rizzing everybody else!
But she's always rizz'd, though.
I'm... I'm sure everybody is blushing now, right?
That was... that was pretty good.
Oh well, okay. I have a third one for you. Are you ready?
Sure, just for you.
Okay, for this last one, I want you to pretend
that the darkness is consuming you
and you're in danger,
and the only thing that will save your life
is if you hit the biggest dab ever.
Ah, the things I do for love. Okay. How's this?
Dab!
Shiori! Wow!
That was weak. That's not fighting for your life,
that's like you're bored. Okay, do it again!
But this time, power, energy!
Powerful dab?
Yes!
Okay. Gotta get all my trauma here. Okay.
Hyuh... Dab!
Ooh! Okay, Shiori, that was pretty good.
Now can you like dab back and forth
like ten times over and over and over again?
Okay, I think that's expecting too much, though.
I think that's enough memes for you, Bibbs.
Through her efforts, Shiori gained two apples
that contain magical powers
from all of her cringe.
Oh, I can make the apples kiss!
All right, now that I have these key items,
I'm gonna head out of here.
All right! Where do I put these apples?
That's not how it works, Shiori.
You're trying to jump ahead,
but you gotta do the trials in order.
Ah, all right. What do?
You need to do all the dabs, okay?
Come on! Go! I'll help you unlock the pink book.
Got it.
Oh fine, even the Nyakuzas want to help.
All right, pink book, let's see.
This one!
What's this book?
Nyakuza... Hmm, they say that that's the
"Book of Playtime," which is my favorite!
All you have to do is juggle the apples.
If you say so!
PLAY TIME (プレタイム)
PLAY TIME
You know, juggling hasn't worked for me in the past.
Uh... let me check what this script says then.
You have a script?
Well, good news.
Please all of them having fun so, even if you don't do it right, it's still good enough.
Huh?
Well, if you're okay with good enough, it's good enough for me!
Alright.
Do your best!
I'll try.
Alright, let's go! Oh!
Hah! Oh, it's not too bad!
Ah! Oh! Whoa!
Spinning and juggling!
Yeah, you like that? You're getting entertained, aren't you?
You're getting best!
Yeah!
Are you sure you weren't born to do this?
Oh, you think I was born to be a clown?
I'm not saying you're a clown, you're Shiori!
Oh, so I'm not funny enough for you now, huh?
How long do you want me to do this for?
Oh, that's good enough! Oh, my luck ran out.
Uh... Alright, let's see what we got.
Whoa!
Ooh!
Huh!
Huh, it looks like you're gearing up, huh?
Because... if there's an RPG section of the trial, then maybe you can use that pot as your helmet?
It does come with a plus three to magic.
Hah! Oh!
Where does it say that, Bijuu?
Yeah!
Whoa, Shiori! You're definitely equipped then, huh?
You just want me to look stupid!
Hey!
Not like that, you know? This way you'll be ready just in case there's a boss fight!
Ugh...
Fine!
I'm only doing this because of love! Ha!
Like this?
Shiori apparently puts the cauldron on her head.
It grants her the power of... I don't know, mild neck pain probably.
Shiori, is wearing that helping?
No, but I feel kind of funny.
Uh, maybe you should try and be Shiori beam, no just to be sure.
Come on Moco-chan, don't tease Shiori.
The script doesn't say anything about a boss fight or Shiori wearing the cauldron! Hah!
Shiori will... remember this!
Alright, what do I do now?
Oh, the Nyakuzas say that you can use the cauldron to unlock the Blue Book of Responsibilities.
All you need to do to complete that task is make us an apple pie.
I'm sorry, you want me to make an apple pie with these?
Mhm!
Uh...
Alright.
Now what book is this?
Oh!
Check this out.
Hey, just wondering but, who wrote your script?
Well, I don't know. I guess it could have been anyone really. Anyway...
Where was I?
Oh, here! After the Nyakuzas' display of awesome magical abilities...
...the likes of which no other creatures could ever dream of attaining...
...Shiori took the greatest spoon ever crafted and used it to stir the apples.
The spoon? Why is it so big?
Hey, I could probably bonk you guys with this.
No bonking, please.
Oh, fine.
I'll just use it for spoon things.
Just like that! Alright. Think this will actually make apple pie?
Hah! Yah! Hah!
Looks good!
Alright, let's see what's inside then.
Oh!
Hey!
Shiori takes the apple pie.
Meanwhile, her friends who may or may not be imaginary but are definitely very hungry...
...look at the pie with anticipation.
Yeah, can you do us a favor and leave the pie on the table so we can imagine eating it?
Oh, my hungry puppies. I don't think you're allowed to eat apple pie though.
What? No!
Please! Please!
No! Writing is really hard work!
We'll see, we'll see.
Oh...
Alright!
Now that we have that apple pie,
what now?
Shiori put the pie on the table.
Then she thought it would be nice to pour tofu milk for her friends too.
I don't have tofu milk.
What? Are you sure?
I'm very sure that I don't have tofu milk.
Maybe we could just pretend?
Alright.
That's a good idea!
Ah...
It turns out imaginary milk is pretty good.
Ah, give it here! I want it for my imaginary coffee.
Oh, I'll trade you for a slice of the apple pie.
Deal! Shiori, can you give Mococo some pie?
How am I going to give my imaginary friends my imaginary pie?
But you know what? I think a better question would be,
what do I do with this?
Cool! Maybe you're supposed to wield it as your sword?
Like this?
It does come with a plus three to attack.
Seriously, where are you seeing these numbers?
Moco-chan, why would a microphone be her weapon?
Huh? I don't know, but if she's an adventurer, she's gonna need a sword, okay?
Like with the power of music?
Yeah!
But she's not an adventurer in the script.
Well, maybe I want to add my own parts to this script, huh?
Is that really so wrong?
Come on, she wants to go home.
Don't worry, Shiori, I can help you with that.
Why don't you go back to the bookshelf?
At least one person's useful here.
Don't worry, Shiori, this is almost over, I promise.
But first, you need to unlock the Book of Memories.
Do you remember ever getting lulled to sleep by a lullaby when you were a child?
Of course not. I had no childhood.
Oh, well...
To unlock the powers of the final book, you need to take the microphone and sing the Nyakuza to sleep.
You've got this, okay?
Alright. I'll do my best.
Nerissa Ravencroft / - Advent -
アブノーマリティ・ダンシンガール / Lyrics・Music: ぐりり
Abnormality Dancing Girl / Lyrics・Music: Guriri
いつもどう頑張って
No matter how hard I always try,
努力をしたとこで
no matter how much effort I put in,
指し示されるは平均値
all that's shown is the average value.
やってられないよ
I can't take it anymore.
くだらない評価に
By these worthless evaluations,
踊らされてばかり
I'm just being toyed with.
もう嫌になっちゃったこの人生
I've grown to hate this life.
なら生まれ変わろうか
So, shall I be reborn?
「異常」が胸を埋め尽くして
"Abnormality" fills my chest completely,
普通じゃない自分になるの
and I become someone who's not ordinary.
自問自答繰り返し手に入れたの
Repeating self-questioning, I've obtained
新しいワタシを
a brand new me.
ほら見てよ
Look here,
ほら触れたよ
look, I've touched it.
凡庸な服を脱ぎ捨て去って
Throwing away these mediocre clothes,
今サナギから蝶になるの
I'm now turning from a chrysalis into a butterfly.
ありのまま全て見せつけて
Showing off everything just as it is,
冷めきった舞台 演者はいない
on this chilled stage where there are no performers.
ならステップ刻んで One Two Three
Then carving out steps, one, two, three.
踊らされるんじゃない 踊るのよ
I'm not being toyed with, I'm dancing.
さあ さあ さあ 狂って
Now, now, now, go crazy!
狂って
Go crazy!
「普通」が呪いをかけてきて
"Ordinary" casts a curse on me,
「異常」に憧れたの
and I longed for "abnormality".
異論 持論に興味などないから
Since I have no interest in objections or personal opinions,
もう鍵をかけて
lock it up already.
「好き」「嫌い」を通り越して
Going beyond "like" and "dislike",
「異常」に恋焦がれていたの
I was yearning for "abnormality".
歪んだ愛の成れの果て創られた
Created as the end result of a distorted love,
新しいワタシを
a brand new me.
ほら見てよ
Look here,
ほら触れたよ
look, I've touched it.
凡庸な服を脱ぎ捨て去って
Throwing away these mediocre clothes,
今サナギから蝶になるの
I'm now turning from a chrysalis into a butterfly.
ありのまま全て見せつけて
Showing off everything just as it is,
冷めきった舞台 演者はいない
on this chilled stage where there are no performers.
ならステップ刻んで One Two Three
Then carving out steps, one, two, three.
踊らされるんじゃない 踊るのよ
I'm not being toyed with, I'm dancing.
さあ さあ さあ 狂って
Now, now, now, go crazy!
狂って
Go crazy!
暗い部屋
A dark room.
1人きり
All alone.
鏡の前
In front of the mirror.
午前0時
12:00 AM.
「アナタ誰」
"Who are you?"
「ワタシ誰」
"Who am I?"
問い掛けど返事は無かった
I asked, but there was no reply.
狂え
Go crazy.
狂え、狂え、狂え
Go mad, go mad, go mad
ほとばしるさ
It's gushing out
新しいワタシを
My new self
ほら見てよ
Look, look at me
ほら触れてよ
Look, touch me
透明な服で着飾って
Dressing up in transparent clothes
今サナギから蝶になるの
Now turning from a chrysalis into a butterfly
ありのまま全て見せつけて
Showing everything exactly as I am
熱狂の舞台 演者はいない
A stage of frenzy, there are no performers
ならステップ刻んで
Then keep the step
One, two, three 踊らされるんじゃない
One, two, three, I won't be made to dance
踊るのよ
I'll be the one dancing
さあ、さあ、さあ
Come on, come on, come on
「異常」が胸を埋め尽くして
Abnormality fills up my chest
普通じゃない自分になるの
I'll become a version of me that isn't normal
歪んだ愛の成れの果て 創られた叶わぬ恋
The wreckage of distorted love, a created unrequited love
「異常」「異常」が胸を埋め尽くして
Abnormality, abnormality fills up my chest
普通じゃない自分になるの
I'll become a version of me that isn't normal
自問自答 繰り返し 手に入れた
Repeatedly questioning myself, I've obtained...
新しいワタシを
...my new self
That wasn't a lullaby!
Eh? Are you sure?
I'd give anything to be back in the library.
What do you mean? I fall asleep to that song all the time!
Oh! Well, it looks like it worked anyway!
You have the last item!
Oh?
Oh nice! The beautiful purple heart!
But what do I do with this now?
I think the Novelites are telling you to put the items in their slots on the table.
Ah, なるほど。All right, let's put this over here...
Ah, I see. All right, let's put this over here...
And then we got the microphone here.
And then last but not least, we got...
And here's my cauldron!
Uh, was something supposed to happen now?
I think so! Mokoko?
Ha! Ha! You did it Shiori!
Now all the books in your archive have been activated!
And you can go home!
Yes!
Oh! Oh!
Those books have unlocked the power of our friendship!
With all of us working together, we'll be able to reopen the portal!
We work together? I think I did everything.
And then, Shiori approached the archway...
...eagerly awaiting the moment when the combined strength of all of her friends would cause the portal to reactivate.
Oh! So I can, I can go home now, right?
Uh... that's weird. The power of friendship usually works.
Eh?
I know, right? Maybe after all this soul searching...
...maybe we're really not friends, huh?
Maybe she needs to find an item to give her a plus three to the power of friendship?
But what item? I think I used everything!
Why not check the cue cards instead? Oh, let me look them over.
I hope it helps. I don't want to be stuck here.
Mokoko! It says here that...
...no matter how hard Shiori wanted to, she can't move backward.
Eh?
Sorry, that wasn't very helpful after all.
So what you're telling me is, I'm gonna be stuck in this Halloween-ish world, right?
Yeah.
Don't worry Shiori, we're still here for you. Maybe there's a silver lining in all of this.
Okay, but I'm talking to a rock, two dogs and one bird.
Well, when you put it like that...
...maybe this isn't so great.
But this is just the start of this world!
I bet if you keep moving forward, you'll discover that it's not as scary a place as it looks now!
Yeah, that's true!
Plus you've gained a whole new dimension, and yeah it's different, but it might be good, right?
Eh, I don't know. I mean, I look great.
But I still like the old me.
You're still the old you too, you know? You just got extra stuff now...
...and you're on the next part of your story.
Yeah, I guess you do have a point.
But you know, I wanted my character arc to be done.
Sometimes I like having things stay the way they are.
Is that really all you want?
Well, duh.
But if all the pages in your book just repeated over and over, you know, it'd get pretty boring, right?
And even if it didn't, moving forward is how we grow.
Yeah, and how we find new games to play, or memes to make!
And how we gain new friends! We would have never met in the first place had we not taken a chance on change.
A new story would be boring without us, right?
I guess. I mean, it's great having you guys as friends, and have the Novelites to keep me company.
But you know, sometimes I just want to look back too. And if this is my book, then I should be able to decide what happens, right?
I want to go at my own pace.
Hey Shiori, what's that on the bookshelf?
Huh? More books?
What's this?
Oh!
Oh, wow!
Oh...
Hang on, there's a cue card I'm supposed to read.
Well, hopefully this one's a good one.
Okay, well... it says,
“Don't worry Shiori, while your power will continue to grow...”
“...and your journey will take you to realities as of yet unbeknownst to humanity...”
“...as long as you have my bookmark, you will be protected.”
“Please use it as your link to the past and your guide to the future.”
Mmm.
Hey, I didn't see that card earlier.
And whose bookmark is that? Where was it?
I don't know!
I just looked away and then when I looked back, suddenly it was there in front of me.
But what do I do with this?
I think the Nyakuzas want you to put the bookmark in the archway.
Ah!
Maybe like... like this?
Oh! It worked!
The Nyakuzas say that thanks to the bookmark, the portal's been opened permanently.
You can go back home, but the 3D world will stay available to you.
They want you to know that this reality is so much bigger than just this one place.
There's a lot to see and archive here.
And when you're done with this reality, there are even more places for you to explore.
It looks like your character arc is just beginning.
But don't worry, whenever you need us, we'll be here to help, Shiori.
Alright!
Whoa!
See ya suckers!
Bye Shiori! See ya!
レイニーブーツ
Rainy Boots
レイニーブーツ 代わりに溺れて
Rainy boots, drowning instead
行けないところまで哀しみを弾くだけ
Just repelling sadness to a place I can't go
レイニーブーツ 跳ねた言葉を
Rainy boots, words that splashed
踏み締めた音に乗って 心まで踊りたいの
Riding the sound I stepped on, I want my heart to dance
雨上がり哀しいにおいの街
A city with a sad smell after the rain
雲をかきわけたお日様が
The sun that pushed through the clouds
眠気交じりで溜まった涙を見ている
Is watching the accumulated tears with a sleepy gaze
雨上がり正しい通り道
The correct path after the rain
足元は湿って危ないわ
It's wet and dangerous underfoot
ぬかるみにハマらないよう注意して
Be careful not to get stuck in the mud
お気に入りの靴の身代わりになって
Sacrificing my favorite shoes
あなたの言葉を弾いてみせるよ
I'll repel your words
遅れたバスに乗りたくないなら
If you don't want to get on the late bus
溜まった涙が跳ねる音のリズムに乗って行け
Go along with the rhythm of splashing tears
レイニーブーツ 代わりに溺れて
Rainy boots, drowning instead
行けないところまで哀しみを弾くだけ
Just repelling sadness to a place I can't go
レイニーブーツ 跳ねた言葉を
Rainy boots, words that splashed
踏み締めた音が鳴って 心まで無敵
The sound I stepped on rings out, my heart is invincible
ジャンプ ジャンプ なんて出来ない
I can't jump, jump
地球にいじわるされて捕まれているの
The Earth is being mean and holding me back
ステップ ステップ ちょっとむずい
Step, step, it's a bit hard
雨の中転ばぬように静かに踊るの
Dancing quietly so as not to fall in the rain
雨上がり水溜まった道
The road is puddled after the rain
どんだけ深く沈んでいける？
How deep can I sink?
降ったり止んだり忙しないね
It's restless with rain falling and stopping
履かなくても大丈夫な人もいるけど
Some people are fine without wearing them, though
梅雨の救世主になって
Become the savior of the rainy season
あなたの言葉で遊んでみせるよ
I'll show you how I play with your words
満員電車は曇ってやばいから
The crowded train is foggy and awful
溜まった涙が跳ねる音のリズムに乗ろう
Let's ride the rhythm of the sound of splashing tears
レイニーブーツ 代わりに溺れて
Rainy boots, drowning instead
見えないところまで哀しみを弾くだけ
Just repelling sadness to an invisible place
レイニーブーツ 跳ねた言葉を
Rainy boots, words that splashed
踏み締めた音に乗って 心まで踊りたい
Riding the sound I stepped on, I want my heart to dance
ジャンプ ジャンプ なんて出来ない
I can't jump, jump
この先道悪い慣れてるあたしに任せて
The road ahead is bad, leave it to me who's used to it
ステップ ステップ ちょっとむずい
Step, step, it's a bit hard
雨の中汚れぬように静かに歌うの
Singing quietly so as not to get dirty in the rain
雨の中汚れぬように静かにうたう
Singing softly as if not to get dirty in the rain
ジャンプ　ジャンプなんて出来ない
Jump, jump, I can't do that
地球にいじわるされて掴まれているの
The earth is being mean and holding me back
ステップ　ステップちょっとむずい
Step, step, it's a bit hard
雨の中転ばぬように静かに踊るの
Dancing softly as if not to fall in the rain
Hah... Give me a few minutes.
Hah... Hah... Wow.
Dancing in the rain is pretty fun.
But you know, my boots feel all gross now.
I think they're covered in water and stuff. Ew.
Need to shake the droplets off.
And you know what?
My jacket makes me feel gross too.
I think it's time we take it off!
Oh my! Oh!
Wow!
What am I showing?
Oh no, my arm!
This arm!
The other arm!
Oh no, what am I doing?
Oh, it feels a little bit better now.
It's a lot less wet.
So, whoo!
Oh, this place is a lot prettier now.
I can see the stars everywhere.
It's a lot better than being in the other world with the voices in my head.
When you hear nothing but "op"
and "pow"
and "let's rock," it gets a little tiring, to be honest.
Hah, it's peaceful.
Even see some beautiful flowers.
They look like they're glowing. Oh!
We should give a congratulations to whoever the gardener is.
Hmm, I wonder what kind of flowers these are.
They're blue and pink.
Meh, could be any flower.
Ta-da-da-da.
I wonder if I can take some.
Hehehe.
Oh, and it looks like the castle is...
Oh, it has a lot of lights there.
Maybe they're having a party?
I wonder who lives there.
But if it's empty, it's mine now.
Oh!
You think I could just barge in there?
And be like "Hey you!"
"It's Shiori!"
"Just wandered in here, sorry!"
Ah, but you know what?
If breaking dimensions isn't enough for you...
well, I think it's time to break your bank!
Let's see what we can break your bank with.
With... Oh, what is this?
Shiori Novella Matching Belt
- A matching design with her outfit!
- Size: Belt / Approx. L115cm
Wow!
That looks like a handy-dandy belt!
Oh, it looks kind of similar to my belt here, right?
Oh, it's over here.
Yeah!
So, if you struggle with falling pants,
or you just don't believe in pants...
You believe they don't cover up that shame well enough...
Well, you can get this belt to help with that.
Yeah, it'll put your faith back in humanity
by 0.1%.
Oh! And if...
if that's not enough for you,
well, if you don't want to wear it...
why don't you whip it?
I don't know, I don't care!
But it's a belt!
Oh, and now it's time for some passion Japanese.
シオリ・ノヴェラ おそろいベルト
衣装とおそろい風！
サイズ：全長約115cm
Shiori Novella Matching Belt
In the same style as her outfit!
Size: Total length approx. 115cm
あ、ズボンとパンツが好きですか？
Ah, do you like trousers and underwear?
あ、私のベルト、かわな...りかば...ぶぶ、すみません。
Ah, my belt... sorry.
買いたいです。
I want you to buy it.
ベルト... ベルト欲しいですか？
Belt... Do you want a belt?
かわな...りかば...
(Unclear Japanese)
Please buy!
Please!
お願いします！
ヤゴー、許して、お願いします！
Yagoo, forgive me, please!
私のベルト、Whip it!
My belt, whip it!
あ、お尻が大嫌いですか？
Oh, do you hate butts?
Whip! Whip! Whip! Whip!
あ、パンツ、パンツありますか？
Ah, underwear, do you have underwear?
Oh, belt, belt!
そして、バンザイ！
And then, Banzai!
カンパイ！
Cheers!
ボンカイ？
Bonkai?
ベルタイ！
Belt-ai!
Ai!
あ、私の日本語上手？
Oh, was my Nihongo jouzu?
Hehehe.
It better be!
Oh, but besides that... um,
皆さん、ありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you very much!
Novelites,
thank you for watching
and helping me not perish.
And kaput.
Thanks to you, I now know to throw away
moldy bread and moldy food.
Yeah!
I now know that there's soft cheese...
...and hard cheese...
...and other types of cheese...
...and I just really like to point...
...'cause I'm cheesy.
But yeah, thank you for watching me...
...and supporting me and keeping me company.
Sorry, I've been yelling a lot.
It feels surreal to be here.
そして...皆さん、全部、ありがとうございます。
And... everyone, thank you for everything.
皆さんはとてもかっこいいです。
You are all very cool.
一番です！
You're the best!
But, you know...
I have one more song for you guys.
That's right, the number one.
So, if you don't mind taking a few more minutes...
...to listen to my voice...
...私の声です。
...it is my voice.
Please, please listen.
Or not, I don't know. Okay.
Give me a few seconds, I'm tired.
Okay, here I go.
星を渡る鳥
Lyrics • Music : Nem
The Bird That Crosses the Stars
この空の果てに
At the end of this sky...
昔々こことよく似た
Long, long ago, much like this one,
命に溢れる星があったという
They say there was a star overflowing with life.
人は欲望に溺れやがて
People drowned in their desires, and eventually...
世界は息をするのをやめた
...the world stopped breathing.
長い、長い時が流れ
A long, long time passed...
聞こえたのはあなたが あなたが
...and what I heard was you, was you,
私を呼ぶ声
...calling my name.
私は鳥になり 遠く、遠く 羽ばたいて行く
I will become a bird and flap my wings far, far away.
幾千の星を越え あなたの元へ
Crossing thousands of stars to where you are.
体は燃え尽き 灰になって 消えて行っても
Even if my body burns out, turns to ash and disappears,
心は時を越え 約束の場所へ飛ぶ
My heart will transcend time and fly to the promised place.
自分の姿も思い出せず
Unable to even remember my own form,
微かな自我は誰にも見えず
My faint sense of self invisible to anyone.
永い、永い時が流れ
A long, long time passed...
たどり着いた あなたが あなたが
...and I arrived at the star where you, where you...
待ち続けた星
...kept waiting.
君と僕が生まれた地球
The place where you and I were born,
ここに同じ名前を付けよう
Let's give it the same name here.
二人の心は一つになり光になった
Our hearts became one and turned into light,
全ての命がまた生まれるように
So that all life may be born again.
同じ過ちをもう二度とは犯さないよう
So that the same mistakes are never made again,
私は愛の歌 ここで歌い続ける
I will continue to sing a song of love here.
星を渡る鳥
The Bird Crossing the Stars
Ha ha ha ha ha...
Thank you for the peaceful, fun memories!
May we all find our happiness down the road!
I'm grateful for all your time, kindness, & warmth!
Let's keep doing our best to be kind + to smile ~
3D SHOWCASE