(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
In-Stock Merch
Light Stick / T-Shirt
Made-To-Order Merch
Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand Coaster
Made-To-Order Merch
Tapestry / Acrylic Panel / Mug
Happi
hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live
On the Run!
It's Ollie's holoplus
ZOM-RAID TIME
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while for the start.
Attention For Visitors
In-Stock Merch
Essentials Pack
hololive English 3rd Concert -All for One-
In-Stock Merch
Made-To-Order Merch
Random Button Badge ¥550
Acrylic Stand Coaster (15 Types) ¥1,650
Tapestry ¥3,300 / Acrylic Panel ¥4,400 / Mug ¥2,200
Happi ¥7,480
I am supporting hololiveEN 3rd Concert!
On the Run! hololive English -Advent-
2nd Anniversary Live
It's Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME
The concert will be starting soon. #holoAllforOne
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors:
Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.
In-Stock Merch
Essentials Pack (28 Types) ¥8,800 each
In-Stock Merch: Light Stick, T-Shirt
Made-to-Order Merch: Random Button Badge
Made-to-Order Merch: Acrylic Stand Coaster
Made-to-Order Merch: Tapestry, Acrylic Panel, Mug
Made-to-Order Merch: Happi
I am supporting hololiveEN 3rd Concert!
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait for a while until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors
Essentials Pack
ALL FOR ONE × HYTE
Every order has a chance to get a rare set!
Every order has a chance to get a rare version of the set!
Pre-order today at hyte.co/allforone
WAH! Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening! It's me Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert! I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun sharing all the great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time, but I still get excited every time I spot something WAHnderful on AmiAmi
— it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi on AmiAmi be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you for everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, Thank you AmiAmi!
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
In-Stock Merch: Essentials Pack, Light Stick, T-Shirt
Made-to-Order Merch: Random Button Badge
Made-to-Order Merch: Acrylic Stand Coaster
Tapestry, Acrylic Panel, Mug
Happi ¥7,480
hololive English 3rd Concert: ALL FOR ONE
hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live "On the Run!"
It's Ollie's holoplus: ZOM-RAID TIME
The concert will be starting soon. #holoAllForOne
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.
In-Stock Merch
Made-to-Order Merch
Let's go EN! Let's go EN! Let's go EN!
All for One! All for One! All for One!
ALL FOR ONE!
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
HEY! HEY! HEY! HEY!
Mori Calliope
MYTH
Mori Calliope / Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis
Hakos Baelz
Promise
IRyS / Ouro Kronii / Hakos Baelz
Shiori Novella
Nerissa Ravencroft
Mococo Abyssgard
ADVENT
Shiori Novella / Koseki Bijou / Nerissa Ravencroft
Fuwawa Abyssgard / Mococo Abyssgard
Gigi Murin
Justice
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame / Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen / Raora Panthera
Yeah!
Press up!
Coming closer now!
Turn it up!
Bring it on!
Get down!
Right now!
Fighter!
Fearless!
Step it up, step it up now!
We've got the power, unstoppable, the fire burning up inside so
Nothing breaks us down, no matter what we're gonna break through!
Never stop, gotta keep it going on and on we go crashing into the dark!
And we gon' break the rules, nobody can do what we do!
We about to move, break out the rules now, move into the groove keep it extra cool!
Extraordinary, gotta let 'em know, rock 'n roll, pump it up, break it down let's go our way!
Louder louder to the beat fly higher higher to the sky!
And here we go again, no time to waste, yes this is our heart and mind!
In this reality I heard a whisper...
Calling me! Calling me!
I see it now, we found ourselves at 2AM!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Start again, we're never gonna stop!
何度だって約束響きあっていける
Time and time again, we'll keep resonating our promise.
Hey! Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not here we go, supernatural feel the vibe and find the light!
無限に広がっていくステージ駆けてゼンノウ Sing Along
Running across the infinitely expanding stage, sing along with all your might.
Never stop and taken over, keep it going on and on!
Shout it out and reach out to the moon, not afraid there's nothing left to lose!
Ask us for something more, yes turn it up into the new world!
New world! We are unbreakable now!
We know what's going on, let's take a risk all from head to toe!
Ready or not, level up to one, burn burn burn!
Focus on us, face it step by step, buckle up!
Shout out to the name until the end! Yeah yeah yeah yeah!
In this reality I heard a whisper...
Calling me! Calling me!
I see it now, we found ourselves at 2AM!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Start again, we're never gonna stop!
何度だって約束響きあっていける
Time and time again, we'll keep resonating our promise.
Hey! Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not here we go, supernatural feel the vibe and find the light!
Hold back, won't keep nobody get in the way of us no more!
Lost or right at your revolutionary, hey yo come on get up get up!
Never lose way, invisible, now going higher and higher the energy grows!
Out of control here we go, run on on and level up we're coming out!
La la la... now!
This is us ruling the world! Start again, we're never gonna stop!
何度だって約束響きあっていける
Time and time again, we'll keep resonating our promise.
Hey! Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not here we go, supernatural feel the vibe and find the light!
無限に広がっていくステージ駆けてゼンノウ Sing Along
Running across the infinitely expanding stage, sing along with all your might.
Never stop and taken over, keep it going on and on!
Shout it out and reach out to the moon, not afraid there's nothing left to lose!
Ask us for something more, yes turn it up into the new world!
New world! We are unbreakable, we are unbreakable now!
エッシノモノ
Everything is mine.
ソ、ワタシノモノ
Yes, everything is mine.
セ、ノ、オッ
Ready, set, go!
スベテノザイホウ
All the treasures...
ボロフネニネムル
...sleep in the old ship.
ROCKY-BIJOU!
ARE YOU READY TO ROCK? ONE, TWO, THREE!
沈んだ伝説、呪われた幽霊船に
A sunken legend, on a cursed ghost ship...
続く夜の航路
...the night voyage continues.
そこに何が残る？
What remains there?
回顧、秘めがあるのなら
If there are hidden memories of the past...
...じゃないでしょ
...it isn't, is it?
無法な火を
The lawless fire
仇なす手よ
The hand that brings harm
命を燃やして 狡猾に かざしてやろう
Burning life, let's hold it up cunningly
止まない雨の弾丸で
With the bullets of unending rain
写し程 この身を焦がす
As much as it reflects, it burns this body
底無の火の花 躍る 色彩
Bottomless flower of fire, dancing colors
蒼乱 崩落的なのなら
If it's chaotic blue, collapsing
私のもの そう 私のもの
Mine, yes, mine
唄ってみせろ
Show me by singing
命の証を
The proof of life
あなたと求める 全てを
Everything I seek with you
輝く船錆びついて
The shining ship is rusted
それでも尚 闇を掴むなら
Even so, if you still grasp the darkness
泡沫と共に 沈め
Sink along with the bubbles
海の暇 一人風に吹かれ
At the leisure of the sea, blown by the wind alone
誇る邪魔な 海賊の火を
The proud, bothersome pirate's fire
風は笑う
The wind laughs
満月の金魚すくい
Goldfish scooping under the full moon
七つの海を泳ぐ
Swimming the seven seas
宝物盗み共
Fellow treasure thieves
踊りと身を狙う
Aiming for dance and body
愚か者身を追い出す
Chasing out the fools
宝探し道連れを
Companions on a treasure hunt
胸に踊る この魂の群れ
This crowd of souls dancing in the chest
影の底で 忍び寄る 絶望の渦
The vortex of despair creeping at the bottom
丸で 歌の閉じた箱
Like a closed music box
食べちゃえば 諦めちゃえば
If I eat it, if I give up
悪の巣穴 逃げられるのに まだ捕まえてる
Could escape the den of evil, yet I'm still caught
欲が重いから
Because greed is heavy
私のもの そう 私のもの
Mine, yes, mine
自分自身を 信じ込ませた 嘘で
With the lies I made myself believe
縛り続けてたって 気付いた
I realized I had been keeping myself bound
蜘蛛の手口 虎の世の回帰
Spider's trick, return of the tiger's world
目を醒ませ あなたの悪夢から
Wake up from your nightmare
連れ出す気分よ
It's like I'm taking you away
証して
Prove it
私のもの また 私のもの
Mine, again mine
欲望のまま 写し羽を纏っても
Even if clad in mirror wings as desired
枯れない 魂までは
Until the soul that does not wither
虹の結末 永遠の媚薬を
The rainbow's end, the eternal aphrodisiac
そんな幻 そう感じていましょう
Let's feel such an illusion
鳴らして 証は 踊る さあさ 行こう
Ring it out, the proof is dancing, now let's go
余計な 殻を剥いて
Peeled off the extra shell
威圧を纏わせた船
The ship clad in coercion
暇な時だけ 残していく
Leaving only when at leisure
神はもう いない
God is no longer here
さらば
Farewell
Hello New York!
Are you ready to put your hands up?
I want to see all your hands up!
And let's go!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
(Everyone!)
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
(Together!)
右にも左にもなくグーグー
Neither left nor right, Goo-Goo
手にも足にもなむいずズンズン
Neither hands nor feet, Namu-Izu Zun-Zun
飯は食わなば 寝る寝る寝ばな
If I don't eat, I gotta sleep, sleep, sleep
Time sleep...
Go go go!
Dance it down!
燦々進化進行
Brilliant evolution in progress
暗渠あり チームはショボどこ
Underground drain, where's the team poor?
いい感じ そうそう出発進行
Feeling good, yes yes, departure in progress
去る者追わざる パッパッピープー
Don't chase those who leave, Pa-Pa-Pi-Pu
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
(Come on everybody!)
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
欲しも おわほら これだろうさあ
Even if I want it, look, this is it, right?
What what what what what? (Wooh!)
脳内全開やっぱポポポレ
Brain wide open, as expected Po-Po-Po-Re
笑ってないで おどれば アイアイアウー
Don't just laugh, if you dance, Ai-Ai-Awoo
範と開けば 堂々待っての
If I open the model, waiting proudly...
のまったんだじょ ほらそわそわぜ
Swallowed up, look, so restless
Chai chai chai chai party!
Oh-wa-a-a-i 気分ハイ今度は
Oh-wa-a-a-i, feeling high this time
Oh-wa-a-a-i I'm on high 今度は...
Oh-wa-a-a-i, I'm on high this time...
つながってんだけどこんなんだ 全面MEMEだ
We're connected, but it's like this, full-front MEME
メンツ思いだ 猿・人・ガール
Thinking of the lineup, Ape-Human-Girl
奢ってんだ 働いてんだ 年金なんだ
I'm treating you, I'm working, it's my pension
様子見んな 暇に撃つ 撃つ 撃つ 昨日あ...
Don't just watch, shoot, shoot, shoot in your spare time, yesterday...
乱心だ 人類滅亡
Insanity, extinction of humanity
春夏秋冬AI暴走
All year round, AI out of control
あーもう三次元 躁々景観信号
Ah, already 3D, manic landscape signals
もう指指まで One Two Three All night All night
Down to every fingertip, One Two Three All night All night
おだだんちゃ！
Odadancha!
Okay New York! You're gonna hate me for saying this.
Let's go vintage!
Oh my God, it's my life ようやく死因に辿り着いた
Oh my God, it's my life, I've finally reached the cause of death
ごめんなさい 抜け殻死んで
I'm sorry, my shell is dead
ほらえ ほらほらえ
Look, hey look, hey
Everyone! We're just getting started! So give me your energy! Hai!
Everyone! We're just getting started! So give me your energy! Yes!
Put your hands up! Put your put your hands up!
目も口も ほらこれだろさあな
Eyes and mouth too, look, this is it, right?
Say what! One one one one!
What! What! Let's go!
脳内全開へ やっぱモッパーリー
Brain wide open, after all, it's a party
笑わないで踊れば I I I
If you dance without laughing, I I I
三度開いてドバッとのまったんだじょ
Open three times and splash, swallowed up
ほらそわそわぜ Chai chai chai chai party
Look, so restless, Chai chai chai chai party
Oh-wa-a-a-i 気分ハイ今度は
Oh-wa-a-a-i I'm on high 今度はパンチ
Oh-wa-a-a-i, feeling high this time
Oh-wa-a-a-i, I'm on high, this time a punch
Put your hands up! Put your put your hands up!
Put your hands up! Put your put your hands up! Hands up!
New York! Are you ready for some spice?
Oh no, fell into the abyss unknown
Left me bleeding heartless all alone
Yeah yeah, yeah yeah
No control, yeah yeah
Don't you dare apologize
Turn my back and felt the cold knife
Listen up to tears of mad vice, yeah yeah yeah yeah
Yeah out of time
Way out of line
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye I'll make you cry
I'll make you cry
Tearing it down to just what I want now
Keep calling me a sinner
No I don't think so
Ready-y-y-y-y-ya (Got me twisted)
Ready-y-y-y-y-ya (So obsessed)
Taking the crown now you're calling me king
You're gonna hear the folks sing
Now sing it!
Ready-y-y-y-y-ya (La-la-life's good)
Ready-y-y-y-y-ya (After all)
Don't back it up, don't back it up, keep that aim
I got thoughts that'll drive you insane
Come over if you like, we'll have a lot of fun
But I got a lot of bite, ha!
I do what I want, make sure you don't forget it
An army on my back, damn think I'm just sadistic
Not living in the lie / Or I am the lie
And I want to see the way you bleed
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye I'll make you cry
I'll make you cry
Tearing it down to just what I want now
Keep calling me a sinner
No I don't think so
Ready-y-y-y-y-ya (Got me twisted)
Ready-y-y-y-y-ya (So obsessed)
Taking the crown now you're calling me king
You're gonna hear the folks sing
Now sing it!
Ready-y-y-y-y-ya (La-la-life's good)
Ready-y-y-y-y-ya (After all)
I want it all so give me some more
Flames burn me up down into my core
Oh you wish I'd stay down but then I just rise
You're not my enemy / Baby you're dead to me
Hear my voice screaming out loud now, yeah!
Ah-yi-yi-ya Ah-yi-yi-ya
La la la la la la la
決めて ANYA
Decide it tonight
LOW-YA!
Tearin' it down to just what I wanna
Keep callin' me a sinner
LOW-YA!
Ah-yi-yi-ya Ah-yi-yi-ya
La la la la la la la
LOW-YA!
Takin' the crown, now you're callin' me king
You're gonna hear a monster singin'
Ah-yi-yi-ya Ah-yi-yi-ya
La la la la la la la
LOW-YA!
決めて ANYA
Decide it tonight
La la la la la la la
決めて ANYA
Decide it tonight
(Laughter)
I didn't know I'm cheating on Calli!
IRyS! You're cheating on Calli!
Yeah, didn't you know?
Oh yeah, oh my god!
Wait, we- we're not doing anything wrong!
We're not- we're not doing anything wrong!
No, no, no, no, we were just... hugging as friends.
It was just te-te, te-te.
It was just heartwarming.
Yes. ね？
Yes. Right?
Kikkerikii!
IRyS!
Okay, let's introduce ourselves, yeah?
Yes!
You! Start with the cheater- oh no.
No, cheat! You also cheater!
No, cheat! You're a cheater too!
Okay, go ahead.
Hi! Kikkerikii!
Hi! Uh, I wish I was someone else right now,
but I'm Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth! Yay!
And you?
Uh, hi! It's IRyS from Hololive English Promise.
Can I get a "Hy-RyS"?
Hy-RyS!
Let's go! Thank you!
We just performed a really hype performance...
...of 決めて ANYA!
...of Kimete ANYA!
This is not my first time performing with you on your song.
Yeah, they put us together a lot these days. Kind of a trend.
It is.
Kiara's the trend.
Yay!
I am sure they can't get enough of us, right?
No, of course not!
That's why we're here now, too.
We're spice. We're sexy.
Oh, yes we are!
Of course. Yes we are.
LOL. Well, you know, it's the first MC.
That's right. Which means...
Um, we're gonna do the sad news, right?
Yes! But I want to deliver the sad news!
It's our first time together, so I want to deliver it too!
I want to do it!
Well, in that case, we battle it out!
We're battling it out! In front of all these people?
Yeah, it's no problem. They're gonna cheer for us.
Yeah. When we think of battles, what do we think about?
I think, like, recently, a lot of the EN members
have been, like, doing arm wrestling.
And I'm very well known for being a noodle arm person.
What about you?
I am very strong!
Everyone knows that IRyS is very strong! Yeah, sure.
Well, you know, I usually am left-handed,
but I will use my right hand to give you a chance.
Okay, thank you Senpai!
Okay, okay, okay. I will take that challenge right now!
Let's do this!
Okay, come here. Come here, come here.
Three! Count us down!
Three, two, one, go!
I just beat her! With her non-dominant arm!
Yeah, that was my right hand though. My left hand is my dominant arm.
So, that wasn't completely fair. Let's do another game!
Another game? Yes!
I mean, yeah, that's true, it wasn't fair. In that case, what- what do you have in mind?
There's this game called, uh, like Blue Light Red Light...
No Blue Light. That was Red Light Green Light.
Red Light Green Light. Okay.
Then you perhaps stand on that side,
and I go towards you.
Okay, all right, all right. Gotcha.
Okay, then I- I can win this! I will get you.
I will get you, okay?
Red light... oh, green light!
Oh, sorry, we're starting. We're starting. Okay.
Red light! Green light!
Red light!
Not my butt! Not my butt!
Okay, yay! But that means it's a draw.
A draw? Which means...
We get to say it together!
Oh!
Ahhh!
Perfect ending!
Perfect!
It's not like this was scripted or anything. I swear I actually did it!
Oh, no, no, no, no! The only thing that was scripted was our entrance. That...
Oh, yeah, that.
Yeah, that.
Okay, then let's do it! Let's do this! Okay!
Everybody watching on YouTube...
Mhm.
...are you aware that if you don't have a ticket, you might be not able to watch anymore of this?
What!?
Yes, guys! This is the last of the free part on YouTube!
If you want to watch more, you have to buy the streaming tickets!
They're available in the description and the official website!
Probably down there! Yeah, you can go get the streaming tickets!
Yeah! You would be crying like me...
...until you buy them!
Yes! Do what she says! I recommend it!
Once you buy them, you'll be happy and you'll be able to watch the rest of the concert!
Yes! Yes! Yes! They're saying it too!
Buy it! Buy it!
Besides that, one more thing...
Mhm.
Now that you got your tickets and you're ready to take even more screenshots...
make sure to share them and your thoughts on social media using the hashtag...
...#holoAllforOne! Yes!
So, I think we should also...
Speaking of All for One, I think it's time for us to, you know, say the thing.
Yeah, the thing!
You guys are aware by now, right?
Because of yesterday.
It's called All for One. We say it together.
We say it together, yeah? All of us.
All of us, お願いします！
All of us, please!
Are you in or what? Okay!
All for One! All for One! Okay, okay!
Are you ready? Okay.
Three, two, one...
ALL FOR ONE!
Official Hashtag #holoAllforOne
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part of the show has ended! Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました! ご視聴ありがとうございました!
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.