(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Hello! Hey, everyone!
Yeah, over here! It's me!
It's 3D Biboo! Yay!
Whoa! Woo!
What?
What's wrong?
It's me, Biboo, the Moai.
Yeah, the big Moai in front of you. That's me!
3D Biboo!
Isn't it great?
Aren't I beautiful? Yeah.
What?
Is this not the Biboo you wanted to see?
Hmm...
Maybe if you say please, I'll come out.
Come on.
Okay, there we go.
Kira kira... Koseki!
Kira Kira... KOSEKI!
溶けない sugar
Unmelting sugar
プリズムの魔法
Magic of the Prism
甘い magic
Sweet magic
ふわり漂う時間
Gently drifting time
切れない flavor
Unending flavor
届いたら
If it reaches you
世界中が煌めく New World
The whole world will sparkle, a new world
始まりはドキドキして
Starting with a thumping heart
巡り巡る物語
A story that comes around
幸せを集めて
Collecting happiness
夢の旅をしよう
Let's go on a dream journey
One, two, せーの！
One, two, ready, go!
願うのねえ
I'm wishing, you know
数千億のキセキ届けたい
I want to deliver hundreds of billions of miracles
このときめき永遠
This excitement forever
紡ぐ光プリズムの
Spinning light of the prism
魔法みたい
Like magic
誰だって寂しいそんな夜には
On those nights when anyone feels lonely
見上げた空に無数の宝石
In the sky I looked up at, countless jewels
なんだってできる信じ合うなら
We can do anything if we believe in each other
眩しいほどに煌めく New World
Sparking so bright, a new world
今一緒にワクワクして
Now getting excited together
くるり回る影模様
Round and round, the pattern of shadows
たゆたう波揺られ
Swaying in the drifting waves
ひと休みしよう
Let's take a break
おやすみ
Good night
目が覚めたらほんの少し広がる虹
When I wake up, a rainbow spreads just a little
モノクロに色が咲く
Colors bloom in monochrome
One, two, せーの！
One, two, ready, go!
願うのねえ
I'm wishing, you know
数千億のキセキ届けたい
I want to deliver hundreds of billions of miracles
このときめき永遠
This excitement forever
紡ぐ光プリズムの
Spinning light of the prism
魔法みたい
Like magic
輝きだすあの未来
That future starting to shine
プリズムの魔法
Prism magic
君に
For you
Yay!
Hello, everyone!
Bombijou-ai!
Eh?
Uh oh.
Mmmm, no! Stop!
You're embarrassing me, feet!
Stop that!
Not on 3D! Oh, Biboo...
Nnn... No!
Darn it!
Mmm... Stop!
Okay, okay, we're good. We're good.
No "tink tink" sounds now.
Bombijou-ai!
I'm Koseki Bijou, sparkling gem of Hololive English Advent...
...and today, Biboo's in 3D! Yay!
Wow. But before we get to business...
#Biboo3D, #Biboo3D, #Biboo3D!
Please post any cute pictures or any, uh, reactions...
...to my cute 3D body, okay?
Yeah.
Tada! I'm in full power now!
Hehehe, nothing can limit me!
You've been waiting a long time, huh?
Huh? For me to make these cute poses...
...to make these cute wiggles? Hehehe!
Look at my body. Okay fine, feet.
That's what you wanted, right?
This?
Yeah, well, there you go.
Okay, well...
What do you think? Do you like my place?
I actually left this place before I went to prison...
...so it looks a little different.
Yeah, it looks a little different now.
I guess no one took care of it while I was gone, but isn't it pretty?
Look at all these crystals! I made those.
I made those by the way. I made that one.
And that one. And that one. And that one.
Yeah.
So here, take a look.
Ooh, there's some greenery over there.
There's a giant hole up there, and there, and there...
...but that's okay. There's a tree! Look at that tree.
Cute. Isn't it pretty?
Hehe, I like it so much. Hehehehe.
Pebbles!
Thank you for coming today.
I'm so excited to share with you
everything I have in store.
But the first thing I sang,
did you recognize it?
Obviously you didn't,
because that was my first...
...original song!
プリズムの魔法、
Prism Magic,
or Prisma Magic.
Did you like it?
I'm very proud of it.
And I hope it made you
feel happy and magical.
Mhm, yeah.
Thank you so much for listening.
And I'm so excited to show you
the rest of the 3D showcase.
Yay! Oh!
What's that?
Eh?
Stairs?
Whoa...
...where does that go?
It looks pretty deep.
Eh, what's that?
Eee-ooo-aaa!
Dang it.
Ooooh... Ugh...
Ow, what was that?
Ugh... Oh...
Huh?
Eh?
Where am I?
It's so dark in here. Hello?
Huh?
Oh?
Ooh! What's this?
A crystal? Oh, it's so shiny!
Oh? Boop-boop-boop.
Ooh!
What is this for?
It looks magical.
Huh...
Huh.
Oh.
Oh, what's... oh, what's this?
Uh oh.
I feel like this is something
I'm quite familiar with.
Eh?
Do I walk through it?
I feel like I have to walk through it.
Hmm.
I bet there's something
behind that door.
Let's go find out.
Let's go!
Ooh! Wow!
This place is big.
I wonder what it's for.
Eh?
Why am I holding a staff?
A weapon?
Hmm. I have a bad
feeling about this.
Oh...
Eh?
Why do I hear boss music?
Don't tell me I have to
fight that thing.
I guess I should. Okay.
You got this, Biboo.
You've done this before,
it's just more physical now.
Come at me, bro!
Okay, watch this!
Hah! Pebbles, go!
Yeah!
Okay, I just have to do
that. Okay, okay!
Whoa! Oh!
Go!
Yeah, I'm not scared of you!
Okay, maybe a little bit. Okay!
Heh!
Yeah!
You're too slow! Hahaha!
Try and catch me! Hehehe.
Whoa-da-da-da-da-da! Boom!
Yeah!
Hahaha! More, more, more!
Oh! Ow!
Okay...
Whoa! Hah!
Hup!
Hah!
Nyea!
Whoa! Hah!
Hah! Oh, he's stuck!
He's stuck!
Okay, I think I'm
running low on mana.
Oh, thirsty. Thirsty.
Got it!
Okay, I'm ready for you. I'm recharged.
Here we go, Pebbles!
Why isn't this working?
I'm not doing that much damage.
(Battle cry and death grunt)
GAME OVER BWEH
I died.
I don't know why the Pebbles,
they didn't do that much damage.
Maybe I have to think of something else.
Let me see, let me see if I have anything...
Oh, yeah!
I see. Let's use this.
Okay, I'm ready now.
Round two! Here we go!
Okay, big boss man thing, whatever you are...
I'm back and I got a big weapon this time!
Yeah, I'm not afraid of you!
Yeah, did that hurt?
Oh, did that hurt? Did that hurt?
You're too slow. I'm faster than you!
And then take this!
And then take that!
Oh spooky! Oh boy!
What are you doing?
Opportunity!
Okay, I need to drink.
I have low health.
Okay, I feel better now.
Are you dying yet?
Please die.
Wait, why isn't it doing anything?
(Death grunt)
GAME OVER DANG IT
Dang it! I thought switching builds would work.
Thank you, respawn crystal. I appreciate it.
What should I do now?
I gotta fight that boss.
Oh, I have an idea.
Okay, I'm going to dual-wield this time.
That's going to work. Yeah!
And I'm going to summon my crystals too.
Okay, I'm ready.
One more try, I'm going to beat that boss.
Let's go!
Curse you, big boss man thing!
I hereby vow, you will rue this day!
It is I, Koseki Bijou!
Your fears made rock!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Ugh!
Aaaah!
I'm getting stunned!
Ugh! I understand!
Wait... let me... Ouch! Ouch!
No! No!
Oh come on! Oh dear!
Stop the block! What the...!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Stop that! No!
Ugh... Ha!
No!
Go away! Go away! Ha!
Yeah you don't like that, huh? Huh? Huh?
Get tired! Oh wait, oh he's mad. Oh dear.
Aaaaah! I get it! I get it!
Come here! Hey you!
Over here! Over here! I'm over here! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Aaaaah! Ha!
Heh! Yah! Okay!
Ready? Ha! Yah!
Ha! Boom! Yah!
I won! Let's go!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Eh? Oh!
So finally you're here, you've finally defeated the first boss.
Kaela! What are you doing here?
Too bad for you, I am the real final boss.
Uh oh. Uh oh.
Yes, so if you want to win, you need to defeat me.
Really?
Come at me bro!
Yeah! Mmm!
Wait! Why do you have three health bars?! What the heck?!
Yeah, why not?
Ugh... I'm tired, whatever.
Oh, you're tired? Okay then.
Bra!
オレンジ
Lyrics: 渡邊亜希子 Music: Funta3
Orange
Lyrics: Watanabe Akiko Music: Funta3
眠れない 夜には
On nights when I can't sleep
独りで ため息
I let out a sigh all alone
みんなは どうなの
I wonder how everyone else is doing
なんだか さびしい
I feel somehow lonely
嬉しくない なんてね
I said I'm not happy, but that's a lie
笑うのは やめて
Please stop laughing at me
本当の 私を
It's just that you don't know...
知らないだけだよ
...the real me
広げた 大地に
On the wide-open earth
一つぶの 種
A single seed
寝ころがって
Lying down...
まだ青い
...looking at the still-blue...
空見上げた
...sky up above
オレンジ色に 早く なりたい果実
A fruit that longs to ripen into orange quickly
君の 光を 浴びて
Bathed in your light
理想や 夢は 膨らむばかり
My ideals and dreams just keep on swelling
気づいてよね
Please notice them
オレンジ 今日も 食べてみたけど
I tried eating an orange today too
まだ酸っぱくて 泣いた
But it was still sour, and I cried
私みたいで 残せないから
Because it's like me, I couldn't leave it unfinished
全部食べた
So I ate it all
好きだよ
I love you
泣けるよ
It makes me cry
好きだよ
I love you
似てても 違うよ
Even if they look similar, they're different
マンダリン オレンジ
Mandarin oranges
友達 恋人
Friends, lovers
二人の心も
Even the hearts of the two
傷つきたくない
Don't want to get hurt
私は逃げてた
I was running away
そしたら光も
Then, even the light
差してはくれない
Won't shine on me
奇跡なのにね
Even though it's a miracle
出会いも恋も
Both meeting and love
誰も蕾を
Everyone, the buds...
まだ青い
Are still unripe
右手さえも
Even the right hand
オレンジ色は
The color orange
あの日見た夕焼けを
Reminds me of the sunset I saw that day
思い出させてくれる
It makes me remember
二つの影が
Two shadows
手を繋いでるみたいだった
Looked like they were holding hands
オレンジ いつか
Orange, someday
甘くなるかな
Will it become sweet?
それともしぼんじゃうの？
Or will it wither?
私の未来
My future
知りたくなくて
I didn't want to know
全部食べた
I ate it all
酸っぱい
Sour
好きだけど
I like you, but
泣けるよ
It makes me cry
好きだから
Because I like you
泣けるよ
It makes me cry
オレンジ色に
Into the orange color
早くなりたい果実
The fruit that wants to turn early
君の光を浴びて
Bathing in your light
理想や夢は
Ideals and dreams
膨らむばかり
Just keep swelling
気づいてよね
Please notice
オレンジ 全部
Orange, all of it
食べてみたけど
I tried eating it
まだ酸っぱくて泣いた
But it was still sour and I cried
私みたいで
Just like me
残せないから
Because I can't leave any
全部食べた
I ate it all
好きだよ
I love you
泣けるよ
It makes me cry
好きだよ
I love you
酸っぱい
Sour
泣けるよ
It makes me cry
好きだよ
I love you
イヤ！
IYA!
Thanks for singing with me,
even though you bonked me and then dragged me here, dang it!
How... how you respond from that?
I thought you're gonna just die and then the 3D gonna be over.
No! I haven't 3D!
This is mine, Kaela!
And you almost ruined it by killing me! No!
I'm gonna get my revenge someday.
Oh really?
Yeah! I'm gonna beat you, zombie!
I gonna wait for that, yeah.
Yeah!
You won't hear the last of me!
I mean you invited me here, right? To sing?
Yeah, I invited... to sing, not to bonk me!
I invited you to sing together.
But then you came in and I was already being the boss and then...
dang it!
That's the plot twist, right? I am the final boss!
Oh my god!
Why you have three life bars?
What the bib!
You're too weak.
I'm gonna get stronger and beat you!
I'm gonna wait for you.
But it was fun, you know?
Singing with you, it was fun.
I guess it was fun.
I guess we were pretty cute, right?
No, you cute.
I'm cool.
No, I think we were both pretty cute, right?
Look at how cute we are together!
Where's my hammer?
Can I have my hammer again please?
Yeah, we're cuties,
you have to admit. Haha!
I'm cool.
I'm...
You can be both, right?
No, you cute,
I'm cool. No.
I can be cool too, look!
Look at that, with that smile.
No, it's not working.
Oh...
well, I'll work on it.
D'you like my place?
Yeah!
Oh, this is your place?
Yeah, it's my place!
I really love that.
Can I, can I mine that?
No! It's my decoration!
I gotta mine that later after this.
Whenever you're not seeing, I gotta mine that.
You know what?
You can leave now.
Oh really?
Yeah!
Just like that?
You've caused nothing but trouble here!
Oh, just like that, I see.
Okay fine.
Wait, I changed my mind,
you can stay!
No, I'm getting my exit.
What?
What... what are you doing?
Hah!
Oh...
Bye!
KAELA!
Oh...
I guess she's gone.
Ah well,
thank you Kaela for singing with me.
grindstone together forever.
Yeah!
But now,
that I've been rudely put here by Kaela,
I guess we should explore the place a little bit, huh?
Want to go?
Let's go!
Okay!
Yay!
Now Loading...
The air feels good over here.
Wow!
This place looks a lot different from when I last left it,
but I kind of like it better this way. Yeah!
Oh! There's a Moai!
Look!
Ooh, nice Moai. I approve, I approve.
Very nice, very tall.
Very かっこいい. Yes!
Very cool. Yes!
Oh!
Look! Grass!
Watch this!
Biboo's touching grass!
Look at the flowers! Oh, they're so pretty!
That feels good, yeah.
That smells great!
Touching grass isn't so bad.
I kind of like it.
Okay!
Let's keep exploring!
Everything's so pretty!
Oh, is that a chair?
Ooh, it looks comfy!
It's not a plastic chair, but it'll do.
I'll sit on it.
But not now, later.
Later, we got a lot of exploring to do.
Oh hey! That's where I was before!
Yeah! Until Kaela brutally bonked me
and dragged me here.
Whatever, I didn't have to walk,
so thanks Kaela, I guess.
Crystals!
Look at the architecture! The sky! Wow!
Huh?
Eh?
In the tall grass!
Is that a wild Pebblemon?
Wow! It's so cute!
Can I have it? I want it! I want it!
I got an idea. Okay.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm gonna catch it with this.
I got one shot though.
I'm ready. I'm ready.
氷晶... 陣内！
Crystal... Prison!
Yay! Let's go see, let's go see!
I caught a Pebblemon!
Yay!
I caught a Pebblemon! I caught a Pebblemon!
Yay yay yay!
Now Loading...
Nice weather. I hate it.
Why are we here? I don't know.
Senpai! Hey!
Hey!
Hi!
Our eyes met. We have to battle!
Wait, fight you, bro?
Fight you?
Did Towa-sama say "bro"? What?
Come on, senpai tax, baby! Pay up!
Wait, but there's two of you and there's one of me!
I need help! Somebody fix this!
I choose...
No, guys!
You're here!
With the powers of chuuni, we will defeat them!
Yeah!
I don't think so.
I'm the Chuuni!
No no no no no... Good luck, kohai.
No no no no no... Good luck, junior.
It's time to battle!
Team Baby, ready to fight!
Biboo, that's right! Go!
Pebblemon! No! Get her!
Koseki Bijou, that was so big! Be careful!
Koseki Bijou... Uh oh!
Okay, that was kind of weird.
It's my turn now.
Okay, Morimon, use Bloody Nightmare!
Sucker!
No! Help! Help! Help!
Fine! I will teach you how it's done! Biboon!
From the fiery depths, yes, Eternal Embers Ablaze!
Okay, my turn! Senpai!
ど、どうしよう。とりあえず中行け！
Wh-what should I do? Anyway, go inside!
Nice shot! Nice shot!
大勝利！
Big victory!
Okay, I wanna do a cool move.
Come on, Koseki Bijou, I'm counting on you!
I'll show you! No! Judgment Ray Ende!
Gosh, this battle's... you know what? Stay there.
What? What? What?
Betray Biboo? Oh, great idea! I love that.
All right, Biboo! Time to pay the step-by-step!
All right, three against one, what you gonna do?
What you gonna do? What you gonna do, Biboo?
Pochi! Help me!
A top ten anime betrayals!
Help, I need help! Get down! Get down!
Yo, what is that thing? I've never seen that thing in my life.
Go, Pebblemon! Rock Kitty!
Wait a minute. Look up!
Biboo is the winner! I won! I won! I won!
I won! I won! I won! And now you guys have to sing a song with me! Yeah!
Biboo, I don't know... I can't sing.
I won! I won! I won! I won! Yeah!
Guys, what's that? What's that? That thing? What's that?
Look out!
Take my Biboo long!
Get a job!
Wakey-wakey, time for school!
Available on the BibooStation
Inside identity, 居場所はどこ？
Inside identity, where is my place?
INSIDE IDENTITY
Lyrics • Music: ZAQ
勘違いが弾けたとか　素直さが痛いとか
Misunderstandings burst, honesty hurts...
誰かが何と言おうと　正しさなんてわかんないぜ
No matter what anyone says, I don't know what's right.
普通に流れていく日常に　無理して馴染ませた
Forcing myself to fit into the flow of daily life.
焦燥ももっとこさえた自分を　噛んで飲んで吐いて笑う
Biting, swallowing, spitting out my frustration and laughing.
あんな僕をわかってほしい
I want you to understand that version of me.
痛いけど言えなくて
It hurts but I can't say it.
なんで誰もわかってくんないのと
Why doesn't anyone understand me?
...思うのぜいたくなのかななのかな
...Is it too selfish to think that way?
感情的な太陽は
The emotional sun
熱を上げすぎてどうにかなりそう
Raises its heat so much that I'm about to lose it
叫びたくてしょうがない
I want to scream so badly
がむしゃらに求めてるアイデンティティ
My identity that I'm frantically searching for
Inside my feeling...
Inside my justice... 邪魔しないで 居場所はどこ?
Inside my justice... Don't get in my way, where do I belong?
「変わったね」誰かが言ってお隣でこだまして
"You've changed," someone says, echoing next to me
ぱたんなに張ってんだか壁 捏ねて起きて今日も最低点
Against what am I putting up a wall? Waking up and starting another awful day
飾ったってこの表情が苦手な僕がいるよ
There's a version of me that's bad at this decorated expression
僕にしかできないことがるってのもしってんだけど
I know there's something only I can do
tell me 誰だってどうにかが心配なの
Tell me, everyone's worried about something
頷く言葉 ただ一つ
There's only one word to agree on
本当はどうなのが気になるよ
I'm curious what the truth really is
答えを探すの 見つけたい 見つめたい
Searching for an answer, I want to find it, I want to gaze at it
孤独を知って愛を知る
Learning of loneliness and learning of love
割り切れるほど大人じゃないんだが
I'm not mature enough to just let it go
寂しいけれど譲れない
It's lonely, but I won't back down
僕だけのブレないアイデンティティ
My very own unwavering identity
行くのこれだけじゃダメさ
Just going like this isn't enough
何かを感じたいからここにいるわけさ
The reason I'm here is because I want to feel something
誰かにもらった快楽が
Pleasure given to me by someone else
僕の幸せとは限らないぜ
Doesn't necessarily mean it's my happiness
名も無い毎日だけど
Even though my days are nameless
意味を確立できる日は来るよ
The day I can establish meaning will come
中二病と呼ばれても
Even if I'm called a "Chuunibyou"
モラトリアムの渦の中
Inside the whirlpool of moratorium
感情的な太陽は
The emotional sun
熱を上げすぎてどうにかなりそう
Raises its heat so much that I'm about to lose it
叫びたくてしょうがない
I want to scream so badly
がむしゃらに求めてるアイデンティティ
My identity that I'm frantically searching for
Inside my feeling...
Inside my justice... 邪魔しないで 居場所はどこ?
Inside my justice... Don't get in my way, where do I belong?
Happy 3D Showcase Biboo!
Yeah, that was so much fun! We did it!
Oh my gosh, congratulations!
Calli! Towa! Congrats!
Happy 3D!
Thanks for inviting us!
Of course! Now that you're here,
is there any poses you want me to do?
Do the worm!
The worm? Oh, okay!
Go, go, go, go! Woo!
How was that? Was that good?
Wonderful.
Yes! So much fun! Congrats!
Thank you for inviting us!
Yeah! How do you feel, Towa-sama?
I feel very good!
You feel good? I'm so happy!
I chose this song because,
you know, we're all very 'chuuni', right?
Chuuni? Senpai chuuni Biboo?
Is Towa-senpai chuuni too?
No, I chose Towa-sama because
I wanted to sing with Towa-sama!
Aww, so cute! I wanted to sing with you too!
Arigatou gozaimasu!
Yoshi yoshi! Cute!
Hehehe, E-N-E?
E-N-E! E-N-E!
ENE generation! Yay!
Yay! E-N-E!
Thank you guys so much
for being a part of my 3D! I'm so honored!
No problem! But next time,
I'm gonna beat you in Pebblemon! Watch out!
Yeah, you better watch out for us three!
Pay your senpai tax!
I'll fight back!
I'm not going down without a fight!
That's the spirit! Good luck!
We wish you luck for the rest of your 3D! Bye-bye!
Biboo! Biboo! Biboo!
Hah... they're gone now.
Oh, that was so much fun singing with my senpais!
Oh, I'm so happy!
But I guess now it's just us, huh? Mmm...
Wait! Wait a second!
Oh! It's you! Hello!
Everyone, everyone, I want to introduce you to my buddy.
This is the Grand Executioner of Worlds!
What? That's his name.
Yes, Grand Executioner of Worlds.
Fine, you can call him Geo or whatever, I guess.
But his real name's Grand Executioner of Worlds, okay?
Geo. Geo.
Cute! Thank you for coming!
Actually, did you know Geo and I have been friends for a long, long time?
But, you know, when I got... you know, in jail, we kind of got separated...
...because he— Aw, don't be sad! Don't be sad!
I'm back now. Have you been waiting here for me this whole time?
Aw, thank you Geo, my loyal companion. I missed you too. Aw.
Well, you're going to be seeing a lot more of Geo from now on, so...
Yeah! I'm so happy to finally introduce you to him! Yeah!
So everyone, how is my 3D debut? Did you like it? Did you have fun?
I had so much fun with Kaela, and Towa senpai, and Callie...
...and Hakos Baelz. Yeah, it was such a good time.
I had so much fun.
Wait a second. Hmm...
Was there something that you wanted me to do in 3D?
Like a very specific, I don't know, dance or something?
I think you know what I'm talking about.
But... ah, I'm a little tired. I don't think I have the energy to do—
Sticking out your gyatt for the rizzler,
you're so skibidi, you're so Fanum Tax.
I just want to be your sigma!
Heh. Heh heh heh.
You didn't think I would end this 3D without doing that, huh?
Get Bibootaxed! Yay!
But now, I have some announcements to make!
Wait, wait, wait, Geo, Geo, Geo! Do you want to help me? Do you want to help me announce some things?
Okay, cool!
So, my announcement today is...
Merch! 3D Live merch! Yay!
And first up, I have...
Boom! What are those?
Koseki Bijou Room Slippers
Approx. H8xW16xD31cm
I'll tell you what they are. They are Biboo's Candy Feet room slippers!
Now you can match with Biboo! Look! Look, check it out!
We can both have candy feet together! Yeah! Ha! Ha!
Wait, where are you looking? Stop! No!
No, don't look! Don't look at that! No!
Get the slippers and look at it yourself. Yeah! Yeah!
古石ビジュー ルームスリッパ
サイズ：約H8×W16×D31cm
Koseki Bijou Room Slippers
Size: Approx. H8×W16×D31cm
Isn't it great? Please make sure you get the slippers and match with Biboo. Yeah!
Well, that's all for merch today. I hope you like those special items.
But now, the very next song is going to be the last one of this 3D debut.
Ah, man. I was having so much fun. Are you sad, pebbles? Are you sad?
It's okay! This next song is extra special and I think it's going to be really good...
...and you're going to enjoy it, so... Are you ready? Let's go!
Now Loading...
Palette
Lyrics・Music:ゆよゆっぺ / meola
Lyrics・Music: Yuyoyuppe / meola
凪いだ夜空へさ
To the calm night sky
静かに笑うんだ
I laugh quietly
想像を映した
Reflecting my imagination
彩りのパレット
A palette of colors
Please distinguish me
溢れ出した白
The white that overflowed
誰か止めてよ
Someone, stop it
消えちゃう
It's disappearing
あぁ...
Ah...
知ってるわ
I know
溶かした青は
The blue I melted
優しい涙
Is gentle tears
あぁ...
Ah...
葛藤は
My struggles
浮かべた赤に
Upon the floating red
優しい音
A gentle sound
I will be eraser's mind
積み上げた嘘
The lies I piled up
回る記憶に
In the rotating memories
絡まった僕らの
Ours, that are entangled
未来が
The future...
色づく
Colors in
あぁ...
Ah...
知ってるわ
I know
描いた黒は
The black I drew
優しい光
Is gentle light
あぁ...
Ah...
葛藤は
My struggles
溢した白に
Upon the spilled white
優しい基礎を
A gentle foundation
あぁ...
Ah...
Dear Pebbles,
Hi! It's Biboo!
How did you enjoy the showcase?
Did it rock? (heh)
To be honest, I missed you all lots
these few months!
Not being able to stream as much and
hang out with everyone was a little lonely...
BUT! I knew the end result was going to be worth it!
So, Biboo took all the feelings of her Pebbles
who were cheering her on and turned it into POWER.
She learned so many new things like how to dance
and different ways to sing all in the hopes that
Pebbles would be proud of her one day.
I hope one of those days is today.
BUT TODAY is just the beginning!
After today, we've unlocked a whole new
DIMENSION of Biboo!
We're just getting started!
No matter when or where you found me,
I hope you will continue to join me on this journey.
After today, we've unlocked a whole new
dimension of Biboo! We're just getting started!
So, no matter when or where you found me,
I hope you will continue to join me on this journey,
TOGETHAAA
This small rock is gonna do BIG things!!
So keep watching, okay?
Today, I am shining bright because of you.
So, from the bottom of my heart,
thank you Pebbles!
Love, Biboo
Coming soon