(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Attention For Visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出しの応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK!
2nd Round of Concert Merch
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors
ライブが素晴らしいものになりますように！！
I hope the concert is wonderful!!
頑張れカリオペ～！！
Do your best, Calliope~!!
ライブ開催 おめでとう、Calli!!
Congratulations on the concert, Calli!!
きっと人生で最高の日になると信じてます！
I believe it will be the best day of your life!
カリオペ〜〜〜！！！ 大好きだーーー！！！
Calliope!!! I love you!!!
2ndライブ開催おめでとうございます！！
Congratulations on holding the 2nd live!!
日本からも応援しているよー！！！
I'm supporting you from Japan too!!!
LAでの2ndライブ開催おめでとうございます！
Congratulations on holding the 2nd live in LA!
全力で楽しんでね！！
Please enjoy it to the fullest!!
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
演出の都合上、明滅の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出しの応援 OKです
Cheering loudly is OK
2nd Round of Concert Merch
待ちに待った2ndライブ！ 楽しんでいこー！！
The long-awaited 2nd live! Let's have fun!!
2ndライブ開催おめでとう！！ 日本からも応援してるよ！
Congratulations on the 2nd live!! Supporting from Japan!
ステージの上で輝く君をしっかりと目に焼き付けるよ！
I'll burn the image of you shining on stage into my eyes!
カリオペ最高！！ 応援してるよ！！
Calliope is the best!! I'm supporting you!!
今からライブが楽しみ！！ 盛り上がっていこー！！
Looking forward to the live!! Let's get hyped!!
頑張れカリオペ！！
Do your best, Calliope!!
最高のステージになりますように！
I hope it will be the best stage ever!
Mori Calliope 2nd Concert "Grimoire"
2nd Round of Concert Merch
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
演出の都合上、過度の点滅にご注意ください
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK!
声出しの応援 OK です
Attention For Visitors
Cheering loudly is OK!
Mori Calliope 2nd Concert "Grimoire"
2nd Round of Concert Merch
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までもうしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while longer for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to the production, please be careful of flashing lights.
Cheering loudly is OK
声出しの応援 OK です
Cheering with your voice is permitted.
Mori Calliope 2nd Concert "Grimoire"
2nd Round of Concert Merch
Essentials Pack / Glow Stick / Towel / Lanyard / T-shirt
Glow Stick / T-shirt / Baseball Shirt
Coin Case / Acrylic Panel / Rubber Mat / Key Chain
2nd Round of Concert Merch
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon...
演出の都合上、公演中は光の強い物、点滅する物の使用をお控えください。
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出しの応援 OK です
Cheering loudly is OK.
Essentials Pack
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK!
2nd Round of Concert Merch
Calli! Calli! Calli! Calli!
Attention
Guilty! Guilty!
Kick off! Kick off!
WHAT IS AN EXISTENCE?
WAKE UP.
She who never imagined rising above it all.
Found the Abyss more beautiful than the Heavens.
Step by step, she journeyed deeper.
Her story woven like a dark spell.
As the Grim Reaper writes her Memoir.
Chika-chika, chika-chika...
せればかせれば せりゃあ即効で Shake it up
If it comes to that, then do it immediately and shake it up
Do what I want したり顔で Knock you out
Do what I want and knock you out with a smug face
渇いては湧き 沸いてはボケちまうちはさ
As it dries, it springs up, as it boils, you start acting like an idiot
せればかせれば せりゃあ即効で Shake it up
If it comes to that, then do it immediately and shake it up
Wanna be 狂い咲く サボれば即ストップ
Wanna be blooming madly, if you slack off, you'll stop immediately
Get your head out your ass and what you got?
会津の会津の 神が舞い降りる
The god of Aizu, the god of Aizu, descends upon us
万歳三唱 すんでの夜通し
Three cheers of banzai, just before the night ends
阿呆 情緒酌量も余地なし
Idiot, there's no room for extenuating circumstances
即死系ハイ 地獄までお行きなさい
Instant-death-type high, go straight to hell
Hey! Hey! Hey!
今すぐにお行きなさい
Go away right now
Mera mera burn it out day
摩訶不思議な運命
A mysterious fate
Mera mera 厄介だ
Mera mera, it's troublesome
灰になるまで Mera mera
Until it turns to ash, mera mera
にさせた さあ 踊り狂っちゃえ
You made it happen, now dance like crazy
You’re very Paradise
Go up and down
せればかせれば せりゃあ即効で Shake it up
If it comes to that, then do it immediately and shake it up
Do what I want したり顔で Knock you out
Do what I want and knock you out with a smug face
My better pinnacle is pinnacle but first give me the mic god!
And may I just remind you I can pull this curtain
Fine down Jordan dungeon de die on day
Come on C-A-L-L you already know
Scythe at the ready slow and steady give 'em a show
They wanna get real close, can't learn to let go
Try and dance for the Reaper, better look up or below
Slay to the beat, breathe it free, redder than the rose
Sink 'em back 'til the sun rise, heaven is closed
Sleep until the next night, you know where we go
Believe I self keep it tight SHINIGAMI FLOW, alright?
Mera mera burn it out day
摩訶不思議な運命
A mysterious fate
Mera mera 厄介だ
Mera mera, it's troublesome
灰になるまで Mera mera
Until it turns to ash, mera mera
にさせた ああ 目覚めな見上げな
You made it happen, ah, wake up and look up
Better start looking about, ほらまだまだ足りない
Better start looking about, look, it's still not enough
Spell tied the sun, sun, sun, sun
Service plus now down, down, down, da-da-down
I don't care sing along, la la la la
But not this time, you don't gotta run
会いたい悶着 狂う執着
I want to see the trouble, the obsession that goes mad
灼熱に飛び込んで give it to ya, give it to ya!
Dive into the scorching heat, give it to ya, give it to ya!
皆さん！ You get the rest, Mori's in the building...
Everyone! You get the rest, Mori's in the building...
So you know you're already dead!
Everybody come on now!
Chika-chika, chika-chika...
Yeah! Jump! Jump! Jump! 地獄までお行きなさい！
Yeah! Jump! Jump! Jump! Go straight to hell!
Mera mera burn it out day
摩訶不思議な運命
A mysterious fate
Mera mera 厄介だ
Mera mera, it's troublesome
灰になるまで Mera mera
Until it turns to ash, mera mera
にさせた さあ 踊り狂っちゃえ
You made it happen, now dance like crazy
You’re very Paradise
Up and down zura-zuran-zuran-zura...
Come on everybody! Jump! Jump! Jump!
危険な海に浮かぶ島　エッグヘッド
Island floating in a perilous sea, Egghead
世界変える未来自慢のラボ
A future-boasting lab that will change the world
天才個性の願い叶えるよ願望
Fulfilling the wishes and desires of a genius personality
未来のお宝探しちゃおう
Let's go looking for future treasures
何が引き起こす　発想の奇跡
What will it trigger? A miracle of ideas
今で終わらせない夢のファンタジー
A dream fantasy that won't end now
常識ひっくり返るテクノロジー
Technology that turns common sense upside down
叶えちゃうラボラトリー
A laboratory that makes it happen
釈迦でエディソン　ピタゴラス
Shaka and Edison, Pythagoras
アトラス　欲（ヨーク）　悪（リリス）のサテライト
Atlas, York, and Lilith's satellites
湧き出すアイデア　止まらない
The gushing ideas won't stop
忙しすぎて猫の手も借りたい
So busy I'd even take a cat's help
海も波も越えていく海賊王
The Pirate King who crosses both seas and waves
常識変えていく発明王
The King of Invention who changes common sense
そんな奴らに憧れてきた
I've always admired those guys
次は誰が王になる？
Who will be the next king?
無限のヒューマ　未来のチア
Infinite Human, Future Cheer
ひらめきを巻き起こせ
Trigger an inspiration
無限のヒューマ　未来のチア
Infinite Human, Future Cheer
過去も世界も飛び越して　Singing!
Leaping over the past and the world, Singing!
Step up! 生み出そうバイディア
Step up! Let's create a 'by-dea'
Step up! ズランズランズランズラン
Step up! Zuran zuran zuran zuran
Step up! 革命よここから
Step up! The revolution starts here
Step up! Woo!
危険な海に浮かぶ島　エッグヘッド
Island floating in a perilous sea, Egghead
世界変える未来自慢のラボ
A future-boasting lab that will change the world
This is my design undefeated until my goals completed
Let's keep on searching for the treasure of to come
Mysterious! A miracle idea gotta set it free
Furious! Fantastic dreams are burning up inside of me
Delirious! Let's turn the world around with new technology
Hilarious! A laboratory cast upon the sea
Just better evil than the contents of mind
Ride on technology create violent satellite
Ideas can't stop rushing and stop thinking they might
Could use a hand too I'm busy working into the night
The Pirate King who braves the ocean while in search of a mission
A ruler of invention that can modify or reason
Once watched in jealousy now someday it gotta be
Next on the throne, I know what I've got to do
Mugen no hyuuma, mirai no chia
Infinite Human, Future Cheer
Hirameki wo makiokose
Trigger an inspiration
Mugen no hyuuma, mirai no chia
Infinite Human, Future Cheer
過去も世界も飛び越して, Singing!
Leaping over the past and the world, Singing!
Step up! Umidasou baidia
Step up! Let's create a 'by-dea'
Step up! Zuran zuran zuran zuran
Step up! 革命よここから
Step up! The revolution starts here
Step up! Woo!
Hollywood!
All Dead Beats here tonight and around the world...
...raise your hands up to the sky!
Here we go!
行こうぜ　聞かなきゃ　振りかざす正義
Let's go, gotta listen, brandishing justice
世界も揺るぐ軍団の対峙
A confrontation of armies that shakes the world
潜む巡る怪しいたくらみ
Mysterious plots lurking and revolving
過去の記憶に隠された狂気
Madness hidden within memories of the past
新秩序　起き抜けの勇気
A new order, the courage upon waking
謎に満ちたりその夢のエネルギー
Full of mystery, the energy of those dreams
天才が見せる世界の形
The shape of the world shown by a genius
どこへ向かう未来のエッグヘッド
Where are you headed, future Egghead?
Hey! Tired of fantasizing wanna run away
Cause I got the place where it's out of space to rise and shine today
Last chance to realize and time is short don't be afraid
So look up okay
Join the rhythm flow, don't be afraid of the stellar beat
Kono kebancho de evil cast a spell on streets
With this kebancho, evil cast a spell on streets
Yeah, it's just like magic
Welcome to Yona Yona Journey, Wake up we're gonna party
ワタワタはStaging　音でハジけなStage shift
Flustered staging, pop with the sound, Stage shift
体はまだ元気　酸欠で頭はCrazy Crazy Crazy
Body's still fine, head's crazy from lack of oxygen
簡単さ　タクタク旋律　勘違い　頭はStaging
It's easy, a rhythm, a misunderstanding, head is staging
まだまだまだ元気　三寒四温　ガナれStage shift
Still energetic, ups and downs, roar out Stage shift
鮮やかなStaging　賛成で朝までCrazy Crazy Crazy
Vivid staging, in favor of being crazy until morning
Alright everybody! Come on, all together now! Come on! Clap!
Welcome to your yo journey
Wake up we're gonna gonna party
Yeah
Aliens life on this man-made planet is sus
We don't gotta understand
The universe, you the curse, all your fears none of that won't fly
窓口かませる as you pierce the sky
Blowing past the counter as you pierce the sky
PM to AM talking 25-50 / See him soaring into the air
Let it free you slowly / Atmosphere can't hold me, but I'm chained by the ephemeral / But then we really had it all
What I wouldn't give just to have it all back
Remember how we lived for that one house track
Killer vibes you and I
Sound-illuminated disco ball sky
Ain't it worth a try? Travel back in time in the night
Paint the summer sky trouble bass rhyming
Light up the stage bring it back from the day
Unlock the cage crazy sing it loud to blackout say
All right everybody! All together now! Come on! Clap! Clap!
Clap! Clap! Clap! Clap!
Clap! Very nice! Clap! Clap! Come on, don't stop! Clap! Clap!
Welcome to your yo journey
Yeah! Welcome to your yo journey!
Wake up we're gonna gonna party
沸いて 沸いて 沸いて staging
Excitement, excitement, excitement staging
Non-stop no no no staging spaceship
身体はまだ元気
My body's still energetic
酸欠で頭は crazy crazy crazy
From lack of oxygen, my head's crazy crazy crazy
Yeah yeah!
乾杯 パクパク 鮮美
Cheers, eating away, exquisite beauty
感情で頭は paging
Through emotions, my head is paging
まだ まだ まだ 景気
The energy's still going, going, going
三界で頭は day-trip
In the three worlds, my head's on a day-trip
華やかな staging
A brilliant staging
賛成で頭は crazy crazy crazy yeah yeah
In agreement, my head's crazy crazy crazy yeah yeah
Ehem! Mean... wait a minute.
Wait, why do you have skin?
Why do you all have skin? I'm confused.
No, don't tear it off! Not now! Not yet at least.
I like to think there's a skeleton inside of everybody.
So just stay... stay as you are.
What's up everyone!
Welcome to Grimoire, Mori Calliope's 2nd concert!
And who am I, you ask? Who am I?
Say my name!
Thank you so much for coming out you guys.
I have dreamed about this concert. It's all I've been able to think about.
I dreamed about the name, I dreamed about what songs I'd perform.
I dreamed about what I'd look like, what I'd wear...
...and I dreamed about all of you!
Welcome, welcome.
Matter of fact, hold on, hold on a second.
What was that that I heard? By the way...
...what was that? People outside cheering "Boat goes binted"?
What's wrong with you!?
Ha! Get a load of these boneheads.
No, they're just excited to be here. It's fine.
You guys are excited to be here, it's fine.
Now listen.
All right, what did you guys think about "Mera Mera"?
That was hot, right? It was hot.
Now listen, listen. Hold on.
Something I want to address really quick.
We were really worried about the wildfires that were going on here, right?
We weren't sure if the concert was going to be able to be held safely.
But you know what? At the end of the day...
...at the end of the day, right? We thought, we have to do this concert.
If we can do something to cheer people up, right?
Cheer you guys up and do something fun together...
...and you know, get back to thinking about fun shit, right? Yeah.
So here we are.
This is the very first time that we are doing a solo live in America!
I heard you guys. There they go. USA! USA! USA! USA!
Awesome. Rather patriotic, very nice.
But you know what? We actually have a band that came all the way from Japan!
Glad to be here.
Give it up for those guys,
and I want to introduce them to you as a matter of fact, alright?
So first of all, we had on the drums, it's Ishi Yuya!
かっこいいね！ Freaking cool.
That's cool! Freaking cool.
Next up,
on the bass, it's Ego!
Ah, I'm jealous man. So cool.
You know, I play a little bass myself, but I'm a beginner,
so I'm very much like "Ah, that's so cool."
I want to be good at the bass someday. Next up we've got on the keys, it's Koushei!
エモいねー。 So emotional.
How emotional. So emotional.
Wow, my gosh. My heart is fluttering.
And last but certainly not least, on the guitar, we got Becky!
かっこいい！ Everyone's so cool.
So cool! Everyone's so cool.
Band saikou!
The band is the best!
よろしくお願いします！
I'm counting on you!
Nice. Now that I've introduced the band to you guys,
we're ready to get into the details about how to have fun at the Mori concert.
Now first, I want the whole venue to turn red,
like the voltage of Hell is going up. Come on, give me red, give me red!
And when this red runs black...
Yeah, yeah. Alright.
Now listen to me, this is important. You turn the penlight into red
when you feel super hyped, which is going to be all the time,
but you know, if you overdo it, it's not as special.
Kind of like, you know, solo lives are rare, we don't get to do them all the time.
But they become more special, so use it only when you're super hyped, okay?
Now then.
Yeah, you guys are excited, I can tell.
Now let me hear something though. I want to know,
where are you from?
USA! USA! USA! USA! Stop, man! You boneheads!
Crazily enough, the only state that I heard was Oregon. Why?
No, but then I got a little bit of everybody in there.
So wherever you're from, thank you so much for coming out to see me.
It's very important to me. Thank you.
You Dead Beats rock! You know that though.
Now, alrighty, also here's the thing though,
we don't just have people here in the venue,
we also have people watching on the internet, on stream!
What's up guys? Hello! I see you, I see you. Hi, hi, hi!
I'm looking at you, Dead Beat at home, Dead Beat at home.
We love you, we miss you. Hi!
"That's us," they say. "That's me, that's me."
Let's go!
Now, you guys... they have so many different chants.
Chat! Chat! Chat! Chat!
Chat! Chat! Chat! Chat! That's you guys. Chat! Chat! Chat! Chat!
Thank you so much! Chat! Chat!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Nice beat! いいね！
Nice beat! Nice!
Yeah, chat, chat... alright, time to stop that, time to...
Okay. Now that we've gotten that out of our system,
you guys who are watching this stream,
have the opportunity to do the coolest thing right now.
Post your impressions on Twitter, okay? #CalliGrimoire
No recording videos, but feel free to take lots of screenshots of me
doing silly stuff and singing and performing, okay?
But sadly, those of you watching on YouTube, I have some bad news for you.
It's all over, the free preview is over! And you know what?
We haven't even gotten to like the sixth or seventh most hype moment
that's going to happen tonight.
Broke-gang, listen. I feel you. But, but,
make sure that you check out the link in the description below
and see if you can, if you can, you know...
Cop yourself... BUY IT! Yeah!
I like that Dead Beat who's like "BUY IT!" Yeah!
You have the assertiveness I need.
Awesome, my freaking boneheads. Now then,
listen up Dead Beats, we got to continue as much as I want to keep talking
so I can like chill for a minute. Listen,
today I brought a bunch of songs here to harvest your souls.
It's my job, don't hate me.
Don't hate me. Heh heh.
Are you ready to be soaked in Mori's music? That's terrible.
That's terrible.
I hate that. I hate that that was in the script.
Forget the script. Let's just go crazy, right?
Right!
No script, no script, we're just running it.
Next song!
Let's go!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.