(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
supported by Pocky ACL (ANIME COLLECTIVE LAB.)
Ayunda Risu
Kureiji Ollie
Vestia Zeta
Moona Hoshinova
Anya Melfissa
Kaela Kovalskia
Airani Iofifteen
Pavolia Reine
Kobo Kanaeru
TERIMA KASIH!
THANK YOU!
Ayo mulai!!
Let's start!!
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も...
Both body and soul...
この手で Make you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine
君を見るたび　上書きされてく欲望に
Every time I see you, my desires are overwritten
重なる eyes, eyes, eyes　目を逸らす smile, smile, smile
Overlapping eyes, eyes, eyes; a smile, smile, smile that turns away
ねえ　その姿かたち　すべてが拍車かけていく
Hey, that look and shape of yours only spur me on
故意から I, I, I　毎秒おかしくなっていく
From this intent, I, I, I am going crazy every second
手を伸ばせば届く距離　1mmも逃したくない
A distance within reach, I don't want to miss even 1mm
穏やかに恋したい　どんなシーンも私に見せて
I want to love calmly; show me every scene of yours
このまま stay by my side　どこにも行かないで
Stay by my side just like this; don't go anywhere
100% 煽って　純粋な愛だから
100% fueling it, because it's pure love
止められない感情　その腕で抱きしめてよ
Unstoppable emotions; hold me in those arms
もっと　ここからだよ　ずっと　もっと近くで
More, it starts from here; forever, even closer
認めあいたいほど　持て余す恋なら spice
The more we want to acknowledge each other,
the more this unmanageable love is a spice
Hey me, what's wrong with me? Tell me　名も無き美津だし
Hey me, what's wrong with me? Tell me,
it's a nameless pouring sweetness
I know　君の全部知りたい　I do need you 今すぐ
I know, I want to know everything about you;
I do need you right now
最初は声を聞く　それだけで良かった
At first, just hearing your voice was enough
だけど次第に　愛　わがままになった
But gradually, my love became selfish
誰かに笑いかけ　その仕草に苛立ち
You smile at someone else, and that gesture irritates me
隠せない自分に気づいた
I realized I couldn't hide it
独り占めしたい　いっそ鎖に繋いで
I want to have you all to myself; I'd rather tie you with chains
二人きりの部屋　近距離　強硬発言封じたい
Alone in a room together, up close;
I want to seal off any forced words
想い捨てて眠りたい　鋭い棘　感じさせて
I want to throw away these thoughts and sleep;
let me feel the sharp thorns
100% 煽って　私だけに依存してね
100% fueling it, depend only on me
歪（いびつ）な愛　まるごと受け止めてよ
Acceptance of this distorted love, all of it
ずっと　私達は　たとえ　吐き気しそうな
Always we will be, even if it feels nauseating
甘い焦燥　抗（あらが）いきれない絶対
This sweet impatience, something I absolutely can't resist
Hey me, what's wrong with me? Tell me　名も無き美津だし
Hey me, what's wrong with me? Tell me,
it's a nameless pouring sweetness
I know　君の全部知りたい　I do need you 今すぐ
I know, I want to know everything about you;
I do need you right now
目を閉じたら　とめどない愛感　触れたい
When I close my eyes, there's an endless feeling
of love I want to touch
私の歌　私だけ
My song, only for me
このまま stay by my side　二度と離れないで
Stay by my side just like this; never leave again
100% 煽（あお）って　純粋な愛だから
100% fueling it, because it's pure love
メラメラ揺れて
Burning and swaying
止められない感情を
With emotions that can't be stopped
手で抱きしめてよ
Hold them in your hands
あとどこから通いあう
From where else will we connect?
ずっともっと近くで
Always, from much closer
認めあいたいわ
I want us to recognize each other
暴く衝動
Exposing impulses
もてあますだけなら
If you're just left with too much
Tell me what's wrong with me
何も持たないふりだし
Back to the start with nothing
右も左も知りたい
I want to know both right and left
And I need you 今すぐ
And I need you right now
Oh baby I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby I need you, I need you always
逃げるなら 今だぜ お嬢 勝利を願っちゃって
If you're gonna run, do it now, missy. Pray for victory
Anya Melfissa!
Vestia Zeta!
Let's go set together, OK!
Are you ready? もしやチャンスだ遊んねぇ
Are you ready? Perhaps it's a chance, no playing around
迷走めいた半信半疑にほら 誰か人生スキャニング
In a straying state of half-doubt, look, someone's scanning life
Out of video 準備万端 今夜勝負に飽き飽きなのよ
Out of video, all ready, I'm tired of competing tonight
弾むパワード残酷私には血の味ね
Bouncing powered, cruel, to me it's the taste of blood
場面密に挑戦 無敵のやまと B20
Challenge the scene closely, invincible Yamato B20
オーデッドライトに乗るようなやりだした十人力
Like riding an Oh-Dead Light, I've started with the strength of ten
Day by day 初出し あらあら 言ったこと全部ピンを刺した
Day by day, first appearance, oh my, I've pinned down everything I said
笑ってくれたっていいさ 止められないプレイヤー壊しすぎね
It's okay to laugh, an unstoppable player, breaking too much
Victory to the world 手に入れた場所の感動はきっとかけがえないはずよ
Victory to the world, the excitement of the place we've reached must be irreplaceable
見てて見てよこの今日 地へいらっしゃって
Watch, watch this day, welcome to the ground
わずかな隙間漏らす全て来ない段階 並べた豪奢すぎる思考回路
Leaking everything through a tiny gap, a stage that won't come, a thought process too luxurious
時代中位の上 ここは独断場
Above the middle of the era, this is my stage
拾い上げたワン切り 勝訴私を強くしてくわ
A one-ring call I picked up, victory makes me stronger
ポジショニング公社から覗かれるのは尺で
Being peeked at from the positioning public corp is annoying
押し警備 1 2 3 死ぬのは嫌で trip to trip
Push security 1 2 3, I don't want to die, trip to trip
気が付いたらロンリーデイ あれれ隠れていただけ
When I noticed, it's a lonely day, oh my, I was just hiding
ねえねねファイティング掲げな ラララ冗談よ全部はキャンセル
Hey, hey, hey, raise your fighting spirit, tra-la-la, just kidding, everything's canceled
開催はやめなさい これが私の憲法になる事も知らずにね
Stop the event, without knowing this will become my constitution
Victory to the world 共に作りたいんだ厚き手前箱を
Victory to the world, I want to create together a thick front box
心地良いこの今日 君に染まっちゃって
In this comfortable today, getting dyed in your color
Hololive Indonesia! Ayo menyala!
Hololive Indonesia! Let's light it up!
Ayo semuanya! Ayo mana suaranya!
Come on everyone! Let's hear your voice!
響け明日へ
Resonate towards tomorrow
冷静不振ブレないで
Don't waver in calm depression
Day by day もがいて まだまだ降り出しにカンパとって
Day by day, struggling, still at the starting point, taking donations
笑ってくれたっていいさ 踊れ皆いつかチャンピオン呼び出すだけ
It's okay to laugh, dance everyone, one day you'll just call out the champion
Victory to the world 絶対追い抜くあの光で夜明けを
Victory to the world, I'll definitely overtake with that light, the dawn
忘れられないほどの勝利を願っちゃって
Pray for a victory so great it's unforgettable
今日という日を 1 2 G 地へいらっしゃって
Welcome this day to the ground, 1 2 G
はあ...
Haah...
Siapa di sini yang lelah dengan kehidupan?
Who here is tired of life?
Aku! Aku!
Me! Me!
Kalau capek enaknya gimana nih, holoID?
If you're tired, what's the best thing to do, holoID?
Balas saja! Cakep!
Just get back at it! Nice!
Bukannya sudah biasa
Isn't it already common
Ditikam oleh kecewa? Aduh!
To be stabbed by disappointment? Ouch!
Saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya, oh oh...
When the world doesn't go as it should, oh oh...
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya kau coba lepaskan saja.
Maybe it's finally time for you to try and let go.
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi.
No need to ask why anymore.
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan.
If you truly can't find the answers.
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya.
Don't cry over it, try to go through its riddles.
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya...
Let it go, because in the end...
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira.
You are stronger than you think.
Dahlasaja, oh dahlasaja.
Just let it be, oh just let it be.
Jalani saja.
Just live through it.
Dahlasaja, oh dahlasaja.
Just let it be, oh just let it be.
Jalani saja.
Just live through it.
Mau gimana lagi?
What else can we do?
まいっか、もうどうにでもなれ
Whatever, let it be what it will be.
Walau kadang mati rasa.
Even though sometimes it feels numb.
Bahkan hingga tak berdaya.
Even to the point of helplessness.
Dan usahamu terasa sia-sia.
And your efforts feel in vain.
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan.
If you truly can't find the answers.
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya.
Don't cry over it, try to go through its riddles.
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya...
Let it go, because in the end...
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira.
You are stronger than you think.
Lepas semua kendali.
Release all control.
Tancap gas dan berlari.
Step on the gas and run.
Terima dan sudahi.
Accept and end it.
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan.
If you truly can't find the answers.
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya.
Don't cry over it, try to go through its riddles.
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya...
Let it go, because in the end...
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira.
You are stronger than you think.
Dahlasaja, oh dahlasaja.
Just let it be, oh just let it be.
Jalani saja.
Just live through it.
Dahlasaja, oh dahlasaja.
Just let it be, oh just let it be.
Jalani saja.
Just live through it.
まいっか
Oh well.
Halo Comic Frontier! Konban-wa!
Hello Comic Frontier! Good evening!
Comic Frontier! こんばんは！
Comic Frontier! Good evening!
Konban-wa!
Good evening!
ようこそ...
Welcome to...
「hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future」へ！
to hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future!
Wah gila gila gila!
Wow, this is crazy!
やばいやばいやばい！
No way, no way, no way!
Makasih banyak semuanya udah pada datang ke konser 5 tahun kita ya!
Thank you so much everyone for coming to our 5th anniversary concert!
5周年のライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to our 5th anniversary live!
Wah nggak berasa nggak sih udah 5 tahun aja?
Doesn't it feel like it's been 5 years already?
まさかもう5周年とはね！
Can't believe it's already the 5th anniversary!
Kalo gitu kita mulai dari perkenalan diri dulu nggak sih? Mulai dari aku aku!
In that case, let's start with self-introductions, shall we? Starting with me, me!
じゃあ自己紹介から始めましょうか？まずはゼータから！
Then shall we start with the self-introductions? First up is Zeta!
はいはいはい
Yes yes yes
Yoshi... ah ushiro ka
Alright... ah, behind me?
よし...あっ後ろか
Alright... ah, it's behind?
アアア！ミッションスタート！
Aaa! Mission start!
Aku Vestia Zeta dari hololive Indonesia Gen 3! Nice to meet you!
I'm Vestia Zeta from hololive Indonesia Gen 3! Nice to meet you!
スタート！ホロライブインドネシア3期生のベスティア・ゼータです！よろしくお願いします！
Start! I'm Vestia Zeta from hololive Indonesia Gen 3! Pleased to meet you!
よし次はカエラ！
Alright, next is Kaela!
Hai hai! Kaela! Grinding every day, the blacksmith from hololive ID Gen 3!
Hi hi! Kaela! Grinding every day, the blacksmith from hololive ID Gen 3!
はいはい！カエロ！毎日鍛冶をやってるホロライブインドネシア3期生の鍛冶屋！
Yes yes! Kaelo! The blacksmith from hololive Indonesia Gen 3 who's grinding every day!
I'm Kaela Kovalskia! Nice to meet you all!
カエラ・コヴァルスキアです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Kaela Kovalskia! Pleased to meet you!
次はこぼだ！こぼ！
Next is Kobo! Kobo!
Yappo! Boko boko Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Hi! Boko boko Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
やっほー！ぼこぼこーこぼ・かなえる、アットユアサービス！
Hi! Boko boko Kobo Kanaeru, at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
君の日々を照らす太陽になりましょう！えへ！
Let me be the sun that lights up your days! Ehe!
Kobokers, mana suaranya!
Kobokers, let me hear you!
Kobokers声を上げて！
Kobokers, raise your voices!
3人で...
Together...
hololive Indonesia Gen 3, Holoh3ro!
ホロライブインドネシア3期生、holoh3roでーす！
We are hololive Indonesia Gen 3, Holoh3ro!
Wah nggak nyangka juga deh konser 5th anniversary hololive ID ini akhirnya ada juga.
Wow, I didn't expect that the hololive ID 5th anniversary concert would finally happen.
やあ、ついにホロライブID 5周年ライブができるとはね。
Man, I can't believe we can finally have a hololive ID 5th anniversary live.
Dari lagu pertama aja udah keren banget guys. Kerasa gak sih semangatnya?
Even from the first song it's already so cool guys. Can you feel the energy?
一曲目からもうめっちゃカッコいいよね！その熱気、感じてるわ！わ！
Even from the first song it's already super cool! I'm feeling that heat! Yeah!
Enggak sih, iya enggak sih, iya enggak sih?
Maybe not, or is it, or is it?
Parah sih!
It's intense!
Adrenalinnya keluar kan ya? Pengen lari aku rasanya nih!
Adrenaline is flowing, right? I feel like running!
Eh eh eh! Mau ke mana? Mau ke mana?
Hey hey hey! Where are you going? Where are you going?
Iya iya sst, ya udah stop stop stop stop stop stop stop!
Yes yes, okay stop stop stop stop stop stop stop!
Nanti keringetan loh, nanti keringetan!
You'll get sweaty, you'll get sweaty!
Ah, kalau Kaela gimana?
Ah, what about Kaela?
Aduh, seru banget! Aku enggak nyangka sih sampai aku bisa ada di sini ya.
Man, it's so fun! I didn't expect to be able to be here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong, konsernya masih panjang banget, jadi kalian tetap semangat ya sampai akhir!
But by the way, this concert is still very long, so keep your spirits up until the end!
Sampai akhir! Semangat semangat semangat semangat!
Until the end! Go go go go!
Eh tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi, emang pada tahu judul konsernya apa?
Eh, but talking about the concert all this time, does everyone know the title of the concert?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah "Chromatic Future"!
The title of our concert this time is "Chromatic Future"!
Ada yang tahu enggak artinya apa? Ayo absen!
Does anyone know what it means? Come on, check in!
Nah ini, Kobo paling tahu!
Now this, Kobo knows best!
Nih, ah... yang jelasin yang paling tinggi. Yuk let's go!
Here, ah... the tallest one explains. Come on, let's go!
Segitu ya? Ya udahlah, ya udah.
Is that so? Oh well, okay.
Nih ya guys ya buat kalian yang belum tahu, "Chromatic Future" itu artinya tuh masa depan yang berwarna-warni.
So guys, for those who don't know, "Chromatic Future" means a colorful future.
Jadi karena Hololive Indonesia kan sudah 5 tahun nih, kita sama-sama dari hari satu sampai sekarang.
So because Hololive Indonesia has been around for 5 years now, we've been together from day one until now.
Nah, jadi itu untuk ke depannya kita tuh juga
So, for the future, our hope is that we can
harapannya tuh kita bisa nyiptain waktu dan memori
create colorful times and memories
yang berwarna-warni sama seluruh fans dari Hololive Indonesia!
with all the fans of Hololive Indonesia!
Ya gitu! Betul Kaela Kovalskia! Catat catat! Iya iya iya iya!
That's right! Correct Kaela Kovalskia! Note it down! Yes yes yes!
Nah, kalian sekarang udah pada tahu kan? Karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
Now, you all know now, right? Because Kaela already explained it.
Kalau gitu, konsernya kan udah mulai nih.
In that case, the concert has already started.
Kalian mau nge-post soal konser ini di medsos, jangan lupa hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture ya!
If you want to post about this concert on social media, don't forget the hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture!
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh...
Because we really want to see your...
apa sih? Pengen lihat semangat kalian!
what is it? We want to see your spirit!
Ya itu! Betul banget, iya enggak?
Yeah, that! Absolutely right, isn't it?
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
No typos, no typos!
Asyik, share ke semua! Oke!
Cool, share to everyone! Okay!
Jadi tapi jujur deh, kalian tuh pas dibilang kita bakal konser loh di Indonesia, kalian pada kaget enggak sih?
So, but be honest, when you were told we were going to have a concert in Indonesia, were you surprised?
Halo? Ada yang dengerin?
Hello? Is anyone listening?
Betul! Aku setuju juga, aku merasakan empati...
Correct! I agree too, I feel empathy...
...terhadap adik saya Zeta. / Empati iya iya.
...towards my sister Zeta. / Empathy, yes yes.
Kalau Kaela gimana, Kaela Kovalskia?
How about Kaela, Kaela Kovalskia?
Aku juga waktu itu enggak nyangka banget kayak "Hah? Beneran? Ini riil nih?" gitu kan.
I also didn't expect it at the time, like "Huh? Really? Is this real?"
Kayak "Lho, bisa gitu? Akhirnya!" Mana udah bersembilan di Indonesia pula, ya kan? Keren banget!
Like "Wait, how? Finally!" Especially since all nine of us are in Indonesia, right? So cool!
Keren banget!
So cool!
Ini kan konser pertama Hololive Indonesia yang bersembilan.
This is the first Hololive Indonesia concert with all nine members.
Sebenarnya tuh enggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar
Actually, this is not only the biggest and
dan terpenting juga untuk fans Hololive Indonesia,
most important moment for Hololive Indonesia fans,
tapi seluruh dunia juga pasti bakal nonton,
but the whole world will surely be watching,
enggak sih? Iya enggak?
right? Isn't it?
Jawab!
Answer!
Iya iya makasih makasih semuanya. Tapi tentu aja ini pencapaiannya enggak bakal cuma sampai di sini aja kan?
Yes, yes, thank you everyone. But of course this achievement won't just stop here, right?
Jadi next-nya mungkin kita bisa apa ya? Dominating the world! Gitu! We are ready!
So next, maybe we can... what? Dominate the world! Like that! We are ready!
Ready ready ready ready! Betul banget Kaela! Zeta!
Ready ready ready ready! That's right, Kaela! Zeta!
Selain dari dukungan fans in this opportunity...
Besides the support of the fans in this opportunity...
...kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih
...we also want to say thank you to all the
untuk semua sponsor yang mendukung terjadinya konser ini!
sponsors who supported this concert!
Terima kasih! Makasih makasih! Thank you thank you!
Thank you! Thanks thanks! Thank you thank you!
Eh tapi ngomong-ngomong di konser ini
Eh, but by the way, in this concert
kayaknya ada yang beda enggak sih? Ela kamu nyadar enggak?
there seems to be something different, isn't there? Ela, did you notice?
Sadar lah! Kalau Kobo mah enggak bakal sadar.
Of course! Kobo wouldn't notice.
Nih nih nih, yang beda tuh kali ini tuh model kita! Ini model baru nih!
Here here here, what's different this time is our models! These are new models!
Gemes banget! Lucu lucu lucu!
So cute! Cute cute cute!
Kameranya deketin ke aku! Kameranya deketin ke aku!
Bring the camera closer to me! Bring the camera closer to me!
Nah mulai mulai. Kalian mau lihat keimutan Kobo nih nih...
Here we go. You want to see Kobo's cuteness...
Ini ini, osiri!
This one, my butt!
Woi woi woi! Kameranya diambil Kobo semua enggak sih?
Hey hey hey! The camera is all taken by Kobo, right?
Ini ke aku! Aku juga! Jangan Kobo doang!
To me! Me too! Not just Kobo!
Stop stop stop stop! Mulai mulai mulai... Semua kamera diambil!
Stop stop stop stop! Here we go... All the cameras are taken!
Oke oke. Kalau gitu... aduh sampai kehabisan napas.
Okay okay. In that case... man, I'm out of breath.
Jangan rebutan di depan konser!
Don't fight in front of the concert!
Iya iya.
Yes yes.
Hati-hati ya, Zeta kalau marah tuh serem loh.
Be careful, Zeta is scary when she's angry.
はいよ、ゼータが怒ると怖いからね
Yeah, it's scary when Zeta gets angry.
怖いよー
I'm scared...
もういいや、ゼータがカメラも独り占めしちゃダメっていうのは…うーん、しょうがない
Fine, whatever. If Zeta says we can't hog the camera, then... sigh, it can't be helped.
ファンの皆んなと遊ぼう！
Let's just play with the fans instead!
さっきみんなからも大きな声もらったわけだし今度はこっちがみんなに大きな声を出したいっす！
Since everyone cheered for us earlier, this time I want us to cheer for you all!
はいはいはい、みんなと一緒に大きな声を出したいっすね！
Yes, yes, yes. I want us to shout our cheers together with the fans!
そう！みんなにじゃなく、みんなとね
Exactly! Shout with them, not at them.
そうそう！そういうことっす！
Yeah! That's what I meant!
だってこれから歌わなきゃいけないからまずは声を温存しなきゃでしょ？
We have to sing later, so shouldn't we save our voices first?
そうっすよ、そんなにカエラの配信時間ほど長くはならないから安心して
That's true. It won't take as long as one of my streams, so don't worry, guys.
まあいい、大声出していいから好きにして
Fine, if you want to shout, go ahead. I'm in.
みんな準備はいいかな？
How about it, everyone? Are you ready?
いけるかな？
Ready or not?!
もう出来てるのかよっすね！じゃあここから！
Seems like they are! Okay, starting with Kobo!
一緒に「BOKOBOKOBO！」って叫ぼう！よろしくいこうよ！
I want us all to shout "BOKOBOKOBO!" together. Okay?
いち、に、さん！
Ready? One, two, three!
BOKOBOKOBO！
BOKOBOKOBO!
いいわねいいわね！次はゼータ！
Cool, cool! Zeta's turn, Zeta's turn!
「ミッションスタート」って言ったら一緒に「スタート」って言うわ！
Okay, okay. When I say "Mission Starto", you all shout "Starto" together!
いい？アアア！ミッション…
Ready? Ahh... mission...
スタート！
Starto!
次はカエラ！
Okay, Kaela's next!
よしよし！きてみんもそしてholoh3roも
Alright! This is for all the fans and HoloH3ro too.
「holoh3ro！」って言ったら「HU-HA！」で返してね！簡単でしょ？
When I say "HoloH3ro!", you respond with "HU-HA!". Easy, right?
さあさあさあ！
Let's go, let's go!
準備はいい？ holoh3ro！
Ready? HoloH3ro!
HU-HA！
HU-HA!
いいわねいいわね！
Great, great, great!
いいわ、ついに3期生は息ぴったり
Awesome. Finally, Gen 3 is in sync.
そうわ、まだまだ元気が残りそうね
Yeah, looks like everyone's still full of energy.
だって、今日の一曲目だけどももうすごく伝わってくるんだもん
I mean, even from our first song today, I can really feel it.
みんな、まさか私たちの1曲目が「100％」だったなんて思ってた？
Did you guys ever suspect that our first song would be "100%"?
思うわけないよな、私もびっくりした
No way anyone did. Even I was surprised myself.
ホシノヴァ気分でライブ開始だなんて！すごいよね？
Opening with Hoshinova mode like that. It was cool, right?
かっこいいっすね、しかもさっきゼータとが歌った…いや違う
It was so cool. Especially earlier when Zeta sang... no, wait.
ゼータとか？ゼータとカエラが歌った時はもう本家の「100％」みたいっす
Zeta? When Zeta and Kaela sang "100%", it felt like the real "100%".
マジかっこよすぎなんだけど、なんか、うー！うー！ってなってき！
It was just way too cool, I was like, "Whoa! Whoa!"
あんあなかっこいい歌を歌ったことあるのかな？
Have you guys ever sung such a cool song before?
かっこつけてんの？本物のかっこつけ
Aura farming? Real aura farming right there.
そう、かっこつけてる、だってムーナの曲がかっこいいもん
Yeah, it was cool. Moona's songs are just so cool.
だってゼータがいつもスタイリッシュとかジャズっぽい曲ばっかっしょ？
Because Zeta usually does stylish or jazzy songs, right?
だからさっき「100％」を歌った時めっちゃ雰囲気が違う
So when we sang "100%" just now, the vibes felt completely different.
しかもカエラのラップも！
And Kaela's rap too!
なんかこう…とにかくかっこよかった！すごいわ！
It was like... anyway, it was so cool! Amazing!
とにかくかっこよかった！すごいわ！
Yeah, it was really cool, really cool earlier.
でも、それだけじゃないよ！次の曲が「NEW ZOMBIE!!」でした！
But that's not all! The next song was "NEW ZOMBIE!!".
これだれの曲かわかるよね？
I'm sure you all know whose song this is?
もちろんたよ、うちの先輩だ
Of course, it's our senpai's.
holoroのパフォーマンスもめっちゃかっこよかったよ、まるでゲームの中にいるみたいだった
Holoro's performance was also really cool, it felt like being inside a game.
そうっわ！しかもバックダンサーもいたし
That's right! And there were backup dancers too, man.
かっこよかったっすね！
It was so cool, guys! Right?!
他になんかあったかな？レーザーも花火も…
What else was there? Laser lights and fireworks too.
すごいギミックがたくさんあったっすね！
There were so many amazing stage gimmicks!
あのバックダンサーたちあたしのソロライブに雇うっす
I'm going to hire all those backup dancers for my solo concert.
おっと、もうソロライブの話？
Whoa, already talking about a solo concert.
まあ言葉も祈りってやつ
Well, thoughts become prayers.
でもこのライブはまだ終わらないよ！まだあど！
But this concert isn't over yet. Not yet, not yet.
でも…さっき何の歌を歌ったか知ってる？
But... do you guys know what song was sung before this?
もちろんたよ、私の新しい曲たから
Of course I know, it's my new song, "dahlah.".
そうっすね、まあいいや
Yeah, forget it.
まあいい
Forget it.
いやいや！タイトルは「dahlah.」だよ！「dahlah.」！
No, wait! The title is "dahlah.". "dahlah."!
おおなるほど
Oh, I see.
「dahlah.」だったか…先に言ってよ！
So it was "dahlah."... You should've said so!
だっていつもそれ言ってるじゃん、本当にまぁいいやって思ってた
You say it all the time, I thought you were just being casual.
それ言って帰ると思ってた
I thought you were just saying it and going home.
じゃあ「dahlah.」ってどういう意味？
So what does "dahlah." actually mean?
人生はしょうがないって意味。人生は重いからまあいいやって言えばいいたけ、その後人生を続けようって意味
It's about letting go. Life is hard, so just say "whatever", then keep moving forward with your life.
そうっすね、大人になったらね
That's true. Now that we're adults.
Untung lagunya santai, easy listening,
Fortunately, the song was chill and easy listening,
jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan, nyapa fans, gitu ya?
so we could walk around and greet the fans, right?
Asik banget ya tadi ya?
It was really fun, wasn't it?
Aku juga suka banget tadi dance bagian ref-nya ya?
I also really liked the dance during the chorus.
Da la da la da la da la da da la da da...
Itu... itu beda lagu gak sih?
Wait... isn't that a different song?
Gak gitu...
Not like that...
Da la da la da la da la da da la da da...
Enggak gitu kah?
Is it not?
Ya tapi pokoknya asik lah ya kalau nyanyi lagu chill santai-santai kayak gini.
But anyway, it's fun to sing chill, relaxed songs like this.
Iya santai dong. Tapi ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu.
Yeah, chill for sure. But speaking of relaxing, we can't actually relax just yet.
Hei, santai!
Hey, relax!
Katanya nggak boleh santai-santai!
I thought we weren't allowed to relax!
Iya iya iya,
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
jangan santai-santai, jangan terlalu santai.
don't relax, don't be too relaxed.
Karena konsernya tuh masih panjang!
Because the concert is still long!
Jadi sebelum itu kalian ada nggak yang mau kalian sampain dulu?
So before that, is there anything you'd like to say?
Mulai dari ini nih yang gak bisa diem.
Starting with this one who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja:
Just three words:
I love you.
Keren! The best! Sangat jelas ya.
Cool! The best! Very clear, indeed.
Tetap semangat, tetap semangat menjalani hidup ya. Udah gitu aja.
Keep up the spirit, keep up the spirit in living life. That's all.
Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang. Semangat!
Anyway, it's still a long way to the end. Fighting!
Sarangheyo! Gomawoyo!
I love you! Thank you!
Oke kalau aku, ya semangat selalu. Semangat santai.
Okay for me, always keep up the spirit. Relaxed spirit.
Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai ya!
Relaxed spirit, okay!
Semangat santai apa tuh?
What's 'relaxed spirit'?
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjut ke...
Okay then, let's move on to...
Wait wait wait, tunggu dulu!
Wait, wait, wait! Hold on!
Sebelum selesai-selesai ini nih ya,
Before we finish up here,
kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu gak sih?
shouldn't we shout together with the audience?
Iya ayo!
Yeah, let's do it!
Ayo ayo!
Come on, come on!
Oke oke. Jadi kita teriak bareng ya. Dalam hitungan tiga,
Okay, okay. So let's shout together. On the count of three,
kita sama-sama teriak 'Chromatic Future'. Oke ya?
we'll all shout 'Chromatic Future'. Got it?
Oke oke! Chromatic... Chromatic Future! Gitu kan ya?
Okay, okay! Chromatic... Chromatic Future! Like that, right?
Iya iya kayak gitu, kayak gitu.
Yeah, yeah, like that, like that.
Oke langsung ya, sambil lihat sini sini sini! Sambil lihat!
Okay, right away, while looking here, here, here! While looking!
Aku ya aku aku, aku yang penonton ini nih, penonton sini nih!
Me, me, me! I'm with these fans, the fans over here!
Aku ini deh, yang tengah yang tengah! Halo!
I'll take this one, the middle one! Hello!
Oke bareng-bareng ya! Satu, dua, tiga!
Okay, all together! One, two, three!
Chromatic Future!
Everything was easy,
I did it all alone
So effortlessly,
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Got all problems solved without any setbacks,
there is nothing uncontrolled
There's no way I can begin,
dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta soar a little higher,
hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a peacock with its wings
Kan kutaklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With the magic of the wind, I will invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit melawan dunia
Everyone who is asleep to rise and face the world
We'll never give up, as long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain, which anchor down us
Walking step by step, trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go! Just believe me!
Let it go, they'll never bring me down, just believe me
Let it go, they'll never bring us down, just believe me
From up there, cruelty,
still am I royalty
And when the universe works against me I will just... let it go
If it's messy, just sip some tea, let it go
Let it go!
I've been living carefree,
there's no bitter words in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold, not letting it show
Things but I'm bigger than my feelings,
so that'll be enough
There is no way I can begin,
dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta be better than ever,
hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a peacock with its wings
Kan kutaklukkan gelap
I will conquer the darkness
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With the magic of the wind, I will invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit
Everyone who is asleep to rise
...melawan dunia.
...against the world.
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves,
We could rise above the pain.
We're stronger than them.
Walking step by step,
Trusting by your pace,
Giving me what I deserve to have.
Let's go!
Believe me,
Let it go.
They'll never bring me down, just believe me.
It'll never bring us down, just believe me.
Won't let their cruelty
Steal my royalty.
And when the universe
Was against me, I will just...
Let it go.
Let it go!
Come on guys, let's do this!
One, two, three, let it go!
Let it go!
hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future