(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
QUEEN MOTHER
ELIZABETH'S 3D SHOWCASE!
KUREIJI HOT CHOCOLATE
WHAT THE FRIGGS
NOT JUST-ICE
Good day, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to the Queen Mother Theater.
May I remind you to unwrap the snacks you may wish to nom,
and please switch your mobile phones on, as photography is allowed.
Please feel free to take screenshots during the performance using the hashtag...
...#ERB3D.
Spread your Queen's performance far and wide.
本日はクイーンマザーシアターへご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to the Queen Mother Theater today.
開演に先立ち、いくつかご案内申し上げます。
Before we begin, I have a few announcements.
館内での飲食は大歓迎です。
Eating and drinking inside is most welcome.
お手元のお菓子はどうぞご自由にお楽しみください。
Please feel free to enjoy the snacks you have.
本公演は撮影OK。携帯電話は電源オンのままで、
Photography is allowed. Please keep your mobile phones powered on,
スクリーンショットには#ERB3Dのハッシュタグを添え、ぜひSNSへご投稿して、
and please post your screenshots to social media with the hashtag #ERB3D,
女王陛下の魅力を世界の隅々までお届けください。
to spread Her Majesty's charm to every corner of the world.
LOVELY TO SEE YOU
Thank you, and enjoy the performance!
Huzza!
さあ、それでは間もなく開演のお時間です。
Well then, it's almost time for the performance to begin.
どうぞお席にて、女王陛下の舞台を心ゆくまでお楽しみください。
Please enjoy Her Majesty's stage from your seats to your heart's content.
ハッツァ！
Huzza!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, what the freak?
Don't get in my way!
I don't have time to deal with the likes of you!
Wait back, and take this!
Golly.
Oh-ho-ho! Know your place!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
And those who dare interfere with me shall receive no mercy.
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Good grief.
And today of all days, my commemorative 3D showcase!
Getting ambushed like this has been quite troublesome.
Stuck with all the showcase preparations and practice I need to do.
I can't afford to waste time on something like this.
There's not enough hours in the day. How annoying.
All right, you pop yourself there, Thorn. Stay there, stay there.
Listen to this, my self-introduction.
I shall practice.
Oh-ho-ho-ha!
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue.
Also known as the Scarlet Queen, the Harbinger of Order, Leader of Justice.
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Lovely to see you, to see you, lovely!
All right, well, how was that?
Tough crowd.
Oh gosh, I'm so behind!
We need to get to the karaoke place, Thorn. Come on, let's go!
What the freak?
You lot again? You never learn, do you?
All right, I guess it's time for round two.
Oh my god, Thorn!
You dare wound my flames?
You'll pay for this.
Very well, I'll deal with you...
...while practicing a song for my 3D showcase!
Two birds, one stone. Listen well!
Huzzah!
踊 / Lyrics: DECO*27 Music: Giga, TeddyLoid
Odo / Lyrics: DECO*27 Music: Giga, TeddyLoid
半端ならK.O.
Half-baked? Then it's a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
If you want to feel light and fluffy, go ahead
開演準備しちゃおうかな
Maybe I'll start getting ready for the show
巻いても沸いても哀・燦々
Whether fast or heated, it's sorrowful and brilliant
惚れ正能
Bewitching true talent
低音響かせろ ろろろ
Let the bass resound, ro-ro-ro
なんとまあつまらない事 まるでおっしゃる通り
How incredibly boring, exactly as you say
ロンリーロンリーロンリーとハンディ 窮屈だそう
Lonely, lonely, lonely... it seems being handy is quite cramped
やんなっちゃってドロンに馬鹿法度だ論外
Sick of it all, so I'm disappearing; foolish laws are out of the question
溺れて落ちて 永 そろそろいいか
Drowning and falling into eternity... isn't it about time?
もっと頑張って上がりまで もっと頑張って
Try harder, keep going until you're on top, try even harder
繋がるわ一人より二人 増えたら心配ないや
We're connected; when one becomes two, there's nothing to worry about
All right 任せてドンマイ 波に相なんだい みんなで乗っちゃいバイ！
All right, leave it to me, don't mind; what's with the waves? Let's all ride them, bye!
パッパッパッと救い出しちゃいそう
I'm likely to rescue you in a flash
半端ならK.O.
Half-baked? Then it's a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
If you want to feel light and fluffy, go ahead
開演準備しちゃおうかな
Maybe I'll start getting ready for the show
巻いても沸いても哀・燦々
Whether fast or heated, it's sorrowful and brilliant
惚れ正能 (正能)
Bewitching true talent (True talent)
低音響かせろ ろろろろろろろろろろろろイェイ！
Let the bass resound, ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro-ro, yeah!
今宵はだんだん だんだん
Tonight, gradually, gradually
わわわわわわ
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa
踊り出せ 踊り出せ 孤独は先に参るなえ
Start dancing, start dancing; don't let loneliness get to you first
わわわわわわ
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa-wa
いつまでも足宛て拡大 バイバイ レッツゴー
Struggling forever, expanding... bye-bye, let's go!
どどどどどめはどこだってどうでもいい今日の化粧
It doesn't matter where the finishing blow comes from; today's makeup...
最高で突っ込んで突っ込んでしまっちゃうでしょう
...is the best, and I'll end up charging right in, won't I?
Up and down attention めまい点灯外
Up and down attention; dizziness lit up outside
どパッと吹き出そうの熱伝の鳥如く
Like a bird of heat conduction about to burst out
別に興味ない 特に感心ない
I'm not really interested; not particularly impressed
むせ返るほど絶え絶え絶頂へ
Drowning to the point of choking, to the peak of exhaustion
合図を
A signal...
ラタタタタラ... yeah
Ratatatatara... yeah
ほら据まって 夜行だ
Look, stay steady, it's the night parade
愛イヤ 鳴いていこう
Ai yeah, let's keep on shouting
パラパパパラ パラパパパラ...
Parapapapara, parapapapara...
...パラパパパラ パラパパパラ...
...parapapapara, parapapapara...
...パラパパパラ パラパラパン
...parapapapara, parapara-pan
カンパネラ K-O
Campanella K-O
Uwah woah woah...
ほとりに据え ほとりに据え
Settled by the side, settled by the side
辛く濯ぎ 祭の日に
Rinsing bitterly on the festival day
Uwah woah woah...
縁留めまで 足よ寝
Until the end of the bond, oh feet, rest
今宵は安針パーティーだ
Tonight is an Anjin party
Uwah woah woah...
摩天楼の格子を きっと woo...
The lattices of the skyscraper, surely woo...
Uwah woah woah...
誓いまで お元気で
Until the vow, stay well
隠れりバイバイ Let's go
If you hide, bye-bye, let's go
This is... THE END!
Ooh yeah!
Huzzah!
Is that the last of them?
Hmm.
My flame... it grows small due to my nerves.
I need to shake it off.
I can't appear before everyone like this.
Ah... my phone.
Oh... what the frig?
My karaoke room booking plus?
I don't have a lot of time till the showcase!
Okay...
Alright, time to go to karaoke. Come on, Thorn.
Okay.
Onwards and upwards! Hah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Sorry, sorry, sorry! Gomen!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Sorry, sorry, sorry! Sorry!
Goodbye, parting is such sweet sorrow, but I will see you on the morrow!
Thank you, thank you!
Until the next battle! Yes, alright!
Here we go. Huzzah!
Alright.
Let's go!
Fallen Angel feat. Aimee B
Lyrics: LiSA
Music: Mitsunori Ikeda
Heaven, please sing for me a song of life.
Heaven, take me into your skies.
There's no place here for me to hide my cries.
Night and day I'm missing you.
I know I'm here for the magic.
All your stars guiding me through and through.
Oh, why does this loneliness feel like forever and ever?
I gotta be, I gotta be in your arms, baby.
So close, so close.
And it's you that I believe in, I believe in.
So close...
...but far away so far I can't touch.
I'll hold on, 'cause it's you I love so dearly.
When the rain, the storm and all is done...
...caress me with your sweet lullaby.
Heaven, please sing for me a song of light
Heaven, save me and my dreams tonight
Someday these wings will perish in your sight
Night and day I call for you
Flashes of moments so tragic
Wandering souls they fall along the way
Tell me you will never leave me forever and ever
I gotta be I gotta be in your arms hear me
So close, so close
And it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away I seek for your light
I'll hold on 'cause for you my heart keeps beating
When the wind, the fire and all is gone
Caress me with your sweet lullaby
Will you be my light? Will you be my strength?
Promise you won't let me go
I'll never betray in the end of time
Still my love's gonna be there
So close, so close
And it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away, so far I can't touch
I'll hold on 'cause it's you I love so dearly
When the rain, the storm and all is gone
Caress me with your sweet lullaby
So close, so close
And it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away I seek for your light
I'll hold on 'cause for you my heart keeps beating
When the wind, the fire and all is gone
Caress me with your sweet lullaby
Hmm... well...
This song is lovely,
but for my showcase performance, should I pick nostalgic songs?
Hmm...
Oh, it's a call!
Bleeh! My favorite kohai!
How are you, Bibi?
Ollie-senpai! Perfect timing.
Actually, I'm having trouble deciding what to sing for my 3D showcase.
Yeah...
Is that so?
Though I think I speak for everyone when I say,
"We'll be happy to hear you sing anything!"
As long as you're enjoying yourself, that is.
Yeah, but...
Isn't it standard to pick songs that match your image?
There's an expectation to be cool, right?
But since this is a special occasion and all, I was thinking maybe I should show other sides of myself.
Hmm, I see.
Well, you know how powerful you look when you sing?
Yes, yes.
So I thought, you know...
Why not try a cute song instead?
Go for that gap moe appeal, you know what I'm saying?
Cute song... that would be different from usual, which would be good,
but I'm a bit worried about doing it alone. Hmm...
Ah! That's it!
What if we invited my brothers-in-arms, ARMIS as guests?
That's a great idea!
Seeing cool people singing cute songs...
Oh, the gap moe will definitely get everybody excited!
But... it's still a tad embarrassing.
It'll be fine!
Come on, try imagining it.
Picture you and ARMIS singing a cute song together!
Okay... me and ARMIS...
Cute song...
...together!
可愛くてごめん
Kawaikute Gomen (Sorry for Being Cute)
Lyrics, Music: shito
私は私のこと愛して
I love myself
何が広いの？ヒーローでしょうか
What's wrong with that? I'm a hero, right?
痛いだとかなんとか言われても
Even if they say it hurts or whatever
届きませんね そのヴィトリオリック
Those vitriolics won't reach me
大好きな抱擁は省く
I'll skip the favorite hugs
大好きなお化粧で
With my favorite makeup
お決まりのハーフツイン巻いて
With my usual half-twin tails
お出かけしよう
Let's go out
日傘持ってぼっちだって
Holding a parasol even if I'm alone
幸せだもん
Because I'm happy
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born
チュ！あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for acting calculated
気になっちゃうよねごめん
You'll be curious about me, right? Sorry
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for making an effort
チュ！尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for being so feminine
むかつく？言っちゃうよね ざまあ
Annoyed? You're saying it, right? Serve you right
貴方は貴方のことだけどうぞ
You worry about yourself only, please
私に干渉しないでください
Please don't interfere with me
類は友を呼ぶと言うけど
They say birds of a feather flock together, but
届きませんね その陰口
Those badmouthing won't reach me
重い奴 俗物
Serious guy, mundane guy
お気に入りのリップで
With my favorite lipstick
崩せない前髪クシでといて
Combing my bangs that won't get messed up
お出かけしよう
Let's go out
軽い女？ふざけるな
Loose woman? Don't mess with me
重すぎる角
Too heavy horns
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute
この時代生きてごめん
Sorry for living in this era
チュ！妬まれてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being envied
イケおじしちゃうよねごめん
I'll be a cool old guy, right? Sorry
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute
自分磨きしてごめん
Sorry for polishing myself
チュ！ぶりっ子でごめん
Chu! Sorry for acting cute
虜にしちゃっててごめん
Sorry for making you captivated
むかつく？言っちゃうよね ざまあ
Annoyed? You're saying it, right? Serve you right
趣味の違い変わり者とバカにされても
Even if I'm made fun of as an eccentric with different hobbies
負けたくない 怖くもない あんたらのこと
I don't want to lose, and I'm not afraid of you guys
希望の見方自分にありたい
I want to be on the side of hope for myself
一番大切にしてあげたい
I want to cherish myself the most
不実な仮面はさせたくない
I don't want to wear a dishonest mask
それが私
That is me
チュ！可愛くてごめん…生まれてきちゃってごめん…
Chu! Sorry for being cute... Sorry for being born...
チュ！あざとくてごめん…
Chu! Sorry for acting calculated...
人生楽しんでごめん
Sorry for enjoying life
チュ！可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for making an effort
チュ！尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for being so feminine
むかつく？言っちゃうよね ざまあ
Annoyed? You're saying it, right? Serve you right
Unyuu... Hyou. You know, maybe,
maybe I'm not cut out to be a ku-ku-ku-cute idol!
That's not true!
I'm sure everyone wants to see that side of you too, Liz!
Oh, but thank you, yeah! I feel better about it since you think so, Ollie-senpai!
It makes me happy you think I'm ku-ku-ku-powerful! Hahahaha!
Yeah! Powerful indeed! Hehehe.
Oh gosh, seems like it's the end of my karaoke room booking rehearsal time is up here.
Ollie-senpai, thank you so so much!
Alright, do your best, Liz! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! I shall!
Okay, here we go! Hup!
Okay, let's go, let's go!
Eh... Oh come on!
Alright, here we go! Woo!
Hmm, my singing is fine,
but now the physical performance side of bits and bobs is what worries me.
I'm really not too confident...
...about my dancing as I'm a... (chuckles) a tad rusty.
Oh, what's wrong Liz?
Zeta Senpai!
Well, actually, I've been worried about my showcase performance...
...as it's getting closer and closer, and I'm not very confident about my dancing.
Hmm, is that all? Don't worry, don't worry!
When it comes to dancing, as long as you have your passion...
...mistakes don't even exist.
Haha, yeah, true. But I'm still a bit worried.
Well, in that case, how about this? Come to my jazz club!
If we practice together, I'm sure you'll have more of a spring in your step.
Wait, right now?
Well, that's really nice of you Zeta Senpai, but you know...
Okay, follow me Liz!
Oh yeah, dance... (grunts)
Let's move and groove!
No, wait, Zeta Senpai!
Wait, what do you mean by move and groove? No, what the-?!
GIRI GIRI
Lyrics, Music: 水野良樹
Lyrics, Music: Yoshiki Mizuno
Yeah!
ギリギリで愛し合いましょう
Let's love each other on the edge
嘘も燃え尽くして夢にして
Burn away the lies and make them a dream
冗談じゃないもっと踊りたい
No joke, I want to dance more
もう我慢できない
I can't hold back anymore
I want I want I want 撃ちあけてくれ
I want, I want, I want you to open up to me
Sha la la la la...
Oh yeah!
Yeah!
Sha la la la la...
Oh yeah!
手錠のままでいい
It's fine to stay in handcuffs
素顔を見せてよ
Show me your true face
心乱されて欲しくなる
My heart is in disarray, and I start to want you
独占なんて嘘でしょう
Monopolizing me must be a lie
はぐらかしてじれったい
It's frustrating how you're being evasive
どうにかなりそう
I feel like I'm going crazy
口付けるほどに足りなくなる
The more we kiss, the more it's not enough
抱き寄せたら意外なほど
When I hold you close, surprisingly...
寂しい目で見つめるから
...you look at me with such lonely eyes...
逆効果だ だったったった
...it's counterproductive
ギラギラな夢を見せてよ
Show me a dazzling dream
全部ばら撒いて星にして
Scatter it all and turn it into stars
純情じゃないところも知りたい
I want to know your non-innocent parts too
もう我慢できない
I can't hold back anymore
I want I want I want 撃ちあけてくれ
I want, I want, I want you to open up to me
Sha la la la la...
Hi yeah!
Your turn. My turn. Mm-hm. Okay.
ドラマなんて飽きたでしょう
You must be tired of dramas
二人だけのラスト描かなくちゃ
We must draw a finale just for the two of us
運命だなんてじゃれあって
Joking about it being fate...
演じ切ればいいんじゃない
...why not just play the part until the end?
裏腹な言葉で
With contradictory words...
また覚悟を試してくるのに
...you're testing my resolve again
独りきりにさせないでよと
"Don't leave me alone," you say...
寂しげに笑うからずるいよ
...it's unfair how you smile so sadly
なななな
Na na na na
ギリギリな恋人たちは
Lovers on the edge...
切ないこの夜を満たせるね
...can satisfy this painful night
擬制じゃないもっと奥の方
It's not a pretense, even deeper inside...
震えていれば赤くなる
...it turns red if it trembles
I want I want I want 撃ちあけだしてくれ
I want, I want, I want you to start opening up to me
Sha la la la la...
Yeah!
泣かないで それ以上
Don't cry any more
心撃ち抜かないで
Don't shoot through my heart
震わせた瞳に狂わされてしまう
I'm driven mad by your trembling eyes
完璧な敗北さ
It's a perfect defeat
もう離せなんかしない
I won't ever let you go
この指を
These fingers...
この愛を
This love...
ギリギリで信じてほしい
I want you to believe, even on the edge
二人なら真実になれる
Together, we can become the truth
告白は最後の誓いさ
This confession is the final vow
もう抱きしめたいよ
I want to hold you already
ギリギリな愛を愛し合わそう
Let's share a love on the edge
遅まきもエキゾチックを夢見て
Dreaming of the exotic, even if it's late
冗談じゃない もう音 踊りたい
No joke, I want to dance to the sound already
もう我慢できない
I can't take it anymore
I want, I want を散らかしてくれ
Make a mess of "I want, I want"
Sha-la-la-la...
Oh yeah!
Oh yeah! Come on!
Hey!
Huh!
Go go!
ふう...
(Sighs)
So, how was it? Once you get into it,
it's a good feeling, right?
Dance like nobody's watching, have fun!
Yes! Somehow I really gained confidence.
Thank you, Zeta-senpai.
Oh, Liz. You always tell others mistake help them grow and believing in themselves.
You really need to start taking your own advice.
Listen to your own heart's flame.
Let that be your strength.
Yeah... You're right.
Sometimes I forget, but...
thank you for reminding me.
Guess I'm only human. Hahaha!
Here, let me help you take that off.
Hey, but I look so dapper though, innit?
It looks so cool!
Wah! Uh!
Ouch!
What's with you, Liz?
I'm sure your debut will be wonderful.
I'm looking forward to it.
As you say, believe in me...
...who believes in thee!
Huzzah!
Well, the preparations for the showcase seem to be going smoothly.
So much has happened since we infiltrated Holo.
Songs, performances,
troubles, challenges, and kind words too.
All of them are irreplaceable memories I'll cherish forever.
I want to do my best for my family, my friends, my kingdom,
and of course my talented girlies, Justice.
Onwards and upwards!
Flame off!
Phew, still, it's been such a busy day.
Maybe I should rest for a bit.
Just a little... little nap won't hurt anybody.
My manager says I should nap anyways, so it's fine.
一番の宝物 ~Yui final ver.~
Ichiban no Takaramono ~Yui final ver.~
Lyrics, Music: 麻枝准
Lyrics, Music: Jun Maeda
顔を合わしたら 喧嘩してばかり
Every time we faced each other, we did nothing but fight
それもいい思い出だった
Even that was a good memory
君が教えてくれたんだ もう怖くない
You taught me that I'm not afraid anymore
どんな不自由でも 幸せは掴める だから
No matter the hardship, I can grasp happiness, so...
一人でもゆくよ たとえ辛くても
I'll go on alone, even if it's painful
君と見た夢は 必ず持ってくよ
The dream I shared with you, I'll definitely take it with me
あった
...there were,
他の誰でもない
and it was no one else.
出会えた目覚めた朝
The morning I met you and woke up,
君はいないんだね
you aren't here, are you?
ずっと遊んでた
We played together forever,
そんな気がしてた
or so it felt like.
気がしていただけ
It was just a feeling,
わかってた
I knew that.
生まれてきたこと
Even having been born,
もう後悔はしない
I won't regret it anymore.
祭りの後みたい
It's like after a festival,
寂しいけどそろそろ行こう
it's lonely, but it's time to go.
どこまでも行くよ
I'll go anywhere,
ここでしたこと
the things I did here,
幸せという夢
that dream called happiness,
を叶えてみせるよ
I'll make it come true.
君と離れても
Even if I'm away from you,
どんなに遠くなっても
no matter how far apart we are,
新しい朝に
at the dawn of a new morning,
あたしは生きるよ
I will live on.
一人でも行くよ
I'll go even if I'm alone,
死にたくなっても
even if I feel like dying.
声が聞こえるよ
I can hear a voice,
死んではいけないと
telling me I mustn't die.
たとえ辛くても
Even if it's painful,
寂しさに泣いても
even if I cry from loneliness,
心の奥には
deep within my heart,
ぬくもりを感じるよ
I feel a warmth.
巡って流れて
Circling and flowing,
時は移ろいだ
time has shifted.
もう何があったか
What happened before,
思い出せないけど
I can't remember anymore, but...
目を閉じてみれば
If I try closing my eyes,
誰かの笑い声
I hear someone's laughter.
なぜかそれが今
For some reason, that is now
一番の宝物
my most precious treasure.
一人でも行くよ
I'll go even if I'm alone,
どこまでも行くよ
I'll go anywhere,
Hmm... (yawns)
Oh, that dream.
What a beautiful, touching song.
You know what? I should probably add that to my showcase.
(Gasps)
MY SHOWCASE!
Oh no!
Flame on!
Oh gosh! I'm gonna be late for my showcase! What the fudge!
All right. My showcase, my showcase, my showcase.
All right. Open door! Let's go!
Come on! Ah!
Now Loading
ELIZABETH ROSE BLOODFLAME
Rosarians!
My Bloodflame Kingdom!
How is the performance thus far?
Let me know what you all think using the hashtag ERB 3D.
ERB 3D.
What have you loved most thus far?
Is it this beautiful theater?
The Queen Mother Theatre? Named after me mum.
Hi, Mum!
(Laughs) Hello!
Was it Ollie's appearance? Flayon and Oga's voiceovers?
Kawaikute Gomen sung with ARMIS?
Giri Giri with Ze-a?
Oh gosh, it would make me super-duper happy hearing your thoughts.
And by the way, I can see you all right now!
Oh my gosh! I see you guys!
I see you at the corner of my eye with a magical invisible box...
...made by the Rosarian invisible wizards!
So I can see you all right now! Oh my gosh!
This is crazy. What do you think about my 3D appearance?
Huh? Huh? Let me know in chat right now...
...what poses you would like to see.
Yeah, yeah, let me know. While you're doing that...
...I'm going to go get Thorn.
Yeah! It's the one, the only, Thorn!
Hello, I'm Thorn! (Laughs)
Let's do a quick pose with Thorn, shall we?
Hah! Huzzah!
Huzzah! (Laughs)
All right, let's see what you guys have put.
Um... huh? A cat pose?
Hah! All right, sure. Let me just put Thorn over here.
Let's take the jacket off for this one. Flame off!
Okay... I need to become Raora.
Nya, nya-nya! Nya!
Nya-nya, nya! Nya! Ah...
T-pose? Okay!
That one's easy! (Laughs)
Yes! I shall assert my dominance on you all!
Oh, you know what I want to do? I want to headpat you all.
Come here! I headpat.
Headpat, headpat, and hug!
Hah! We must do this, we must hug!
Hug, hug! Hah! One more!
What else have you all put? Victory pose?
Like this?
Hah!
Yes, I am victorious!
For I am the Queen of the Bloodflame Kingdom!
Yeah.
I love you all very much too!
So happy you're all here!
Oh gosh.
Absolute cinema, yes!
Okay.
Oh, a twirl? Okay, we shall do a twirl.
All right.
Hah! Yes.
Twirl.
Whoa!
Is that okay?
A twirl.
Jazz hands.
A spin! Spina!
Twina!
Oh gosh. A curtsy? Oh, that's a good one.
Like this...
I curtsy.
And I bow.
Cute? Hey, you mean... you mean...
...you mean powerful, right?
Powerful! Yes, yes, yes! Powerful!
Rawr!
I know you guys also like my shocked face.
So let me just think of something real shocking.
What the frig!?
What the frig!
What the frig! Time is nearly up for poses!
Oh, I guess it's time for the next song!
Would you like to hear another song?
Yes! Sure you do!
All right, just wait one moment. I need some bits and bobs for this one.
All right. Some bits and the bobs...
...and the bobs and the bits.
All right.
Here we go. Here's the bits and the bobs.
I have a stand. It's my mic!
Look at that! And I have a guitar.
Ha! I'm so かっこいい.
Ha! I'm so cool.
All right. Let's go with a cute... I mean, a powerful song next.
Please listen to: 私の恋はホッチキス
Please listen to: Watashi no Koi wa Hotchkiss
The next song is 'My Love is a Stapler'. Let's go!
わたしの恋はホッチキス
My Love is a Stapler
Lyrics: 稲葉エミ Music: 藤末樹
Lyrics: Emi Inaba Music: Miki Fujisue
なんてなんだろう　気になる理由
Why is it, I wonder? The reason I'm curious.
君へのこの想い　便箋にね
These feelings for you, on this letter paper...
書いてみるよ
I'll try writing them down.
もしかして　気まぐれかもしれない
Maybe it's just a whim.
それなのに枚数だけ
And yet, only the number of pages...
増えていくよ
Keeps increasing.
好きの確率　割り出す計算式
If only there were a calculation formula to figure out the probability of love,
あればいいのに
it would be nice.
キラキラ光る願い事も
Sparkling wishes,
ぐちゃぐちゃへたる悩み事も
And messy, tiring worries,
そうだホッチキスで
That's right, with a stapler,
とじちゃおう
let's fasten them together.
始まりだけは軽いノリで
The beginning was just a light feeling,
知らないうちに熱くなって
But before I knew it, I became passionate,
もう針がなんだか
And now the staples...
通らない
...won't go through.
また明日
See you tomorrow.
どうしようかな　読み返すの恥ずかしい
What should I do? It's embarrassing to read it back.
あれこれと便箋にね
Even though I wrote this and that...
書いたくせに
...on the letter paper.
気持ちごと　ゴミ箱行きじゃなんだか
If I throw these feelings in the trash can,
この胸が切ないから
my heart will feel so painful,
持っていようかな
so maybe I'll keep them.
今の気持ちを　表す
Expressing my current feelings,
辞書にもない
is not even in the dictionary.
わたしの恋はホッチキス
My Love is a Stapler
君がいないと何もできないよ
Without you, I can't do anything
言葉
The words
探すよ
I'll search for them
ワクワクしちゃう計画とか
Exciting plans and...
グタグタスキル展開とか
...clumsy skill developments
全部ホッチキスで
I'll staple them all
閉じちゃお
Together
今日のできごと 思い出して
Remembering today's events
いつも心がキュンとなって
My heart always skips a beat
もう針がないから
I'm out of staples
買わなくちゃ
So I have to buy more
ララ また明日
La la, see you tomorrow
キラキラ光る願い事も
Even sparkling wishes and...
ぐちゃぐちゃへたる悩みごとも
...messy, draining worries
そうだホッチキスで
That's it, I'll staple them
閉じちゃお
Together
始まりだけはわかる祈りで
With a prayer that only knows the beginning
知らないうちに熱くなって
It gets hot before I know it
もう針がなんだか
For some reason, the staples
通らない
Won't go through
ララ また明日
La la, see you tomorrow
Wooh!
And that was "My Love is a Stapler"!
How was it? Did you like my guitar playing?
Oi! Well, you guys didn't know this,
but I'm actually a professional air guitarist.
I know, I know. Surprise, shocker.
Professional air guitarist here. Look out!
Anywho, now it's time for an announcement!
Everyone, let's call for our favorite four-legged friend, Bobby!
3, 2, 1, Bobby!
Come here Bobby, you're such a good boy.
Yes, you're a good boy. Yeah,
show yourself to the camera, do a little twirl or something, yeah.
Oh, you're so cute.
Wait a minute! What the freak?
Bobby!
We should... come here, come here, come here.
Up you get.
Oh, he's such a little cheeky guy. Little cheeky guy.
Oh golly.
Well, as you can see on Bobby's head,
the announcement is merchandise!
Oh my goodness, we have this!
Ba-ba-da-daa!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame Paper Knife & Acrylic Stand
Wow! A paper knife letter opener inspired by my sword, Thorn.
A set product that includes an acrylic stand
where you can plop your mini Thorn into.
It looks real cool on your desk and you'll get all the maidens.
I should know, a lot of them have visited my dressing room to see the prototype.
And that's no lie, it's pretty awesome.
And also, the sales date will be after the Justice collaboration stream.
So once that's all done and dusted, it'll be out there on the shop.
And that concludes the merchandise. Thank you Bobby!
Everybody thank Bobby! Thank you Bobby!
Thank you so much! You're such a good boy,
you're such a good boy, yes you are, you are, you are!
Alright, back to the Duke and the Queen Mother you go.
Oh gosh, I honestly can't believe it. Time has flown.
And it's already time for our last final seventh song, "Symphony"!
This has been quite the journey and a half,
so before I end, I just want to thank everyone.
The cast, our wonderful guests, the crew, managers, the director.
Thank you so much. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you, thank you so much.
And of course, my friends, my family, my beautiful kingdom.
Thanks for supporting me so much. I wouldn't be standing here right now.
Not only do I get to fight for justice,
but with my wonderful girlies, Raora, Gigi...
...Gigi, and Cecilia,
but I also get to do what I love.
So thank you so much.
I get to give the gift of smiles
and strength through the art of performance and singing.
I hope I can do this forever
and we could keep spreading smiles throughout the realms together.
That would make me so happy.
Anyway, before the allergies hit me too much,
let me just move my stand.
Allergies guys, the allergies.
I can't stand the stand!
It must get out of the way!
Don't mind me.
Alright, wait a minute.
Before I do my last tune,
we gotta bring back my beautiful backing dancers, right?
Come on! Flame on!
And they're back.
Are you ready?
Yes, yes, yes!
And now, for our final song,
please listen to "Hero too".
Hands up!
I want to be an idol and a hero for all of you too!
Let's go!
Hero too
Lyrics: 夢乃ぺた (from Dizzy Sunfist) Music: 林ゆうき
Lyrics: Peta Yumeno (from Dizzy Sunfist) Music: Yuki Hayashi
Onwards and upwards! Huzzah!
What am I to be?
What is my calling?
I gave up giving up, I'm ready to go!
Future's left unseen,
it all depends on me.
Put it on the line to follow my dream, yeah!
Tried all my life,
I've tried to find
something that makes me hold on and never let go.
Hero too, I am a hero too.
My heart is set,
and I won't back down.
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero.
True heroes stand up for what they believe,
so wait and see.
Yeah!
So wait and see.
What do they think of me?
What do they think I'll be?
I could not care less,
I don't wanna know.
Am I doing right?
Am I satisfied?
I wanna live my life like it's meant to be, yeah!
Tried all my life,
I've tried to find
something that makes me hold on and never let go.
Hero too, I am a hero too.
My heart is set,
and I won't back down.
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero.
True heroes stand up for what they believe.
People will judge for no reason at all.
Can they might try to tear our dreams down?
Don't listen.
They may look down on me,
count me out.
I'm going my own way.
They may look down on me,
count me out.
I'm a hero,
I've got music!
Hero too, I am a hero too.
My heart is set,
and I won't back down.
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero.
True heroes stand up for what they believe,
yeah I'll be.
Hero too, I am a hero too.
My heart is set,
and I won't back down, huzzah!
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero.
True heroes stand up for what they believe,
so wait and see.
I have met so many heroes in my life.
Gave me the strength and courage to survive.
Gave me the power to smile every day.
Now it's my turn to be the one to make you smile.
Yeah...
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah...
...to make you smile!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Parting is such sweet sorrow, but I will see you on the morrow.
Make sure to eat good noms. もぐもぐ。
Make sure to eat good noms. Munch munch.
Hydrate! 水、水。
Hydrate! Water, water.
And get good sleeps! 寝、寝。
And get good sleeps! Sleep, sleep.
As we want our Bloodflame Kingdom to be happy and strong.
大きく成れ。
Grow big and strong.
Let's try our best together.
これからも一緒に頑張ろう。
Let's keep doing our best together.
Onwards and upwards! And don't forget...
...that my voice be your strength.
チュチュチュ！
Chu chu chu!
Cheer for everyone as loud as you can!
Rosarians, HUZZAH!
HUZZAH!
innit
QUEEN MOTHER
Dear Rosarians, my beautiful Sparks of Joy,
the smiles and happiness I get from performing for you all
I'll cherish and forever appreciate.
Thank you for making my wishes come true
BIG HUGS my Bloodflame Kingdom - Liz