(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
The Empress
Empress (Calliope ver.)
Lyrics: てにをは (歌い分け：Mori Calliope)
Music, Arrangement: てにをは
Lyrics: てにをは (Vocal arrangement: Mori Calliope)
私は手近 いで醜い
I'm close at hand, and I'm ugly
テンプレートに流し込まれたみたい
It's like I was poured into a template
デコレーションじゃ隠せない生来の拳、刻
My innate style can't be hidden with decorations... Strike
Remember the name, it's self-obsessed some might say
Ignore the cause, ain't no praise, begin those days
Listen up those place notes, but it's more than just a pretty face
Poison grace, poison snakes, cut the race, cut the brakes
It’s got to be the way you carry yourself
So dissimilar to royalties, hilarious wealth
Nature's spoiling me and you, we should bury ourselves
Or you can sneak atop the throne by honest stylish stealth
So Empress (Wake up!)
心におわす
Dwell in my heart
Empress
どうかお与えください
Please grant it
Empress, Empress
Empress
Wake up, Empress me
左様さ、いかにあるべきか
That's right, how should I be?
Show them all you for
In this diamond-in-the-rough
いつまでも
Forever
偽物でも　ほら
Even if it's a fake, look
背筋が伸びてきたでしょ
Your posture has straightened, hasn't it?
ハイカラ作った　このティアラ
This stylish tiara I made
そろそろ誰が　本物なのか
It's about time we found out who the real one is
教えてあげなくちゃ
I'll have to show you
No matter how much space is rented for rent,
I'm barely out of pocket and beauty's at no expense, okay?
Look confident, got you bouncing up on a fence,
To the left lies the tempts, so you better use some common sense.
Okie-dokie, okay then, Empress,
a miracle in the mirror straight up not impressive me.
Day to day it's clear I make such a mess of me,
Fresh face, dress me to freshen all the guests and be...
Empress,
心のまま
As your heart desires
Empress,
美しくおありなさい
Stay beautiful
Empress, Empress, Empress...
Empress!
Wake up, Empress in me
ほら、頭を垂れなさい
Now, bow your head
Show them why it's time to
do much more than meets the eye.
蔓延ってるあの
That widespread,
市民権得た流行のビシャス
socially accepted trendy vice
ほっとけ　涙が勿体ないから
Leave it be, your tears are a waste
そろそろ誰が　本物なのか
It's about time we found out who the real one is
教えてあげなくちゃ
I'll have to show you
桜は　己を
The cherry blossoms realize
美しと自覚せるか
That they are beautiful
蓮華は　自分を
The lotus blossoms bloom
可憐だと思い咲けるか
Thinking that they are lovely
漏れなく　こよなく
Without fail, dearly
魂を磨くこと
Polish your soul
気高く　濁らず
Nobly, without getting muddy
美をばよ　全う致しましょう
Let's fulfill our beauty
目覚めよ、Empress in me
Awaken, Empress in me
さぁ、玉座を空けなさい
Now, clear the throne
Show them why it's time to
burn it down and take the throne.
Empress in me
もっと頭を垂れなさい
Bow your head lower
Show them why it's time to
do much more than meets the eye.
偽物でも　ほら
Even if it's a fake, look
背筋が伸びてきたでしょ
Your posture has straightened, hasn't it?
ハイカラ作った　このティアラ
This stylish tiara I made
そろそろ誰が　本物なのか
It's about time we found out who the real one is
分からせてあげましょう　優しく
I'll make you understand, gently
It's about time to reveal
it's the me that I knew was real all along.
Something's wrong, guess I gotta show you my appeal.
Wake me up, wake me up...
Uh oh, wake me up...
Uh oh, wake me up, wake me up...
Wake me up.
えへん！
Ahem!
皆さん、ようこそ、カリオペ誕生日ライブへ！
Welcome everyone to Calliope's Birthday Live!
Welcome everybody to this year's live show, ARCANA!
The Arcana is the means by which all is revealed.
Is it not, Dead Beats? I know you guys know what I'm talking about, right?
Check it out, first of all, this stage.
ステージ、素敵ですね。
The stage is wonderful, isn't it?
Look, we're in a crystal ball! Can you believe it?
This was all Mori's idea, which it might have been a bad idea...
...'cause I don't know how we're gonna get out of here. Well, we'll figure it out.
But in the meantime, guess what? I have assembled all of these tarot cards here.
Tarot cards featuring my friends!
For example, right, we have Marine-senchou, who I just performed Empress with.
Yes, yes, a bit of artwork on her card over here for The Empress, so lovely.
Thank you so much to Gumshrue for drawing these beautiful illustrations.
Um, but yeah, I decided to pick Arcana that, like, fit my friends.
But then I took it a bit further and decided, "What if we sang a bunch of Mori songs?"
そうですね、今日は森カリオペだけの曲、歌います！
That's right, today I'll sing only Mori Calliope songs!
That's right!
This show is Mori songs only. That's right.
And I tried to pick songs that fit the Arcana and then matched them up with talents...
...that I thought also fit the Arcana.
So we have some amazing guests lined up today...
...and I hope that you guys will get super excited because I've been looking forward to this for so long.
Thank you so much, everybody, for dropping by to be a part of this.
And you know what? You can continue to be a part of it.
How can you do that? You might ask. By using the hashtag!
Yes, up in one of these corners is gonna be the hashtag...
...it's probably over here, but it might also be over here.
Use the hashtag, okay?
Oh, the hashtag that we have decided upon
for this show, okay?
So make sure that you use that and then type
your impressions, right?
You guys love the internet.
You're always doing stuff on it...
...and saying silly stuff here, there and everywhere.
Go ahead and, you know,
upload screenshots and your thoughts and
impressions and I'll read 'em.
I'll read 'em later.
Once I've, you know, calmed down and stuff like that,
you know?
Because we got a show to do, right?
WE GOT A SHOW TO DO!
Let's try and have as much fun as we can while we
are stuck here in this crystal ball together.
For Mori's birthday, yes! And it's Mori's birthday,
so you know that we've got announcements, right?
Stick till the end because
we got a couple really big ones coming up and you
don't want to miss 'em.
If you want. You don't have to, but...
...but if you want to... you should. You should stay.
Stick around. Hang out with us. It's gonna be fun.
Oh, what kind of songs can you expect to hear,
I wonder? Hmm?
Only some of Mori's favorites.
Yes, there are actually... um... mostly guests.
I think there's maybe one solo song, but...
...almost every single song has a guest.
Wow, probably the most guests that I have ever had
in any live that I have ever done. All guests!
And also very few MCs.
That's right. We're gonna be too focused on performing,
so get ready to not hear a lot of talking,
but there's gonna be lots of singing and dancing!
Why am I being goofy? This isn't how I'm supposed
to be on stage.
I'm supposed to be goofy during streams and think
goofy on stage.
But I can't help myself.
I can't help myself. I'm a... I'm a dummy.
What can I say?
Don't say that. Don't put yourself down, Mori.
The MC is going off the rails, so we better just
continue singing at this point.
Or else I'm gonna say something even more stupid.
Yes. I love MCs, Dead Beats! You guys know this...
...I really don't love MCs. Let the show go on, yeah?
Oh, but first, I have to summon the next guest.
That's right.
The next guest I will be bringing forward
with this...
...tarot card.
As you can see, these are very powerful.
So, let's go ahead and call the next person and
get this show rolling.
Here we go!
Taza!
興味ない 持ってない やってないし 感じない 感じ外
I don't care, I don't have it, I'm not doing it,
I don't feel it, out of touch
How did it get to this no regrets we just run into
the night
タイド
Tide
Backs to the walls crackin' let me out
I'm losin' grip before I fall back and take a bow
Missed hits and pitfalls level up
Our festive time is limited so do it now
鳴り止まないまま 置いていかれた髪と声
While it won't stop ringing, the hair and voice
left behind
叫び続けろ 誰かが気づいてくれるまで
Keep on screaming, until someone notices
Inside I can't give up, my soul moves just a little
Another slight voice in my mind, I can turn
the tide
Inside I can't give up, my soul moves just a little
I've found it hard to be strong
And as I go along I'm falling out of touch
Seek out your fire, re-ignite your flame
No more living sick and tired, no apologies required
And I know maybe there's no one else who
feels the same
Passion fades but so do scars, we'll paint the
future make it ours
曖昧な日々でも意味ある
Even vague days have meaning
行けるどこまで行ってみるだけ
I'll just go as far as I can
まだまだ届いてもないよ
I haven't even reached it yet
目の前のその壁を壊せ
Break down that wall in front of you
これとあれとこれとあれも 卑猥に欲張って
This and that and this and that too,
obscenely greedy
何が目隠して公開して 明日明後日を動かして
What's hiding it, reveal it, move tomorrow and
the day after
もうしない否定
I won't deny it anymore
It's irrelevant if you end up a shell of what
you were
Pushin' the limits to be and now there's no
tellin' where
You'll end up if you say that it's over, hold it
together
You know we're still in control the moment workin'
through hazards and loss
I wanna push it past the steam just a little
And as a little voice control it, I can turn
the tide
Inside I can't give up, my soul moves just a little
もう止められねえ この体を炎の中へ
I can't be stopped anymore, throw this body
into the flames
Seek out your fire, re-ignite your flame
No more living sick and tired, no apologies required
And I know maybe there's no one else who
feels the same
Passion fades but so do scars, we'll paint the
future make it ours
...make it ours.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I wanna push for destiny
Just a little, a little.
Now it's time to go 'cause the fight is still on, yeah.
The night is never running when the spark is gone, you know.
Refill some light inside your room, just a little, a little.
Whoa...
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Seek out your fire, re-ignite your flame!
No more living sick and tired
No apologies required.
And I know...
Maybe there's no one else who feels the same.
Passion fades, but so do scars
We'll paint the future, make it ours.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
曖昧な日々でも意味ある
Even vague days have meaning,
いけるところまでいってみるだけ
I'm just going to try going as far as I can.
まだまだ届いてもないよ
It's still not enough,
目の前のその壁を壊せ
break down that wall in front of you.
Get out the rat race, chasing simple evolve
But the Kingdom of Swindom is open to all.
Until the game hits a place to make a profit
Rep-a-swing is the thing now, moving your stuff.
Look-a-boys, a-lady. Look-a-boys, a-heady.
Look-under-lady. Look-a-boys, a-heady.
Shout out to all the crazy people standing at the fire
Just to set fire, reach the way high.
響き渡るスピード感
A sense of speed that resonates,
耳になんて残しやがらせ
making it stay in your ears.
似て非なる自信家自惚れ
A narcissist's overconfidence, similar yet different.
恐怖心　畏れ　戦慄け
Fear, dread, tremble.
驕って縮んじゃ解け
Being proud and shrinking, unravel it.
権威ぶったハリボテ
吹けば飛ぶような文字
An authoritative papier-mâché,
letters that would blow away if you breathed on them.
Stupid 道化
Stupid clown,
そこ退けそこ退け
get out of the way, get out of the way.
Shut up 妄言
Shut up, delusions,
猪才な嘘の根
the root of mediocre lies.
ボロ儲けしてルンルンが得意なネズミ
A rat that's good at making a fortune and being happy-go-lucky.
香水を振り撒いても消えやしないその汚臭
Even if you spray perfume, that foul stench won't go away.
What ya looking for? You are skeptic.
Don't spin it. Keep skeptic.
夢も現も no way / Making fire
インターネット人目も厭わず fire
Neither dreams nor reality, no way / Making fire
Fire on the internet without caring about people's eyes.
Watch you relevant me for a pyramid scheme?
I refuse to be a part of any derelict dreams.
Slide over and hear the screams
And they say us are basically got to get the stairs in those plays.
代わり映えのない
おもちゃは捨てちゃいなよ　コンセプト
Throw away the toys
that have no novelty, that's the concept.
似て非なる自信家自惚れ
A narcissist's overconfidence, similar yet different.
恐怖心　畏れ　戦慄け
Fear, dread, tremble.
驕って縮んじゃ解け
Being proud and shrinking, unravel it.
権威ぶったハリボテ
吹けば飛ぶような文字
An authoritative papier-mâché,
letters that would blow away if you breathed on them.
勘違いしてる奴等ばかり　うんざり
Fed up with nothing but people who are mistaken.
決してあんたの方には風は吹かない　諦め
The wind will never blow your way, give up.
あんたの芝居はまだまだお粗末
Your acting is still poor.
借り通るまでもないチョロそうなワンパターン
A simple one-pattern that isn't even worth borrowing.
針山の地獄を並べ立て鼻で笑う
Listing the hell of the needle mountain and laughing in your face.
偽りの光　暴露できるならやってごらん
A false light, if you can expose it, go ahead.
全然物足りない
さら掃除をしろ白くはならない
Not enough at all,
do the cleaning, it won't become white.
汚れる前に差しからせ
Let it be stained before it gets dirty.
似て非なる自信家自惚れ
A narcissist's overconfidence, similar yet different.
恐怖心　畏れ　戦慄け
Fear, dread, tremble.
最終警告のすん止め
A last warning stop.
すらあんたにとっては致死
Even that is fatal for you.
Stupid 道け
そこ退けそこ退け
Stupid clown,
get out of the way, get out of the way.
Shut up 妄言
猪才な嘘の根
Shut up, delusions,
the root of mediocre lies.
ボロ儲けしてるルンルンが得意なネズミ
A rat that's good at making a fortune and being happy-go-lucky.
香水を振り撒いても消えやしないその汚臭
Even if you spray perfume, that foul stench won't go away.
It starts with just a thought within
A wish that rode on mellow wind
Begins and ends with "hello" and "goodbye"
今、何ができるだろう
What can I do now?
何になれるだろう
What can I become?
終わりには手に入れたいから
Because I want to have it in the end
Vaporize those who don't begin to guess
A life so well, a part of the plan
Or absorbed into a far-flung
With a forty-four in the skirt of hand
何回だって落胆したって大丈夫
No matter how many times I'm discouraged, it's okay
存在しないじゃあすべてを白へ
It doesn't exist, so turn everything to white
嵐へ 溶かしていくのさ
Into the storm, I'll let it melt
On the winds of desperation flying
For a false world to see
何を求めるの 運命はもう 決められてるのに
What are you seeking? Though destiny has
already been decided...
Numbing pain is numbing happiness
Something anyone can find
進もう 自分のためさ
Let's move forward, for my own sake
Alone, it's hopeless though this soul can say "I tried"
立ち向かうために Be born inside
Be born inside, in order to face it
Recalling all the days we met
A place that I belonged and yet
My world was filled with walls of every side
解き放つのは旋律 超えてゆく現実
What I set free is a melody, transcending reality
無敵なの 今この一瞬は
I'm invincible in this very moment
My hesitation has been hard to cold
Benefits of persecute to a story told
Unpleasant resentment the more you told
Give us out of the binds of stories of old
猛り 燃やし尽くしてよ 永遠に
ここから出ていくために
Rage, burn it all away, forever
In order to get out of here
檻を壊しただけ
I just broke the cage
On the winds of desperation flying
For a false world to see
Though I may decide to fight it
Fade it is hard to hide it
It's always been decided for me
涙 期待 哀悼を 永遠に流してまた
Tears, expectations, mourning... letting them flow
forever once again
足りない あり得ない そこにある
It's not enough, it's impossible, yet it's right there
My hope 満ち足りるまで また走る
Until my hope is satisfied, I'll run again
場所へと進んでゆく Be born inside
Moving toward that place, be born inside
Souls divide called inner side
The dice was decisive, must have it nice
A gorgeous device to trigger entice
It's got a price
躍動しよう 私のよう
ただハートは重し 鮮やかなスペース 尊く 掃う
Let's surge, just like me
But the heart is a weight, sweep it away with dignity
They're never gonna change
Why do myself, reject any and all help
Put all my chips and fold to help
Blood, sweat, cross-stopped thoughts invading
Nobody's waiting
After all said and done there's nowhere left to run
じゃあ R.I.P. 優しいビースト じゃないきゃな
Well then, R.I.P., I've gotta be a kind beast
ビート 止めてって願うなんて異常死体
もう 魂すらも不要
Wishing for the beat to stop is like an abnormal corpse
I don't even need a soul anymore
Be born inside!
Our world's turned once again
For that reason I still sing
And we've shared so many tears by now
Though I'd never change a thing
泣いても笑って 死にたくなった日々も私なの
Crying, laughing, even those days when I
wanted to die, they are all me
この世界にはもうこれ以上 何もない
There's nothing more left in this world
Numbing pain is numbing happiness
Something anyone can find
進もう 自分のためさ
Let's move forward, for my own sake
この絶望の風の中飛んでゆく
I'll fly through this wind of despair
何を求めるの 運命に抗いはしないのに
What are you seeking? Though I don't
resist destiny...
そこにある幸せ 戦い手に入れる
The happiness that is right there,
I'll fight to get it
扉 開く その日まで
Until the day the door opens
Your hope is more than just a place
You're never satisfied
進む先は誰かに決められた道じゃなくて
The path ahead isn't one decided by
someone else
私のモノさ I want be born inside
It's mine, I want to be born inside
もう 戻れない
I can't go back anymore
Believe that somehow we're alive
DONMAI
Lyrics: Mori Calliope, Jean-Ken Johnny
Music: Jean-Ken Johnny
Arrangement: Jean-Ken Johnny, ED Vedder
Hello again, my heat is over...
The tide is high but I'm still low...
You let the gala glamour me for me, babe
Cool and wild we can never be free, yeah
There is never any gold...
Hide and seek, take a peek at the skill no one could teach
A dance with the deuce that you know you'll never reach
Pickin' up on the wanna be somebody
A telephone fax and boys and girls, ready or not now boys and girls
High up on your throne, let it steady to the bone
Pumpin' in this midnight cold, oh-oh
People come and go, only way that you can grow
Is not to give a damn at all, oh-oh
FEEL THE DRIVE
When hell's breaking loose come and dance with me
FEEL THE VIBE
I know what I am and the right to believe
Can't catch up, I'm still in the fight...
Never say die but I tell myself
"DON'T MIND"
'Cause I'm betting all on me
Still here burning with desire, don't you tell me that you're tired
Are you joking, maybe joking, while I'm stoking up the fire
People say you lost your vision but you're seeing crystal clear
I'm making my own decision, don't you let me disappear
What do you want from me? Guess I'll never agree
Deep heavy body and a drama and it's all just meant to be
インターネット盛り上がってチリチリみたいになったトースター
絡まって空になって勝者、みんな舞って今夜
The internet is heated up like a toaster that's turned to ash
Tangled up and empty, the winner, everyone dance tonight
People come and go, only way that you can grow
Is not to give a damn at all, oh-oh
FEEL THE DRIVE
When hell's breaking loose come and dance with me
FEEL THE VIBE
I know what I am and the right to believe
Can't catch up, I'm still in the fight...
Never say die but I tell myself
"DON'T MIND"
'Cause I'm betting all on me
決めまくって回想、後に引きに引けない真相
巻き散らして喚き出して辺り散らし暴走
Deciding everything in a reminiscence, a truth that can't be taken back
Scattering about, screaming out, running wild all around
難船時、なんか分かんねぇ自尊心
後生大事に自分なりで我慢してる口頭
At the time of shipwreck, some unknown self-esteem
Cherishing it as if it's life itself, enduring in my own way, verbally
笑わせんな、聞きませんな、君のそのアジェンダ
Let it be known, I'm still here and I will never surrender
Don't make me laugh, I'm not listening to your agenda
People come they go, there are highs and endless lows
Only way that you can grow is not to give a damn at all
Hello again, my heat is over...
The tide is high but I'm not alone...
FEEL THE DRIVE
When hell's breaking loose come and dance with me
FEEL THE VIBE
I know what I am and the right to believe
Can't catch up, I'm still in the fight...
Never say die but I tell myself
"DON'T MIND"
'Cause I'm betting all on me
FEEL THE DRIVE
When hell's breaking loose come and dance with me
FEEL THE VIBE
I know what I am and the right to believe
Can't catch up, I'm still in the fight...
Never say die but I tell myself
"DON'T MIND"
'Cause I'm betting all on me
Taste of Death
Lyrics: Mori Calliope, KIRA
Music, Arrangement: KIRA
Ha, so bored of basic bread
I need a bigger track to satisfy what I crave
Ha, I heard you wanna play
My heels on your neck, come and try in this game
...got you in my sights right now, still alive.
See now how I excite you, death's so the prize.
I'm still the best at making y'all cry.
But I'll get good, my, my.
Watching you from the shadows where I wander
暗闇で fear making me stronger
Fear in the darkness is making me stronger
死神が止まらないんだ
The Reaper won't stop
Very last breath, get a taste of death
One by one fall into my trap
Desiring the touch of a maniac
This is how it feels on the edge, 君の the end
This is how it feels on the edge, your end
Take your very last breath for a taste of death
Okay, okay, okay, I gotta hold back this lust
Vivid up bust, you can trust me, I got the stamina to be up with you all night
Give me the runaround, I'm gonna chase you down till I pin you to the ground
Slam my name, boy, it's my favorite sound
Da-da-da-da-da-die
Got you in my sights right now, still alive
See now how I excite you, death's so the prize
I'm still the best at making y'all die
Better get good, my, my
Watching you from the shadows where I wander
暗闇で fear making me stronger
Fear in the darkness is making me stronger
死神が止まらないんだ
The Reaper won't stop
Very last breath, get a taste of death
One by one fall into my trap
Desiring the touch of a maniac
This is how it feels on the edge, 君の the end
This is how it feels on the edge, your end
Take your very last breath for a taste of death
I just can't wait
To watch your heartbeat stop
Set my insides on fire
Seeing your body drop
Just us...
...one and fighting, come on inside and don't fight me
Heart accelerates, screaming and biting, leave me shaking, aching, find it
Let yourself do me and take this body and use me
While death consumes you, girl, I'll make you choose me
Watching you from the shadows where I wander
暗闇で fear making me stronger
Fear in the darkness is making me stronger
死神が止まらないんだ
The Reaper won't stop
Very last breath, get a taste of death
One by one fall into my trap
Desiring the touch of a maniac
This is how it feels on the edge, 君の the end
This is how it feels on the edge, your end
Take your very last breath for a taste of death
Take your very last breath, get a taste of death
Make 'Em Afraid
Wait, a world was at my finger
Yeah
What now, stop running, you know me as the chick who won't back down
I'm coming, the girl who threatens your empire
A fire, an urge to be bad
You can expect to meet the angels that you had
Now, the tables have turned
The bridges are burned with desire for human applause
Pause, rewind, relive and relay all the shit that I wanted to say
I beckon you all to be part of making it no more a start of...
...the end
Humankind's God-sacred laws of voice to take them higher
Higher!
I've got delusions of your revolution
Love dreams come true, love dreams come true
Come on!
Make 'em afraid of you
Because I'm the queen of fools, they see what they want and they're done
Set the beast on the loose and make 'em afraid of you
Write it, I'll break the rules and even if you cannot find love
If you got the stuff to prove it, make 'em afraid of you
Defy, I'm out of my mind
Chasing a nice delight, feel the animal taking a bite
Revive, teeth, and cry out as I clench through the pain
They say there is nothing to change and my prayers are a gentle temper
So liar, you think you're no good, don't act like I should
The joke's on you, disguise the limit
Guess my ambitions make my own decisions
Defying on the brink, watch the kingdom start to fall
Humankind's God-sacred laws of voice to take them higher
Riding your rhythm, so make me your villain
Love dreams come true, love dreams come true
Come on!
Make 'em afraid of you
Hey!
Na-na-na-na-na...
Make 'em afraid of ya.
I'm just the queen of fools,
Distill what they want it all.
I've said to myself, no losing,
Make 'em afraid of ya.
Write it up, break some rules,
I'll never let go of my love.
If you've got the stuff to prove it,
Make 'em afraid of ya.
Yeah, yeah!
Ha...
Goodbye to this vulnerable side,
I watch as it burns to...
Conclusion.
Your revolution.
Observation.
Your misconstrued myth come true, come on!
Make 'em afraid of ya.
Hey!
Na-na-na-na-na...
Make 'em afraid of ya.
Make 'em afraid of ya. Ow!
I'm just the queen of fools,
Distill what they want it all.
I've said to myself, no losing,
Make 'em afraid of ya.
Write it up, break some rules,
I'll never let go of my love.
If you've got the stuff to prove it,
Make 'em afraid of ya.
You're Not Special
Lyrics: Mori Calliope
Where to begin...
...in this wicked world?
There's a million others just like you.
Yeah.
You talk too much, you're all out of touch,
猿回しの猿になれない存在。
An existence that can't become a showman's monkey.
You talk too much, you're all out of touch,
猿回しの猿になれない存在。
An existence that can't become a showman's monkey.
Yeah, it's "anything goes" when you're forced to create while advancing on tiptoes.
Actually worthless, with no purpose,
No place to face all your work.
What's the point if you'll never return from this morphous?
Enormous snore built in the bridges they burned.
First getting supercilious smiles and waves,
The praise in the bonus to make sure you stay.
So the story goes, you're the one they'll remember.
Lie, call it labors of love.
Why put in the effort?
'Cuz you're not special, none of us are,
Even those plagued by stardom fade into dust.
Nothing matters, who the hell else should I be?
A puppet, a pawn, if I fail I'm gone...
...so everyone else can be happy.
With no question, I fall in line,
Believing promises every time.
Soldier onwards, spare me your honesty,
'Cuz I know my place now.
A washed-out prophecy.
Out of sight, out of mind, we'll never see the same view.
Lost, so exhausted, but you can't give in.
Keep getting fired up, might forget the ones who saved you.
There's no bias, and no-hopers never win.
So, we close our eyes and pretend that this might end right...
...just a means to an end.
Why put up a fight then?
'Cuz you're not special, none of us are,
Even those plagued by stardom fade into dust.
Nothing matters, how much more love can I spend?
A puppet, a pawn, if I fail I'm gone so everyone fallen can ascend.
With no question, I fall in line,
And play my part so the chosen shine.
Persona non grata, better left out of the sun,
'Cuz I know my place now.
Just watching through the looking glass to the past as it comes to pass.
A million eyes demand an outburst till their very last.
Forget to find my whereabouts, my own way.
Each moment passing is a debt I gotta pay.
And now just look me in the eye... (Yeah, yeah)
...it's time that we realize. (Realize, realize)
The non-existence of you, don't gotta cry.
So set for me an enterprise, so you can never make it mine.
So you can take it when it's over, leave nothing behind.
So the story goes, you're the one they'll remember.
Lie, call it labors of love.
Why put in the effort?
'Cuz you're not special, none of us are,
Even those plagued by stardom fade into dust.
Nothing matters, who the hell else should I be?
A puppet, a pawn, if I fail I'm gone so everyone else can be happy.
...happy with no question,
I fall in line.
Greedy promises every time.
Soldier onward, spare me your honesty,
'Cause I know my place now...
A washed out prophecy.
A WASHED OUT PROPHECY
I am the picture of a perfect human every day.
Whoa...
Black Sheep
I am the picture of a perfect human every day,
and I kinda got nothing left for making mistakes.
I am the notorious stain on my life,
'cause I got what's on the mannequin with no right to complain.
I'm a masterpiece born on some days I can't get up.
If I showed a better way, this yet I don't think you would let up.
Numbers pressing me, pinning me down,
I won't let you see me frown.
Reality is drowning, someone see me now.
Na-na-na, na-na-na, na-na-na...
この世界に全く意味ない
There's no meaning in this world at all.
Na-na-na, na-na-na, na-na-na...
死んじゃっていい
It's okay to die.
Feeling like the pens run out at last,
living like a moth beneath the glass.
Ever just a slave into my past,
I just laugh.
If you retreat now, this life will never change.
Just like lyrics you've heard a thousand times.
Tired and inspired brief refrains.
Stay on repeat loud, my mind am I deranged?
When I can hear the bridges setting in my heart again,
I swear I'm gonna break the chain!
We're living in the upside down now!
We're living in the upside down.
Some call it niche, others call it just unlikable,
but this here is an art form, others are recyclable.
I'm breaking for row, set out I won't be controlled.
My hand is stronger than ever and yet I fold.
No-no-no, no time for falling, and my exploited head is so tall and I'm...
defenseless, expendable, pretending that I'm dependable.
Don't look, don't belong near my own friends, there's no end.
Nothing's getting better, so I'm thinking of pushing and pulling
myself and seeing how far I bet, pray.
Na-na-na, na-na-na, na-na-na...
この世界で生きたくない
I don't want to live in this world.
Na-na-na, na-na-na, na-na-na...
死んじゃっていい
It's okay to die.
Feeling like there's nothing left to write,
living like I'm running out of time.
Ever losing sleep wondering why,
I can't die.
逃げ出した人生は変わらない
A life you ran away from doesn't change.
何回聞いたことがある
How many times have I heard that?
歌詞、戯言は要らないね
Lyrics, I don't need your nonsense.
I really need you now though life may never change.
I want to scream how I feel until I'm gone.
Resonance of empty outrage,
days of deep losses always stay the page.
So I'll create it and I'm dying at the middle of my heart again.
Tonight I'm gonna break the chain!
We're living in the upside down now!
We're living in the upside down.
I am the picture of a perfect human every day.
Woo! Woo! Woo!
Welcome!
Thank you IRyS, thank you Bae!
It's my birthday, it's my birthday!
I am the picture of a perfect human every day!
It's my birthday!
Okay you fools!
Hey, it's my birthday! Thank you for coming to celebrate my birthday in my crystal ball!
My crystal ball, welcome! What do you guys think?
Whoa! Whoa!
You're like a... what do you call it? One of those mysterious fortune tellers!
Yeah, fortune teller, yep!
Well, there's a little problem though. I haven't figured out how to get out of here.
So we're stuck? What about us?
Uh... yeah, you guys are gonna have to figure it out in a little bit.
We came out of a tarot card... carrot? Tarot card?
Carrot?
Carrot? Carrot card?
Tarot card! We came out of a tarot card!
Surely we can just go back to the tarot card?
Nah, it's a... it's a one-way trip, ladies, sorry. I didn't think that far.
Time to start the MC part!
Yay!
No no no, you guys... I'm sure that you'll find your way back.
I'll lay it out in a little bit, but right now
I wanted to introduce you guys to the crowd.
Guys, jikoshoukai!
Guys, introduce yourselves!
HiRyS! It's IRyS from Hololive English!
Your Seiso Nephilim here to bring hope,
and I am the positive energy
in the Wheel of Fortune card thingy
that we're a part of.
Is that what you think?
Is that your... is that your guestimate?
Okay. Yeah, 'cause it's helping Chaos, obviously!
Obviously! Hope is like, you know, the good stuff!
Right? Okay, that's a guess.
And so this is the bad stuff over here?
Is that what you're trying to say?
Hey, not me! That's her!
She said it! She said it, not me!
I did! That's right! I'm bad! Chaos is bad!
She's bad! What's up!
I am Chaos, the end of ends,
a doomsday rat trapped in a cage of ice...
Gill-best-friend... I just... Oh my god,
I'm like, drooling, help!
I'm Hakos Baelz from Hololive English!
Witness me!
Witness! Witness! Witness!
So am I the... am I the bad side?
There's no such thing as 'bad side'
in Wheel of Fortune, you guys.
Wheel of Fortune is like gacha, right?
And if you get like a good result...
And then if you get like the bad...
there is no such thing as bad result!
It's Chaos!
You guys want to know the real...
the wheel reason...
The real reason... the wheel reason...
The real reason... Stop it, stop it,
stop it, omaera!
stop it, you guys!
Okay, the reason that I chose you guys
for Wheel of Fortune is because
I'm so fortunate to have met you both
in my life.
Aww! Oh my god!
Yeah, but seriously, you guys' guesses
were pretty good too. I don't know,
you guys just seemed very Wheel of Fortune-esque,
so that's why I chose you guys.
Wheel of Fortune, I see.
So, what did you guys think about
performing together? Was it fun?
I loved it! That was so much fun!
Yeah! Me too! I'm a picture
of a perfect human every day!
Yes! And performing was so much fun!
I love how whenever the camera went
to each of you guys,
you could see your personality.
Like Baelz... she's just like...
And then IRyS is like smiling and cute,
like... like idol!
Like my diva, my diva, my princess.
Yeah, I love that, I love that so much.
I'm seiso!
Yeah, it's very cute. It made my heart
go like 'ba-bump'.
My friends are so cool singing it, though!
Like, yeah! (Singing) I'm a picture
of a perfect human every day!
So cool!
Get into your feelings, you know?
この世界いつも...
Kono sekai itsumo...
...僕ら食らってんだ!
...bokura kurattenda!
死んだっていい!
Shindatte ii!
Yeah! You can die, that's cool,
but not yet, not yet!
Not unless you die striving trying
to find your way out of here.
But I'm not going to help you guys.
You have to do that yourself.
Time... time to go bye-bye!
Okay! Okay! We're being kicked out!
But how do we get way?
I'll look this way. Okay, let's see.
I'm pretty sure there's like an NPC around here...
Wait! Let's zoom out this way!
Good luck! Give us a countdown!
Are you ready? Like a race queen!
Three, two, one, pyun!
Three, two, one, zoom!
Off to the races they go!
Those two are maximum silliness.
Anyway, I had to kick them out because
guess what guys? It's my birthday!
Which means that...
ah, there is merchandise.
There is merchandise and goods for you guys,
so check it out, okay? I will introduce
each merch item at one time.
Hope you guys are ready. There is some
limited stuff this time,
so hope you guys are ready to grab them
real quick. Now, first up is...
Birthday Celebration 2025
Mystical Songstress... oh wait,
hold on a second.
First of all, take a look at all of this.
There's a mystical song... mystical songstress poster...
I'm sorry, I don't know where I'm looking ever,
any time, any second of the day.
This is a poster. I know you guys like posters,
so it was recommended to me this time,
let's do a poster that features the main
key visual of the merchandise.
It is drawn by Kuno Norari-sensei.
Arigatou gozaimasu! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
Second is Lucky Dead Beat's Random Rubber Strap.
You can get one random design out of
four possible designs.
The illustration is by Keijo-sensei.
There are lots of different outfits,
and so I don't know, if you want, you can
try to collect all four.
You know, I'm pretty sure that you can
grab them separate,
so try to get all of them, okay? Yes, yes.
Now, the third item is... I know you guys
have been waiting for this...
Underworld University Sweater!
The same design as my recently released
new outfit. Kawaii, right?
new outfit. Cute, right?
Kawaii. You can wear the same sweater
that I do. Yatta!
Cute. You can wear the same sweater
that I do. Yay!
Hope you guys grab it, it's very comfy.
Now next up, fourth is... Stay HYDRATED!
Water Bottle, okay?
You can use this when heading off to work
or traveling.
You know, Dead Beats, we love to drink water,
despite the fact that a lot of you guys
are skeletons, you still need water, right?
To live. I mean, that's just... those are the rules.
I don't make them. So make sure that
you stay hydrated
with your special Mori Calliope water bottle.
It's very subtle.
Nobody'll know that you're like... that you're like a big Holo fan...
STAY HYDRATED! ボトル
STAY HYDRATED! Bottle
All of fans will know...
Yeah, that's what I'm trying to do these days,
so hope you guys enjoy.
Fifth item is...
Situational Voice, "The Fortune I Got
from the Dark Forest Songstress".
Voice Pack / シチュエーションボイス
「暗き森の歌姫からの加護」(日本語＆英語)
Voice Pack / Situational Voice Pack
"The Fortune I Got from the Dark Forest Songstress" (Japanese & English)
It sounds so silly, it's like maximum freaking
silliness, like some kind of isekai anime title.
I hope you guys enjoy it. I think it's very cute
and fits the theme of the main illustration.
Also, if you buy the full set...
Complete Set Purchase Bonus / フルセット購入特典
Illustration: 久乃のらり
Complete Set Purchase Bonus / Full Set Purchase Bonus
Illustration: Kunono Rari
...for a limited number of orders, you could get
the hand-autographed postcard, RIP Mori's hand.
But there actually aren't many this time
because, you know, RIP Mori's hand.
I gotta watch out for my hand health,
and I'm very busy.
So make sure that you grab yours,
they're in very limited supply, okay?
For the normal set, there is a
foil-stamped postcard included instead.
And this was drawn by Kunono Rari-sensei,
thank you so much again.
Birthday Merch Complete Set Purchase Bonus
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PR card
You will receive also, this is big, a card that
can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game! Yatta!
As a thank you bonus for the complete set
of premium talent merchandise.
It's the only time you can grab it,
do not miss out on it.
This card will only be given to customers who
purchase from the Hololive Production official shop...
Sorry, words, English, hard.
Holo EN everybody.
Given to customers who purchased from the
Hololive Production Official Shop, okay?
And this bonus card is an
Oshi HoloMem card.
You can only use one of these in the game to
show love for your Oshi. So show some love for Mori!
For more details on the card and rules, please
visit the Hololive Official Card Game page.
And do note that the card only
comes in Japanese.
So, with that being said everybody, we still
have a little bit more of the show to go.
Are you guys ready to continue?
Let's keep having lots of fun because we
still got a couple performances left.
Okay? Are you guys watching?
It's about to get even crazier! Let's go!
Ouroboros
Lyrics: Mori Calliope, Elliot Hsu
In ages forgotten a reaper was born
Spinning tales of deadly belief
A yearning to traverse that forest of thorns
In remembrance of what lie beneath
The dangers abounding, the Ouroboros untold
Cloud my vision until I cannot see
Peculiar enchantments begin to unfold
And the underworld calls back to me
As the light grows dimmer and fades
Cross that river now, make our way beyond the gates
Release from our confinement, together we'll find it
The trail is fraught with perils and yet we don't mind it
But looking towards horizons, reminding me of then
Can't repent, though I've hardly been spent
A journey downward towards somewhere new yet familiar
I'm learning how to stand for the smile I swore to defend
Till the end, as we further descend then shall we go
To be swallowed by fates below
A moment in history, a flicker in time
A mystery I still can't break through
I'm deathly defiant of crossing that line
I don't want to break down before you
Reach downward to glory, yet upward what for?
An Ouroboros of earthly desire
Devouring my tail just to tell it once more
Am I still the gold statue you admire?
Collecting all the stories with a joy
And reflecting on the thorns that near destroyed me
I sing about a journey's end and now we come upon
Another one, the sun setting earlier than believed
From this point downward I cannot return
With a final dream I sought, it's so close yet far within my reach
Though I'd like it to be known this time it's on my own
Release from our confinement, together we'll find it
The trail is fraught with perils and maybe all is as it should be
I promise I'll still be me
My mistakes somehow made a good story great
A journey downward toward somewhere new yet familiar
I'm learning how to stand for this smile I swore to defend
Till the end as we further descend then shall we go
Swallowed up by what waits below
Mina-san! What did you guys think about our performance today?
Oh my gosh, it was so fun!
Hey, wait a minute though, it's not over yet, so don't leave, don't leave!
Don't run away to go get the limited merch or anything like that.
It's not time yet, because we still have a little bit more to go.
You guys are gonna miss the grand finale, so just stay right there!
But, um, yeah, no, this show was amazing.
We didn't have a lot of MCs, but that's because, you know, we were working hard to perform for you guys.
And look at all these tarot cards that we have here of me and all of my friends together.
You know, I wanted to celebrate Hololive original songs, especially by Mori this time.
I'm a big believer in like, "Let's go, Hololive original music!"
And I wanted to celebrate all of that with you guys today by singing some of my favorite songs by me together with my friends.
And so I hope that you guys were able to enjoy today's show.
And take a look at this stage! Isn't the stage amazing?
I know that we looked at it a little bit earlier before, but I mean, it's basically like a dream venue for me.
So sparkly and beautiful, oh my gosh.
It's been so amazing, and getting to explore all the different tarot cards as well with you guys.
Because you know, as you know, "The Arcana is the means by which all is revealed."
And so I hope that you guys had some fun getting to kind of like, see my choices of songs,
like who I chose to sing in each song and stuff like that.
But we gotta move right along, we gotta move right along.
Because, as you may have noticed, a special premiere has showed up on my channel.
And our last guest might have something to do with that.
This is a performance I'm very excited about.
Um, I gotta go change really quickly, but in the meantime, let's go ahead and summon one more person to the stage!
Are you guys ready? Without further ado, here we go! よいしょ！
Are you guys ready? Without further ado, here we go! Here we go!
皆さーん、最後のゲストはなんと、TOOBOEさんです！
Okay, everyone, here's our final guest. It's TOOBOE-san!
よろしくお願いします。よろしくお願いします。
Great to be here. Great to be here.
よろしくお願いします。はじめまして、はじめましてです。
Great to have you! Nice to meet you, yeah.
はじめまして。見てる方には、そうですね、
Nice to meet you. I guess this would be my first time greeting
はじめましての方が多いかなと思います。よろしくお願いします。
most of your viewers? It's a pleasure to be here.
はい、よろしくお願いします。
And it's a pleasure to have you.
実は、あの、TOOBOEさんは、去年のカリオペの
Believe it or not, TOOBOE-san, you were my
Spotifyで一番よく聴いてたアーティストだったんですけど。
most listened to artist on Spotify last year.
ありがとうございます、本当に。
Thank you so much.
いえいえ、こちらこそ。ホロライブに入る前ずっとファンですから。
No, thank you. I've been a fan of yours since before I joined Hololive, even.
へえ、本当に。
Really?
本当に嬉しいですね。
I'm so happy to have you here.
いや、こちらこそ恐縮ですね。
Please, you flatter me.
はい。そうですね、あのTOOBOEさんの曲は、本当にかっこいいと思う、マジで。
I think your songs are really cool. For real.
なんかメロディのセンスが、やばいです。本当に。
Your taste in melodies is actually crazy.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
はい。そうですね。そして、負け犬の話がすごく好きだから、リリックもめちゃくちゃ面白いと思うんで、
And I love a good underdog story, so your lyrics really hit home, too.
一緒に曲作りたいなと思いました。
It really made me want to work on a song with you.
ありがとうございます。ぜひ、楽しかったです、本当に。
Thank you. Working with you was a lot of fun.
よかった。ありがとうございます。
I'm glad it was. Thank you.
そして、私とTOOBOEさんは、ちょっと共通点があるんだけど、
What's more, TOOBOE-san and I have something in common.
将来の夢は漫画家だった。
We both dreamed of being manga artists.
あ、そうですね、そうですね。
Oh yeah, that's right.
だから今回アニメーションミュージックビデオを作ろうかなと思いました。
That's why we thought we should make an animated music video for this one.
はい。
Right.
今回キャラクターデザインはカリオペとTOOBOEさん。
TOOBOE-san and I designed the characters.
はい。
Right.
アニメーションはカリオペでした。そうなんですね。
And I made the animation. Is that so?
そうですよね。何かあれですよね。
That's right. It's, like,
僕あんまり、あの、絵柄が多分相当違うものなので、
our art styles are really different,
どうしようかなと思ったんですけど。
so I was wondering how we would do this.
せっかくならお互いの良さ出せるようなアニメ作れればいいなってことで。
But we decided to aim for an anime MV that'd showcase both of our styles.
僕もちょっと全体の話のプロットとかも考えましたし、
I worked with you on the overall plot and story,
キャラもちょっと1体か2体描かせていただいて、
and designed a couple of characters.
成りましたね。はい。
And it all came together.
はい。
Yeah.
なかなか面白いMVになりましたから、皆さんぜひこの後チェックしてほしい。
Yeah, it's quite an fun and entertaining music video, so please check it out, guys.
はい。ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
じゃあ、どんな曲を作ったかな？
I bet everyone's wondering what the song is like.
皆さんに聴かせましょう。
So let's have them listen to it!
はい。行くぞ！
Yeah. Okay, here we go!
皆さん、これは最後の曲です。
Everyone, this is the last song.
TOOBOE x Calliope 新曲 "Sepia" Check it out!
TOOBOE x Calliope new song "Sepia". Check it out.
Sepia feat. TOOBOE
Lyrics: Mori Calliope, TOOBOE / Music, Arrangement: TOOBOE
誤解しないで、滑稽だな
Don't misunderstand, it's laughable
察せ、毒され Everyday
How time flashes by every day
誰も化かせない、運命の囚人
Another prisoner of fate no one could fake out
Stay awake now, you know you wanna fire away
もう責任なんてないさ
Now there's no question where the fault lies
共鳴さえできない毎日
These days I struggle just to empathize
もう戻らないって、解っているんだろう
There's no going back, and you know that
Cast a blessing on my cursed role
And feed this bleeding egotistical soul
Before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
時日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうのさ
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼、美しき蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
嫉妬のセットにまみれた
Dripping in jealousy that's a bit too daring
ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
An ecstasy that's just a little bit lacking
迎えも解けないまま、他人傷つけて
I hurt somebody without ever opening my eyes
当然、才すら無いわ
But there's no talent here, it's clear to see
転がり落ちたイカサマのダイス
The rigged dice falls and rolls
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I ever notice your love and affection
Cast a blessing on my cursed heart
Why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか、神様、教えてくれ
Pray tell me, God
言葉少なに貴方に捧ぐ
I give to you silently
今にも消えてしまいそうなこの命を
My life that's about to burn out
愛おしいセピア色した
Ah, and these sepia-toned
何より大事なこの景色を
Sights, most precious of all
もう少し見ていたいよな
That I wish I could watch some more
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
If I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The devils on my shoulder never let me be
Obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
Somebody save me
My world is caving in 'cause I thought I deserved it all for free
時日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうのさ
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼、美しき蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
皆さん、聴いてくれてありがとうございました。
Everyone, thank you for listening!
よいしょ。
All right.
またね。
See you later!
Catch you on the flip side!
Peace!
ARCANA
2025 BIRTHDAY 3DLIVE