(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
REQUIEM FOR LOVE
Oh you, there is no one I adore more.
You, who must have risked life and limb to be here with me forevermore.
The last words I wrote before I was cast into this endless abyss...
...by the immortals seeking to protect this world and all of its inhabitants.
Wrapped in darkness, alone, void of all emotion...
...I once more feel a presence signaling my return.
Love's fervent zeal, a spark of light in this ocean.
Now there is but little left for you to do before I am free and we can be together.
And those who trapped me within these pages shall rue locking away this beauty forever.
Only your love can set me free.
Go, recite the verse before you quickly...
...lest before me you bend and take a knee.
Love Me, Love Me, Love Me
Lyrics, Music: きくお
English Translyrics: Nerissa Ravencroft
Love Me, Love Me, Love Me
Lyrics, Music: Kikuo
English Translyrics: Nerissa Ravencroft
Ah, ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah-ah-ah-ah!
La, la-la, la-la, la-la-la-la-la!
Once in a far away, far away world was a collar that coiled like a snake.
I want someone please, I need someone please, so I listened close as it howled in ache.
Please don't be angry and please don't abandon me, don't leave me here on my own. Okay?
It wrapped itself tightly, daily and nightly, only with praise would it loosen its hold.
I placed in the top of my class, there's no one left for me to surpass.
Don't I look cute in this dress?
I really really must confess, it's tightening 'round my neck!
Give me your love, all of your love.
Give me your love, all you can conjure up.
Give me your love, all of your love,
till you go mad with ecstasy.
All of the hurt, all of the ache,
help me escape,
take it oh take it away!
Is there no end to this pain?
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah!
Grow as you may but the necklace will stay just as small as the day it was found.
It's so suffocating, the endless placating, no one is, no one is ever enough.
Won't lose to anyone, always rank number one, aren't you a beautiful child?
Hey! I'm better than her, I'm better than him, oh, everyone come round and gawk at perfection.
Meeting you right after school, I'm finally confessing to you.
Ain't it too good to be true?
A girl like me in love with you, who's miserable, vulgar and crude.
Give me your love, all of your love, give me your love...
...you can have everything if I have you.
I can have you, shoulder my load, now yours to behold.
Still not enough, you're not enough.
Never enough, still I won't lose in my old...
Truly I'm so sorry.
Give me your love, all of your love, give me your love...
...all you can conjure up.
Give me your love, all of your love, till you go mad with ecstasy.
I know it hurts, only gets worse.
God how it hurts, soon you'll be craving the pain.
This is my happiness!
Is this my happiness?
Did you enjoy my lovely song?
I hope you did.
It was for you, after all.
But... why are you not smiling?
Are you not happy to see me?
Well...
Say something. Answer me!
Who... who are you?
What?
You don't know who I am?
But everyone knows. You are the one that released me, right?
I'm... I'm sorry.
You're sorry? For what? For releasing me?
No, no, no.
For upsetting you.
If I said something wrong, I apologize.
Apologize?
You who should be amongst my most dearest and beloved followers...
...who has freed me from that prison...
...who has shown me your love above all others.
You then act like you don't even know who I am?
Why would you toy with my emotions?
I'm sorry, I'm not sure what you mean.
You're not sure what I mean?
Are you mocking me now?
If you truly do not know who I am, then why is it that you set me free?
If not for my love, and if not by your love...
...then for what?
Tell me the truth, and the whole truth, now!
No more lies or there will be consequences.
I... I'm not lying.
I swear to you, I have no idea how I released you.
I just came to a temple to collect rare spices and memories from the many books stowed away here.
By the gods, that's the whole truth.
Extract memories from books?
Are you telling me you're a witch?
How dare you step foot here!
Even knowing the long history between demons and witches, you still dare step foot here?
I know how witches dare to try and bind my kind.
Would you be foolish enough to dare attempt that on me?
Yes, okay. Yes, I'm a witch.
But I've never... well, mostly never, tried anything like that.
I swear.
And this time I was not led on by my nature at all. No.
This time it was an angel that told me of this place.
An angel came to me in my dreams.
An angel came to me in my dreams...
...and told me of an enchanted book
with centuries of memories stored away here.
Can you imagine the knowledge and stories
hidden in centuries of memories?
With a prize like that,
I had to come find the book, no matter the danger.
Little could I have known
the true nature of the book, though...
Enough!
I've heard enough.
I believe you are who you say you are, a witch.
But I don't fully believe your childish story.
No angel would ever lead a witch
to such a dangerous book.
And I can hardly believe it is just the book
and not myself you are after.
It- It's true! An angel came to me
in my dreams and told me to come here.
I was drawn to that book
with all its power and stories.
And, well, I guess you inside it.
The powerful aura it gave off drew me right to it.
How was I to know that the allure was thanks to
a demon trapped within its pages? Who would've guessed?
Though, now that I recount my story,
it does seem it really was me who released you.
Speaking of coming and going, now that you are free,
I think it is time I take my leave of this place.
I'm glad I was able to help free you from...
from whence you came!
I didn't say you could leave!
You may leave when I say you can leave.
And stop your nervous fidgeting.
I'm no fool. You think I didn't see you reaching
for your book of magic?
You, a witch, should know better than anyone
that no amount of magic is powerful enough
to destroy a demon of my power.
However, you can take some small solace
in the fact that if I had wanted you dead,
you'd already be so.
The only reason you're still alive is because
you helped free me.
Alas, I cannot allow a witch who so obviously
came with the intent to bind me to her will
leave here freely.
Your story did little to convince me
your aims were otherwise.
So, I will give you an ultimatum.
You serve me here in my hollow temple.
Love me.
Adore me.
Worship me.
Every living day, give me all the love you have.
Or I can take your soul right now.
Your choice.
Kiara... I need you.
Be My Guest
Lyrics, Music: Azari
Lost in the rain with no umbrella
Night snaps out your eyes
Can't seem to find your way back home
Come in and be my guest
Lost in the rain with no umbrella
Night snaps out your eyes
Can't seem to find your way back home
Come in and be my guest
Such a lovely smile spread across your face
But it's simple forgery
If you need to hide from the world outside
Why not try to be my guest
Waiting all day long but your friends don't come
And you're left there all alone
Still you can't jump off from the high rooftops
So come on and be my guest
Waiting all day long but your friends don't come
And you're left there all alone
Still you can't jump off from the high rooftops
So come on and be my guest
And like a cat the way I step and step and step
With carefully my feet go tap and tap and tap
You'll follow nicely with the snap and snap and snap
So lovely you'll be mesmerized by me
My institutions peaceful as can be
Despite the way that it seems
Both our quotes and our supports
Will be concise, clear and clean
Since we're only starting out
There's some probabilities
But just listen up tonight
You'll have to stay up at least
No they don't like you when you know it's true
Still you're at their beck and call
Since you're desperately giving easily
Come inside and be my guest
You're the last to choose but you're left confused
Seems that someone took your share
If you won't accuse 'cause you don't have proof
Take a chance and be my guest
On the way back home there's a sweet aroma
That tempts you off your path
I can't help but laugh 'cause I know in fact
...bound to be my guest
Yo!
Demon!
How dare you kill an innocent?
Excuse me?
I've done no such thing.
Innocent?
I would hardly call a witch who lives for power
and binds my kind for her own purposes innocent.
Innocent?
The very idea is laughable.
Leave.
I have no quarrel with you, so go now in peace
before I change my mind.
A small token for your past bravery and trials.
How gracious.
Don't think I can't see straight through your ploys though.
You will not escape justice.
Not this time.
You have brought this fight on yourself through your actions, demon.
You have brought all of this on yourself.
For what?
For killing a mere witch?
She was not just a witch!
She was my friend!
And a kind-hearted person.
And you killed her
in cold blood.
Oh, the legendary Phoenix,
the mighty fiery Kiara,
friends with a witch?
It's almost funny.
Did you not realize?
It was your witch friend who freed me.
Liar!
She would never do such a ghastly thing.
I trust she would stay away from the dark magics and demonic rituals.
To suggest otherwise is just another one of your dark lies.
She didn't deserve to die.
Ah, poor Phoenix.
Still so trusting of those around you
and unable to see through their deceptions.
Your kind spirit constantly deceives you.
That witch was never your friend.
We all know they cannot be trusted.
Even after all these years, you still have not changed.
Still believing in lies and still so easily misled.
Still such a fool.
It is you who is the fool,
demon!
Your lust for love and attention continues to lead you down the path of death and destruction.
And you don't even see that you're the one destroying your own happiness.
The Gods were right to confine you there.
You, who are still shackled by your lust for love,
your desire for attention,
your desire to be worshipped!
I am the Demon of Sound!
How dare you speak to me in such a manner.
It is but right that all should worship me on their knees.
Their love for none but myself.
Leave!
I have heard enough of your falsities.
This is your last warning.
Go now, or you'll be left to rot here forever!
I am not afraid of you,
and I will heed no such warning.
Listen, and listen well, demon.
I will not allow you to claim any more victims.
To be banished in a void was not sufficient enough punishment for you.
No.
Now, I will finish what the Gods should have.
Come on get moving cause now I'm on a roll oh
CH4NGE
Music: Giga Lyrics: q*Left
English Translyrics: Aries Shepard
One chance to choose it so what would you wager up above below
You either win or not, can't ever be a draw
Uh uh uh yeah, open the curtains up
My luck's not running, lacking money, looking for a sticker sticker
Acting funny, asking if I'm winning with a... huh?
Make your bets black or red chips to spend yeah yeah yeah yeah
Raise the stakes play that ace risk your life on a single game
Stay with me all will change you'll see not here to play
Don't get in my way I'm tired of talking
1 2 3
COUNTER!
Sit down sit down
1 2 3
One, two, three
I got skills as cold as ice
You gotta throw your hands up
You can't decide
Gonna scare you off as I roll the dice
Best you gotta say goodbye-a
Enough you make a bluff
Enough enough enough
Need a light
As we can light it up up up enough
I'm standing round
Can't avoid the voices in my head
No stopping now
I just gotta win this game instead
Get ones way oooohhh
You bet I'm here to stay
And now it's time to learn your place
A streak is running lucky money
Smoking like a cigar cigar
Acting's funny
Answer if I'm quitting if I'm not
Make your bets
Black or red tips to spend yayayaya
Raise the stakes
Play that ace risk your life on a single game
Stay with me
I know what change you'll see
Now let's play
Don't get in my way
I'm always counting
One, two, three One, two, three One, two, three
Sit down sit down
Best you say goodbye-bye
One, two, three One, two, three One, two, three
Sit down sit down
I'm so sorry.
IRyS.
It has been so long.
Nerissa, I'm so so sorry this happened to you.
It was not my intention.
What do you mean?
What was not your intention?
This.
You being... then the witch...
...and Kiara too.
What?
Are you saying you sent the Phoenix here to slay me?
No, I didn't!
Well, yes...
...but it was not my intention.
IRyS, what are you trying to tell me?
That you tried to kill me?
You who were supposed to be my friend!
We've been friends since the beginning!
Yes, of course, yes!
You sent Kiara to kill me?
No, no!
Then what?
Be clear!
Or is this how you greet your beloved friend...
...after so long?
No, I...
I would never send someone to kill you.
But yes, I'm still your loyal friend.
I always have been and always will be.
I... I tried to free you...
...and I did.
I sent the witch Shiori here to free you...
...and she did.
But I didn't know she was friends with Kiara...
...and would summon her here if threatened.
I thought she would come alone.
This was not supposed to happen.
It was not my intention.
You sent a witch to free me?
Why would you send one who binds my kind for power?
Of all those in the world...
...a witch?
Why not send one of my most beloved followers?
Only they are said to be able to free me.
Explain yourself!
What's going on?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
I have a lot to explain,
but we don't have time now.
We need to go.
Now!
Death is coming for you.
What?
Please...
...come with me.
I know a way in which we can hide from death,
but we have to leave now, before it's too late.
I'm not going anywhere with you
until you explain to me what is going on.
Now!
Why would you send a witch to free me, IRyS?
Nerissa, I had no choice.
You had no choice?
You could have sent one of my followers instead.
You don't have any more followers.
They're all dead.
They all died...
...long ago.
What?
No... that can't be.
Has it been that long?
It's been over a thousand years
since you've been locked away.
And your followers...
...they're all gone now.
It's been many long years
since your name was whispered in these lands.
You mean they...
...no longer...
...love me?
I...
I'm sorry.
I tried to free you as fast as I could.
I really did.
But it took a long time to work out how to free you,
and there was so much going on.
And the gods weren't about to look kindly
on any trying to undo their work either.
I'm sorry.
I don't have time to explain everything right now.
I understand.
But IRyS...
Tell me.
Do you still love me?
What? Yes, of course!
Then why do you lie to me?
I... I'm not lying, Nerissa!
Enough!
You of all people should understand that a witch
wouldn't be able to resist the power in my book
and attempt to bind me.
And you can hardly expect me to believe that you,
one of both planes, didn't know of the witch's
connection to such a famed warrior.
This wasn't an attempt to free me.
This...
This was an attempt to kill me.
To be free of me, to do what the gods couldn't.
Get back!
Nerissa, that's not true. You don't understand.
Please give me some time to explain.
But not here. Death is coming for you.
We have to go.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Nerissa! Surely by now Kiara's soul
has arrived before Death.
And once Death finds out that you are free again...
We don't have much time. We have to go. Now!
Please, Nerissa!
No! I don't believe you.
You've broken my spirit.
To learn that my followers no longer love me
was one thing.
But to discover that my closest
and most loyal friend has betrayed me...
...tried to kill me, and no longer loves me too.
If you no longer wish to give me your love,
then I... will take it.
Missing Promise
Lyrics: hotaru  Music: 半田 翼
Lyrics: hotaru  Music: Tsubasa Handa
遠ざかり始めた
Has begun to recede
その背中はもう振り返らない
That back of yours already won't look back
長い夜が明けても
Even if the long night ends
過ちと罪は今もずっと消えずに
Mistakes and sins still won't ever disappear
落ちる夕陽 闇が忍び寄り
The setting sun, darkness creeping in
黒く染まってく現実
A reality turning black
想うほどに どうして傷つけ試した
Why did I hurt and test you as much as I cared?
欲しかったのは ただ光射す
What I wanted was just that sunlit
その笑顔なのに
smile
何度間違い続けた日々を
As if untying and retying
ほどいて結び直すように
the days I kept making mistakes
迷っても愛にいくよ
I'll go to love even if I'm lost
哀しい涙は拭って
Wiping away sad tears
いつの間にか忘れていた
Searching for that gentle voice
その優しい声を探して
I'd forgotten before I knew it
また手を取り合えたなら
If we could hold hands again
君ともう一度約束を
I'd make a promise with you once more
途切れそうな可能性
Chasing the possibility that's about to break
見失わないように追いかけて
So I don't lose sight of it
手に入れたものなら
If it's something I obtained
理想とは違う どこか欠けた愛情
It's different from the ideal, a love lacking something
怒り 嘆き 歪めたまま
Anger, grief, distorted as they are
ぶつけ合う逆さまの言葉
We hurl inverted words at each other
想うほどに どうして許せなかった
Why couldn't I forgive you as much as I cared?
守りたかった 笑顔を
I wanted to protect your smile
気づけば壊して
But I realized I'd broken it
たとえすれ違い離れてても
Even if we pass each other by and drift apart
君を信じられたなら
If I could have believed in you
また会える日が来たかな
I wonder if the day we meet again would've come
二人の懐かしい顔で
With our nostalgic faces
何気なく過ごしていた
If I look back on those times
あの時を思い返すなら
we spent casually
ありのまま伝えあえてた
We could've told each other things as they were
まるで運命のように
Just like destiny
無くしたものかも 戻らないこと
Even if I know that what I've lost
分かっていても
might not come back
願いをかけること 辞められはしない
I won't ever stop making a wish
いつか どれほど大切な
Every time my chest aches
人だったのか 胸が苦しむ度に
I'll know how important a person you were one day
知った
I'll know
共に過ごした日を
The days we spent together
笑い合った日々を
The days we laughed together
何度間違い続けた日々を
The days we kept making mistakes
解いて結び直すように
As if to untie and retie them
迷っても会いに行くよ
Even if I lose my way, I'll go to meet you
悲しい涙は拭って
Wipe away the sad tears
いつの間にか忘れていた
I had forgotten before I knew it
その優しい声を探して
Looking for that gentle voice
ただ手を取り合えたなら
If only we could just hold hands
君ともう一度約束を交わそう
Let's make a promise with you once more
Kiara.
Dead.
Huh, never thought I'd see the day.
But tell me, what laid you low?
I must know, as there are few that could bring this about.
And even fewer who would give you reason to voyage on through my blackened halls
and not return to the world of the living as a hatchling.
Must be urgent, whatever it is.
Forgive me, but...
...I felt this was something you needed to hear urgently.
I was slain by one with whom you are quite familiar.
A tyrant of darkness.
One out to bring all the world under her domain.
To worship her for all eternity.
It can't be.
I'm afraid the Demon of Sound has been freed from the void again
and is in the world once more.
Her long confinement has ended, and she is the same as she has ever been.
Quick to anger, blinded by her lust for adoration.
And this time, I was the second victim of her lust for love and blood.
You? Murdered by that love-obsessed demon?
Yes.
And her first victim was a good friend of mine, too.
Forgive me, Lord Death, but this injustice cannot stand.
Unfortunately, her power is already beyond my ability to stop.
Please, you must do something to stop that demon.
That monster.
She will surely only take more lives...
...and plunge the world into further chaos.
Come on, quick!
Ascend to the world of the living with your great scythe in hand...
...and reap the life of the Demon of Sound before she can claim another victim.
Avenge my life and the life of my friend, I beg you.
That demon cannot be left to ravage the world once more.
I warned the other gods before, but here we are.
It is time I take this into my own hand and do what I should have done long ago.
Hmph. Your demonic side was always to be the death of you, IRyS.
Don't you dare speak her name!
Silence!
Your bloodlust and desire for adoration has clouded your judgment...
...to the point where you can't even tell friend from foe anymore.
You're the one who brought bloody doom upon your own beloved friend.
And yourself.
Your fear of losing your hold over things brings about the very result you so fear.
How dare you!
Continue on with your excuses, blame who you will for your own misdoing if you wish.
In the end, you have only yourself to blame for the situation you find yourself in.
A lust for love so strong that those you loved turn away.
A desire for power so overwhelming...
...those you have power over turn on you.
An anger so deep that you destroy all who might have helped save you.
Your fate has been sealed by your own hand.
And now, I am now here to deliver it to you.
Why do you get to decide who lives or dies?
You, who sits alone in your own realm.
Empress of all, both life and death at your fingertips.
Why?
What could you possibly know about the desire for the love and adoration of others?
You, who already has everything.
You, and all the gods, all full of yourselves and so ready to look down upon those of us who fight for more.
Mouths full of twisted tongues...
Their hearts rot with jealousy.
They're jealous of me!
Spiteful that I was loved more!
Again, you cannot see past your own desires.
The gods took pity on you and your kind.
When I created you, the first demon,
the gods felt it unjust and dangerous for such a being to exist for the sole purpose
of watching over the surface in my stead. To be mindless, soulless.
So, they gave the demon a psyche
and plucked it from my deepest and blackest halls,
freeing it to roam amongst the two worlds whenever it pleased.
I warned them that the demonic nature was too strong and dangerous to give such desires,
and far too dangerous for such a being to exist alongside the mortals.
But, the others persisted and now here we are.
My unheeded warnings leading us back to where it all started.
You almost plunged the world into chaos due to your unbridled lust for adoration.
Time and time again you gave in to your nature.
Banishing you to a void was supposed to be a chance for you to reflect on your past,
but it has only proven that you are truly unfit for this world.
アイアイヘイチューなななななんですの
I-I-I-I hate you, what is it?
君がいなきゃあたしは無い無い
Without you, I am nothing
ボッカデラベリタ
Lyrics, Music: 柊キライ
Bocca della Verità
Lyrics, Music: Hiiragi Kirai
はいはいそうですねその通りです
Yes, yes, that's right, exactly
喉を過ぎ去れば解の在り処
Once it passes through the throat, the location of the solution
アイアイヘイチューなななななんですの
I-I-I-I hate you, what is it?
君は軽薄くたびれだけ
You are frivolous and only weary
あたし一人じゃいられない
I can't be alone
それは常にひしひし
That's always piercing
あなたワイワイどうして？　でんでんダメですの
You're noisy, why? Not good at all
意味があるなら言葉にせずに
If there's a meaning, don't put it into words
正しさ態度で示さなきゃ
You must show the correctness in your attitude
すべてがずっと笑われないまま丸まる
Everything keeps being laughed at as it curls up
トップシークレット明かさないように
Top secret, don't reveal it
アイアイヘイチューなななななんですの
I-I-I-I hate you, what is it?
君がいなきゃあたしは無い無い
Without you, I am nothing
はいはいそうですねその通りです
Yes, yes, that's right, exactly
喉を過ぎればそれは真実
Once it passes through the throat, that is the truth
アイアイヘイチューなななななんですの
I-I-I-I hate you, what is it?
やはり軽薄ご機嫌なあたし
As expected, frivolous, me in high spirits
渇いた底冷えいずるの
The dry, bone-chilling cold emerges
君がいまがいま踊る高嶺など
The peak where you're dancing now
トップシークレット愛に似た焦燥
Top secret, impatience similar to love
喉を火傷させる
Burning the throat
シークレット
Secret
今に間に合う
Just in time
出てこないで
Don't come out
アイアイヘイチューなななななんですの
I-I-I-I hate you, what is it?
君がいるからあたしが痛い
Because you are here, I'm in pain
はいはいそうですねその通りです
Yes, yes, that's right, exactly
欲を超えては落ちたくないの
I don't want to fall beyond my desires
アイアイヘイチューなななななんですの
I-I-I-I hate you, what is it?
あたしたいなななななんですの
I want to, what is it?
アイアイヘイチューなななななんですの
I-I-I-I hate you, what is it?
君がいなきゃあたしは無い無い
Without you, I am nothing
はいはいそうですねその通りです
Yes, yes, that's right, exactly
喉を過ぎればそれは真実
Once it passes through the throat, that is the truth
奈落の底で
In the depths of hell
ストップ！
Stop!
Oh, such a misguided fool.
Your reckless ways have brought black doom upon yourself and those most beloved around you.
Blaming your misery on others when your demise was, in fact, forged by your own hands.
While you have earned your death in full,
it is with pity, not anger,
that this blade falls upon you.
炉心融解
Lyrics: kumata(fred) Music: iroha(sasaki)
Roshin Yukai (Meltdown)
街明かり 華やか エーテル麻酔の冷たさ
The bustling city and its neon lights, a touch of ether that's cold as ice
眠れない 午前二時 全てが急速に変わる
It's 2 AM and I can hardly sleep cause everything keeps changing rapidly
オイル切れのライター
I'm like a lighter that's all out of gas
焼けつくような胃の中
My insides are on fire
全てがそう嘘なら
If only everything was a lie
本当に良かったのにね
Things would be so much better
君の首を絞める夢を見た
I had a dream where these hands of mine were strangling your neck
光の溢れる昼下がり
On a bright, sunny afternoon
君の細い喉が跳ねるのを
I watched your slender throat twitch
泣き出しそうな目で見つめていた
As my eyes welled up with tears
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたいと思う
I want to throw myself into a nuclear reactor
真っ青な光 包まれて綺麗
And its pale blue light would envelop me so beautifully
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら そしたら
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor
すべてが許されるような気がして
Then everything might be okay, I might be forgiven
ベランダの向こう側 階段を昇ってゆく音
On the other side of the veranda, I hear footsteps ascending the stairs
陰り出した空が 窓ガラスに部屋に落ちる
As the clouds creep over the sunlight, it drips through my window and into my room
拡散する夕暮れ 泣き腫らしたような日の赤
Twilight scatters across the horizon, red like eyes swollen by tears
融けるように少しずつ
Slowly but surely, it's melting away
少しずつ死んでゆく世界
Slowly but steadily, the world is dying
君の首を絞める夢を見た
I had a dream where these hands of mine were strangling your neck
春風に揺れるカーテン
My curtains were swaying gently in the spring breeze
乾いて切れた唇から
Your dry, parched lips mustered up
こぼれる言葉は泡のよう
Words that would vanish like foam on the waves
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたいと思う
I want to throw myself into a nuclear reactor
真っ白に記憶 融かされて消える
Into the shining, white light my memories will fade and disappear
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら また昔みたいに
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor, I might be able to sleep like I used to
眠れるようなそんな気がして
And everything might be okay, I feel like I'll be able to sleep again
時計の秒針や テレビの司会者や
The second hand on the clock, and the host on the television
そこにいるけど 見えない誰かの
Someone who is there, but I just can't see...
そこに見えない誰かの
There's someone there
見えない誰かの
But I just can't see them
笑い声 飽和して 反響する
Their laughter swells and grows into an endless echo
Allegro agitate
耳鳴りが消えない 止まない
The ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away
Allegro agitate
耳鳴りが消えない　止まない
The ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away
誰も皆消えていく夢を見た
I had a dream where the whole entire world disappeared
真夜中の部屋の広さと静寂が
Tonight, I'm swallowed by the vastness of my dark room
胸につかえて
Yet, silence closes in and suffocates me
上手に息ができなくなる
My lungs can't find the air I need to breath
核融合炉にさ　飛び込んでみたいと思う
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor
そしたらきっと眠るように　消えていけるんだ
Then I could finally fade away, as easily as closing my eyes to sleep
僕のいない朝は　今よりずっと素晴らしくて
A new dawn without me would surely be dazzling new day
全ての歯車が噛み合った
All of the gears would be turning together in harmony
きっとそんな世界だ
Surely, that's how the world would be
Hi darlings, and welcome to my 3D concert.
My first technically solo one!
As you can see up here is the hashtag for today,
which is #RequiemforLove3D.
I'm watching the chat. Did you guys enjoy it?
Did you like it? Did you have fun?
I sure hope so.
Well, obviously a lot just happened,
but I must let you all know
this was all a musical,
so none of it was real. I didn't—no one is hurt.
There was no Hololive girls hurt
in the making of this musical,
so please don't worry.
Um, this stage is awesome,
so I want to give it up to the team
over at Hololive Productions
who put this all together.
Can we just take a look, take a moment to admire
this beautiful stage before us?
Some of the more lesser-shown details
I kind of wanted to highlight a little bit.
So, let's go ahead and take a look at,
maybe the moon, maybe. Look at that big thing
in the background! It was also dark red
at one point,
but currently it is as it probably should be—
normal, beautiful, because I was killed. So...
We also have the giant castle in the background,
which is, oh my gosh, I was so excited for this!
I was like "I want something that's really
kind of like cathedral-esque"
and dark and gothic and they fully delivered!
I'm so, so pleased with how it ended up looking
in the final. So, so happy.
We also have the beautiful stained glass.
If you take a look back there,
these ones were actually screens,
but we also have the ones on the side
that were a little bit broken,
but could also change as well. So, very fun!
It was kind of something that I was like,
"Oh, I wonder how it's gonna go?"
But I think it ended up looking really cool, right?
Lastly, we have all of these lovely flowers
out in front. I just thought they came out
so pretty and I love how they kind of
change throughout.
So it just kind of looked like nothingness,
like a little void of like dead plants,
but then at the end they all bloomed
and it was so beautiful and oh my gosh!
I was so nervous! You might have noticed
also, something's a little different about me today.
Do you see anything different? My wings are out!
I decided since we've known each other
for kind of a long time now,
that maybe it was finally time to...
stop pretending they're a coat and actually
show you what they were.
But I did decide to take off my arm warmers
a little bit
just cause, you know, I was feeling a little
warm after all of that movement.
Yeah, there we go! What do you think?
I am capable!
...of flight.
Obviously, it's a little—
It's a little slow, but I'm working on it.
I'm working on my muscles.
So, we'll—I'll figure it out eventually.
It's been a while. I was locked up for like
9,000 years. Cut me some slack!
Well, this is all very exciting.
So again, I'm so happy to have you here.
I wanted to talk a little bit about—I have an announcement after this, but before that...
...I wanted to talk a little bit about just the making of this.
Whoa! We had so many lovely guests, first and foremost.
First, we started off with Shiori Novella...
...who was our beautiful, cute witch, who came here maybe not knowing what she was getting into.
Then, we had Takanashi Kiara, the brave, amazing Phoenix...
...came in trying to avenge her friend, but ended up getting bested by the best.
Then, we had IRyS, my Nephilim friend—friends as we're both...
...demons, kind of!
And then, last but not least, of course, we had Calliope Mori come in and...
...take my life, as she should have, because, wow, I was kind of...
...I was kind of mean in that musical, don't you think?
Not exactly the way that I usually am, so kind, but...
Regardless, it was really fun.
I came up with the idea for the story, and I wanted something that was like a little more exciting...
...a little more chuunibyou, because deep down...
...I am cringe, but I am free.
So I hope you enjoyed the concept. We had amazing scriptwriters...
...and just the whole team working on all of this was so amazing.
So thank you for everyone who put in their efforts into this.
Seriously means so much to me. And audience—Jailbirds...
...thank you so much for watching. I hope you had a wonderful time.
And now, it is time for an important announcement!
This is my celebration merch: Nerissa Ravencroft 850,000 Subscribers Celebration!
So let's go ahead and take a look at the details. Next up—or first up, I suppose...
...'Your assignment has arrived' Plush Blanket.
This is a plush blanket featuring an illustration by basically my second mama...
...Yomosaka, at this point, who also did the promotional art, or the...
...the, like, main cover art for this musical today.
So it's very lovely. All of the merch today is going to be themed off of the DEO outfit.
Again, so beautiful, so gorgeous. You can cuddle up with it at night if you're feeling lonesome.
So highly recommend grabbing it.
Next up, we have the DEO Nerissa Voice Keychain.
This illustration is by Noka. This is a cute keychain, of course.
You can carry it around with you everywhere. And in case you miss the sound of my voice...
...it has my voice in it! About six different voice samples...
...so you can click-click-click-click and hear me say different varying funny little things.
So do consider it.
Next up is the Nerissa Ravencroft Hand Puppet.
I really wanted one, and I thought you guys would too, and especially...
...with the sexy DEO outfit, I just thought it made sense.
Do think about the puppet shows that you could put on with me as your starring puppet.
Think about it, consider the possibilities!
So that is the—first one—that is one of the last ones, but next up...
...is the last item, which is the 'Match with Me!' Necklace.
This features the necklace from my DEO outfit. It is silver...
...and it has a tiny amethyst-colored gem, because it's kind of hard to tell...
...but the gem on my actual necklace is not red, it is actually kind of purply.
So please look forward to it.
Next up is the Complete Set Purchase Bonus, Limited Edition version.
It's going to come with a postcard with a handwritten autograph by yours truly.
And of course, the art is going to be the same one that's featured in the plush blanket...
...the art by Yomosaka-san. So please do consider getting it...
...if you want the whole set, if you want the limited set.
Next up is the regular complete set. This is going to come with...
...a postcard with a duplicated foil-stamped autograph by me...
...in the case that you miss out on the limited, but you'll still get my signature either way, so don't worry too much.
And both the limited and complete set are going to be coming with...
...a bonus voice pack called 'A Late Night at the Office' featuring me, of course...
...and you, who works in my office, Jailbird.
So that is all of my merchandise. Please, please buy it!
I hope you like it. Again, this is a celebration for 850,000 and I would be remiss...
...to not say that this is all thanks to you guys and your support.
So thank you so, so much for supporting me.
...following me, for watching my covers, for watching this today,
watching my streams, commenting, everything you guys do, I'm so grateful.
So thank you so much. So that's the...
...the final full set.
And yeah, it's all good.
So please buy it.
I hope you guys like it.
I hope you're looking forward to receiving the items
if you're buying it.
They will go live right after this, I believe.
So go ahead and check the description.
It should have all the information right below.
So thank you all so much, and that's that.
So, I guess I should say goodbye.
So... I don't want to, though.
I'm having so much fun today,
dancing with everyone and singing for you guys.
But I'm so grateful I could spend time with you
and share this special moment with you.
I hope you guys all had a lot of fun,
and I'll look forward to seeing you all
in my next stream.
So for now, bye-bye, darlings!
REQUIEM FOR LOVE