(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D SHOWCASE
#3DKirin
Ceres Fauna
Ring-a-ring-o' roses, fa-la-la-la,
round and round, fa-la-la-la,
jumping up and down, fa-la-la-la,
koko ni... te...
here I... am...
Hey, aren't you here early?
Wait, or perhaps am I late?
Welcome to my 3D showcase, everyone!
Thank you for showing up right on time.
I'm ready, I promise, I'm ready.
We have a lot of fun stuff planned for today.
It means a lot to me that you came to see me.
Here I am, in 3D, for you!
I have a lot to show off today,
including myself, but also this beautiful forest,
to which I call home, which I can finally show to you.
I'm excited!
And if you're also excited and you want to talk about the stream,
feel free to post with the hashtag #3DKirin,
which you can see on the screen somewhere.
And while I'm here for you in 3D,
do you have any pose requests you would like to see from me?
I'm taking your requests right now, so you better get them in while you can.
What do you think? What do you think?
I'm in a generous mood right now. I just might even do the splits for you.
Don't think I've forgotten. I remember. I remember.
You want to see? Okay, I said I was generous, but...
...but am I really so generous? I don't know.
Splits? Is there a way to do the splits in a, a ladylike manner?
Well, there's two methods. You can, you can go this way.
That's more of a lunge. Or you can go this way.
Maybe, maybe we scrap that one.
Do you have any idol-like pose requests for me?
Mermaid pose? No.
I'm not doing mermaid pose. No mermaid pose.
A slap. You want to be slapped.
I shouldn't be surprised at this point.
All right, come here. Come here.
Hoo-cha!
You want another one? You want another one?
That wasn't enough for you?
Hoo-cha!
All right, all right. I think that was enough of that.
Let me show you around a little bit.
Hopefully you're not too, too dazed from the slaps.
We have in my lovely forest many features,
such as a fountain. Perfect ASMR ambiance.
Lots of bubbles. Mm-hm.
Not only do we have a fountain... well, first of all,
there are so many beautiful flowers around.
And this giant tree! The World Tree has finally been complete.
I built it. I built it myself. I did that.
I'm nature. I did that.
We also have a bench. Beautiful feature.
And a gazebo! How many hit points do you think this thing has?
I bet it wouldn't even flinch if I hit it with an arrow. Very scary.
But...
I think I'm not the only one in this forest.
Hmm, could it be?
Nemu, come out, come out, wherever you are.
Are you sleeping again, Nemu?
(Gasps)
She's cute, she's cute, she's really cute!
Look at you, Nemu, just look at you.
Oh...
Hey, where you going? Hey!
I'm trying to pet you.
Where are you off to?
Is my 3D showcase not yours?
Don't get a big head. You know I'm the real Keeper of Nature, right?
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Are you... Are you really just going to go to sleep?
Like this? During my 3D showcase?
I guess I shouldn't be surprised at this point.
Do we have anybody else here in this forest?
Hmm...
Could it be?
There's many fully grown trees around, but...
Hey! Sapling, is that you?
Wait, but you're looking a little bit different.
What happened to you? Aren't you supposed to have a sprout?
Usually you're calling me bald, but today you're the one who's bald.
Oh no, no, no, don't look so sad. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Don't be so sad.
Come here, come here. There, there.
I will love you even if you're bald.
Incredible! Is this the power of nature?
No, you probably did this all on your own. You're pretty incredible too, you know.
Alright, Sapling, why don't we sit you down right here?
It's your 3D showcase too. Look at you go.
Aren't you awfully cute?
Let me guess... that's not your preferred seat.
This must be your preferred seat.
So cute, so cute!
What a cute 3D form you have.
Look how boing boing.
I feel like I'm getting shown up a little bit on my own debut.
But at least we have Nemu looking especially cute, and now we have Boing Boing Sapling.
I'm very cute too, right?
Well, thank you very much for coming, and this is not all we have.
Did you think I was really going to come here and just talk to you for an hour straight?
Well, that is something that I would do, but...
We have lots planned for today.
So please stay tuned and enjoy.
And let's go ahead and get started, shall we?
I'm back! Hello!
For our first section, I would like to call some friends in!
Hello, hello friends! Are you here?
Friends here!
Oh, Council! So cute!
You are here! Welcome, welcome!
Thank you for coming to my 3D showcase! I wanted to have you guys here.
And who might you be? Would you like to introduce yourselves, starting over here with IRyS?
Alrighty! Hi-RyS! It's IRyS from Hololive English, with the fellow lovely ladies, as usual. Let's go!
Welcome, welcome!
You're looking so cute! Glowy!
Thank you!
And next we have...
What's up! It's Baelz Hakos from Hololive English! Banya-cha!
So cute!
And next, who is this?
Oh, Kronichiwa! It's Ouro Kronii from Hololive English Council.
And you are so 3D and so dynamic.
Oh, look at that 360!
Oh my god! So much movement! Oh my god!
I love those sleeves! Defying gravity!
Thank you!
And up next we have...
Oh hi! I'm Nanashi Mumei!
Fauna, you're so cute!
Thank you, thank you!
Well, since I am in 3D, I wondered if you guys
had any requests for me?
Poses or actions that you can only get
right now when I can move...
...like this?
Ooh! Poses! What should we ask for?
You have one, Mumei? You have an idea?
I have an idea. I have an idea.
Okay, um, not so much a pose, more of an action.
More of an acting action, actually. Oh!
Could you pretend that you're
in a category 5 hurricane?
Um... Okay, like outside? Not in a shelter?
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Let's go! Outside!
Okay, reporting it!
She blew it away!
I guess I should be screaming.
How's that?
How's my acting?
Amazing! Me! Me! It was amazing!
Very convincing!
Thank you, thank you. Are you next? Are you next?
I want you to pretend that you *are*
a category 5 hurricane.
Okay, okay!
Is this more of a tornado?
This is more of a tornado.
It is similar to a tornado.
She's down! Drink some water!
Amazing. Thank you. Getting dizzy.
I have one! Okay, you gonna go easy on me?
What if you were a tree
in a category 5 hurricane?
It keeps going! Okay!
Ooh! She wavy! She wavy!
Look at you!
Oh no! You're snapping the trunk!
Oh no, my branch fell!
She lost a branch! No!
Wait, I was thinking of asking for a pose that
had nothing to do with a hurricane.
But everyone's asking for
a category 5 hurricane thing, so...
I was originally going to ask for a newborn baby
pose 'cause you always, you know, 'Mommy'.
But instead, I'm going to ask for
a newborn baby in a hurricane!
Okay! Waah!
Waah!
Even the sound effects! Oh no!
Thank you, thank you.
That baby's kind of strong.
Yeah, a baby... We can't have
a baby getting into trouble.
But I did not bring you here
just for category 5 hurricanes.
I also would like to play a little game.
It is a 3D showcase classic...
...Charades!
Charades with CouncilRyS / CouncilRySとシャレード
Charades with CouncilRyS
Yay! Whoo! Look at this!
Yeah, so I'll be pantomiming various
words which I do not know,
and they will have one minute to guess.
And that's pretty much it.
Everybody knows charades, right?
So let's start. First word.
Only sillies don't know.
First word. Oh, is this group effort?
It is group effort.
Huh? What?
She's pointing up. She's pointing up.
And now she's...
Wait, is it two words? Two words? Two words?
She saluted. What is she doing?
A bird word? Are you a plant?
A tree? It's tall. It's tall and short.
Middle?
Oh, evolution! Evolution?
Oh wait, no. Nature? Nature?
Dancin'? Is she dancin'? She's a baby!
Oh my, baby getting into trouble,
and then the mother...
What? Talk to the hand? Talk to the hand?
Oh, stepdaughter? Stepmother?
Wait, she cryin'. She cryin'. Someone's cryin'.
She's so sad.
Oh my gosh, what is... I can't get
hurricane out of my mind, I'm sorry.
Alright, time's up!
The word was 'Teenager'!
お題 Teenager 少年
Subject: Teenager
Oh! That's a hard one! Extremely hard one!
It is hard! I was height?
I was trying... yeah, I was trying
to go for like height,
and then I was trying to go like
baby into kid into teenager.
That's like the... 'Don't talk to me!'
Oh! 'Don't talk to me!' It looked like
a seed or a plant or something!
I was gonna say 'Maid' until the
'don't talk to me', talk to the hand thing.
Evolution?
Snap! Evolution!
Alright, next word!
Next one!
Horse race! Horse race!
Yes!
お題 Horse Race 競馬
Topic: Horse Race
You got it!
That one was a little easier. Good job.
Yeah, that was much easier.
You were like a horse.
Alright, up next... oh, okay.
Swimming! Swimming! Swimming!
Eh? Huh?
What is she... getting the water out of the way? What?
I don't think that's what she's doing.
Pebble thrower? She's putting stuff... she's spreading...
Is she cooking? Cooking? Kneading dough? Kneading dough? Baking?
Oh, she dead! Oh, she dead! Oh, she done there! Oh!
Did she just stab... stab and guts are spilling out?
Her blanket's too hot while she sleeps?
Oh, is she pregnant? Inside? What? Surgery? Surgery!
Surgery! Surgery! It was surgery!
お題 Surgery 外科手術
Topic: Surgery
That's surgery? Uh-huh! Good job!
Oh, that was the swimming move at the beginning! These are difficult words.
Alright, next up. Right in there. Damn.
A wig?
She's sneaking! She's sneaking! Bald fauna playing Hitman! Hitman! Hitman!
Oh! No? Assassin? Assassin!
Oh, is it Matrix?
Assassin! It was assassination!
お題 Assassination 暗殺
Topic: Assassination
Close. Assassination. Close enough.
I mean, technically, was I wrong? Not really. No, the mods allow it.
Alright, next word. It was close enough.
Chicken! Chicken! She's a bird! Bird! Bird! Chicken! Big bird!
What? Peacock? Rooster? Rooster?
Bigger bird. Ostrich! Ostrich!
Emu! Did you say emu? Oh my god, they're so cute.
She eating now? Chicken? Oh, is it delicious then? Turkey!
Yes! Turkey! Turkey!
お題 Turkey 七面鳥
Topic: Turkey
Good job, good job.
Why'd you say emu again? Wait, were you eating the turkey?
Eating the turkey! She was eating the turkey! How am I supposed to show it? Fauna...
Alright, next question.
Oh... down on the ground. Baby! Baby! She's a baby! She's a mom! Rock-a-bye baby!
Babysitter! Oh, yes! Babysitter!
お題 Babysitter ベビーシッター
Topic: Babysitter
Babysitter! That's so fast! Why'd you put the baby on the ground?
Babysitter, you gotta treat your baby nicer. Yeah, I don't know why they left the baby on the ground.
I guess... new parenting... parenting hack. New parenting hack!
Dammit. Just don't allow the baby to hit the category 5 hurricane.
Gotta be careful in case of natural disasters. Hey!
Keep it in the house, that's what you're supposed to do.
Are you trying to say I'm a natural disaster? Keep it in the house.
You're the most beautiful natural disaster. Oh, thank you! Oh, thank you!
I mean, she truly is making my heart go all over the place. Doki doki!
Doki doki! You're so cute! Oh, thank you!
Alright, next question. Next, next one.
Salt! Salt! Cooking! Cooking! She's got the salt! Spice! Bowl! Spice! Curry!
Shaker! Oh! Yes! Salt shaker!
お題 Salt Shaker 食卓用塩入れ
Topic: Salt Shaker
Oh! What was it? Salt shaker specifically. Oh, I see! I see!
You see? I see! Alright, thank you guys for joining me!
I appreciate you being here to celebrate with me! Thank you!
Yay! Thank you! You're the goddess of the forest! You're so beautiful!
Thank you! This is my forest now! Oh my god!
Can we eat tea together? Yes! Tea in the garden!
...and crumpets!
Shrimp crumpets!
We can have a tea party together.
Yes, please! I want a shrimp crumpet!
Yeah, in the gazebo!
In the gazebo!
Well, thank you for joining me.
And up next, I will be...
...perhaps doing some performances? Oh?
Please stay tuned!
Thank you! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Good luck! Thank you!
Bye-bye! Thank you, guys!
語れない 眠れない トロメライ
Ineffable, sleepless dream.
不可思議のカルテ
Lyrics: 児玉雨子 Composition: カワイヒデヒロ
Fukashigi no Karte
Lyrics: Ameko Kodama Composition: Hidehiro Kawai
あなたの見てるショウタイム
The showtime you are watching.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart no one can read.
不可思議 知りたいだけ
I just want to know the mystery.
嘘も現実も
Whether lies or reality,
どっちも真実だったの
Both were the truth.
本当よ
It's true.
今日も独り言
Another soliloquy today.
何にも無理をしないで
Don't push yourself for anything.
私 愛されたい
I want to be loved.
有耶無耶 サヨナラ 軽いめまい
Vague goodbyes and a slight dizziness.
あなたのいない現象界
The world of phenomena where you aren't here.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart no one can read.
自意識 溢れ出して
Self-consciousness overflowing.
鼓動 世界像
The heartbeat, the world-view,
いつも噛み合わないの
They never seem to align.
いたくて
It's painful.
毎晩 願い事
Making a wish every night.
何にも うんと言わないで
Don't say "yes" to anything.
混ざり溶け合いたい
I want to mix and melt together.
他愛ない わからない 理由 存在
Silly, incomprehensible reasons and existence.
あなたと残す後悔
Regrets left behind with you.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart no one can read.
不快 繰り返して
Repeating unpleasantries.
正しい 夢は
Righteous dreams are...
哀しい 声は
Sorrowful voices are...
美しい
Beautiful.
疑わしい
Suspicious.
羨ましい ねえ
Enviable, aren't they?
どれ
Which one?
語れない 眠れない トロメライ
Ineffable, sleepless dream.
あなたの見てるショウタイム
The showtime you are watching.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart no one can read.
不可思議 知りたいだけ
I just want to know the mystery.
終わらない ことはない トロメライ
There is nothing that doesn't end, a dream.
あなたと跨ぐ境界
The boundary I cross with you.
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart no one can read.
思春期 傷口 胸の内
Puberty, a wound, inside the chest.
不可思議 知りたいだけ
I just want to know the mystery.
Ah! Watame-senpai!
Yay! Hello! Hello!
Thank you!
This was my first guest of my 3D Showcase,
my beloved Senpai, Watame-senpai!
Yay! Hey!
ホロライブJP4期生、ホロライブEN4期生…
Hololive JP 4th Gen, Hololive EN 4th Gen...
角巻わためだー！
It's Tsunomaki Watame!
Yay!
Thank you for coming to my forest.
What do you think of the stage?
すごい！
Amazing!
Very beautiful place.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
Wow!
Oh, Fauna's house?
Oh! My house?
Very big!
Very big な！
Very big, right!
Mmm... Do you want to go?
行きますか？
Shall we go?
Let's go!
Wait! We have a show!
だめか？まずだめか？
No? Not right now?
そっか。じゃああとで。After.
I see. Then later. After.
あとで。Ah... ah...
Later. Ah... ah...
Very... 3Dだよ！かわいい！
Very... 3D! So cute!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Same 同じ色。ね？ピンク。ピンク。
Same, same colors. Right? Pink. Pink.
白。白。白。
White. White. White.
White. ね？同じ。同じ。
White. Right? The same. The same.
全身ね！かわいい！
Head to toe! So cute!
Kawaii!
So cute!
かわいい。Big face, small face. イエーイ！
Cute. Big face, small face. Yay!
Kawaii! Kawaii!
So cute! So cute!
Kirin...
Simp Kirin... Hi!
Kawaii!
So cute!
なに？なに？なに？なに？
What? What? What? What?
Nani nani nani...
What what what...
Love, love.
Ah! Nani nani nani...
Ah! What what what...
これこれこれこれ。
This this this this.
ぎゅう〜
Squeeze~
一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for singing with me!
こちらこそありがとう！また歌いましょう！
Thank you too! Let's sing together again!
はい、はい！頑張ってね！ありがとう！またね！Thank you! またね！
Yes, yes! Good luck! Thank you! See you! Thank you! See you!
ありがとう！またね！バイバイ！
Thank you! See you! Bye-bye!
Ah... I feel healed already. Wata-senpai... she's so cute!
That was just our first guest though, and I think we have one more on the way.
Doesn't something smell a little fishy to you? Hmm...
もうそう♡えくすぷれす
Mousou♡Express
Lyrics: megrock Composition: 神前 暁 (MONACA)
Lyrics: megrock Composition: Satoru Kousaki (MONACA)
妄想かね、暴走する、ちょっとお灸に…
Is it a delusion? I'm running wild, on an express...
飛びのいて今会いにいきたいの。
I want to jump out and go see you now.
言い訳とか理由だとか面倒くさいな。
Excuses and reasons are such a pain.
運命だから仕方ないよね。
It's destiny, so it can't be helped, right?
叶わなければこの恋は…
If it doesn't come true, then this love...
永遠に醒めることもないの。
will never wake up for eternity.
何も知らない目を閉じて…
Closing my eyes, knowing nothing...
かわいいままで欲しいのにな。
Even though I want to stay cute.
思い通りにならない世界ならもういらない。
If it's a world that doesn't go my way, I don't need it.
欲しいのはひとつだけ。全部全部全部…
There's only one thing I want. All of it, all of it, all of it...
思い通りにならない世界と変えたい。
I want to change it with a world that doesn't go my way.
欲しいのはひとつだけ。全部全部全部全部！
There's only one thing I want. Everything, everything, everything!
この気持ちはこの気持ちにしかわかんないのに。
Even though only these feelings can understand these feelings.
みんな勝手に決めつけすぎだし。
Everyone is just assuming too much.
知らないわ 知ったふりで そんな簡単に。
I don't know, pretending to know so easily.
あきらめちゃうのもったいないよね。
It's a waste to just give up, right?
叶わなければこの夢は…
If it doesn't come true, then this dream...
永遠に醒めることもないの。
will never wake up for eternity.
何も知らない目を閉じて…
Closing my eyes, knowing nothing...
かわいいままで欲しいのにな。
Even though I want to stay cute.
思い通りにならない世界なら…
If it's a world that doesn't go my way...
世界なら漏れない
If it's the world, it won't leak out
欲しいのはいつだって 全部全部全部
What I want is always everything, everything, everything
思い通りにならない
It doesn't go as I want
世界とか要り得ない
A world like that can't exist
欲しいのはいつだって 全部全部全部
What I want is always everything, everything, everything
全部全部全部全部
Everything, everything, everything, everything
全部
Everything
叶わなければ この恋は
If this love doesn't come true
永遠に冷めることもないの
It will never grow cold for eternity
何も知らない 目を閉じて
Knowing nothing, close your eyes
かわいいままで 星の願い叶
While staying cute, my wish to the stars comes true
思い通りにならない
It doesn't go as I want
世界なら漏れない
If it's the world, it won't leak out
欲しいのはいつだって 全部全部全部
What I want is always everything, everything, everything
思い通りにならない
It doesn't go as I want
世界とか要り得ない
A world like that can't exist
欲しいのはいつだって 全部全部全部
What I want is always everything, everything, everything
全部全部全部
Everything, everything, everything
せーの！
Ready, go!
ドキドキ
My heart's pounding
HIDE TARGET BODIES (+1000)
FAUNANA (+2000)
ASMR ASSASSIN (+5000)
Hmm, is there someone hiding over there?
You don't have to be shy.
Come on over, take a seat.
You didn't think you could enter my forest...
...without being invited for a cup of tea, did you?
Come on, scoot closer.
Have a sip.
It won't hurt, I promise.
Hey you.
You're finally awake.
You were trying to enter the forest, right?
Walked right into my tea party.
Same as all the other saplings in this forest.
That was your first mistake.
Those who join me for tea...
...tend to have a hard time leaving afterwards.
Speaking of leaves...
...look at you, you've already sprouted yours.
You're growing into a wonderful little sapling already.
My tea is pretty potent.
Don't worry little sapling.
You'll come around to life with nature.
You can leave all of your human worries behind.
Civilization, society, work...
...none of that matters when you're a tree.
I'll take good care of you.
Now, it looks like you do need some care.
Your fresh new sprouted leaves need some attention.
Here, here, let me get some tools.
Hmm, what should I use on you?
Let me check my box.
Sage?
No.
Wrench?
Hmm.
Banana?
Maybe.
Scalpel?
Hmm.
No, scissors would be better.
I'll just grab whatever.
Starting with you.
What's that look for?
Oh, worried about these?
You know I love you.
I just need to prune some of your leaves.
I would tell you to stay still...
...but you don't have much of a choice like this.
Here, here, this one...
Mm... and this one...
There, doesn't that feel better?
I'm sure all those extra leaves were weighing you down.
Oh, what about this one?
Uh... maybe that one was important.
Don't worry about that little sapling.
It'll grow back.
Uh... let's move on here.
I will use this brush to clean your leaves.
The... uh... remaining leaves, I guess.
Yoshi yoshi, yoshi yoshi.
There, there.
I'll accept you even if you lose all of your leaves...
...and must rely on me to provide you...
...with the nutrients you're no longer able...
...to create through photosynthesis.
Yoshi yoshi.
Mhmm, looks good.
Now, if you want to grow those back...
I think you'll need some water.
Oh, but not too much.
Don't want those roots to rot away.
Mhmm, there.
With care like this, you'll want to...
...stay in the forest forever, right?
Now, let me just get you one more thing.
Hey! Where are you looking?
Don't even think about it!
Here, here, have a bite of this.
I'm sorry for hitting you with a book.
There, there, there, there. You'll be okay.
Come on, I need you nice and revived...
...so you can watch the rest of...
...my showcase, okay?
神様の神様
Kamisama no Kamisama
Lyrics/Composition: 真部脩一
Lyrics/Composition: Shuichi Mabe
いっさいこの世はどうなって いるのかな
I wonder how the heck this world is turning out.
私は虎を飛び越えて 地球の周りをくるるり
I leap over tigers and spin 'round and 'round the Earth.
エクスタシー・モンキーの作りたて このバイオ・リザーブ
The freshly-made Bio-Reserve of the Ecstasy Monkey.
前途の洗濯機みたいね So I'm just spinning around
Like a washing machine ahead, so I'm just spinning around.
Around, around the world
さきにきりかな たな たな から
Is it the mist ahead? From the shelf, the shelf...
Spinning around, around, around the world
ときにものかたり おもい つたえたいから
Because sometimes I want to tell a story and convey my feelings.
最近どうなんて言われりゃ
If someone asks how things have been lately,
I'm fine thank you だっていうでしょ
I'll just say I'm fine, thank you.
ぐんぐんてんがりになる私を
As I'm spinning and soaring more and more,
そっとそばにきて光って
Come softly to my side and shine.
愛した時から
From the moment I loved you,
私が神様
I am God.
...さい あなたの虜に
...love, to be your captive.
成り上がり
Rising in the world,
歴史は去れど繰り返す
History passes but repeats.
はじめとおわりがある不思議
The mystery of having a beginning and an end.
カストルプツェル ゲッコー
Castrop-Rauxel, moonlight.
巡り巡る この季節に
Going around and around in this season,
ヴェッティント ヴェノ
Wettingto Veno,
この手にして
Hold it in these hands.
I'm just spinning around around around the world
好きにしてもいい
You can do as you like,
もういい いいかな
is it okay? Is it?
欲しいものかな かな
Is it what I want?
かななら
If it is...
それが意味かな かな
is that the meaning?
かななら
If it is...
トントントンカラリン
Tonton Tonkararin,
とんと届かない
doesn't reach at all.
そんなアナザービューもあるでしょう
There's probably another view like that too.
コンコンコンガッテ
Konkon Kongatte,
ほどけない
can't be untied.
恋に身を窶そうよ
Let's lose ourselves in love.
神様 私が
God, I am...
あなたの神様
your god,
みたいねー
it seems.
Let Me Stay Here
Into the sky 小鳥たち
Into the sky, little birds,
ほほえんで歌を
smiling and singing a song.
輪になり踊ろう
Let's dance in a circle.
Blue and evergreen trees
夢をのせて
carrying our dreams,
恋する魔法に
in the magic of love,
かけられた
I was cast.
風にささめく妖精
Fairies whispering in the wind,
ここはおやすみ
goodnight here.
ユニコーンの背中で
On the back of a unicorn.
高いお城の窓から
From the window of a high castle,
シャボン玉 吹け飛んでね
blow soap bubbles and let them fly.
お星様
Mr. Star.
It's just a fairy tale
Sweet dreams awake
Like a lollipop
Running everywhere
Wandering around
お願い
Please,
Let me stay here
Ring a ring a roses
Fall around and round
Walking in the garden
I want to stay here forever
Ring a ring a roses
Fall around and round
Walking in the garden
ここに来て
come here.
お願い
Please,
お星様と
with the stars,
はにかんでキッス
a shy kiss.
二人をいつまでも
Both of us forever,
幸せに包まれながら
while being wrapped in happiness.
Just my dream
The golden sunlight shows
If it's time to wake up
Waiting quietly
Shutting my eyes and I say
お願い
please,
Let me stay here
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
バニラソルト
Vanilla salt
甘い
If it's
だけなら
just sweet,
ソルトかけましょう
let's sprinkle some salt.
誰よりももっともっと私を
More than anyone, I want you to
知ってほしいからさらけだしたい
know me more and more, I want to bare it all,
でもできないのk-k-nothing
but I can't... k-k-nothing,
もどかしすぎる
it's just too frustrating.
弱さ見せようとすればするほど
The more I try to show my weakness,
無駄に強がりすべてが裏腹
the more I pointlessly act tough, everything is the opposite,
本当は私泣き虫なんだ
the truth is I'm a crybaby,
黙ってたけど
though I've kept quiet about it.
でも甘いだけの愛はちょっと
But love that's only sweet is a bit
私が求めているものとは違う
different from what I'm looking for.
It's different from what I'm looking for.
白と言われたら黒だって言っちゃう
If I'm told 'white,' I'll say 'black,'
素直になれないあまのじゃく
I'm a contrarian who can't be honest.
好きと言われたら大嫌いだって
If I'm told 'I love you,' I say 'I hate you,'
嬉しいのになんでなんだろう
even though I'm happy, I wonder why that is.
甘い
Sweet
バニラに
vanilla,
ソルトかけるように
like sprinkling on some salt.
一途に好きになってしまったら
Once I fall in love single-mindedly,
24時間7日間ずっと
24 hours a day, 7 days a week,
あなたのことひたすらthinking
I'm just thinking about you,
かなり極端
it's quite extreme.
まさかここまであなたにはまると
Nobody ever expected I'd
誰も予想なんてしてなかった
fall for you this much,
天気予報じゃ当たらないんだ
a weather forecast won't predict
恋の行方は
the destination of love.
二人で一緒にいる時間に
In the time we spend together,
刻まれた思い出は
the memories carved within
宝物なんだ
are my treasures.
右と言われたら左に曲がっちゃう
If I'm told 'right,' I'll turn 'left,'
素直になれないあまのじゃく
I'm a contrarian who can't be honest.
好きと言われたら大嫌いだって
If I'm told 'I love you,' I say 'I hate you,'
嬉しいのになんでなんだろう
even though I'm happy, I wonder why that is.
バニラ…
Vanilla...
甘いだけのバニラより
Rather than just sweet vanilla,
ちょっと塩したほうが
if you add a little salt,
甘みも増してゆくし
the sweetness actually increases,
飽きがこない
and you'll never get tired of it.
甘いだけの愛もそう
Love that's only sweet is the same,
ちょっと塩したほうが
if you add a little salt,
二人の距離も縮まり
it'll shorten the distance between us,
きっと今日より素敵な未来が待ってるの
and surely a more wonderful future than today awaits.
白と言われたら黒だって言っちゃう
If I'm told 'white,' I'll say 'black,'
素直になれないあまのじゃく
I'm a contrarian who can't be honest.
好きと言われたら大嫌いだって
If I'm told 'I love you,' I say 'I hate you,'
嬉しいのになんでなんだろう
even though I'm happy, I wonder why that is.
甘い
If it's
だけなら
just sweet,
ソルト…
salt...
バニラソルト
Vanilla Salt
かけましょう
Let's pour it on
バニラなソルトで
With vanilla salt
Ah, thank you for listening!
Ooh, that song brings back memories.
Vanilla Salt from Toradora.
We did a members' watchalong of that together...
...so that song is special to me.
It always brings back memories...
...and it makes me a little bit emo.
But maybe I'm always emo inside.
I don't know, there's something about songs...
...that have memories attached to them.
It brings out the feels.
But maybe it's also this beautiful place...
...that brings out the feels.
Maybe it's you that brings out the feels.
Did you like the songs I chose?
I really wanted to go for things or songs...
...that had like a soft effect to them.
And I was happy to be able to sing...
...some of my favorite songs for you.
I wonder if you've heard all of them.
Do you know where they're all from?
They're all from anime.
But I was happy to sing them.
And I was especially happy to be able to perform...
...with Watame and Gura as well.
So thank you too for performing with me.
And thank you, you guys...
...because it's because of you...
...that I'm able to stand here like a true idol.
And look, I changed!
I changed from before.
I'm wearing my idol outfit now.
It's really pretty.
I especially love when it glows like this.
I think it matches the nighttime ambiance perfectly.
And I really feel like a magical princess.
Because, because look, come here, come here.
Let me bless you with my sparkles.
Doesn't it feel magical?
I really love it.
And I really love the nighttime version of the stage.
It has completely transformed.
I might be a little biased...
...I think I like the nighttime version better.
It has these glowing orbs in the forest.
I really wanted it to have a magical feel...
...and it has beautiful glowing flowers.
There might even be some glowing mushrooms.
Do you think they're poisonous?
Will you check for me? No, no, don't do that.
It's too dangerous.
Plus, I don't like eating mushrooms. Do you like them?
Have saplings learned to take all of my habits...
...for their own yet?
But, I think in this stage, we also have...
...perhaps you've seen, dancing saplings!
Look at you, aren't you cute?
And they each have their own personalities...
...as we all do.
Which one is you? Is that you? Is that you?
And the stage has also transformed the gazebo.
Now instead of a tea party, we have this bed...
...which perhaps I will collapse on...
...after this is done.
Oh, it's so sleepy.
I need to hang in there a little more.
Send me your energy.
But actually, wouldn't I...
...wouldn't I go sleep in my beautiful cottage...
...in the background?
Maybe, maybe this is where the saplings sleep.
Saplings have to sleep outside.
At least I gave you a nice, nice bed to sleep on.
A nice gazebo.
What do you think? Do you like the daytime version...
...or the nighttime version?
I'm a fan of the nighttime version myself.
Well, I do have one more thing to show you...
...in this stream.
Can you guess what it is?
It would be... Ta-da!
Wha! It's merch!
I have more merch for you!
I wanted to make something that would be really useful.
And earlier this year...
...when I came to Japan for the first time...
...I discovered phone rings.
They're a magical invention.
I... they changed my life.
Sap-Ring Smartphone Ring
I don't mean to sound like an infomercial here.
No, you cannot skip the ad.
No skip ad.
Um, if you're not familiar with the concept of a phone ring,
basically, you stick it on the back of your phone, any phone,
and then you can use it to prop up your phone anywhere you go
and watch YouTube, watch me on YouTube maybe
or whatever else you want. Um, it's super useful to have a little stand.
And it also can help you hold your phone too, you can stick your fingers in
スマホ［サプ］リング
Sap-Ring Smartphone Ring
and it makes it more comfortable. You don't want to strain your pinky, do you?
So that is the merch that I have created for you. I hope you'll find it useful.
It is in the shape of a cute golden apple with a cute sapling.
There's kind of a sapling theme. It makes sense because all of this is possible
because of you guys. Thank you, thank you.
Cute saplings around, cute sap-ring, phone ring.
I hope you like it. I hope you find it as useful as I have found it.
I hope it'll be useful merch for you.
And so with that, I'm afraid that our time is just about up,
but again, I really wanted to thank you, you for being here
and watching and cheering me on. I'm just... I'm just a gaming Kirin,
but because of you, I can also be an idol.
And it has been a really magical experience here in my forest.
I'm glad you can finally see... finally see where I've been streaming all this time.
Closet... closet is over there. Hehe.
That's where... that's where I'm streaming for you.
Finally revealed. Thank you, thank you from the bottom of my heart
for coming today. I appreciate it.
Because of you, I can be here and be an idol and a gamer
and live out my dreams. Thank you, thank you.
And please don't forget to watch the other Council members' 3D showcases
and watch IRyS's too, even if it was a while ago. Hehe.
And I want to thank you, thank you, thank you. I can't say it enough.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you for watching.
And I will see you very soon. I appreciate you.
Thank you for being here. I hope you had a good time.
And I will see you next time. Farewell, bye-bye!
Bye! Bye!
WHAT THE TRUCK
0 DAYS SINCE LAST UUUUUUUUUUUUUUU
BETHANY
MOTHER TRUCKER