(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Yeah, that's karma.
Yeah, get down.
Howl!
Checkmate, I'm a superstar.
Still the same but you rock with it (uh-huh)
Yeah, like 24/7 I'm a hot mess, you love-hate.
Get less boring, oh my God.
Home run, about to swing my shot, uh-huh
Yeah, like a villainess, villainess, bring on the jackpot!
余所も見飽き役も変わらない
Still tired of looking elsewhere, the roles don't change
ハートにぶちかます
Blow it into the heart
(Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Life's just a table, want to stop to fool around.
Chaos speak right now, I can show you how
(Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Don't get confused, we are not the same.
I'm a ruthless dame.
No way, no way out, way out, way out.
Good versus evil, so who've I become?
Just sit back and party, just leave it to one.
Whoops, uh. Lose my lips, lose my le-le-lips, yeah, uh.
That's karma, tadah!
Whoops, uh. Lose my lips, I'm about to say some, check it.
Yeah, that's karma, tadah!
Sorry I'm just better.
Sorry we're go-getters.
In my power, wicked, sonic, tricky, why you runnin'?
Bet you think you're clever.
(Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Whatever.
Whoo! Talk about a come by ya
(Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Hey y'all, checkin' this out!
偽の僕　ごちゃ混ぜ
Mixed up the fake me
欲望召し上がれ
Enjoy the desire
相手はバケモノ、しょうもな世界　飛ばす Boom boom
The opponent is a monster, in a hopeless world, let it fly Boom boom
Don't mess with me
ドラマチック　狂い咲き人　この指止まれ
Dramatic, people blooming out of season, come together
ハードにハートは灰になって
Hard and heart turns to ashes
弾けて恥じらい捨てちゃいな
Pop it and throw away your shyness
叫び踊り誇れ　機動的招待　どしたって頂戴
Scream, dance, and be proud, dynamic invitation, no matter what, please
おどけたパラダイス
A clownish paradise
惹かれ合う　鏡花水月　共鳴　共鳴
Attracting each other, mirror flower water moon, resonance, resonance
Good versus evil, but I'm which one?
Just stuck here in the middle, that's not any fun.
Whoops, uh. Lose my lips, lose my le-le-lips, yeah, uh.
That's karma, tadah!
Whoops, uh. Lose my lips, I'm about to say some, check it.
Yeah, that's karma, tadah!
想像から創造
From imagination to creation
衝動から猛火
From impulse to raging fire
ほら　あっと言う間に怒りに変身　変幻自在
Look, in the blink of an eye, transforming into anger, ever-changing
毒々しい本能
Poisonous instinct
(Yeah, yeah, yeah)
暗い咆哮
Dark roar
Whoa! Talk about a fire, fire!
Fire! So I'm just better.
Sorry we're go-getters.
In my power, wicked, sonic, tricky, why you runnin'?
What you think you're clever
Who-who-whoever
Whoa! Take it out! Kumbayah! Oh!
嘘じゃない狂信 Switching to minor
No lie, this devotion, switching to minor
Comfort me 過去のみ ONLY
Comfort me, only the past
WOW! It's today 優雅に破茶滅茶
WOW! It's today, elegantly chaotic
Welcome to Misfortune's Game
WOW!
テメェのせいだ
It's your fault
所詮ここが好き この子に決めた
After all, I like it here; I've chosen this girl
角度を調整 覚悟を微調整
Adjust the angle; fine-tune the resolve
飽きたるボーイからホットなバースに
From a bored boy to a hot verse
Best side of this special story score the rest
Gambler by nature chips start to stack
Racing life like animals until we crack
死ねよ 死ねよ 吐きつくパラサイト
Die, die, the spitting parasite
ヤンデレるテメェのせいだす
It's your yandere-ing fault
What can break down Just so when you've had enough
DIE! DIE! I can say you're not as pressed
右向きゃ右左向きゃ左
Turn right if you face right, left if you face left
Believe this fact of whether you're on this path
飽きたるボーイからホットなバース Worthless die
From a bored boy to a hot verse; worthless die
寄ってたかってらっしゃい
Come one, come all
Gambler by nature chips start to stack
Racing life like animals until we crack
優雅なDreams Await my thirst stars
Elegant dreams await my thirsting stars
Close your eyes and all you see is black
死ねよ サイコパス 吐き出すためにDIE
Die, sociopath; die just to vomit it out
悪夢の崩壊でデーモン
Demon in the collapse of a nightmare
Must be starving 時間の無駄無駄 DIE! DIE!
Must be starving; it's a waste of time, DIE! DIE!
I can say you're not as pressed
テメェのせいだ
It's your fault
閻魔か北極星 散らそうサイコ
Enma or the North Star, let's scatter, psycho
世代交代 悪役になりそう
Generation change, I'm gonna be the villain
不届き千万 飲み飲みトラップに
パラダイス・ボーン・オンリー
Outrageous; drinking in the trap
Paradise born only
あちらもこちらへ カマ持って登って見下してやろうか
Over here and over there, I'll climb with a scythe and look down on you
死ねよ 死ねよ 吐きつくパラサイト
Die, die, the spitting parasite
ヤンデレるテメェのせいだす
It's your yandere-ing fault
What can break down Just so when you've had enough
DIE! DIE! I'm the one who's not as pressed
テメェのせいだ
It's your fault
世間に足りぬ華
A flower missing from this world
パッと咲かせて 乱れ狂うわ
Bloom it instantly, and go wild
皆さん!
Everyone!
Welcome, welcome to a very special showing
of several songs from my brand new album, PHANTOMIME.
As you can see, the stage that I'm performing on today
is a bit different than the usual that you might be used to.
But we wanted to make this kind of like...
...I don't know, a more intimate feeling setting, I guess.
And I know that you guys at home are watching,
so I'm just kind of imagining the audience all around me.
But yeah, it kind of feels like a TV live to be honest.
It's really cool. I love all of the different settings
that they have come up with here.
Just now I performed two songs
that I've already done before off of the album.
Two songs that you guys are very familiar with, of course.
GOGETTERS from Suicide Squad Isekai ending,
and then also Overkill, which is one of my craziest songs yet,
that I have released the music video for on my channel.
Probably one of my favorite songs that I've ever made,
and definitely a good follow-up to JIGOKU 6.
But from here on out, I think that I'd like to do
some songs that you guys haven't heard yet.
In fact, I think I'd like to perform two of them,
and maybe, maybe another one after that
if you guys are really feeling it, I don't know.
But the next song that I would like to introduce
is a song called "Cult Following".
It's my collaboration song with Worgasm.
And then after that, after that song,
I will perform a song that you guys have been waiting for
for a long time, and I know you guys are really excited.
I'm super excited about,
but I won't spoil the surprise.
So with that being said,
let's go. Check it out.
Cult Following.
Cult Following
Could you rub the eyes?
This ain't the only battlefield
I can tell of vibes
Ego was a non, so I put
the camera down and faced it
They went and got complacent
Come and run with me
You say you stand for nothing,
no one else can relate
Just know the company you keep
is in the business of hate
Are you afraid?
Don't run away
I'm close to getting paid
Dancing on my own
in a bulletproof vest
Going shoot-shoot-shoot,
oh baby did you miss?
Ricochet, Ricochet
You can think about me
anytime of any day
Forget your street fights,
this a trench war
I'll make you march-march-march
'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision
let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row
Now here we go
This ain't a lifeline,
it's a call to arms
Become the wizard,
the unforgiven
Make a decision,
if you're looking for permission
to riot you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity,
click flash,
now you belong
The situation isn't fluid at all
Took out my reddest paint markers
and I ruined the wall
It's not that complicated
I could choose to run but I crawl
Just let the anchors of the skeptics sink
or watch as we fall
I'll be dancing on my own
in a bulletproof vest
Going shoot-shoot-shoot,
oh baby did you miss?
Ricochet, Ricochet
You can think about me
anytime of any day
Forget your street fights,
this a trench war
I'll make you march-march-march
'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision
let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row
Now here we go
This ain't a lifeline,
it's a call to arms
Become the wizard,
the unforgiven
Make a decision,
if you're looking for permission
to riot you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity,
click flash,
now you belong
Dancing on my own
in a bulletproof vest
Going shoot-shoot-shoot,
I'm gonna see who shoots best
Fighting all your battles
now they're kind to fail
They go ready-set-rage,
and then they follow us to hell
Finger on the trigger,
bout to cock it and run
Got a lyric in the chamber,
but I'm holding my own gun
Forget your street fights,
this a trench war
I'll make you march-march-march
'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision
let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row
Now here we go
This ain't a lifeline,
it's a call to arms
Become the wizard,
the unforgiven
Make a decision,
if you're looking for permission
to riot you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity,
click flash,
now you belong
Let them, write you onward,
locking
Locking
Stand for nothing
play the coward
Step by someone you've devoured
It's a sick and twisted mess,
create and exist
Let them, write you onward,
locking
Locking
Stand for nothing
play the coward
Step by someone you've devoured
It's a sick and twisted mess,
create and exist
DONMAI
Hello, again
My head's just full
The tide is high,
but I'm still low
Raise that gun like you're aiming for me, babe
Cut and run, we could never be free, yeah
There
is never any gold
Hide and seek, take a peek
at the skill that one can teach
A dance with the ideals
that you know you'll never reach
Picking a random one to be somebody
Telephone facts and poison wells...
Real tight up on your throat
Ride it steady through the gloat
Perfect sinners made of gold
Woah oh
People come and go
Only way that you can grow
Is not to give a damn at all
Woah oh oh oh
Feel the drive
One hell's breaking loose come dance with me
Fever dies
I am what I am in the rot and the meat
Kick it to the curb we're still in the fight
Never take the leap but I tell myself don't mind
Cause I'm betting all on me
Still here burning with desire
Don't you tell me that you're tired
Are you choking, maybe joking while they're stoking up the fire
People say you lost your vision but you see it crystal clear
I'm making my own decisions before they let me disappear
What do you want from me?
Guess we'll never agree
Believe in everybody ends up drowning in their own damn entropy
Internet's the mojo
You're addicted like I told ya
絡み合った神になって進めばいいんじゃねえの
You should just become intertwined gods and move forward, shouldn't you?
People come and go
Only way that you can grow
Is not to give a damn at all
Woah oh oh oh
Feel the drive
One hell's breaking loose come dance with me
Fever dies
I am what I am in the rot and the meat
Kick it to the curb we're still in the fight
Never take the leap but I tell myself don't mind
Cause I'm betting all on me
Gimme the good moss, so
後に引けないshow, so
A show with no turning back, so
撒き散らして 喚き出して 当たり散らしbo, so
Scattering around, screaming out, throwing things around, boo, so
何番煎じ 何なのか分かんない自論 護生大事に
Cherishing discussions of repeated origins
ドヤ顔でかましてる愚鈍
Pulling a smug face while being foolish
笑わせんた 聞きませんな 君のそのアジェンダ
Don't make me laugh, I'm not listening to your agenda
Let it be known 蹴ろよ I will never surrender
Let it be known, I will never surrender
People come and go, there are highs and then there's lows
Only way that you can grow is not to give a damn at all
Hello again
My hair adjusts for show
But tide is high
But I'm not alone
Feel the drive
One hell's breaking loose come dance with me
Fever dies
I am what I am in the rot and the meat
Kick it to the curb we're still in the fight
Never take the leap but I tell myself don't mind
Cause I'm betting all on me
Don't mind because I'm betting on me, yeah
Feel the drive
One hell's breaking loose come dance with me
Fever dies
I am what I am in the rot and the meat
Kick it to the curb we're still in the fight
Never take the leap but I tell myself don't mind
Cause I'm betting all on me
Ah, thank you very much everybody!
That was "Don't Mind", my collaboration song with Jean-Ken Johnny of MAN WITH A MISSION.
Probably one of my favorite songs that I've ever made.
I seriously, I can't stop kind of listening to it on my own because I'm really, really proud of how it turned out.
And I feel like I got to use, um, I guess,
a certain sort of like tone and and sound of my vocals that I don't use very often
but I actually am like really happy with how it sounds.
And I hope that you guys also enjoyed it lots.
And, um, I feel like it's a song that I can show to my family.
I might even show it to my sister, which is crazy cause she's like hyper-normal person.
I don't know.
I think also my dad might really like this song, maybe.
But most of all, I hope you guys enjoyed it as I'm really quite proud of it.
And so yeah, those were two songs that I haven't performed before, you guys.
Oh my gosh.
初披露です。
This is the first performance.
でした。
It was.
It's like the first time, the first time that it was shown anywhere is Hatsuhiro.
It's like the first time, the first time that it was shown anywhere is the first public performance.
Um, so I hope that you guys enjoyed those two songs.
But, since the vibes are really good right now and I think you guys are enjoying the show...
Um, let's go ahead and do one more song that you guys haven't heard me perform before.
The next song is called "Skeletons", produced by Yafumi-san.
It's, uh, it's another one of those songs that I feel like you guys were kind of asking for
a little bit more of like a softer, more emotional piece.
And so I put my heart into it. And I hope that you guys will enjoy it.
Please enjoy my performance of "Skeletons".
Hold on, just let it go
skeltons
Skeletons
I shatter it all, time to decide
Veiled, scattered thought
Sever it loud, time to decide
Ahem... running low on time
It's all too broken inside to decide
Haaaah...
Just let it go
Shatter it all
Time to decide
Tides, get it done
Savor it loud
Time to decide
Ahem...
Running low on time
It's all too broken inside to decide
It's out of my control
We'll just stay on the downlow
With no direction to grow
For the seed of a dream that expanded and landed me high
High... to high
There's got to be something I missed while on the ride
Haaaah...
The past escapes me
We're all just drifting
Let me go, let me go
Yeah
I'm in the in-between, both sides to swallow
Wit' use, costly, and lined inside the road
My bad, under the この狂った状況なら
My bad, in this crazy situation
ポジションばかり気にしちゃってんね
I keep worrying about my position
I'm not great
And people ask why your as still a hot mess
Like they don't figure that improvement's a process
You lose some, you talk less, you work on your aim
And spare the others that are followin' meaningless shame
At times I cannot see the point of me bein' here
Well, I'll reminisce about it all in a couple of years
The age of misfit, optimist that I missed it
Until I flashback to every wall that my fist hit
At my limit when I'm quick to give up the fight
Miracles gather in the mundane and they catch the light
I notice
Alright, jump
だって火花散り舞って
Because the sparks are scattering
捨てたような日がある後も、Out of control
Even after the days I feel like I've thrown away, out of control
It's out of my control
We'll just stay on the downlow
With no direction to grow
For the seed of a dream that expanded and landed me high
High... to high
There's got to be something we missed while on the ride
If this is only the beginning of the fiction we've read
Over and over like a fairy tale that doesn't leave your head
I'll make believe that happily ever after waits at the end
While just imagining the stories I would rather live instead
Can't fix all the cracks
Like washing skeletons
手を伸ばさ
Reaching out
この目で
With these eyes
見届ける
I'll see it through
未だどこかに在る誰もいない
Still somewhere where no one else is
私のことは何も気にしないで
Don't worry about me at all
この痛みの姿かたちでさえも
Even the shape and form of this pain
直に正しい方へ進んでいった
Soon began to move in the right direction
それが光のように見えたはずだ
It should have looked like light
Haaaah...
The past escapes me
We're all just drifting
Let me go, let me go
Yeah
Thank you.
That was Skeletons, my collaboration song with Yafure-san.
I hope that you guys enjoyed the show today...
...but as all wonderful plays must come to an end,
so must this live.
But wherever you are in your life, as an actor or player
in the grand play that is existence,
I hope you're doing well and I hope that these songs
provide some kind of happiness for you in your time of need.
Whatever that time might be, I guess.
I hope that you'll listen to PHANTOMIME.
本当に、えっと、聴いてください。本当に聴いてほしい。
Really, um, please listen to it. I really want you to listen.
PHANTOMIME、新アルバムです。
PHANTOMIME is my new album.
マジで、今まで一番最高の作品になりました。
Seriously, it has become my best work to date.
チェックしてください。
Please check it out.
I'd really love it if you could listen to it lots
and share it, help me share it with the world.
Help me share with the world my best piece until now.
Thank you so much everyone.
Peace!
Mori Calliope
PHANTOMIME
Mori Calliope: PHANTOMIME MINI 3D LIVE
M1: Go-Getters
M2: Overkill
M3: Cult Following
M4: DONMAI
M5: skeltons
Special Thanks
All my Dead Beats!!
PHANTOMIME 3D LIVE MINI