(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
愛の小さな歌
Small Song of Love
いま 幸せなのは
Now, the reason I'm happy...
ほがらかな あなたの
...is because of your cheerful...
温もりが 駆けてゆく
...warmth running through...
私の心を あの月のように
...my heart. Just like that moon...
優しく照らして
...you gently illuminate me,
そして全て 包んでくれた
and you've embraced everything about me.
不安を払い去ってくれた
You've swept away my anxieties.
あなたがいなければ 私は
If you weren't here, I...
星のように 輝けないまま
...would remain unable to shine like a star.
愛の小さな歌
This is a small song of love.
届けたい あなたへと
I want to deliver it to you.
歌ってゆく
I'll keep on singing.
夢をいつも掬う
Always scooping up dreams
だから　もう彷徨った
That's why I've wandered
あなたがいてくれたから
Because you were there for me
続けられたわ
I was able to continue
笑顔の日々をくれた
You gave me days of smiles
あなたが居なければ私は
Without you, I would be...
流星
...a shooting star
愛の小さなお歌よ
A little song of love
またあなたに
I want you...
唄わせたいの
...to sing it again
夜は静寂で
The night is silent
風が花を咲かして
The wind makes the flowers bloom
少し眠たい目と月の音色
With slightly sleepy eyes and the moon's melody
愛しき場所
A place I love so much...
離れそうなほど
...that it feels like I'm about to leave it
あなたが居なければ私は
Without you, I...
星のように
...like a star...
輝けるまま
...continuing to shine
愛の小さなお歌を
A little song of love
ただあなたがいて
Just you being here...
くれるだけでいい
...is enough
What is this?
Lagi, lagi nyanyi sedih-sedih, tapi kok... tapi kok banyak asap sih?
I was singing a sad song, but why... why is there so much smoke?
Kenapa sih? Ih menyebalkan.
Why? Oh, it's so annoying.
Ah! Pergi, pergi! Pergi! Hush hush hush hush hush hush!
Ah! Go away, go away! Go away! Shoo shoo shoo shoo shoo shoo!
Lagi, lagi lah.
Let's try again.
Semuanya, bisa lihat Moona nggak? Do you see me? Hey!
Everyone, can you see Moona? Do you see me? Hey!
Hey!
Moonuy!
Dadaaah... Oh.
Bye-bye... Oh.
Hai, I'm Moona Hoshinova from Hololive Indonesia Generation 1!
Hi, I'm Moona Hoshinova from Hololive Indonesia Generation 1!
Akhirnya! Akhirnya!
Finally! Finally!
Setelah menunggu 17 tahun mamanya mengandung...
After waiting 17 years of gestation...
Eh salah, maksudnya 17 bulan!
Oh wait, I mean 17 months!
Moona akhirnya bisa bergerak, tidak gepeng lagi!
Moona can finally move, no longer flat!
Oke, jangan lupa ya, ambil screenshot dan tweet sebanyak-banyaknya
Okay, don't forget, take as many screenshots as you can and tweet them
dengan hashtag #MoonaHoshinova3D!
with the hashtag #MoonaHoshinova3D!
Nah, ini Moona kan pengen nyanyi dan bergerak sebanyak mungkin nih.
Well, Moona wants to sing and move as much as possible.
Jadi tonton sampai akhir ya!
So watch until the end!
Kalau begitu, langsung saja ke lagu berikutnya.
In that case, let's head straight to the next song.
行くよ！
Here we go!
BLUE CLAPPER!
手をあげて Clap your hands
Put your hands up, clap your hands
誰もが誘われ
Everyone is invited
Clap your hands 響き増すように
Clap your hands, so the sound grows
BLUE CLAPPER
Lyrics · Composition PandaBoy
Knock, knock, knock
ほら一緒に行こう
Come on, let's go together
Everybody clap your hands
誰もが誘われ
Everyone is invited
Clap your hands 響き増すように
Clap your hands, so the sound grows
Knock, knock, knock
光射す
The light shines
僕たちの未来
On our future
Wooo!
Woooo!
Three!
Two!
One!
発進　見落とさず Diving　待っても意味ない Timing
Dive in without missing the start; there's no point in waiting for the timing
溢れそうな涙に Swimming Swimming
Swimming in the tears that are about to overflow
弾けてる Lightning　まだ見えないよ Maybe
Popping lightning; I still can't see it, maybe
この先は何があるの?
What's lying ahead?
まだ早いよ　夜明け　追い付くまで　夜更け
It's still too early for dawn; late at night until it catches up
でもたまには止まって Thinking Thinking
But sometimes stop and think
前を見据えて Ready　踏み出すのは勇気
Eyes on the front, ready; taking a step is courage
掴んでみせるよ　キラキラ輝くの!
I'll show you I can grab it, it'll sparkle and shine!
My story　叶う日待ってる
My story, waiting for the day it comes true
砂時計から
From the hourglass
叫んで　君にずっと見てて欲しいから
Shouting, because I want you to keep watching me
手を挙げて Clap your hands　空の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands　響き渡るように
Clap your hands so that it resonates
響かせて　響かせて
Let it resonate, let it resonate
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody Clap your hands　空の向こうまで
Everybody clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands　響き渡るように
Clap your hands so that it resonates
響かせて　響かせて
Let it resonate, let it resonate
光り射す　僕たちの未来
Our future shining with light
Yeah!
終わらないブラッシング　決めていくよ　Breaking
Never-ending brushing, deciding on the breaking
勘違いでもいいでしょ　衝動に夢中
It's fine if it's a misunderstanding, right? Absorbed in the impulse
君は何を Feeling?　解き放てよ Sparking
What are you feeling? Unleash the sparking
暗闇に放つレーザービーム
A laser beam shot into the darkness
光らせて　ステージ　創るから
Let it shine, because I'll create the stage
さあ叫んで　君にもっと見てて欲しいから
Now shout, because I want you to watch me more
手を挙げて Clap your hands　空の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands　響き渡るように
Clap your hands so that it resonates
響かせて　響かせて
Let it resonate, let it resonate
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody Clap your hands　空の向こうまで
Everybody clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands　響き渡るように
Clap your hands so that it resonates
響かせて　響かせて
Let it resonate, let it resonate
重なるウェーブ　世界を揺らして
Overlapping waves, shaking the world
Yeah!
Again!
Ha!
終わりが来るとしても　知らないよ
Even if the end comes, I don't know
何度だって回るよ　期待したいの
It'll spin any number of times; I want to have expectations
Don't give me crazy!　Don't mind relation!
Don't give me crazy! Don't mind relation!
限界まで行こう　すべてさらけ出して
Let's go to the limit, expose everything
手を挙げて Clap your hands　空の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands　響き渡るように
Clap your hands so that it resonates
響かせて　響かせて
Let it resonate, let it resonate
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody Clap your hands　空の向こうまで
Everybody clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands　響き渡るように
Clap your hands so that it resonates
響かせて　響かせて
Let it resonate, let it resonate
光り射す　僕たちの未来
Our future shining with light
Yeah!
Itu dia! Thank you everyone for listening Blue Clapper!
That was it! Thank you everyone for listening to Blue Clapper!
As you can see...
This song is so hype!
I just can't stop jumping.
I just like, "Ooh, I want to like using this song for hyping,"
I was like, "Ooh, I want to use this song to get hyped,"
because you know, jumping while singing is fun even though I'm just like (heavy breathing).
But it's fine.
That's fine.
Anyway...
Have you guys seen? Have you guys seen this?
This!
Yeah!
It's Momo!
Lucu kan? Lucu kan? Lucu kan?
Cute, right? Cute, right? Cute, right?
Yeah!
Jadi next, Moona bakal menyanyikan lagu sambil diliatin Momo.
So next, Moona will sing a song while being watched by Momo.
Jadi, ya gitulah. Kita nyanyi sambil joget.
So, yeah, that's how it is. We'll sing while dancing.
Terus nanti ada Momo-lah di sekitar situ.
Then Momo will be around there later.
Kalian nikmati aja, oke?
You guys just enjoy it, okay?
Alright!
Momo, kamu ke depannya.
Momo, you go to the front.
Shuuu!
Alright.
You guys ready?
Oh, ready?
Okay.
Music start!
多分 憧れてた
Maybe I was longing for it
追いかけてた
Maybe I was chasing it
いつまでもそういたかった
I wanted to stay like that forever
完璧なあなた 嫌になった
I grew to hate you, who's so perfect
同じ様に アイもらって
In the same way, I received love
育ったのにな
Even though I grew up like that
いつからか差が開いてた
Before I knew it, a gap had opened
八つ当たりだってしたかった
I even wanted to take it out on you
ねえ ベイビー
Hey, baby
神様は試練与えた
God gave me a trial
「強くなれよ」と うざいよ
“Become stronger,” he said. So annoying
平等なんて嘘すぎ
Equality is such a lie
分かってるけど
I know that, but...
可愛いとか
Like being cute
モテたいとか
Like wanting to be popular
諦めないの 女の子だし
I won’t give up, I’m a girl after all
しおらしく
Being demure
猫かぶり
And playing innocent
オンリーワンだよ
I'm the only one
愛してね
So please love me
生き方は無限にある
There are infinite ways to live
大げさな言葉
With exaggerated words
いじらしく
Lovably
猫かぶり
And playing innocent
私らしく行こう
I’ll go my own way
今じゃない人生 生きよう
Let’s live a life that isn’t just about the now
だって理想言えば
Because if I speak of my ideals
キミがいなくて
You aren't there
ないもの全部欲しがって
And I want everything I don't have
鏡を見たって ため息
Looking in the mirror, I sigh
あなたが悩んでいた 知らなかった
I didn't know you were struggling
みんなと同じだとしたら
If we're all the same
ピーンと張った糸
The tightly stretched thread
緩んでいく 運命
Is starting to slacken. It’s fate
神様は楽しんでる
God is enjoying this
予測できないヘタを選んだ
Choosing an unpredictable failure
私はそれ以上に楽しんでやるぜ
I'm going to enjoy it even more!
勉強とか
Like studying
仕事とか
Like working
諦めないの 女の子だし
I won’t give up, I’m a girl after all
元気よく
Cheerfully
愛想よく
Amicably
変わりはグロリ
The changes are dizzying
ついてきて
Follow me
明日分愛せるの
Can you love me for tomorrow too?
お母さんがくれたアドバイス
The advice my mother gave me
張り切って
Being enthusiastic
ミスしても
Even if I make a mistake
私らしく行こう
I’ll go my own way
胸張って生きる
I’ll live with my head held high
空見上げれば
When I look up at the sky
心が温められていたんだ
My heart was being warmed up
月に似てる
It's like the moon
痛くない
It doesn't hurt
神様は夢与えた
God gave me a dream
変われるために サンキュー
Thank you, so that I can change
見ててやるよ さあ 最後まで
I’ll show you, come on, until the very end
付き合ってもらうよ
You’re going to stay with me
雨はやんで 傘は閉じた
The rain stopped, the umbrella closed
今まで見えてなかった景色
A scenery I hadn't seen until now
瞳が反射して
Reflected in my eyes
世界を照らした 胸躍る
Illuminating the world, my heart leaps
可愛いとか
Like being cute
モテたいとか
Like wanting to be popular
諦めないの 女の子だし
I won’t give up, I’m a girl after all
しおらしく
Being demure
猫かぶり
And playing innocent
ナンバーワンでしょ
I'm number one, right?
愛してね
So please love me
生き方は無限にある
There are infinite ways to live
大げさな言葉
With exaggerated words
いじらしく
Lovably
猫かぶり
And playing innocent
私らしく行こう
I’ll go my own way
今じゃない人生 生きよう
Let’s live a life that isn’t just about the now
うわっ、gila.
Wow, crazy.
Gini nih kalo misalnya ya...
This is what happens if, for example...
Manusia-manusia jompo disuruh joget, ngos-ngosan.
Old folks are told to dance; we get all out of breath.
Everyone, bentar.
Everyone, hold on a second.
ヤッペ！
Yay!
うわああ！
Wahhh!
Ah, akhirnya.
Ah, finally.
I am having fun.
Gimana gimana gimana? Suka gak suka gak?
How is it, how is it? Do you like it or not?
Do you guys like it?
Hiyak! Encok...
Hiyak! Back pain...
...ugh... wah!
Well, Moona milih lagu ini karena kan...
Well, Moona chose this song because...
...Moona ingin menunjukkan sisi idol-nya Moona.
...Moona wanted to show Moona's idol side.
Benar. Buktinya Moona berhasil menunjukkan dengan kalian... ya...
Correct. The proof is Moona successfully showed you... yeah...
keimutannya Moona. I am cute.
Moona's cuteness. I am cute.
You guys...
I am having fun.
Are you guys having fun?
Yeah!
Of course, of course.
It's so nice. It's so nice being here.
I am in my own bedroom right now.
I know, I know. Who is like literally...
...dancing for performance in the bedroom? Well...
Now you have me.
Yeah!
Oke! Jadi Moona mau kenalin nih. Kan biasanya kan...
Okay! So Moona wants to introduce this. Usually...
...kalian cuma ngelihat di kayak pagi Moona gitu kan?
...you guys only see it on Morning Moona, right?
Sekilas doang. Jadi Moona mau nunjukkin...
Just a glimpse. So Moona wants to show...
...keseluruhan dari kamarnya Moona.
...the entirety of Moona's room.
Yeah.
Very like it.
I like it very much.
Yeah, jadi kita mulai dari... dari sini deh kayaknya.
Yeah, so let's start from... from here, I guess.
Kalian lihat gorden.
Look at the curtains.
Ini... ini yang beli mamanya Moona ya.
These... these were bought by Moona's mom.
Biasa kan kalau gorden-gorden gorden Indonesia...
Usually, typical Indonesian curtains...
...kayak gini ya. Kalian bisa lihat banyaklah...
...look like this. You can find many of them...
...di tempat penjualan online gitu ya.
...on online shops and such.
Terus di sini tuh ada buku-bukunya Moona.
Then over here are Moona's books.
Kan Moona pernah cerita kalau misalnya Moona itu suka buku.
Moona mentioned before that Moona likes books.
Terus ada juga... gimana?
Then there's also... how about this?
Can you guys see that?
One of my songs. I put my jacket in there.
Ai no Chiisana Uta and also...
High Tide!
Yeah!
And also we have this.
We have these pictures.
I love it very much.
It's from Nyari-mama, Alma-mama. Yeah, thank you.
So, once also... Ooh, it's so nice.
I really like it. And also I have this.
My usual for doing my homework...
...and also make-up-ey.
I have my precious streaming PC.
Streaming PC with also this chair.
And I also have my a lot of, you know, tea.
Because... because why not?
Why not?
Right. Yeah.
And I also have this.
My bedroom. But yeah.
Terus kalau misalnya bingung, wah, Moona kalau streaming...
Then if you're wondering, like, wow, when Moona's streaming...
...pasti duduknya itu kayak warteg. Benar!
...she must sit like she's in a warteg. Correct!
Benar. Jadi akhirnya Moona bisa menunjukkan ke kalian...
Right. So finally Moona can show you guys...
...kalau cara duduk Moona kalau sambil makan adalah...
...that Moona's way of sitting while eating is...
Yeah!
Gini teman-teman. That's how you do it. Yeah!
Like this, friends. That's how you do it. Yeah!
It's the best.
No! No!
Well, well that's... that's what we can show in my room.
I want to tell you that...
We have a lot of things, you know.
But first of all, I want to show you my body.
Oh yeah, look at that. Look at that! Sheesh!
Nice, isn't it? It's wiggle-wiggle.
Yeah, wiggle-wiggle. Everything is wiggle-wiggle.
And and also look at my hair. Look at my hair.
Are you guys screenshotting?
Nice, nice.
And also, can you guys see... my ear?
See that? My ear.
There.
Isn't it nice? I love it. I love it.
Hey! Don't! No! Na-ah!
I see, I see a lot of people like want to moonwalk.
It's been a while, I don't know how to do it.
That's how we do it, baby!
Tapi... tapi karena ini karpet ya,
But... but because this is a carpet,
jadi kalau moonwalk itu agak-agak agak sulit...
so moonwalking is a bit, a bit difficult...
...syung syung syung gitu. It's, it's so hard but yeah.
...like that. It's, it's so hard but yeah.
Wow! Wow! It's a flawless moonwalk though.
I mean, after all, I am the celestial moon.
You want to take a screenshot?
Sure, I'm gonna... I'm gonna pose.
While pose... What is that?
Oh my God! Superchat!
I'm gonna pose while I get a superchat then. Hya!
Wa! There's a lot of superchat coming! What is this?
Oh! Whoa! I got balls in my hand! I got balls in my hand!
There's a lot of balls in my room! And I'm liking it. Yeah!
Glistening balls. Nice, isn't it?
Okay. I, I have a lot of things, you know.
I cannot... I cannot look all of the superchat.
So I'm gonna keep it. I'm gonna keep it.
And I will sing a lot more for you.
But, I think my head a little bit dizzy
because of the... of the balls.
Probably the balls is come to me so...
Whoa!
Look up at the night sky, what do you see?
The glowing beauty in the twilight and the mystery.
Know what's a fantasy and light it all up.
When the time has come, I'll be rising high.
No form like a lifeline,
but never you'll see my shine.
I... I will catch your eye.
It's pulling you in, like gravity.
You will be bowing on your knees, yeah,
it's pulling you in, so close to me.
Watch my glory and mind following me like the high tide.
My rain will never stop,
the dawn begins to rise to the top.
Let my power entwine,
following me like the high tide.
I can be your bright enigma, it's no surprise.
But you give me into the brilliance,
like a moth to a light.
Pray hard to get but I'm patient,
succumb to my bloody radiance, yeah.
When you look up at the night sky, what do you see?
My shine.
And the moon just sighs
It's pulling you in
like gravity
You will be bowing on your knees, yeah
It's pulling you in
close to me
Watch my glory and my
power will be like the high tide
My reign will never stop
The tide begins to rise
up to the top
Let my power
and my power we'll be like the high tide
we'll be like the high tide
I shine so bright
and deep in the night
the way the waves come tonight
(Vocalizing)
Moona! Bangun!
Moona! Wake up!
(Moona wakes up)
Where am I?
Moona di mana?
Where's Moona?
Risu!
Moona! Kamu... Oh my god. Kamu tahu?
Moona! You... Oh my god. You know?
Kamu harus terbangun secara menyeluruh.
You have to wake up completely.
Maka dari itu kita harus bernyanyi sekali lagi.
Therefore, we have to sing one more time.
Kalau gitu, gimana kalau kita nyanyi...
In that case, how about we sing...
Preserved Roses!
短(みじか)い夢(ゆめ)を重(かさ)ねて
Stacking short dreams upon one another
永遠(えいえん)に満(み)ちてゆく花(はな)の
Of flowers that bloom for eternity
偽(いつわ)りと重(かさ)ならない
They don't overlap with falsehoods
押(お)し込(こ)めたい命(いのち)の
The lives I want to lock away
孤独(こどく)を君(きみ)に捧(ささ)げる
I offer this loneliness to you
Preserved Roses
Lyrics: Akio Inoue  Composition: Daisuke Asakura
身体(からだ)の奥(おく)溢(あふ)れて
Overflowing from deep within my body
本物(ほんもの)の鼓動(こどう)さえ
Even my true heartbeat
描(えが)いている風景(ふうけい)に
In the scenery I'm drawing
全(すべ)てが詰(つ)めたい吐息(といき)になって
Everything becomes a cold sigh
汚(けが)さないで
Don't stain it
光(ひかり)絶(た)やす方(ほう)へ
Towards the side where light fades
どちらにでも行(い)ける
I can go either way
怖(こわ)がらないで
Don't be afraid
望(のぞ)まない明日(あした)はもう来(こ)ない
The tomorrow I don't want will no longer come
鮮(あざ)やかなだけを繰(く)り返(かえ)し
Repeating only the vivid moments
長(なが)い終(お)わりに君(きみ)はまた
In the long end, you again...
短(みじか)い夢(ゆめ)を重(かさ)ねて
Stacking short dreams upon one another
永遠(えいえん)に満(み)ちてゆく花(はな)の
Of flowers that bloom for eternity
偽(いつわ)りと重(かさ)ならず
They don't overlap with falsehoods
この世界(せかい)を傷(きず)つける
Hurting this world
願(ねが)うなら見(み)せてくれる
If you wish, they'll show you
宝物(たからもの)は消(き)えないで
May your treasures never vanish
君(きみ)が見(み)る明日(あした)の
Of the tomorrow that you see
新(あたら)しい息吹(いぶき)を
A new breath of life
伸(の)ばした腕(うで)に迎(むか)える
Welcoming into your outstretched arms
離(はな)さない
I won't let go
欲(ほ)しいまま溶(と)け出(だ)す
Melting away as desired
熱(あつ)い場所(ばしょ)探(さぐ)る思(おも)い
Feelings searching for a heated place
国(くに)無(な)き者(もの)の微笑(ほほえ)みに
In the smile of a stateless person
誘(いざな)われながら
While being beckoned
汚(けが)れてしまう前(まえ)に
Before it gets stained
ときめいた抗(あらが)いこぼれて
A fluttering resistance spills over
火(ひ)を放(はな)つ蜜(みつ)に華(はな)やかに
Vividly in the nectar that catches fire
鼓動(こどう)を映(うつ)し出(だ)せるなら
If my heartbeat can be reflected...
激(はげ)しい色(いろ)を注(そそ)いで
Pour in intense colors
掻(か)き乱(みだ)した幻(まぼろし)を
The disturbed illusion
君(きみ)が信(しん)じるなら
If you believe in it
真実(しんじつ)だって越(こ)えるだろう
It will probably even surpass the truth
移(うつ)ろう影(かげ)を止(と)めて
Stopping the shifting shadows
狂(くる)う術(すべ)も知(し)らないで
Without knowing even how to go mad
血(ち)を探(さが)し染(そ)めたその手(て)は
Those hands that searched for and stained with blood
押(お)し込(こ)めたい命(いのち)の
The lives I want to lock away
孤独(こどく)を君(きみ)に捧(ささ)げる
I offer this loneliness to you
Oh...
Oh! Wah!
Oh! Wow!
Sepertinya, Moona sudah tersucikan!
It seems Moona has been purified!
Mantap!
Awesome!
Wah!
Wow!
Hah, thank you banget loh Risu-chan!
Hah, thank you so much, Risu-chan!
Wah! Yeay! Seru banget!
Wow! Yeay! That was so fun!
Wih... Lagi, lagi, lagi. Tahu nggak sih kenapa Moona milih Preserved Rose ini?
Wih... Again, again, again. Do you know why I chose Preserved Rose?
Kenapa?
Why?
Pengen aja sih.
I just felt like it.
Wah... Biar-biar bangun gitu kan?
Wow... So you'd wake up, right?
Iya biar bangun, biar "wah" gitu kan ya? Iya.
Yeah, to wake up, to be like "wow", right? Yeah.
Iya. Lagian kayaknya keren banget kalau...
Yeah. Besides, I thought it would be really cool if...
...Preserved Rose kita kan nyanyi. Ya udah, kita nyanyikan saja.
...we sang Preserved Rose. So, we just sang it.
Betul!
Correct!
Iya. Anyway, ini kan kita lagi berdua nih.
Yeah. Anyway, we are here together.
Mumpung berdua, boleh lah kita promosi teman kita besoknya.
While we're together, let's promote our friend for tomorrow.
Dia juga 3D showcase loh.
She's also having a 3D showcase.
So tomorrow, our other friends...
...are gonna do a 3D showcase.
Siapa nih? Ada siapa besok?
Who is it? Who's tomorrow?
Besok itu ada Iofee teman-teman!
Tomorrow there's Iofee, everyone!
Yeay!
Kalau begitu, karena Moona sudah bangun...
In that case, since I've woken up...
He-eh.
Mm-hmm.
Saatnya Risu, adios!
It's time for Risu, adios!
Adios! Bye-bye! Makasih ya, bye-bye!
Adios! Bye-bye! Thank you, bye-bye!
Adios! Bye-bye!
Wah gila keren banget.
Wow, crazy, so cool.
Risu cukup semangat juga ya.
Risu was quite energetic too.
Semoga nanti 3D showcase-nya juga semangat. Oke.
Hopefully the next 3D showcase will also be energetic. Okay.
Moona juga masih semangat nih.
I'm still energetic too.
Jadi semoga kalian masih bersemangat ya?
So I hope you guys are still energetic too?
Kita nikmati acara malam ini.
Let's enjoy tonight's event.
Selanjutnya, Moona pengen nyanyi lagi nih.
Next, I want to sing again.
You guys ready? Palette.
かすみに吹かれて
Blown by the mist
立ち止まり気づいたよ
I stopped and realized
区別つかない
Inseparable
モノクロの世界
In this monochrome world
彩色しても
Even if I color it
何も見えなくて
I can't see anything
まるで私は
It's as if I
息を止めていた
Had stopped breathing
もういいよ
It's okay now
遠くても
Even if it's far
叶えたい
I want it to come true
私は
I...
壊れた世界
The broken world
想いも
And my feelings
抱きしめていたいのに
I want to keep holding them
夢見たキャンバスに
On the canvas of my dreams
描き続ける意味は
The meaning of continuing to draw
この胸に
Is within my heart
輝いている
Shining bright
証に
As proof
与えることに
In giving
意味などないけど
There's no meaning, but
古い上着は
This old jacket
脱ぎ捨ててしまおう
I'll cast it aside
壊してよ
Destroy it
その冷たさを
That coldness
溶かして手を伸ばした
Melt it and reach out your hand
もういいよ
It's okay now
遠くても
Even if it's far
届けたい
I want to reach you
私は
I...
受け止めてく
I'll accept it
涙も
Even the tears
抱きしめていたいのに
I want to keep holding them
夢見たキャンバスに
On the canvas of my dreams
心込めるのは
Pouring my heart into it
この空に
In this sky
描き足してく
Continuing to paint
証に
As proof
壊してよ
Destroy it
その冷たさを
That coldness
溶かして手を伸ばした
Melt it and reach out your hand
もういいよ
It's okay now
遠くても
Even if it's far
叶えたい
I want it to come true
私のこの世界
This world of mine
想いも言葉まで包んで
Wrapped in thoughts and even words
夢の境界線に
On the border of dreams
色を足していく
Adding color
この胸に
In this heart
今輝いて
Shining now
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong
壊れかけてもいい
It's okay to be broken
この心は
This heart of mine
永遠に羽ばたいて
Will fly forever
響くように
So it resonates
塗り替えていくパレット
The palette is being repainted
Oh! 楽しかった!
Oh! That was fun!
トワ様ありがとうございます!
Thank you, Towa-sama!
演出家も... めちゃカッキー!
The direction too... was so cool!
ムーナちおめでとう!
Congratulations, Moona-chi!
Congratulations!
You know, today, to sing your original song Palette...
Oh my God, I'm so excited.
Palette is one of my favorite Hololive songs.
Because I always, usually... it's on my karaoke playlist.
So singing with you it's like...
めちゃくちゃ嬉しい。
I'm so happy.
ありがとう!
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
いやもういっぱいこれからも一緒に歌おう。
Let's sing together a lot from now on too.
Together singing!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh my God, thank you so much, I'm so nervous.
You know, when I first invited you since... since you were on a break.
So thank you so much for making time for me. Thank you.
いやいっぱい Thank you やん。
No, I should be saying thank you a lot.
Many many thank you. こちらこそ。
Many many thanks. Same here.
いやね、ムーナに誘われて一緒に歌おうって...
Moona invited me to sing together...
言ってくれて本当にもう嬉しかったよ。ありがとう。
...and I was really happy she said that. Thank you.
もっとありがとう! いつもいっぱいありがとう!
Thank you more! Thanks for everything, always!
はい! じゃね、ということでね。
Alright! Well then.
まあ、ムーナまだ歌うんでしょ? いっぱいね?
Well, Moona, you're still going to sing more, right? A lot?
ということで皆さんまだまだたくさん聴いていってくださいね。
So everyone, please continue to listen a lot.
トワはここでバイバイ! ムーナ頑張って!
Towa says bye bye here! Good luck, Moona!
ありがとうございました、トワ様!
Thank you very much, Towa-sama!
めちゃめちゃ Thank you so much トワ様。
Thank you so, so much, Towa-sama.
Next, I want to sing a song.
Moona pengen nyanyi lagu...
Moona wants to sing a song...
...ini lagu dari Indonesia.
...this is a song from Indonesia.
So this song is from Indonesia.
And I want to show you to the overseas...
...for Japan also to hear this Indonesian song.
I hope you guys enjoy it.
Next song is...
Matahariku.
Tertutup sudah pintu hatiku
The door to my heart is closed
Yang pernah dibuka waktu
That was once opened by time
Hanya untukmu
Only for you
Kini kau pergi dari hidupku
Now you've gone from my life
Kuharus relakanmu
I must let you go
Walau aku tak mampu
Even though I can't
Tercurah warna pelangi
Rainbow colors poured out
Di dalam hati
Inside the heart
Sejenak luluh hening
For a moment, melting into silence
Menjauh pergi
Going far away
Tak ada lagi cahaya suci
There's no more sacred light
Semua t'lah beranjak
Everything has moved on
Aku terdiam sepi
I'm standing in silence
Dengarlah matahariku
Listen, my sun
Suara tangisanku
The sound of my crying
Kubersedih
I'm sad
Karena panah cintamu
Because your arrow of love
Menusuk jantungku
Pierced my heart
Kuucapkan matahariku
I say, my sun
Puisi tentang hidupku
The poem about my life
Tentangku
About me
Yang tak mampu menanggung kobaranmu
Who can't bear your blaze
Hempaslah warna gelap di dalam hati
Away with the dark colors in the heart
Sejenak kuharap kau menjauh pergi
For a moment I hope you go far away
Tak ada lagi cahaya suci
No more holy light
Semua nada beranjak aku terdiam sepi
All tones move away, I'm left in silence
Dengarkanlah Matahariku
Listen, my Sun
Dengarlah Matahariku suara tangisanku
Hear, my Sun, the sound of my cry
Kubersedih karena panah cinta menusuk jantungku
I am sad because the arrow of love pierces my heart
Dengarlah Matahariku suara tangisanku
Hear, my Sun, the sound of my cry
Kubersedih karena panah cinta menusuk jantungku
I am sad because the arrow of love pierces my heart
Cahaya Matahariku
My sunlight
Puisi tentang hidupku
A poem about my life
Tentangku yang tak mampu menaklukkan waktu
About me who is unable to conquer time
Dengarlah Matahariku suara tangisanku
Hear, my Sun, the sound of my cry
Kubersedih karena panah cinta menusuk jantungku
I am sad because the arrow of love pierces my heart
Now Loading
（笑い声）
(Laughter)
ムマ...
Mooma...
ムーナだよー
It's Moona!
パギパギー、ハッ
Morning, morning! Hah!
Now Loading ...
Ih gimana ya?
Oh, how should I do it?
Malam Moona!
Good evening, Moona!
Hachi-desu, pagi ini...
Hachi-desu, this morning...
Menang!
I won!
Okay okay okay, ini kita kapan keluarnya ya?
Okay, okay, okay, when are we going out?
Okay kalau gitu Moona duluan, asyemona, bye bye!
Okay, then Moona will go first, asyemona, bye bye!
Ha ha ha ha...
Warna-warna yang terlihat
The colors that are seen
Diriku mahir sembunyi rasa
I am skilled at hiding feelings
Sebenarnya hitam pekat
In truth, it is pitch black
Kututup rapat jadi rahasia
I close it tight, making it a secret
Satu dua kali kutak apa-apa
One or two times, I am fine
Kamu pikir hidupku baik-baik saja
You think my life is just fine
Siapa yang peduli punya air mata
Who cares about having tears
Kamu hanya pinta diri berikan tawa
You only ask of me to give laughter
Ha ha ha ha...
Wajah yang kuberi perisai jitu
The face I give is a precise shield
Ha ha ha ha...
Sampai-sampai kau begitu
Even to the point that you are like that
Malam hari berkelana
Wandering at night
Pikiran liar ku juaranya
I am the champion of wild thoughts
Bukannya ku tak berusaha
It's not that I don't try
Ingin kulepas sekuat tenaga
I want to let go with all my strength
Satu dua kali kutak apa-apa
One or two times, I am fine
Kamu pikir hidupku baik-baik saja
You think my life is just fine
Siapa yang peduli punya air mata
Who cares about having tears
Kamu hanya pinta diri berikan tawa
You only ask of me to give laughter
Ha ha ha ha...
Wajah yang kuberi perisai jitu
The face I give is a precise shield
Ha ha ha ha...
Sampai-sampai kau begitu
Even to the point that you are like that
Aku bulan yang terangi
I am the moon that illuminates
Malam-malammu yang sepi
Your lonely nights
Lalu siapa yang temani
Then who accompanies
Rasa gelisah kupikul sendiri
The feeling of anxiety I carry alone
Ha ha ha ha...
Wajah yang kuberi perisai jitu
The face I give is a precise shield
Ha ha ha ha...
Sampai-sampai kau begitu
Even to the point that you are like that
Ha ha ha ha...
Wajah yang kuberi perisai jitu
The face I give is a precise shield
Ha ha ha ha...
Sampai-sampai kau begitu
Even to the point that you are like that
Wah, how is that guys?
That... that is... that is...
This is my newest original song.
I'm so nervous. I'm so nervous.
Wait, I don't know if I make a mistake. I might make a mistake.
Oh my God.
But anyway, that's my newest song.
What do you guys think?
Jadi, itu adalah lagu...
So, that was the...
...original song pertama yang bahasanya Indonesia.
...first original song in the Indonesian language.
Sia! Yang bahasanya Indonesia...
Sia! The one in Indonesian...
...akhirnya guys, akhirnya...
...finally guys, finally...
Ya, ditunggu aja ya nanti rilisnya kapan-kapan.
Yeah, just look forward to it, it will be released sometime.
Secepatnya, secepatnya.
As soon as possible, as soon as possible.
Nanti bakal rilis secepatnya jadi...
It will be released as soon as possible, so...
...semoga kalian suka sama lagunya.
...hope you guys like the song.
I hope you guys really like it.
I hope you... you like the new song.
The Indonesian song that I am...
...the one that I'm working on right now. Thank you so much.
So, what do you guys think for tonight?
What do you guys think about my... my whole showcase? Do you guys like it?
Do you guys like it? Ah...
Anyway, anyway...
You guys want to see... Right now, right now...
...I'm on the stage of hololive Indonesia stage.
This is massive! Sorry, this is so massive.
I mean look at that. Wow!
There's so many things. I have moon in my back.
And we also have kind of like a boat... boat? Ship!
I mean ship.
And also we have kind of like a boat, two boats in the left and the right.
And we have like Indonesian symbols on the back. Yeah.
Yeah, it's so beautiful.
This hololive Indonesia arena right now.
I have a galaxy because it's follow my theme right now. So I really like it.
I have a galaxy because it follows my theme right now. So I really like it.
I mean look at that!
Oh my God, guys! Look at that!
Look at how beautiful it is.
Anyway, I just want to thank you for you guys for waiting for this long months.
Anyway, I just want to thank you all for waiting for all these months.
So thank you so much for waiting for a long time.
Thank you for your patience.
And thank you for watching, and thank you for everything.
Thank you so much!
Then, I will... I'll ask you, what do you guys... what do you guys think?
What do you guys think?
But before we end this stream, I just want to tell you that...
Tomorrow... tomorrow...
...we can have something. Tan-ta-da-dan!
...we'll have something. Ta-da!
Wow! 3D Showcase! 3D Showcase!
What is it?
Airani Iofifteen will have a 3D showcase tomorrow.
September 17 at 8 PM. It is the same time.
So guys, don't forget to come to her 3D showcase...
...because I wonder what it will be.
I mean she said there's gonna be a lot... a lot of things. Yes. Yes!
Jadi, terima kasih semua jangan lupa ya datang ke 3D showcase-nya Iofi.
So, thank you everyone, don't forget to come to Iofi's 3D showcase.
Dan abis itu abis Iofi ada Risu. Jadi jangan lupa ya datang.
And after that, after Iofi, there's Risu. So don't forget to come.
Bye bye! Thank you, Moonafic!
Yay!
Thank you for waiting... 17 months! After a long time finally... I can show you my 3D Showcase* Thankyou for all the support and All the love you gave to me I will always love you
Moona Hoshinova 3D Showcase #MoonaHoshinova3D