(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D SHOWCASE
BAU BAU!
Hello, hello, BAU BAU!
I'm not a chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Mococo!
Together we're Hololive English -Advent's-
twin demon guard dogs,
we are FUWAMOCO!
BAU BAU!
Oh, can you believe it?
We're finally here together in 3D!
Yeah! And just for today,
for this special occasion,
we're back home here in the Northwest Passage
in Abbotsford!
Yeah, Ruffians!
Yeah, this is it! This is the Abbotsford home!
Can you believe it?
It's nice, right?
This is the place that these puppies grew up!
Yeah! And you know, I'm so excited for our first time to be in 3D,
but to tell the truth, I'm a bit nervous, Fuwa-chan...
Is it okay if I hide behind you, Fuwawa?
Moco-chan, no! You can't, okay?
This is our chance to show the Ruffians
just how fluffy and fuzzy we are, you know?
Okay, I'll do my best then!
Yeah! Ruffians, we have so much to show you!
But I know something that will help me calm down a bit.
Ruffians, can you do me a favor, please?
Well, can you please tweet with the hashtag...
#FWMC3D!
Please share your thoughts and your favorite
moments from today with us, okay?
We'll go find them, okay?
Don't forget to like, okay?
Bau!
Watch, watch.
Hi!
But...
Whoa!
It's time at last.
What?
I'm... Hi!
I'm still a bit nervous, though.
Hi!
Ca- Ca- Can you do the thing?
The thing?
The thing!
Ah, okay.
Okay, Mococo, are you ready?
Yeah!
Okay.
Ei! Haha!
Good. Now, Fuwawa, your turn!
Oh, my turn?
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Turn around, turn around!
Is this just because you want to hit me?
No! It's okay!
Okay...
Okay, here we go!
Ei! Ow! Oh, wow!
Maybe I'm a bit better now.
You're good?
Yeah, I think I'm okay.
Oh, wow!
If we're ready now, maybe we could share a song with the Ruffians!
Yeah!
Our first song for today!
Yeah, you know, it's a very important song to us.
Our very own original introduction song, okay?
Please dance along and Bau Bau with us, okay?
Okay!
Lifetime Showtime!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime, anytime Bau Bau yeah!
Future is bright,
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
All together now! Lifetime Showtime!
Let's hear your voices! FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!
FUWA! MOCO! BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
My heart an' soul an' tail are FUWAWA!
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away.
Just call for me, we're only a bark away.
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe.
Let's go!
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!
I love being tricky, doggy kisses are for me.
I love lots of walkies, don't need no leashes for me.
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere.
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you.
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい
Want to be together
Lifetime showtime, anytime Bau Bau
一生涯 Sing with you
For a lifetime, Sing with you
Stars wink, moon spotlight, fur-ever glow.
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime, anytime Bau Bau yeah!
Future is bright,
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Woooo... BAU! Woooo... BAU!
Step back now, all locked up, we stepped out, Bau Bau!
Moving back, doggy door keeps you the way, Bau!
Hearts burst, fluff & fuzz, we're meant to be free.
Make a break for it, it's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement, dreams sparklin' within our eyes.
Gonna keep you smiling, our breezes won't stop flyin' by.
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs,
the bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable.
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why いつだって It's that day!
And that's why, always, it's that day!
Today! Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow! Bau Bau!
一生涯 Walk with you!
For a lifetime, Walk with you!
Good and bad times, it doesn't matter!
いつだって It's that day!
Always, it's that day!
Lifetime showtime everyday Bau Bau yeah!
Future is bright,
Happy lucky puppy sisters!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU, everybody BAU BAU!
Hello hello BAU BAU, everybody BAU BAU!
ダメダメ ノンノン Don't touch the ears!
No-no, non-non, don't touch the ears!
モフモフ ノンノン Don't touch the tail!
Fluffy-fluffy, non-non, don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！BAU!
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! BAU!
フワワじゃないよ！モココだよ！BAU!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo! BAU!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah Bau!
And together, we're... FUWAMOCO!
Gather up our dreams,
And suddenly you'll come to realize,
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky.
Never-ending dreams,
We don't know if they all can be achieved,
But we'll keep on going fur-ever,
Together here with you!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたい It's showtime! 一緒にいたい
It's showtime! Want to be together! It's showtime! Want to be together!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you
Fuwa fuwa, moco moco, hand in hand with you.
Bring your smile, rain or shine,
We'll protect it, won't forget our pledge to you!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime, anytime Bau Bau
一生涯 Sing with you
For a lifetime, Sing with you
Stars wink, moon spotlight, fur-ever glow.
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime, anytime Bau Bau yeah!
And together,
We're fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Together with us, let's cheer!
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!
Once more!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU, FUWAMOCO BAU BAU!
Bau Bau! Hi!
Thank you so much!
You know, it means so much to us to...
...today!
Wow!
Hot!
あつい！
Sweaty!
Did you notice something?
This was actually the full version of Lifetime Showtime!
You know, the first time ever!
What did you think?
You know it has the BAU BAU BAU BAU...
We hope you enjoyed it!
But you know, now... I'm a bit sweaty.
Me too!
So hot!
Well, Lifetime Showtime is actually a song that we shared with you...
...for the very first time on the day we debuted...
...just a little bit more than a year ago.
Our introduction song.
You know, with Lifetime Showtime...
...we really hope that maybe you could tell us apart...
...you know, because we're twins, sometimes it's a bit tricky to understand.
Yeah, twins! BAU BAU!
Yeah, it can be hard to understand.
Sometimes I see people...
...they still don't know. They can't tell the difference!
Why?! I'm fluffy!
I'm fuzzy! Mococo's fuzzy!
Yeah! Why is it hard? BAU BAU!
So, uh, maybe we should help them.
Maybe that would be good.
Excuse me, I'm just gonna kind of steal this camera from you.
Oh, we'll be taking that.
Mococo-chan, here you go.
No shaky paws, okay?
Okay!
I'll show you the difference, okay?
I'm Cameraman Mococo! Okay!
Time to introduce yourself, Fuwawa, okay?
REC Mococo CAM
BAU BAU! I'm Fuwawa.
I'm the fluffy one!
Ah! Don't look too close, okay?
You didn't see anything just now, okay? You didn't see anything.
But I'm really fluffy! Fuwa fuwa!
Look, I have long hair.
So cute!
And as you can see here, my... my ears. They're bigger, right?
Show your ears more! BAU BAU BAU!
But Ruffians...
...you know, do not touch. The ears are not allowed, okay?
If you do something like that...
...I might just... ooh... BAU!
I'm gonna have to make you talk to the claws, okay?
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
But you wouldn't do anything like that, right?
No, they're good Ruffians.
Well, I'm a bit embarrassed, but...
I'm gonna go close up, close up, close up! BAU BAU!
BAU! Well...
You know what, Fuwawa?
What?
Today you're no longer Demon Guard Fuwawa.
Why?
You're brand-new gravure idol Fuwawa! This is your debut DVD!
Debut? BAU!
Try to do a sexy pose!
BAU! Okay... ah...
Sexy pose! BAU!
BAU! Is that sexy?
Are you trying? The Ruffians are gonna complain, okay?
BAU! You can do better than that!
Let me try again, let me try again!
Okay, okay!
BAU! Cute!
Okay, and your final... the final attack! Okay!
BAU!
Ruffians, what are you seeing there? You're being silly!
They're always silly. BAU BAU!
Well, I guess it's my turn now.
Mococo-chan, exchange!
Yeah, exchange! Okay!
BAU! Mococo!
Now this is your time to show the Ruffians just how fuzzy you are!
Yeah! Okay!
REC Fuwawa CAM
I'm Mococo! M-O-C-O-C-O!
Got it? Okay!
No mistaking it. BAU BAU!
You know, I...
This is me.
I feel a bit self-conscious now, but, Mococo's okay.
I'm the fuzzy, younger twin sister! BAU BAU!
And... my tummy. Don't look too much, okay?
Mococo-chan!
What if the Ruffians get on your bad side?
Yeah, well, if you get on my bad side...
...you'll have to talk to the claws! And I'll rough you up!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
Well, we wouldn't want that, BAU?
No, you wouldn't want that.
But you're good Ruffians, right? Yeah!
I'm filming you.
I'm posing.
You're posing? What do you mean?
This isn't cute enough?
No!
So cute, もこちゃん！
So cute, Mococchi!
Yay! Cute!
Yay! もこちゃん！
Yay! Mococchi!
So cute!
もこちゃん！
Mococchi!
I had a test today and I got a hundred percent!
Good job! Yay!
Congratulations! Bauwbauw!
Bauwbauw!
もこちゃん！
Mococchi!
Can you show us your fuzzy tail?
My tail?
Yeah!
Like this?
More fuzzy, more fuzzy!
More fuzzy?
Yeah!
Like that!
Is this a bit much?
もこちゃん、I want to get a close-up!
Mococchi, I want to get a close-up!
Wait, why so many close-ups?!
No! Not my tummy!
That's enough, okay? No more!
What?
No more!
No! I'm done!
Maybe the Ruffians can tell us the point now?
You better!
Well then...
お返ししますね、お姉ちゃん！
I'll give it back, sis!
おっかよー！
Okkayo!
Bauwbauw!
But you know, I guess if the Ruffians are happy, we're happy.
Yeah! After all, we're protecting their smiles.
Bauwbauw!
Well, since we're here, let's show the Ruffians around, もこちゃん！
Well, since we're here, let's show the Ruffians around, Mococchi!
Yeah, okay! Here!
Oh! It's our house!
Yeah, like this! Mention, this is our childhood home here in Northwest Passage.
Yeah, the Makai!
What do you think? Do you like it?
Is it a little bit different than you expected?
It's pretty nice! I mean, don't worry about the paint!
Yeah, you know, we just got into a little bit of fun and mischief!
Yeah! Mama Puppy and Papa Puppy aren't home right now.
Yeah, don't worry about that, okay?
Don't bother knocking on the door!
You can see they're not home! Wait, don't try!
Yeah! But you know, Northwest Passage is just filled with lots of nature!
So let's go take a look over here!
You see these? They're the wild dande-bauwbauws!
Dande-bauwbauws!
They're so fluffy!
Right? I love them so much! They're really nice to look at, just like the rest of it.
You know, some people, because they grow wild and everything, they think they're a nuisance.
But we love them, もこちゃん！ You know, our moons!
But we love them, Mococchi! You know, our moons!
Oh! Over here we have two moons, twin moons!
It's a bit different in the Northwest Passage, you know?
And you know, it's because of the twin moons that Mama Puppy received the blessing and that we're here now.
Don't you think they're so pretty?
Just look up at them and you want to go bauwbauwbauw!
And over this way, we have a stream!
Yeah, it's really fun playing in it on a hot day, summertime! So many memories!
And back over this way!
Bauwbauw!
Right here, this is our Legendary Tree of Promise!
Yeah, a very special part of our home! You know, we can't be without it, right?
And actually, it's even more beautiful at night! But well, you'll just have to take our word for it.
Yeah, okay! Bauwbauw!
Bauwbauw!
We're so happy to be able to share our home like this with you, Ruffians!
Somewhere special!
I'm looking forward to making so many more memories with you, Ruffians!
Bauwbauw!
間違いなくこれは...
No mistake, this is...
It's I, the Great Perocino! Bauwbauw!
Pero! Are you here to ruin our 3D debut, Bauwbauw?!
Nah, I'd never do anything of the sort! You would?!
After all, the star of the show is finally here now! Your mentor, the Great Perocino!
The Ruffians have been waiting for me! Don't you hear it? They're chanting my name!
Ruffians? So were we just the opening act, Bauwbauw?
Pero, you're just our pet, okay? And a nasty one at that, okay?
You're not the star!
No! I think it's time we put you in your place!
Bauwbauw! Let me!
おっかよー！
Okkayo!
Here, もこちゃん！
Here, Mococchi!
おっかよー！
Okkayo!
Come on, just like this!
Hi!
Fuwawa, catch!
Yah!
Ouch! Mococo!
Hi! Stop!
Bau Bau! Mococo-chan!
Look how fluffy Pero is!
Not as fluffy as me! Hi! Catch!
Yah! Eh! Stop bumping him around!
Yah! Hi! Let me see!
Give him a few punches!
Yah! Yah! Mococo-chan! Just like that!
Stop! Hi!
Well, maybe I'll show you a bit of mercy, hi!
But you have to admit, we're super strong, right? Hi!
Well, you aren't weak, I guess.
Okay then, admit it, hi, that you're just our pet!
I am not your pet! I am your mentor! Respect Pero-chan!
No, no, no! Mococo-chan, we have to do something!
Quick! Bau bau him!
Take this! Stop stretching me out!
What do you say? Do you apologize for being so nasty?
I'll never apologize!
Okay well, this is your last chance!
Never! I'll go down like this! I'm not done!
Okay then! Goodbye then!
Goodbye! Bau Bau!
Well, that was fun!
Hi! 楽しかったね！
Hi! That was fun, wasn't it?
Do you think he understands us, Ruffians? Hi!
Oh, Mococo-chan. Let's do a game of respect Pero, okay? Hi! No!
After all, the best thing about having a pet is playing with them, right?
Yah! The proper way of playing with a pet! Right!
Aegis Potato! Mogu Mogu! Aegis Potato! Mogu Mogu!
It's so much fun!
あ！誰かの気配！
Ah! I sense someone!
I feel someone's presence! Maybe...
More people who've said... hi!
It's a good smell, Mococo-chan, it's a good smell!
Wait... a bit of a cute smell maybe? A cute smell!
Korone Senpai! Okayu Senpai! Bau Bau!
Thank you for coming!
Yes! I'm...
...Korone Abyssguard! Yah!
And I'm...
...Okayu Abyssguard! Hi! Yah!
Yah! Bau bau! You've become Abyssguards!
Yes! We did!
Big foam! Yah! Yay! Yah!
We're so excited you could make it all the way to Makai!
魔界魔界魔界まで来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming all the way to Makai, Makai, Makai!
Thank you! Arigatou! Abyssguard 実感！
Thank you! Thank you! It really feels like being an Abyssguard!
Thank you for inviting us to the EN Concert!
Thank you!
And now we're all sisters!
四姉妹になりました！
We've become four sisters!
A big family! Yah!
Korone Abyssguard to Okayu Abyssguard! Yah! Yah!
Korone Abyssguard and Okayu Abyssguard! Yah! Yah!
Welcome!
Welcome to Makai!
え、何やるんですか？
Eh, what are we going to do?
4人じゃないとダメですか？
Does it have to be four people?
3人もできるらしいけどね、でも4の方が楽しいかも！
I heard three people can do it too, but maybe four is more fun!
あ、そうだね！
Ah, that's right!
え、やりたいです！
Eh, I want to do it!
Yeah, now! Right now!
今から？ちょっとルール分からないけど大丈夫ですか？
Right now? I don't really know the rules, is it okay?
え、今度にしよう、Mojanは。今度ね！
Eh, let's do Mojan next time. Next time!
今日、えっと、モココ、一緒に歌って踊りたいんですけど大丈夫ですか？
Today, um, Mococo wants to sing and dance together, is it okay?
いいよー！
Sure thing!
We can sing and dance together, okay? Yah! Okay!
Okay! Formation! Formation! Formation! Hi!
Let's all nyan-nyan and wan-wan together! Here we go!
いぬねこ。青春真っ盛り
Dogs and Cats. The Prime of Youth
This next song is a special collab with our dear Senpais, Korone Senpai and Okayu Senpai!
Please listen! Inu-neko. Seishun Massakari!
Please listen! Dogs and Cats. The Prime of Youth!
君のワイシャツの袖をまくって...
Roll up the sleeves of your shirt...
駆け抜けたら
If we run through
チラリ見える背中
A glimpse of your back
不意打ち 高鳴る胸の音にドキドキ
Suddenly my heart starts racing, thumping with excitement
BAU BAU!
猫? 猫? ニャーニャーニャン
Cat? Cat? Meow meow meow
犬? 犬? ワンワンワン
Dog? Dog? Bow wow wow
猫! 猫! ニャーニャーニャン
Cat! Cat! Meow meow meow
ニャニャニャラニャニャニャラニャニャニャニャン
Nya nya nya nya nya nya nya nya nya nya nya nyan
大福餅ぽたぽた焼き うまいのはどっちですか?
Daifuku or potapotayaki, which one is tastier?
僕的にはいそべ焼き 全然関係ないやい
For me, it's isobeyaki, not that it matters at all
待ち受けてる小春日和 こんなに高いところ
Waiting for Indian summer, in such a high place
のぼっちゃった誰か助けて ニャニャニャンお散歩こ
I've climbed up, someone help me, meow meow meow, going for a walk
今日も行く
Going again today
おてんばにゃんこわ
The tomboyish kitty
語り出す君に
To you who starts talking
ワンコも負けじと
The puppy won't be outdone
教えてあげたいの ちゃんと聴いててね
I want to tell you, so listen closely
Keep it up!
犬! 犬! ワンワンワン
Dog! Dog? Bow wow wow
猫! 猫! ニャーニャーニャン
Cat! Cat! Meow meow meow
犬! 犬! ワンワンワン
Dog! Dog! Bow wow wow
ワンワンワワンワンワワンワンワンワンワン
Wan wan wan wan wan wan wan wan wan wan wan wan
チーズケーキ豆乳プリン うまいのはどっちですか?
Cheesecake or soy milk pudding, which one is tastier?
僕的にはミルクの骨 いい子ぶってごめんなさい
For me, it's milk bones, sorry for acting like a good girl
駆け寄ってくお帰りなさい 尻尾が取れちゃう前に
Running up to you, saying "Welcome home," before my tail falls off
抱きしめてねホリホリホリ ワンワンワンコワンポコニャ
Hold me tight, dig dig dig, doggy doggy walk meow
今日も行く
Going again today
待ち受け画面
The lock screen wallpaper
お揃いにペットに したくなっちゃうよね
Matching ones, you'll want to make us your pets, right?
ベイビー嬉しそうなあの笑顔 ハマってしまいそう
Baby, that happy smile, I might get hooked on it
ブルブルしちゃう前に 愛してよね ねえ
Before I start shivering, please love me, okay? Hey
ニャンニャンニャン ワン! ワン!
Meow meow meow bow! bow!
犬派ですか? 猫派ですか? あなたはどっち派ですか?
Are you a dog person? A cat person? Which side are you on?
笑顔になる魔法みたい あなたと結ばれたんだ
Like magic that makes you smile, I've been connected with you
私のことなでなでして いつもギュっておねだりしよう
Please pet me, and I'll always beg for a hug
ずっとずっと仲良くいよう
Let's be friends forever and ever
ニャニャニャンお散歩こ
Meow meow meow, going for a walk
よろしくね
Please treat me well
バウ!
Bau!
BAU BAU!
おかゆ先輩、ころね先輩、ありがとうございます!
Okayu-senpai, Korone-senpai, thank you so much!
戌神ころね先輩、猫又おかゆ先輩、ありがとうございます!
Inugami Korone-senpai, Nekomata Okayu-senpai, thank you so much!
戌神ころね先輩、猫又おかゆ先輩、とっても尊敬しています!
Inugami Korone-senpai, Nekomata Okayu-senpai, we respect you so much!
いえいえ、ありがとうございます!
No, no, thank you guys!
おかゆ先輩、ころね先輩、とっても尊敬しています! 今日一緒に立って踊ってくれてありがとう!
Okayu-senpai and Korone-senpai, we really admire you! Thank you so much for dancing with us today!
フワちゃん...
Fuwa-chan...
モコちゃん...
Moco-chan...
聞いてもいいですか?
Is it okay to ask?
いいよ、聞いて!
Ask, it's okay!
エッと... ハグしていいですか?
Um... Can we have a hug?
お! いいよ! ウェルカム!
Oh! Okay! Welcome!
大丈夫? みんな大丈夫?
Are you okay? Is everyone okay?
BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
バイバイ! バイバイ!
Bye bye! Bye bye!
BAU BAU! BAU BAU! バイバイ!
BAU BAU! BAU BAU! Bye bye!
よしモココ、次行こう!
Okay, Mococo, let's keep going!
うん! 行こう!
Yeah! Let's go!
あのね、歌って踊ってたら、お腹がちょっと鳴っちゃった!
You know, after all that singing and dancing, my tummy's gotten a bit rumbly!
鳴っちゃった?
Rumbly?
うん、お腹空いちゃった!
Yeah, I'm a bit hungry!
もしかして、あそこに行けるかな?
Hmm, maybe we can go to THAT place?
アッ、名物も食べられるかな?
Ah, and maybe get a bit of a specialty?
名物! ラフィアンズのみんなも付いてきてくれるよね?
Specialty! Ruffians, you'll come along with us, right?
High! Okay!
High! One, two... Let's go go!
Pon pon pon pon pon pon pon pon!
Wow! High here!
It's Akihabara! Akiba! High!
Bau bau! High!
Look at all the buildings, the signboards!
Right! I can feel all of
Akihabara's electronic energy
getting me...
Exciting! Biri biri! High!
Well you know Akihabara has a bunch
of different stories to tell too,
so let's check them out! High!
Well please, over here! High!
Over here! We have a pharmacy!
And it seems like right now,
their top seller
is something that will help when your
Bau-Bau's feel like really rough.
I heard that it's been kind of tough recently,
so if you need something, please go here!
And over here! We have YAGO!
The arcade here in Akihabara,
the latest and greatest games.
Ah, but Fuwawa, I forgot my coins,
so is it okay if I depend on you
so that we can play some
games together?
High! Bau-Bau!
Well next, let's check out
the food! We have RAMEN! High!
You know in case you need something
to really fill you up
and get ready to enjoy more of Akihabara!
This way! Next, over here! Over here! High!
We have the Pero Cafe!
I hear that they have some...
some sort of suspicious and nasty maids,
but I'm sure it's relaxing enough.
And you know they have
Pero-lattes as well! High!
In case you need something.
And right beside there's Cover Denki
for electronics. You know, they've been
in Akihabara for a long time,
so they're well-trusted. And in
this way, we have Game Island!
You know there's lots of retro games,
so I'm sure if there's something you're
looking for, they have it! High!
And then back this way! High!
We have the train!
The trains just go by
BAU BAU BAU! BAU BAU BAU!
Ah, but we also have some
light stage lights. High!
I wonder why? That's kind of strange.
But you know when you're in Akihabara
you're most likely here for...
SHOPPING! High! Bau bau!
Well, let's share some of FUWAMOCO's
picks with you, how about?
High! Let's go!
Bau-Bau!
First up, we have our
1st Anniversary Merch set! High!
It comes with the FUWAMOCO
Happy☆Puppy Happi,
which you can wear to rep FUWAMOCO,
your favorite twins! High!
We also have our
BAU BAU Voice Keychain,
so we can cheer you up anywhere
your paws take you! High!
And our Pero Plushie,
which you can use as a good
punching bag, of course! High!
Finally, we have our Pero glass set
that you can use to enjoy
a nice drink with your donut!
Please check them out! High!
まずは FUWAMOCO の
1周年記念グッズを紹介します！
First, we'll introduce FUWAMOCO's
1st anniversary commemorative goods!
FUWAMOCO ハッピー☆パピーはっぴを
着たら、
If you wear the
FUWAMOCO Happy☆Puppy Happi,
ラフィアンズだね！って
周りのみんながすぐわかるよ！
everyone around you will know
you're a Ruffian right away!
そして、BAU BAU ボイスキーホルダー！
Next, the BAU BAU Voice Keychain!
ポチ1つで、いつでもどこでも
FUWAMOCO の声がすぐ聞けるよ！
With one press, you can hear
FUWAMOCO's voices anytime, anywhere!
ペロのぬいぐるみは、パンチングターゲット
として使うしかない！
The Pero Plushie can only be used
as a punching target!
最後は可愛いドーナツにぴったり合う
FUWAMOCO の可愛いグラスセットです。
Finally, a cute FUWAMOCO glass set that
goes perfectly with cute donuts.
ぜひゲットしてね！
Please be sure to get them!
Next, to commemorate our
3D debut today...
...we have our brand new
FUWAMOCO Tail Keychain! High!
Now, this is the only time
you're allowed
to touch our tails however
much you want, Ruffians! High!
Please hang up these special 3D debut items from wherever you think looks best!
Yeah! 次は3Dお披露目グッズです！
Yeah! Next is the 3D debut merch!
こちらのフワモコのしっぽキーホルダーです！
It's this FuwaMoco tail keychain!
Nice! 今回だけは許してくれるよ！
Nice! I'll let it slide just this once!
このキーホルダーなら、好き放題しっぽ触れます！
With this keychain, you can touch the tail as much as you want!
Oh! 一番可愛いところに飾ってね！
Oh! Decorate it in the cutest spot!
BAU BAU!
WHOA! That was... FUWAMOCO STAGE!
Oh, so excited! But...
what did we come here for again?
Ruffians, do you remember?
Mococo-chan, tell me... I'm hungry! We're hungry!
As you know, if you come to Akiba...
...we need to get our favorite...
DONUTS!
It looks like Fuwawa forgot her coin purse...
You know, fluffy brain! BAU BAU!
Ruffians, is it okay if you treat us to some donuts this time?
We'll have it next time, okay?
Please, can you give us a donut?
お願い！ドーナツ！Oh!
Please! Donuts! Oh!
Thank you! Thank you!
I'm gonna take a bite, okay? Ready? Wait...
Am-am-am-am-am!
Wait, wait! What about Mococo?
Thank you! What about Mococo?
Am-am-am-am-am-am-am!
Where's my donut?
So good, so tender!
Me too! Can I have a donut?
My donut please! Me too!
Thank you! Thank you!
This time it's donuts! FuwaMoco power!
Okay, ready? Ah...
Am-am-am!
This tastes a little fluffy!
And mine... ah... am-am-am!
It's a bit fuzzy and pink!
Mococo-chan, I want to taste it too. Can I have a bite?
I guess we'll share a bite or two? Okay...
Only small, okay?
You heard it, okay? Here you go!
Am-am-am-am-am!
You ate it all! It's so fuzzy!
Okay, I get a bite now. Mococo-chan, just a small bite.
Not as big as my bite, okay? I'll be fair.
Okay, here you go... Ah...
Am-am-am-am-am!
BAU BAU! It was great too!
But you know, I still want my donut. I only had one!
Mococo, I would like my donut!
Donuts! Donuts! Donuts!
一個残りあった！
There was one left!
Mococo, you know, I've been looking forward to the donuts so much!
No, no, it's not fair! It has to be equal!
No! No! It's mine! It's mine!
Well, then we only have one choice!
BAU BAU! What is this?
A wrestling ring?!
This is... FUWAMOCO WRESTLING!
BAU BAU! All the Ruffians!
Oh my goodness! Hello!
BAU BAU! It's so cute!
So fuzzy, so fluffy!
Thank you for coming to cheer us on!
Mococo, I'll make sure that I beat up Mococo-chan a lot, okay?
No, I'm gonna win, okay?
I'm gonna do my best, okay?
BAU BAU!
Mococo-chan, I won't let you take that donut!
No, it's mine!
Stretch! Stretch!
Okay... let's get a bit more ready, Mococo-chan!
Take off the jackets!
BAU BAU! All ready!
Wow, wow, wow! I, the Great Pero-chino,
will be the referee for today's fight!
I guess we have a nasty referee for a nasty fight then!
But it's going to be fair because... Pero-chin!
I've been counting on that!
Mococo-chan, it's my donut, why don't you understand?
It's mine, I'll win! You had the last donut!
No!
I'm going to win this time! I never win!
I'll show you it's my turn!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
Moco-chan!
It doesn't have to be like this!
You can just give me the donut you ate!
No! It's mine!
I'm not gonna let you back-seat this, okay?!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
How does it feel now?
This is for the donut!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
Now I've got you!
No! No!
The donut is mine!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
Moco-chan!
One! Two! BAU!
I'm not just a pretty face!
I call upon the power of the Piko Piko Hammer!
Moco-chan!
I'm gonna get you!
Come back! Piko Piko Hammer!
Moco-chan!
Moco-chan! It's okay here! I'll help you out!
I got you now!
Yeah! How does that feel, Moco-chan?!
It's my donut, okay?!
I got Moco-chan! Oh!
Don't let go, Moco-chan!
Moco-chan! Don't think you can get away from me!
No! I'll win!
You're almost there, Moco-chan!
Yes! Strong puppy! You can do it!
Yeah! Just like that! Just like that!
I'll get you!
No! Moco-chan!
What are you doing? BAU! BAU BAU BAU!
Moco-chan, stop! It hurts!
How are you stay- How are you so strong, Moco-chan?!
Moco-chan is so sexy!
Piki- Piko Piko Hammer!
No! No!
I'm doing it! I'm winning!
Ha!
Moco-chan!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!
Honestly, you can't use the chair!
No!
I found it, I'm gonna use it!
Hæ! Oh!
Mococo-chan, wait!
Mococo-chan, that's a plastic toy!
You can't win against this!
Ha! This is a magical weapon, okay!
Hæ! Well let's see how good it is then, hæ!
Bau! Bau!
Mococo-chan! Bau! Bau!
Hæ! Bau! Bau! Bau!
Bau bau bau!
Bau! Bau! Bau! Bau bau bau bau bau bau bau!
Hæ! Mococo-chan...!
Bau bau bau! Bau! Bau!
Hæ! Hæ! Hæ!
Hæ! Bau! Hæ! Hæ!
Bau bau bau! Hæ! Hæ!
Mococo-chan! No! No!
Mococo-chan! No! Hæ! Hæ!
Bau bau bau! Hæ! Hæ!
Bau! Bau bau bau! Hæ! Hæ!
One! Two! Bau!
Hæ! Bau bau...!
Bau! Hæ! Hæ! Bau! Bau!
Mococo-chan, no! Hæ! Bau bau...!
Hæ! Hæ! Hæ!
Mococo-chan, no! Let go! Hæ!
Bau! Bau bau bau!
Ask her! Ask her!
What do you say, Fuwawa? Do you give up?
Hæ! Yes! Yes! Yes! Ow!
Bau! The winner is Mococo-chan! Bau! Bau! Bau!
Hæ! Hæ! Bau! Bau!
Hæ! I'm the winner! Hæ!
A place to haunt... Fuwawa, get up.
It's okay... I won...
Hæ! Take my hand.
No... It's okay...
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah... Hæ!
Bau bau!
Ha, wow! I'm the winner, right!
Uh, I guess... I'll get my donut later then, hæ!
But you know, as winner... and loser...
Hæ! Hæ! I'm not a loser! I promise!
When you lose, you get punishment!
Uh, no, no, no! The punishment, Mococo-chan,
the punishment! And no donuts? No, no, no!
Hæ! The Ruffians have a special...
...and very embarrassing one they want you to say!
No!
Hæ! It's... it's not good, hæ!
What do you mean not good? Embarrassing? Really embarrassing?
Ah, Pero is too embarrassed so go away, go away!
Do I have to?
Hæ! That's what the Ruffians want, okay!
Bau bau! Do your best!
Okay...
Ruffian... you wouldn't mind a soggy,
doggy, sweaty hug from Fuwawa, would you?
You are my little Bau-tamp after all...
Come here!
Bau! Mococo-chan see you! Bau!
I can see you!
Hæ! It's... it's too bad, hæ!
That was a tough one, hæ!
But you know the Ruffians like embarrassing stuff like that, hæ!
With you, then there's gonna be more pluses against you here, hæ!
I think so... Hæ! Bau bau bau!
Hæ! As long as it means that we can protect each other, right! Hæ!
Well, if it's okay, I feel a little bit more comfy with my jacket!
Yeah, it's a bit chilly, hæ! Okay!
Let's go get them!
Bau! Hæ!
This is good now!
Much better! Uh, wow!
You know we did a bunch of pro-wrestling here in Akihabara!
Yeah! And there's some crazy things that can happen here! Hæ!
So... Next! Let's sing another song!
Hæ! Okay! Please listen to...
Saikyou Maru-Batsu Keikaku!
子作りしましょう　ホッ！
Let's make babies! Ho!
最強○×計画
The Ultimate OX Plan
推したいも　推しておりましょう
Whether we want to or not, let's keep supporting!
一生尽くして　ゆきましょう　ホッ！
Let's devote our entire lives to it! Ho!
殿方好みの　おなごに
To become the kind of women a gentleman likes,
磨きをかけて　ゆきましょう
let's keep polishing ourselves.
ゆきましょう
Let's do it!
前進　全霊の
Moving forward with all our spirit,
気合をここに　たぎらせて
let our fighting spirit seethe right here!
有り余るほど
To the point of excess,
お命を　お守りします　ホッ！
we will protect your lives! Ho!
今宵こそは　迸る　誠意で
Tonight, with gushing sincerity,
今日も　明日も　とめどなく　ホッ！
today and tomorrow, without end! Ho!
漲る力の　遺伝子を
The genes of our surging power,
掛け合わせて
let's multiply them together!
その地上で　最強の　子孫を
On this earth, the strongest descendants,
お家のために　残しましょう　ホッ！
let's leave them for the sake of our family! Ho!
たった一つの　この身さえ
Even with just this one body of mine,
主も
and you too,
あなたさまへ
my master!
鉄は熱いうちに　惹き足しへ
Strike while the iron is hot, to attract more!
永遠愛されて　西へ　ホッ！
Being loved forever, towards the west! Ho!
まみえぬ　定めの　帳を
The veil of a destiny where we cannot meet,
互いに　越えて　ゆきましょう
let's cross it together.
ゆきましょう
Let's go!
疾風　迅雷の
With the speed of a lightning bolt,
奥義を　噛みしめて
let's savor the secret technique!
連綿と　連なる
Continuous and unbroken,
命の　営み　しましょう　ホッ！
let's carry out the work of life! Ho!
墨を足す　清き　御心に
Into your pure heart where ink is added,
あなたさまを　感じます　ホッ！
I can feel you, master! Ho!
二人の方の　愛の果て
At the end of the love between us two,
相思の果て
at the end of our mutual affection!
この地上で　最強の　思想を
On this earth, the strongest ideology,
私　この身に　宿らせて
I will let it dwell within my body.
末代の　証しと　いたしましょう
Let's make it the evidence for all generations!
主も
And you too,
御身は　安泰で
your body is safe and sound!
主も　主も
Master, master,
主も主も主も主も　ああー！
Master, master, master, master, ahh!
ホッ！　突如として　解き放つゆけば
Ho! If we suddenly release it,
主も主も主も主も　しなやかに
Master, master, master, master, flexibly!
二人の　愛が　実ります
Our love will bear fruit!
実ります　ホッ！
It will bear fruit! Ho!
この地上で　最強の　思想を
On this earth, the strongest ideology,
この世の　ために　残しましょう　ホッ！
let's leave it for the sake of the world! Ho!
たった一つの　この身さえ
Even with just this one body of mine,
主も
and you too,
あなたさまへ
my master!
主も主も　主も主も　押忍！
Master, master, master, master, OSU!
ふわわ！
Fuwawa!
もこもこ！
Mokomoko!
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Demon World Watchdog Sisters☆★
この世界に爆誕　BAU"DOLです
Exploding into this world, we are BAU-DOLs!
BAU BAU!
Wakeupしたら　君にMorning
Once we wake up, good morning to you!
Newな出会い　鼻きかせ察知して
Sensing new encounters with our noses,
Doggy Doggy Doggy
右に左に　BAU BAU BAU
To the right, to the left, BAU BAU BAU!
悩んでいても　来ちゃうFuture
Even if you're worried, the future will come.
まずは目の前の　道　ステップして
First, take a step on the path in front of you.
Happy Lucky Puppy
一緒に歩こうよ
Let's walk together!
ドーナツの　穴の中には
Inside the hole of a donut...
きっと
...there is surely...
Surely
夢が詰まってるから
Because it's filled with dreams
ふわわ
Fuwawa
もこもこ
Mokomoko
魔界乃番犬シスターズ★
Underworld Guard Dog Sisters
２匹が揃えばもう大騒ぎ
When the two of us are together, it's a huge commotion
もっと
More
迷わずに Go my way
Without hesitation, Go my way
君の絶対味方 BAU DOL です
We are the BAU DOLs, your absolute allies
BAU BAU!
ふわわ もこもこ
Fuwawa Mokomoko
FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO
ふわわ もこもこ
Fuwawa Mokomoko
FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO
BAU BAU!
ひとりじゃないよ We're together
You're not alone, We're together
Heart 繋がってる君とずっと
Our hearts are connected with you forever
Fluffy Fuzzy Yappy
一緒に歌おうよ
Let's sing together
ドーナツの穴の向こうへ
Beyond the donut hole
きっと きっと
Surely, surely
君が待っているから
Because you are waiting
ふわわ
Fuwawa
もこもこ
Mokomoko
魔界乃番犬シスターズ★
Underworld Guard Dog Sisters
２匹が揃えばもう止まらない
When the two of us are together, we can't be stopped
お耳も
Even the ears
しっぽも お触りは厳禁
and the tails, touching is strictly prohibited
スリル満点爆弾 BAU DOL です
We are the BAU DOLs, a thrill-packed bomb
BAU BAU!
Hey!! RUFFIANS!!
Kept you waiting, huh?!
Can I get a heck yeah!?
Let's shout "BAU"!!
BAU!!
Now hear the howling of my soul!!
Are you ready?!
モコちゃん！この曲は可愛く歌おうねって言ったでしょ！
Moco-chan! This song is supposed to be sung cutely, I told you!
bau bau
じゃ、Bメロから... せーの！
Then, from the B-mero... ready, set!
ドーナツリングに誓って
Swear upon the donut ring
ずっと ずっと
Forever, forever
笑顔を守るから
Because I will protect your smile
ふわわ
Fuwawa
もこもこ
Mokomoko
魔界乃番犬シスターズ★
Underworld Guard Dog Sisters
２匹が揃えばもう大騒ぎ
When the two of us are together, it's a huge commotion
もっと
More
迷わずに Go my way
Without hesitation, Go my way
君の絶対味方 BAU DOL です
We are the BAU DOLs, your absolute allies
この世界に爆誕 BAU DOL です
Explosively born into this world, we are the BAU DOLs
BAU BAU!
ふわわ
Fuwawa
もこもこ
Mokomoko
FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO
ふわわ
Fuwawa
もこもこ
Mokomoko
FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO
BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! Thank you so much!
Thank you!
That was our brand new original song, "Born to be "BAU" DOL"!
BAU BAU BAU!
What did you think?!
We hope you were BAU BAU-ing along with us and yelling...
...FUWAWA! MOCOCO! Just like that!
You know, it's such a fun and energetic song!
And the dance even makes it more fun, huh?!
So we hope that you'll dance it together with us too, okay?
Please!
But you know what...
I'm exhausted now, you know?
Donut pro-wrestling, singing and dancing...
It's been a busy day!
We had so much fun here at Akihabara, right Moco-chan?
Yeah!
Maybe it's time to go home.
Aw, okay.
You know, it's always a little bit hard to say goodbye to Akihabara...
But we'll be back soon!
For sure!
Yeah, you could never stay away from Akihabara forever, right?
So much stuff to see!
Yeah!
Okay Moco-chan, let's go home!
BAU BAU!
Now Loading
淋しい熱帯魚
Lyrics: 及川眠子 Music: 尾関昌也
Lonely Tropical Fish
Lyrics: Neko Oikawa Music: Masaya Ozeki
Stop! 欲しくって
Stop! I wanted it
髪を飾り
And decorated my hair
Non-stop! 優しい目を
Non-stop! For your kind eyes
待つはプールサイド
I wait by the poolside
ズキ ズキ せつなく
Throb, throb, painfully
震える胸
My heart trembles
まぼろしでもいい
Even if it's an illusion
会いたいのに
I want to see you
Heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You're not coming
私の想い
My feelings
ジョークにしないで
Don't make them a joke
Lonely, ゆらゆら swimming
Lonely, swaying swimming
ゆらゆら dreaming 愛が揺れる
Swaying dreaming, love wavers
Stop!
Love! 花柄の
Love! Only my floral
水着だけが
Swimsuit
Love me! 目立ちすぎて
Love me! Stands out too much
泣きたくなるの
It makes me want to cry
チリ チリ 焦げてる
Sizzle, sizzle, burning
この痛みを
This pain
冷たい水辺に
Into the cold water
そっと浮かべて
Gently let it float
Heart on wave
泳ぎだすけど
I start to swim, but
あなたの夢には
To your dreams
追いつけなくて
I can't catch up
I can't, ね こんなに
I can't, you know, even though it's this
苦しいのに
Painful
なぜ なぜ あなたじゃ
Why, why, if it's not you
なきゃだめなの
It won't do
Lonely, ゆらゆら swimming
Lonely, swaying swimming
ゆらゆら dreaming 愛が揺れる
Swaying dreaming, love wavers
Stop!
Heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You're not coming
私の想い
My feelings
ジョークにしないで
Don't make them a joke
Heart on wave
泳ぎだすけど
I start to swim, but
あなたの夢には
To your dreams
追いつけなくて
I can't catch up
Thank you! Thank you!
Oh, we're back in the forest passage! Whoa!
Just like we said, it's so beautiful at nighttime! Ah!
Oh, we really wanted to share this view together with you! Hi!
For a long time that we waited for it, right Mococo-chan?
Right! Uh!
And today, we're able to sing the songs that we really loved here for you!
Yeah!
In the place that we grew up.
Uh, it means so much to us!
But you know, we're no longer puppies, so you know...
One, two!
Yeah!
Hai! Hai! Hai!
Hi! Hi! Hi!
Actually...
...there's something, right Mococo?
There's something we wanted to tell you!
Is it okay if we go out that way?
Let's go!
こっち行こう！
Let's go this way!
行こう！
Let's go!
Abyssgard!
Right here, right under the tree of Abyssgard.
Yeah, the tree of Abyssgard.
It's a very special tree to us demon dogs,
but especially us demon guard dogs.
We'd like to sing our last song for today right here.
Right here.
And this song means so much to us...
...because it's all for you.
You know, all of it. Everything is for you.
Thank you so much always.
Well, please listen to our last song for today.
Kimi ga Tame.
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes
キミガタメ Lyrics: 須谷尚子 Music: 下川直哉
Kimi ga Tame Lyrics: Naoko Sutani Music: Naoya Shimokawa
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes
わたしは何色ですか
What color am I?
赤深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep red
渡そう 陽の光を
I'll hand over the sunlight
悲しみが溢れ
Sadness overflows
瞼 閉じました
I closed my eyelids
こぼれた滴は
The spilled droplets
心に沁みゆく
Soak into the heart
行き渡る波は
The waves that spread
弱く 舞いえます
Can dance weakly
とどけし揺りかご
The delivered cradle
眠りを誘う
Invites sleep
夢に なつかしい
Nostalgic in dreams
面影をさがす
Searching for traces
手を伸ばし 強く
Reach out your hand strongly
抱きしめたくなる
I want to hold you tight
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes
わたしは何色ですか
What color am I?
藍深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep indigo
渡そう 高き空を
I'll hand over the high sky
喜びが溢れ
Joy overflows
巡りあいました
We met each other
こぼれおつ笑みは
The smiles that spill out
別れを隠す
Hide the parting
人は いつしか
People eventually
朽ち果てるけれど
Rot away, but
唄となり
Becoming a song
語り継がれてゆくでしょう
It will be passed down, won't it
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes
わたしは何色ですか
What color am I?
緑深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep green
If you wish for the deep green
渡そうこの大地を
I'll give you this land
脆く儚げなものよ
Oh, such a fragile and fleeting thing
強く美しきものよ
Oh, such a strong and beautiful thing
あるがまま ha-
Just as you are, ha-
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes
わたしは何色ですか
What color am I?
安らぎを覚えたなら
If you feel a sense of peace
そこにわたしはいる
I'll be right there
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes
わたしは何色ですか
What color am I?
うら深き望むなら
If you wish for the inner depths
渡そうこの想いを
I'll give you these feelings
渡そうこのすべてを
I'll give you everything
Ah, thank you so much, Ruffians! Thank you!
You know, we're not the best at
expressing our feelings through words,
but you know, today is a special day.
So you know, we did our best
and we wrote some letters for you.
Is it okay?
Do you want to hear them? Do you?
Okay! Okay!
Fuwawa, I'll go first, then okay? Okay.
Dear Ruffians,
Thank you for all the fluffy headpats,
for all your warmth,
and for always being here for me
during this past year.
I never would have dreamed that I could be
standing here right now,
having already done so many
amazing things a little more than a year
from the day we first met,
but here I am!
And it's truly all thanks to you.
There have been many sunny days
and some rainy ones too,
but they've all been special
and full of meaning because
you know what?
You were there by my side.
Thank you from the bottom of my heart...
Please continue to share
that beautiful smile of yours
with me lots and lots,
and I'll make sure that nothing
can lay a paw on it. Okay?
Sincerely, your fluffy Fuwawa.
Bau bau!
Ah, next, Mococo-chan, your turn.
I guess it's my turn then, huh?
I'll do my best, huh!
Ruffians!
I can't believe we're finally here, after so long.
I'm so happy we've been able to spend today together.
To be honest, there were many hard times...
times when we doubted ourselves and were frustrated with our own limits...
but because you were here by my side with kind words and lots of headpats...
because you accepted me even when I was maybe a bit needy or being silly...
because of that, we were able to reach today!
There's still a lot of growing I have to do, but I...
hope you can watch me do my best and take even one step forward everyday.
Because you know, one step forward a day is seven steps a week!
And eventually, that will amount to something amazing.
And of course, I will always be waiting here for you, ready to protect your smile!
Nothing will ever break the pledge we made to you.
So get ready, because your smile is going to be protected, whether you like it or not!
Got it?
Sincerely, your fuzzy Mococo.
Bau bau!
Today, another huge dream of ours has come true.
Thank you so much, always.
Please let us continue to protect your smile for-ever and ever, okay?
For-ever and ever!
Bau bau!
これからもよろしくね！
We look forward to your continued support!
Bau bau!
Dearest Ruffians,
Thank you for always being by our sides!!
We had so much fun wrestling, singing and dancing for you in 3D!
We're going to protect your smile furr-ever & ever!
FUWAMOCO
FUWAMOCO 3D SHOWCASE
#FWMC3D
BAU BAU!
せーの！
One, two!
BAU BAU!
またねー！
See you!
お疲れ様でしたー！
Thank you everyone!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!