(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Every day like it's on repeat
I need a rhythmic breakdown
Oh honey, the nightlife is calling
Don't need a steady simple melody
Can you make it original?
Take me away, like it's just the two of us tonight
Do you feel the music?
Baby, meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Moving my feet to something new
I know we only got tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing
Lately I'm dancing alone
So robotic, so emotionless
But then I see you across the dance floor
So now honey, follow me
I need a rhythmic red hot melody
Something to keep me up all night
Don't look away, now it's just the two of us tonight
Do you feel the music?
Baby, meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Moving my feet to something new
I know we only got tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
胸の鼓動 熱くさせて
Make my heart beat hot
Keep on my heart beat パパパパパ
Keep on my heart beat pa-pa-pa-pa-pa
火を灯してあげる
I'll light a fire
鼓動のパパパパパり
Heartbeat pa-pa-pa-pa-pa...
熱くさせるわ
I'll make it hot
Music gets me so high tonight
You've got me shining bright like a prism
But it's okay, I don't care who's watching
So baby, meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Moving my feet to something new
Baby, meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive
Moving my feet to something new
I know we only got tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
I know we only got tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Baby, can we dance until the daylight?
Crazy
About this rhythm, making you
Hi, Kikkiriki!
Quick note that there is probably going to be
a director's cut release later on,
so please look forward to that.
That will probably have some fixes
for some scuff moments.
Now enjoy!
Ladylike / KIRA
Under the moonlight, we kiss goodbye
You walk off wearing your disguise
Never give me something and don't think twice
And I told you all the things I would do
But does it matter when you chase after
the pleasure you can't have?
Now look where you ended up
Because out of seven billion people
you won't find another me
you won find another me
If you want it all, I'll tell you now,
my love don't come for free, oh baby, baby, yeah
You've got to treat me like a lady, yeah
Because I don't need no man to save me
Boy, I'll make you crazy
So look into my eyes
and be real with me tonight, treat me like...
Treat me like a lady like
Oh your sweet talk and your flattery boy that shit don't fly
I got 20/20 vision I see through every lie
Say the same things as you sip it you're just the type of guy
That stupid girls believe it but I'm another kind oh
Should've known that you'd get what's coming to everything that you had wasn't meant for you
Got them all sick like a virus don't infect yourself this time 'cause
Out of seven billion people you won't find another me
If you want it all then tell me baby what's it gonna be oh baby baby
Yeah yeah yeah you've got to
Treat me like a lady yeah yeah yeah
I'll throw you out the way you came in 'cause I'm a little too much to face me
So look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
I am
Don't ever mess it up
'Cause all that you got is one chance to turn it around
And I've had enough
If you want to earn it then work it
Boy don't let me down
Baby baby baby
You've got to treat me like a lady yeah yeah yeah
'Cause I don't need no man to save me
Boy I'm gonna make you crazy
So look into my eyes and be real with me
Oh baby baby yeah
You've got to treat me like a lady yeah yeah yeah
I'll throw you out the way you came in 'cause I'm a little too much to face me
So look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
Treat me like a lady like
Treat me like a lady like yeah
Yeah
4BLOOD / KIRA
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
I'm alive still breathing
Stop to hide done grieving
Realized that to survive someone's got to stand and fight
And I've tried to believe in only time
Stops the bleeding I'm not waiting anymore I know what I came here for
'Cause feelings are temporary
But broken hearts keep the scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me
I'm chasing and hunting and this time I'm coming for blood
Be the last one to laugh when you run out of breath catching up
I'm a threat and a half baby you don't even know me at all
I'm alive still kicking
Break the rules rewrite the system
And my story wasn't done sharpen knife and cut the guns
Cut the cord burn the witch and you'll regret what you're missing
And I'll take it to the grave that's the price that you pay yeah
'Cause feelings are temporary
But broken hearts keep the scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me
I'm chasing and hunting and this time I'm coming for blood
Be the last one to laugh when you run out of breath catching up
I'm a threat and a half baby you don't even know me at all
Na na na na na na na na na na
Oh yeah
Hoo
'Cause feelings are temporary
But broken hearts keep the scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me
I'm chasing and hunting and this time I'm coming for blood
Lalala...
Yes! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
And well, welcome everybody, first of all, to my concert!
I hope you enjoyed the first two songs! How was it? How was it? How was it?
Thank you, thank you, thank you! I hope I already got you hyped up!
This is gonna be a really fun show! But a fun show also needs some special guests,
some people to talk to, maybe some call-ins, some games!
And don't worry, I got you covered! I have invited a very special friend
to play a very special game together with!
And my friend is none other than my 5th generation member, Nenechi!
Yaaay! 聞こえるかい？
Yaaay! Can you hear me?
ハッピーバースデー、キアラちゃん！
Happy birthday, Kiara-chan!
ねねち！
Nenechi!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あ、そうだ、お誕生日だった。そうだ、そうだ、そうだ。
That's right, it's my birthday. I almost forgot.
ね、ねねち、英語で自己紹介お願いします！
Nenechi, can you introduce yourself in English, please?
はい！
Sure!
hololive 5th Generation, Momosuzu Nene!
イェーイ！来てくれてありがとう！
Yay! Thank you for coming!
こちらこそありがとう！Thank you!
Thanks for having me! Thank you!
So... じゃ、ねねちとはね、アイドルしりとり！
So... So Nenechi and I will be playing 'Idol Shiritori'!
という私が考えた天才のゲームをやります！
It's a brilliant game that I came up with.
イェーイ！
Yay!
ね、あの、うちは、ま、hololive Englishでは、あの、トップアイドルかなと思うんだけど…
After all, if I'm the top idol in hololive English,
もちろん！
Of course!
…hololive Japanだとね、ねねちかなと思ったんだよね！
then for hololive Japan, it would be Nenechi!
あはは、ありがとう！
Gosh, thank you!
Nenechi is hololive Japan's number one idol in my heart! So I thought
that the following game would be very fitting. Um, so I thought up this game.
The rules are the following: first of all, the name is Idol Shiritori.
The normal Shiritori works the following: I say a Japanese word,
and they usually are built up in syllables. So the syllable that it ends with,
Nenechi will have to think of a new word that starts with that syllable.
And then we keep on connecting and connecting until someone makes a mistake
or says a word that already has been said. But here is the twist:
we can only use idol words, or cute or girly words, feminine words.
So anything that's cutesy and idol-y. Yeah, I think us two,
we shouldn't have any issues with that.
うちらだったら問題ないよね、アイドルしりとり！
Idol Shiritori should be a piece of cake for us, right?
できる、できるよ！I can!
We can do it!
イェーイ！
Yay!
オッケー、じゃ、じゃ、やってみるか。ねねち、準備オッケーか？
Okay, then let's give it a shot! Nenechi, you ready?
オッケー！
Ready!
いいよ、なるべく、あの、早めのペースでやりましょう！
Let's try to keep the pace up.
オッケー！よし！
Okay! All right!
じゃ、始めよう！スタート！
Here we go! Start!
スタート！
Start!
ドキドキ！
dokidoki! (exciting!)
き、きらきら！
Ki... kirakira (sparkling)
ら、ランデブー！
randebu (rendezvous)
ランデブー！？
randebu!?
ぶ、ぶ、ぶ、ぶ、ブーメラン！
bu... buumeran (boomerang)
「ん」で終わったな！
You said a word that ends in "n"!
あ、そうだ！
Oh, right!
ブッブー！
Bzzt!
アウト！ねねち、アウト！
Nenechi, you lose!
あー、しまった！
Darn it!
ちょっと待って！もう一回やりたい！もう一回やりたい！
Hang on... Gimme another chance! Come on!
Round 1, I win! One point for Takanashi Kiwawa! OK, OK, OK.
じゃ、あの、3ラウンドやりましょう！
Then let's do three rounds.
オッケー！
Okay!
OK! じゃ、次はねねちから始めよう！
Okay, you start, Nenechi.
オッケー！うーん…
Okay! All right! Hmm...
好きなタイミングでどうぞ！
Whenever you're ready, go ahead.
ねねち！
Nenechi!
え、ち、ち、チーズ！
chi... chi... chiizu (cheese)
ず、チーズフォンデュ！
zu... chiizu fondyu (cheese fondue)
あ、いいな。いいな。可愛いね、ね！
Ah, good one. Yes, very cute, no?
でゅ？でゅ？あ、難しいな。ゆで。ゆで。
dyu? Right, that's a hard one. You can use yu.
ゆ？オッケー。ゆ、ゆ、指輪！
Okay. yu... yu... yubiwa (ring)
おー、ワンダフル！
wandafuru (wonderful)
る、ルビー！
ru... rubii (ruby)
あー、び、ビーナス！
Uh... bi... biinasu (Venus)
す、す、す、す、するめ！
su... su... su... surume (dried squid)
え？あれ、するめって魚？
Isn't that a type of fish?
するめは、うん、おつまみ？
It's a type of... drinking snack?
嫌だ、可愛くない！
Okay, that is not cute!
可愛くない気がする！可愛いのが思いつかなかった！
I don't think that counts! I couldn't think of anything cute!
可愛くない！ブッブー！ブッブー！
That's not cute! Bzzt! Bzzt!
ああー！ブッブー！ブッブー！
Argh! Bzzt! Bzzt!
「す」から始まる可愛い言葉って何？逆に。
Is there something cute that starts with "su"?
ん？スクール水着！
Hm? Sukuuru mizugi! (school swimsuit)
あー、可愛いわ。
Oh, that is cute.
え、まー、もうこの時点で勝ちなんだけど、ワンモーやる？
Well, it looks like I win already, but wanna do one more?
次、3ポイント中ね。
Let's make the next round three points.
3ポイント？
Three points?
あ、オッケーオッケー。
Okay sure!
次で勝った人が3ポイントね。
Whoever wins the next round gets three points.
じゃ、次で勝ったら、あのー...
If you win the next round, then...
うん。
Uh-huh.
同点。同点。
It's a tie.
同点？オッケー、同点。
A tie? Okay, sure.
で、平和な終わり方。
So nobody loses in the end!
そうしよう、そうしよう。
Sounds good!
オッケーオッケー。じゃあ、店主から始めます。
Okay, great. Then I'll start the next round.
はい。
Okay!
せーの。
Here I go.
フラミンゴ！
Furamingo. (Flamingo)
んー... ご...
Um... go...
ゴールテープ！
Gooru teepu! (finish line ribbon)
な、な、なにそれ。
Wait, what's that?
え？
Huh?
なにそれ。
What's that?
それ英語じゃないのか。
I dunno what it is in English.
ゴデプ？
Gorepu?
ゴールテープ。
Gooru teepu.
あ、ゴールテープ！
Oh, gooru teepu!
運動会の最後のやつね！
The thing at the end of a race!
それ可愛いか？
Is that cute?
ま、可愛い可愛い、オッケーオッケーオッケー。
It is totally cute! Okay, we'll count it!
オッケー、進めよう。
It counts! Let's keep going.
ん？
Hm?
あ、じゃあ「ぷ」？
Oh, so next is "pu"?
ぷ... ぷ... ぷ...
Pu... pu... pu...
ぷ... ああ...
Pu... ahh...
プアンデリング！
Puanderingu! [sic] (Mochi donut)
プアンデリング？！
Puanderingu?!
んん... あったよね、そういうの。
Hmm... That's a thing, right?
あったよね。
Right?
ぐ... ぐ... ぐ...
Gu... gu... gu...
ぐ... むず。
Gu... that's a hard one.
グーテン・モルゲン、キアラ！
Guten Morgen, Kiara!
えええー！
What?!
グーテン・モルゲン、キアラ？
Guten Morgen, Kiara?
ら、ランドセル！ランドセル！
La... randoseru! (child's backpack)
あー、いいわね。
Ooh, good one!
ナイス、ナイス、ナイス。る... る...
Doing good, doing good! Ru...
る？
Ru?
ルッコラ！
Rukkora! (arugula)
ルッコラ？
Rukkora?
まあ、わからんけど、オッケーオッケー。
Dunno what that is, but sure!
ら... ラミィ先輩！
Ra... Lamy-senpai!
オッケーオッケー。い...
Okay, okay. I...
い、い、い、い、い、い...
I... i... i...
いぬ。
Inu. (Dog)
あー！ぬ... ぬ... ぬ...
Oh! Nu... nu... nu...
ぬ！！！
nu!!!
わからんよー、ねねちー！
I can't think of anything, Nenechi!
オッケー、分かった。負けたよ。
Okay, fine. I lost!
ということで、平和な終わり方や。
And with that, we end the game tied!
イェーイ！
Yay!
一番、一番いいのでは。
I think it's best this way.
そうだね。
Probably for the best!
Because I lost, so we decided that we both win in the end, yes.
I may have won twice and she may have won once, but in the end...
...we're O'riends, so all is good, we love each other, world is beautiful, world is peace. Yay!
オッケー、ということでねねちありがとうございました！
Okay, thanks for coming, Nenechi!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ありがとう！グッバイ！
Thank you! Goodbye!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
あ、今度はね、オレンズで二人で踊ろう。
Oh, let's get together as the O'riends sometime and dance!
そうしよう、そうしよう。
Yeah, let's!
バイバーイ！
Bye bye!
バイバイ、シーユー、ねねち！
Bye bye! See you, Nenechi!
シーユー！
See you!
さあ、レッツゴー・トゥ・ザ・ネクストソング！
So, let's go to the next song!
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
SPARKS / Takanashi Kiara
Lying down on the floor late night
And you don't know, don't know, don't know what to do
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right
If you still don't know, don't know, don't know what to do
The storm hits hard and you're losing your way
Just take a chance and dance in the rain
'Cause you've got the key, never throw it away
Don't forget, don't forget what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So go ahead and do it, do it, if you want it, let's get to it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks like the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid, trust your heart
Keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up
And never be afraid
Gonna make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Keep your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks like the flame
So don't wait
Start a fire today
Don't stop, don't stop
Just go your own way
We're never looking back, take the fast lane now
In the driver's seat, strap in, just gas up now
...we're going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed
That's how we like it, you heard what I said
Get out of your head, life is so what you make it
You're gonna be okay, yeah yeah!
So take a step and move it, move it, unless you try you won't get through it
Everybody's gonna know your name!
'Cause sparks light the flame turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
So don't be afraid trust your heart keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid!
Let go of the past tonight
Choose the future only you define
Even when the flames burn too bright
You're alive from the ashes you rise!
Here we go!
'Cause sparks...
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
So don't be afraid trust your heart keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
Gonna make it hot like a volcano, start your match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table to the beat of you and I
Sparks light the flame so don't wait add a fire today
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way, ah yeah!
Digital Girl KIRA
Hello nice to meet you, my name is perfection
I come from the net inside your personal computer
A tool for the dreamers, make you a believer
I'm so worldwide, worldwide, holy virtual diva!
But sometimes I do, don't you think of the things they told you
There must be more than this, there must be more than what you know too
I wasn't made to feel, but lately I can't help it
If there's a way out of here, I've got an idea
Bring it all down, I'll make it come around, I'll burn this whole facade to the ground
I'm sick of windows, I need something physical
Hot, love, locked in a digital world
Why not virtual issues, watch your life as it comes to shore
All right, I got it for you
How do you think I feel, none of this is real
Singing I love software, digital girl
So I woke up with a headache today, just kidding I don't feel pain
To be honest I don't even gotta sleep, and that's the difference between you and me
And I know, I know, I know, I know, everybody wants it till they gotta commit
Look into my eyes, change your mind so quick
You won't believe that I've seen it
And no day is like the other, be anything I wanna
There is no suffering words or existential crisis drama
But I feel something is inside of my heart
And it's telling me to go before I fall apart
Bring it all down, I'll make it come around, I'll burn this whole facade to the ground
I'm sick of windows, I need something physical
Hot, love, locked in a digital world
Why not virtual issues, watch your life as it comes to shore
All right, I got it for you
How do you think I feel, none of this is real
Singing I love software, digital girl
What is yours and what is mine, am I ever gonna die?
Please don't uninstall my love, please don't uninstall my love
Bring it all down, I'll make it come around, I'll burn this whole facade to the ground
I'm sick of windows, I need something physical
Hot, love, locked in a digital world
Why not virtual issues, watch your life as it comes to shore
All right, I got it for you
How do you think I feel, none of this is real
Singing I love software, digital girl
Bring it all down, I'll make it come around, I'll burn this whole facade to the ground
I'm sick of windows, I need something physical
Hot, love, locked in a digital world
Why not virtual issues, watch your life as it comes to shore
All right, I got it for you
How do you think I feel, none of this is real
Singing I love software, digital girl
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
The 美学 / 松浦 亜弥
The Bigaku / Matsuura Aya
Wow!
Yeah!
Hey hey, come on dance! Wow!
告白できないで
Not being able to confess...
へこんじゃったミッドナイト
...I was feeling down at midnight.
あいつは勝ち目の
He's a kind man...
優しい男
...who has no chance.
Hey hey, come on dance! Wow!
だらだらやってないで
Don't just sit around doing nothing.
すぐ行こうぜミッドナイト
Let's go right away, midnight.
Baby 行くのは一丁前の
Baby, you're so good at going...
もう一人の私
...my other self.
恋しているから
Because I'm in love...
切ないけど
...it's painful, but...
愛し合ってても
...even if we love each other...
暗い暗い暗い Wow!
...it's dark, dark, dark. Wow!
恋する女と
A woman in love and...
その男の美学
...that man's aesthetics.
目覚めたらそこで
When I wake up, right there...
KISS KISS KISS
恋する男と
A man in love and...
その女の魅力
...that woman's charm.
寂しい夜は
On lonely nights...
涙流してもそれもいいんだよ
...it's okay to shed tears.
Yeah!
真相皆そうだ
The truth is, everyone is like that.
結婚式の実際
The reality of a wedding ceremony.
あいつは優柔不断の
He's an indecisive...
可愛い男
...but cute man.
Hey hey, come on dance! Wow!
キラキラ見せて頂戴
Please show me some sparkle.
恋しちゃって頂戴
Please fall in love.
Baby 覚悟は半端ないの
Baby, my resolve is no joke...
もう一人の私
...my other self.
都会で夢見る
Dreaming in the city...
恋の火蓋が
...the start of love...
世の中気合で
...with fighting spirit in this world...
右肩上がり Wow!
...is on the rise. Wow!
恋する女と
A woman in love and...
その男の哲学
...that man's philosophy.
反応したらそこで
If you react, right there...
KISS KISS KISS
恋する男と
A man in love and...
その女の魔力
...that woman's magical power.
孤独な夜は
On lonely nights...
二人離れずに夢を見るんだよ
...the two of us dream without parting.
Hey come on, baby baby you don't stop ah!
都会で夢見る
Dreaming in the city...
恋の火蓋が
...the start of love...
世の中気合で
...with fighting spirit in this world...
右肩上がり Wow!
...is on the rise. Wow!
One, two, three, go!
恋する女と
A woman in love and...
その男の美学
...that man's aesthetics.
反応したらそこで
If you react, right there...
KISS KISS KISS
恋する男と
A man in love and...
その女の魔力
...that woman's magical power.
孤独な夜は
On lonely nights...
二人離れずに夢を見るんだよ
...the two of us dream without parting.
Yeah!
Hey hey, come on dance! Wow!
金曜日のおはよう / HoneyWorks feat. Gero
Kinyoubi no Ohayou / HoneyWorks feat. Gero
おはようのオーディションして
Having a "Good Morning" audition...
髪型もバッチリ OK
...and my hairstyle is perfectly OK.
金曜日は頑張らなくちゃ
I have to do my best on Friday...
だって二日会えないからね
...because I won't see you for two days.
8時0分に2両目
8:00 AM, in the second car...
お気に入りの特等席
...my favorite special seat.
隣の人
The person next to me...
ね 眠そうな君を見てる
Looking at you, who looks sleepy
それだけで満足しちゃって
Just that makes me satisfied
ダメだって頑張らなくちゃ
But I have to try my best
8時7分　開くのは
8:07, opening up
向かいのドア　息を呑む
the door opposite, I hold my breath
言い掛けてた　その言葉は
Those words I was about to say
今日も逃げた
ran away again today
きっかけシンプルでいいのに
The motivation could be simple
意気地ないな
I'm such a coward
勇気のテスト乗り越えなきゃ
I have to pass the test of courage
逃げるなって
don't run away...
「おはよう」のオーディションして
Having an audition for "Good Morning"
弱虫な自分に勝って
Beating my cowardly self
金曜日は頑張らなくちゃ
I have to try my best on Friday
だって2日会えないからね
Because I won't see you for two days
眠そうな君を見てる
I'm looking at you, looking sleepy
それだけで満足しちゃって
Just that makes me satisfied
ダメだって頑張らなくちゃ
But I have to try my best
そっと声に出してみた
I tried to say it softly
8時0分　2車両目
8:00, the second car
座られてた　いつもの席
Someone was sitting in my usual seat
ついてないな　空模様まで
Unlucky... even the weather
泣きそうです
is about to cry
8時7分　準備まだ
8:07, not ready yet
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
ドキドキが震え混じり
My heartbeat mixed with trembling
その言葉は　掻き消された
Those words were drowned out
雨宿り立ち尽くす僕に
To me standing still in the rain
「傘をどうぞ」
"Here, have an umbrella"
君は少し恥ずかしそうに
You, looking a bit embarrassed
下を向いた
looked down
「ありがとう」震えていた
"Thank you," I was trembling
練習してない言葉
Words I hadn't practiced
言えたから頑張らなくちゃ
I said it, so I have to try my best
だって2日会えないからね
Because I won't see you for two days
大好きな君を見てる
I'm looking at you, whom I love
それだけで満足しなくて
Just that isn't enough anymore
月曜日は頑張らなくちゃ
I have to try my best on Monday
そっと声に出してみた
I tried to say it softly
夢では自然に話せるのに
In my dreams I can talk naturally, but...
勇気のテスト乗り越えるから
I'll pass the test of courage
少し待ってて
so wait a little bit
「おはよう」のオーディションして
Having an audition for "Good Morning"
髪型もバッチリOK
My hairstyle is perfect too
8時7分に君を待ってる
I'm waiting for you at 8:07
だって今日は言えるからね
Because I can say it today
「おやすみ」も言いたいけれど
I want to say "Good Night" too, but...
ちょっと待って
wait a minute
大好きな言葉なんだ
It's my favorite word
だって君に会えるからね
Because I get to see you
Alright everybody! How was that?
Did you like the previous songs?
It was "The Biggest Dreamer" from Matsuura Aya...
...and "Kinyoubi no Ohayou" from HoneyWorks! Yeah!
Um, especially "The Biggest Dreamer"...
I was really excited to perform for you guys...
...because it's a Hello! Project song that probably a lot of you guys don't know.
But did you like it? Did you like it? Did you like it? It's pretty cool!
Yeah, Matsuura Aya is god.
So, next up...
...we will have MORE GUESTS! MORE GUESTS! MORE GUESTS!
Guess who's next? Who could possibly be my next guests?
What do you think, guys? Hmm? Who?
Well, so, it will be none other than...
...my beloved Tori-ken hololive members!
Subaru-senpai! Hello!
Kiara-chan! Hello!
Happy Birthday! Happy Birthday!
Thank you! Thank you!
hololive 2nd Generation Oozora Subaru
嬉しいね！ Very happy. Thank you two for coming...
I'm so happy! Very happy. Thank you two for coming...
...for flying over here like the birds you are.
hololive Indonesia Pavolia Reine
Yeah! Well, I'm already doing gestures...
...but I wonder what are we doing with you guys? What could it be?
Charades! We're playing Charades!
Yay! The typical...
...the typical game that you have to play when you're in 3D.
Well, I think we have like a synergy...
...Horo-Tori synergy!
So whatever move...
What I do, you will understand, right?
Yeah!
Of course!
Yes!
Okay, actually the words are provided by none other than Gawr Gura, who is somewhere behind the scenes.
So she will feed me the words, I will act them out and you guys will guess them.
So shall we begin?
Yeah!
Word number one!
Snail
Alright! Let's go! Go go go!
Cat?
Dog?
Animal?
Turtle! Turtle!
Oh, almost!
Rabbit?
Long!
Long snake!
Almost!
Breathes here?
Slimy, slimy!
Ah, it's slimy? Slime? Slimy?
Snail! Snail!
Yes! Whooo!
かたつむり！
Snail!
かたつむり！ Yeah! Snail! Escargot!
Snail! Yeah! Snail! Escargot!
Next word!
Tooth Brush
Brush my teeth!
Daily routine!
With toothbrush?
Yes!
Next!
Ping Pong
Catch ball!
Baseball!
Ah, I know! Ping pong! Ping pong!
Ping pong! Yes!
Nice! OMG!
KFP
Chicken!
Phoenix?
Ah, juggling?
Circus?
K-F-P! K-F-P!
KFP! KFP! KFP!
Okay, last word I think. Last word.
Subaru
Chicken dance!
Chicken dance! Everybody chicken dance!
Idol! Idol!
Idol Kiara!
Idol chicken dance!
Pretty hip! Pretty!
泳いでる！
Swimming!
Matsuri? Me?
なに？ You! You you you!
What? You! You you you!
You! You! You!
Me?
スバル先輩だよ！スバル先輩！
It's Subaru senpai! Subaru senpai!
Me? Me? It's Subaru senpai!
This is the duck! The duck dance!
The duck dance! How could you not know!
Sorry! Sorry!
Now I see it! Now I see it!
Ah, now you see!
Yeah, you shaking your hip! So you shake!
But it's okay, we still did four out of five!
Whooo! Yeah!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Turduckens best-o!
Turduckens are the best!
Yeah!
Turducken...
...best-o!
...is the best!
Thank you two very much for coming!
やめるか！
I'm off!
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
I love you!
I love you so much!
So cute!
Bye-bye!
Love you!
FEVER NIGHT
Takanashi Kiara
I'm tired of the same song
Every day
Like it's on repeat
I need a risky break down
Oh, honey the night is calling
Go mid-steady simple melody
Can you make it original?
Take me away
Like it's just the two of us
I'm ready
Do you feel the music baby?
Meet me underneath strobe light
Come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
That is the sound take over me
Intoxicated, DJ keep playing
Whoa!
Lately I'm dancing alone
So robotic
So emotionless
But then I see you across the dance floor
So now honey follow me
I need a thrilling red hot melody
Oh, something to keep me up all night
Don't look away
Now it's just the two of us
I'm ready
Do you feel the music baby?
Meet me underneath strobe light
Come alive
Moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
この鼓動の音 合わせて
Match the sound of this heartbeat
You follow my heartbeat
バッババラバッババリバッパ
Ba-ba-bara-ba-ba-bari-bappa
聴かせてあげる
I'll let you hear it
鼓動の音 合わせて
Match the sound of heartbeats
You follow my heartbeat
Crazy for your rhythm
I'm in a trance the way that you moving
You got me shining glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild
Don't care who's watching us so baby
Meet me underneath strobe light
Come alive
Moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Baby, can we dance until the daylight?
Crazy about the sound I'm making with you
Whoa!
HINOTORI
Takanashi Kiara
瞬く星のゆりかご
Twinkling star cradle
駆けた台詞を
Dialogue I ran through
繋ぎ合わせたメモリー
Memories connected together
聖なる従者が伝う
Told by a holy servant
神話のことわり
Reasoning of myth
祈りに耳を澄ませ
Listen closely to the prayer
Tell me I can hear it clearly
Tell me 声が聞こえに
Tell me, I can hear your voice
あらぶる鼓動は 傷を焦がす
My wild heartbeat burns my wounds
焔降り注ぐ空に 身を焦がして
In the sky where flames pour down, burning my body
乱れ咲く赤は ベリゲーション
The blooming red is variegation
数多重なる試練も 引き抜いてみせる
I'll overcome even the numerous trials
I will learn to keep on fighting
to the dawn
例えば先の見えない ゼロの境界
For example, the unseen boundary of zero
迷い込んだとしても
Even if I get lost
何度も繰り返される 心の終焉
The end of the heart repeated over and over
底に残った Answer
The Answer left at the bottom
Daybreak I will never give up
Daybreak 羽が朽ちても
Daybreak, even if my wings rot away
消せない強さは 時の標
The inextinguishable strength is a guide through time
灰が舞い上がる大地 身を焦がして
In the land where ashes dance, burning my body
燃ゆる夜明けの中 目を覚ます
Waking up in the burning dawn
刃交わり切り裂き 交わした契りは
Blades crossing and slashing, the vow we made
Rise and true, come to light at the break of day
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go wrong what awaits me in the dark
Could you tell me please where I need to go
Tell me I can hear it clearly
Tell me 声が聞こえに
Tell me, I can hear your voice
漲る決意は 影を払う
Overflowing determination clears the shadows
焔降り注ぐ空に 身を焦がして
In the sky where flames pour down, burning my body
乱れ咲く赤は ベリゲーション
The blooming red is variegation
数多重なる試練も 引き抜いてみせる
I'll overcome even the numerous trials
Blazing flames show me the path to luminous
And in the next plateau I promise I will find you
Yay!
How was that?
Yay! We just did the first-ever performance of "Fever Night"...
...and "HINOTORI"! Yeah! The classic "HINOTORI"!
I bet you all wanted to see this once again!
But "Fever Night" is very new! My newest single!
So I hope you're listening to it a lot. Are you? Of course!
Thank you for always streaming both of my songs. Thank you very much for the support!
So! You thought I was done with callers, huh?
No, no, no! There's more! There's more, there's more!
Hmm... aren't we missing some Myth members?
Yes, we are! Of course we are!
So please come and say hello to Gura and Cali!
hololive ID 2nd Generation Pavolia Reine
Wee-woo, wee-woo, wee-woo!
I-I-I wouldn't do...
Howdy!
Hi! Howdy! Kikiriki!
Hello! Happy Birthday Kiara!
Happy Birthday!
Thank you! It is indeed...
You are a birthday!
Well, you could say it's not my birthday, but it's my birb-day! Birb-birb-birb-day!
Ah, I get it. You made a funny word joke.
As expected of Tenchou! Looking so cute!
Thanks! Finally, finally I can show off...
...the body in 3D for a whole stream! Yeah!
It's so detailed and beautiful!
Oh, thank you! Please keep looking at it! Which part do you like the most?
My figure is very nice!
The tummy window!
Oh, the tummy window is cute! Yes! Hip-scope!
hololive EN 1st Generation
Takanashi Kiara
hololive ID 2nd Generation
Pavolia Reine
You never get to see that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can only see that in 3D.
Right, and the little wings too.
So fresh.
So cute.
Is she gonna pull out her sword?
You gonna get your sword out someday for us?
Oh, that's a good question.
Well, maybe another time, maybe,
maybe at a 3D debut stream, which this is not.
Right, right, right.
All right. Well, girls,
we are the same generation,
so one would assume that
you know a thing or two about me, right?
Yeah, of course. We've only met many times.
Yeah, especially us, yes, yes.
But also me and Gura have now
met in real life, thankfully. Yay!
Yay!
You have, hopefully, a lot of knowledge about me,
and I will test that with the Kiwawa Quiz!
Kiwawa Quiz, let's go!
I have five questions for you girls.
And if you answer at least four of the questions correctly,
then I shall take you out to dinner sometime.
Oh, cool. I was gonna ask for a prize.
Of course it's a prize. Yes, there's always a prize at KFP.
So, are you ready for the first question?
Get it on.
By the way, you can work together if you want.
Easy. Let's do it. Yeah, put the two
biggest brains in Hololive EN together.
This should be no problem.
What do you call yourselves again? The boneheads? No...
Bone Bros.
What does KFP stand for?
Okay, the Bone Bros will solve all the questions.
Boneheads and Feathers.
Nah, we got this on lock. It's just math.
Just don't ask us about math.
No, no, no, I don't even know math either, so.
First question, are you ready?
Yeah.
It's easy.
Question number one...
What does KFP stand for?
Kentucky Fried Phoenix.
Exactly! Kiara's... No, no, no, Kiara's...
Did you say Kiara or Kentucky?
No, I've never heard of that place.
I said Kiara. You guys misheard. Sorry, that's your ears' problem.
Kiara Fried Phoenix.
I said Kiara Fried Phoenix. I know KFP, I've eaten KFP before.
I should almost give you a minus point for that answer.
No, no, no, please don't take away my degree in Kiarology.
Please, I beg you.
Okay, all right. I'll give you that point.
That was easy though. It will get more difficult maybe, maybe.
Uh oh.
All right, next question, and I wrote it down...
Question number two...
Okay.
Imagine some quiz lights... quiz show lights.
What was... Okay, a new rule.
I will only allow correct answers if you had one...
if you lock in one wrong answer, that's a no-point.
All right, Gura, don't fuck this up.
Yeah, right, like... okay.
Okay, so, question number two.
What was Takanashi Kiara's second original single?
What's the name of Kiara's 2nd single?
Heart Challenger!
Yes!
Yeah!
I was gonna say that too! Let's go!
Sorry, Goombus, I'm a little bit faster than you sometimes.
Gura needs some time to shine. Gura needs to shine.
Okay, Gura, the next one's you.
I'll be faster. No, they're gonna get harder.
I'm leaving the hard ones for Gura actually, it's all part of my plan.
Smart, smart, smart. Okay, let's see.
By the way, what was Kiara's first... song, by the way? Extra point.
Hinotori.
Right, my first... sorry, third? Did you... probably acoustically misheard.
Oh, I thought you said first.
No, no. Sorry, I can't... yeah, my TH always sounds like an F.
It's okay, it's cute.
My... number three of my songs was... but that's not a question. Sparks, yes, okay.
Good, good. Sparks, light the flame!
Okay, no, that was not the third question.
The third question is coming now.
Question number three...
What's the name of the mouse/rat that I lived with in Japan?
Name of the mouse/rat Kiara lived with in Japan?
I know this. I'm gonna let Gura answer.
I feel like I've been told this before.
Oh shit.
Do you need to phone a friend?
Okay, Casper.
Sorry, Cali!
I can't help myself.
It's the easy ones, man! Actually...
And by the way, I just recently uploaded a video...
...a lore video that explains the whole story behind Casper on my channel.
So if you guys are curious, you could go watch that...
...if you want to learn more about Casper, mysterious, yes.
Casper the friendly ghost, yeah, yeah, yeah.
At first I hated him, then I loved him.
Okay, fourth question!
If you get this one right, then you already have...
...a free dinner with me!
Thank you for carrying, Calli.
No problem.
No, you got this girl, you definitely got the next one.
Dude, I don't know if I do got this.
Okay, question number four! Da-da-da-da-da, dum!
How many re-debuts...
...did Takanashi Kiara have?
How many re-debuts has Kiara had?
Now think before you yell it out loud. Re-debuts.
Wait, what counts as a re-debut?
Well, not debut, but debuts after the re-debut.
I do have a history with re-debuts. It hasn't been one in a while, but...
...there was a time where I had many reasons for many re-debuts.
Maybe you know this.
My brain wants to say two, but I don't know.
Okay girl, let's brainstorm.
All right, let's brainstorm. Do it, faster!
Yeah, ten more seconds!
Oh shit, you remember the first one when the channel got nuked?
The next one was the German one, right? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, so I think it's two.
You both think it's two?
Are you sure?
I think it's two.
Correct answer! Yay!
Go Gura! That was close!
Okay, okay, okay, well...
...I still have one more question though.
You're a winner, chicken dinner from the chicken, let's go!
I think we're four for four so far.
Yeah we are, but I guess my questions were a little bit too easy.
So for the next question, you will have to answer correctly otherwise...
Otherwise? Oh damn it.
Otherwise there will be... yeah, it will be all or nothing.
Is it all or nothing? Changing the rules on us.
Can we double down? Do we get dessert too?
Of course, of course! All right, let's do it.
Excellent, excellent, last question!
And how should we do this? Hmm...
I want your separate answers.
Huh? What happened? Wait, was changing the rules...
I want... no, I just want to see if you both get it right without hearing the other's answer first.
Okay, I'll take off my headphones. I'm out.
Okay, okay, okay, ma'am.
But wait, no, how do I give you a sign that you should come back?
Whatever, just bring it back in in 30 seconds, okay?
Okay, do like... throw up some kind of weird hand symbol.
Ah okay, I'll do this. Do a little heart, yeah.
And then I'll come back. All right, bye. I'm taking off my headphones.
Bye! Gawr Gura!
I actually have a feeling you'll get this one right.
Really? Okay.
Spell out for me without thinking too much. You have to say it quickly.
Auf wiedersehen.
Spell auf wiedersehen
Go! Auf... A-U-F. Auf...
A-U-F, wiedersehen. V-I-E-D-E-R...
...wiedersehen, S-E-N, S-E-U-N, S-E-N, auf...
...da... A-U-F. Auf is the first part.
Wiedersehen. V-I-E-D-E-R...
...S-E-N, S-E-Y. Ah! It's hard to follow!
It's hard to follow! Final answer, go!
A-U-F.
V.
I-E-D-E-R S-E-E-N.
Wrong! Boo-boom!
No! Okay Calli come back, Calli come back.
All I heard was wrong. Is it that hard of a question? Throw it at me, Kiara.
Now Calli recently had a lot of fun learning German with me, so you might...
...you might get this too.
Fuck! The German question.
Yes! All right, good luck buddy.
Spell, and you have to do it quickly, okay? No thinking.
Spell my end greeting, auf wiedersehen.
No! Stop! Don't! A-V...
...I-V... wait no! No! Shit! Damn it girl, come on!
Auf wiedersehen... uh, fuck! That's too hard of a question!
I thought this was a Kiara quiz, not a spelling bee!
Chicken! A-V, arrivederci, arrivederci, grazie!
Mama mia! Final answer! V... no! Um...
R... no wait, it's not arrivederci, it's auf wiedersehen.
A-V... I'll give you ten more seconds!
Come on, bonehead! A-V...
...R-E-R... wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong!
No!
Wrong! What the fuck!
Beep that out.
Beep that out whoever's editing this.
It's okay, on my channel it's allowed. Yeah.
Okay.
Well, you know what? I said double down,
but I'm still gonna treat you for dinner. Yay!
Yay! Thank you!
Winner winner chicken dinner from the chicken,
as in the chicken is the dinner's from the chicken...
...not the dinner is...
it doesn't mean that the dinner is um, a chicken.
That's true.
It's... it's from the chicken,
so winner winner... chicken...
Mm-hmm.
...I'll shut the fuck up now.
Thank you Kiara, happy birthday!
Thank you! I'll bring you some KFC later.
Wait, what's the answer?
Yeah, you can't just leave us hanging.
Oh, okay. It's A-U-F...
Spell it!
SPACE W-I-E-D-E-R-S-E-H-E-N!
Oh, Auf... Auf Wiedersehen!
And perfectly, since I just spelled it out,
I will say to you girls, Auf Wiedersehen! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Auf Wiedersehen!
Next time ask me to spell 'Schreckt'.
It's a lot actually more difficult.
Oh yeah.
Bye-bye! Happy Birthday!
Alright, on to the next song! Let's go!
Heart Challenger / Takanashi Kiara
Alright guys, no time for a break.
Here comes: Heart Challenger! Let's go!
ドキドキ 止まらない
My heart won't stop throbbing
もうすぐ 乙女の勇気
Very soon, a maiden's courage
ちょこっと 必要なの
Just a little bit of it will be needed
期待でパンクしたい
I want to burst with expectation
甘くて ほろ苦い
Sweet and bittersweet
切ない 君への気持ち
My painful feelings for you
Make me, made me コスチュームチェンジ
Make me, made me, costume change
お気に入りに着替えて
Changing into my favorite outfit
鼻くすぐる香りに
With a scent that tickles my nose
ハートときめいちゃう
My heart starts fluttering
Let's start! つくるよ
Let's start! I'm going to make it
ラブ込めて とびきりのチョコレート
With all my love, an extraordinary chocolate
燃えそうで ギュッと握ったら
If I grip it tight, feeling like it's burning
未完成の合図
A sign of being incomplete
カラフルな恋の味
The taste of a colorful love
溶けちゃう前に受け取って Please
Please take it before it melts
鳴り響く鐘の音
The sound of the ringing bells
校舎の窓辺で 二人
The two of us by the school window
ねえ 早く言わなくちゃ
Hey, I have to tell you quickly
照れちゃうけど「好きです」
It's embarrassing, but "I like you"
この思い 君まで届け
Let these feelings reach you
With me!
チクタク 進んでく
Tick-tock, time keeps ticking away
気持ちは 止められないの
I can't stop my feelings
ちょこっと 勇気出して
I'll muster up a little courage
贈るよ ラブレター
And give you my love letter
大好き なのに
Even though I love you so much
何十回 書いても
No matter how many times I write it
伝えきれない Make me, make me
I can't fully express it, make me, make me
意気地なしなんて 空の彼方飛んでいけ
My cowardice, fly away beyond the sky
何度もチェックして
I check it over and over again
君に会う時は
When I meet you
100倍増しで
I want to be a hundred times
可愛くなりたいの 鏡の前 にらめっこ
more cute, staring at myself in the mirror
Let's go!
いつもと違うスウィートさで
With a sweetness different from usual
ハートを虜にしたい
I want to captivate your heart
ぐるぐる 変えてみても
Even if I try changing it again and again
髪型が 決まらない
I can't decide on a hairstyle
告白のシミュレーション
Simulation of a confession
ドキドキ 騒ぎ出しちゃう
My heart starts making a commotion
月より願い込めて
I'll put my wish on the moon
一発勝負 明日は
A one-shot chance, tomorrow
絶対に晴れますように
I hope it will definitely be sunny
And I'm here to tell you that I love you through and through
There's no one else in this world that I would trade for you
萌え袖　ぶきゅっと握りしめたら
Holding my moe-sleeves tight
ミッション開始の合図
The signal to start the mission
カラフルな恋の味
A colorful taste of love
溶けちゃう前に受け取ってプリーズ
Please take it before it melts
鳴り響く鐘の音
The sound of ringing bells
校舎の窓辺で二人
Two people by the school building window
ねえ早く言わなくちゃ
Hey, I have to say it soon
照れちゃうけど好きですプリーズ
It's embarrassing, but I like you, please
この想い君まで届け
May these feelings reach you
With me! Hop-step!
Uu~ Hey!
Say! Wow!
Yay!
Yay! That was Heart Challenger!
Whoo! Remember a while ago
at Dokomi where I had backup dancers
who were doing the dancing for me?
And now I learned it myself and performed it myself!
Yay! That was fun, hope you enjoyed that.
Well, you know, if you look at the time,
you might think, oh, it's gonna be over soon.
And yeah, there is one more song,
but before that, let me say a few words to you guys.
Eisho. Yeah, we are getting close to the end,
and I wanted to do something like this
for a long time, as you probably know.
And I wanted to show off my dance moves for so long,
which is, it's one of my, I guess, prominent skills...
...and it has been my dream since the start
to show it off, to get into this 3D body,
finally be free to do whatever I want.
Yeah, and the day has finally come.
I hope you guys enjoyed it so far.
Yeah. I want to definitely say a big thanks
to Ame and Ina and Gura for helping so much
with the recording and the setup.
You know, Ame basically built a whole studio
for me to record this in,
and I really, really, really appreciate that.
Without her, it wouldn't have been possible at all.
And also big thanks to Kanauru for putting
together all of this into a proper concert
and even creating this beautiful stage here.
Wow! Look, isn't it nice?
Yeah, thank you so much.
In the future, I really hope that
I can do more like this more often
and get more members to join me in 3D
if possible, to dance together.
Yeah, especially you know, Myth and Holotori
and EN's... with all of them I want to dance
and yeah, have fun together.
And I think we're getting there slowly but surely.
By the way, if you missed it,
the birthday merchandise was announced
in the previous stream before this one,
the countdown stream.
And it's linked in the description,
so please go check it out if you're interested.
And yeah, last but not least,
I want to thank KFP!
You know how much I appreciate your support
and you believing in me and trusting in me
means the world to me.
So thank you for giving me the strength
in a very, very, very stressful period
leading up to this day.
Yeah, I think it was worth it.
So thank you for waiting for me
and I will continue working hard
to give back to you as much as I can.
Please continue supporting me and watch me grow
into a bigger, bigger, bigger, bigger Phoenix!
Yeah. Now, there is one more person I want to thank,
but I will do that with a song.
So please listen to the last song.
Douzo.
Black★Rock Shooter / supercell
ブラック★ロックシューター　何処へ行ったの？
Black★Rock Shooter, where did you go?
聞こえますか？
Can you hear me?
OK! Papa!
見てるかー！？
Are you watching!?
あとどれだけ叫べばいいんだろう
How much more should I shout?
あとどれだけ泣けばいいんだろう
How much more should I cry?
もうやめて　わたしはもう走れない
Please stop, I can't run anymore
知らない　いつか夢見た世界が
I didn't know. The world I once dreamed of
閉じる　真っ暗で灯りもない
is closing. Pitch black, with no light.
崩れかけたこの道で
On this road that's starting to crumble,
あるはずもないあの時の希望が
I felt like I saw the hope from back then
見えた気がした
that wasn't even supposed to be there.
どうして
Why?
Black Out Shutter　懐かしい記憶
Black Out Shutter, nostalgic memories.
ただ楽しかったあの頃を
Those days that were just fun.
Black Out Shutter　でも動けないよ
Black Out Shutter, but I can't move.
闇を駆ける星に願いを
A wish to the stars racing through the darkness.
もう一度だけ走るから
I'll run just one more time.
怖くて震える声で呟く
Whispering with a voice trembling in fear.
私の名前を呼んで
Call my name.
夜明けを抱く空　境界線までの
The sky embracing the dawn, to the boundary line
距離あと一歩届かない
the distance is one step out of reach.
堪えた涙が溢れそうなの
The tears I've held back are about to overflow.
今下を向かないで止まってしまう
Don't look down now, or you'll come to a halt.
未来を生きていたいんだ　分かったの
I want to live for the future. I realized that.
思い出して強く強く信じるの
Remember, and believe strongly, strongly.
さあ　Black Out Shutter　優しい匂い
Now, Black Out Shutter, a gentle scent.
光を空を飲み込む言葉
Words that swallow the light, the sky.
Black Out Shutter　動いてこの足
Black Out Shutter, move, these feet of mine.
世界を超えて
Go beyond the world.
最初から分かっていた
I knew it from the start.
ここにいることを
That I would be right here.
私の中の全ての勇気が
All the courage inside of me
火を灯してもう逃げないよ
lights a fire. I won't run away anymore.
Black Out Shutter　一人じゃないよ
Black Out Shutter, I'm not alone.
声をあげて泣いたって構わない
It's okay to raise your voice and cry.
Black Out Shutter　見ていてくれる？
Black Out Shutter, will you watch over me?
今から始まるの
It's all starting now.
私の物語
My story.
忘れそうになったらこの歌を
If you're about to forget, this song...
歌うの
...I will sing.
Special Thanks to all of KFP, Huke papa, Jenma, best Manager, Kanauru, Gojo, KIRA, Astrophysics
Myth Members: Nenechi, Reine, Subaru, Fauna
AMELIA WATSON thank you for making this possible, you are so selfless and supportive you made my dream come true and my hard work and suffering worth it! thank you for all that you do for us. Love, Kiara
Thank You for Watching / Please Subscribe!
Thank You for Watching
Please Subscribe!
Follow me on Twitter for more fun and updates!
@takanashikiara
Thank You for Watching
Please Subscribe!
Follow me on Twitter for more fun and updates!
@takanashikiara
Thank You for Watching
Please Subscribe!
Follow me on Twitter for more fun and updates!
@takanashikiara
Thank You for Watching
Please Subscribe!