(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ALERT
REPORT TO HEADQUARTERS IMMEDIATELY
SPECIAL MISSION ASSIGNED.
MISSION
UNDERCOVER INVESTIGATION
TARGET
FIVE ESCAPED FUGITIVES
TEAM:
JUSTICE
The Scarlet Queen ELIZABETH Rose Bloodflame
The Chaser GIGI Murin
The Artist with the God Eyes RAORA Panthera
The Ancient Automaton CECILIA Immergreen
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Taking you up or below, taking you up or be-
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Taking you up or, b-b-below we go
They think they wanted her
They wanna get, get down
We take them down, down, down
Within the borderline
Wide and no surprise
You ain't gonna win but you can try
Pistol in control
In-between my line
Listen, listen
Run and hide and scream out, already locked you up
Looking so always fine
Tell me context, won't hear anything
Aiming right on your heart
Throwing the keys out, shut down now
Love it, the forbidden
You'll never be forgiven
No one to just forget
We got it
Behind our eyes
The color you die
Stepping on the edge
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Difficult you, got nowhere to go
Show you something real, my level
Now you never know up or below
Run in the light, oh my dear
What's wrong, what's right
Dressing in a fantasy, wanna be the seize
Show that you will never make it out
I follow now
It's do it, do it
Locking you in now
ABOVE BELOW
Sing your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop, it's just us, dance!
Get down, get down, get down
Lookin' like that
Runnin' like that
Get down, get down, down, down
Pick me up, up, up, let's go
Going up from the below
Told you already know
Don't stop, they know it
Run in the light of my brio
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night of my brio
Come take a bite
Never ending ending star
You'll never focus up, you'll never focus up
No one to just forget
We rise up! We rise up! Yes!
Standing on the edge of the unpredictable,
beautiful, physical, you got nowhere to go
Show you something real, high level,
no you'll never know, out of control
The law you should know
Just a little unpredictable, beautiful,
just look at it, look at it baby, go
Next level, almost criminal, out of control
It goes below
ABOVE BELOW
Yay!
Hello everyone!
Hello!
Hi everyone!
At last, we are in 3D and we've gotten
to perform "Above Below"!
Yay! My god!
I feel like our performance was awesome!
Awesome!
If you really liked the show from it, remember we
have a hashtag, #Justice3D. Post it on social
media and we'd love to see that!
Huzzah!
Now that we're finally in 3D guys... you want to
do an introduction but full energy with a pose?
Full pose?
Full poses?
We have some full poses.
Alright, okay.
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen,
the harbinger of order, leader of Justice,
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Lovely to see you, to see you lovely!
So cool! So cool!
Hey everyone! Look at her go! Look at her go!
Be careful! It's party time!
From hololive Justice... JUSTICE FISTER!
On official hololive English channel.
It really is.
Hi everyone, it's me, Ancient Automata from
hololive Justice, Cecilia Immergreen!
In 3D!
Ciao everyone, this is Raora Panthera from
hololive English -Justice-.
Justice!
Big cat means BIG TROUBLE!
And everyone, take a look at where we are now!
Ta-da!
The Justice hideout!
It's finally done!
I guess I gotta take off my skirt.
What?!
Whoa, what are you doing?
Look away! Look away!
Oh my god, Cecilia!
It's not naked!
This is some gotcha, very, very normal pants.
Alright, that was wrong. That felt wrong.
Well maybe you shouldn't have done it.
Can we sit down though?
Yeah, let's sit down.
HR? HR?
Calling HR!
Please! Oh, please!
What's happening now?
They're fighting again.
Stop fighting! Get on your places and shut up!
So guys, what's the plan for today?
How about we...
Ice cream!
How about we get some ice cream? Liz, ice cream?
Well, it's our 3D debut,
so I think it'd be nice to do something fun of course.
Ice cream! Ice cream is fun!
Maybe we should play a game? Maybe a game?
And then whoever wins gets ice cream! Treat!
ATTEEEEEEEENTION!
Up and at 'em, maggots! It's time to get to work!
No slacking off while I, Sergeant Smokey, am busting my scales off for justice!
Heeey, long time no see you! How are you doing? Oh, it's nice to see you!
"Heeey"?! GET IT TOGETHER!!!
Now line up and stand at attention, peabrains!!
Ah... okay, calm down, Dees.
Let's just do as Smokey says. It's his first big appearance. He seems pretty fired up.
Okay, I will do it for you, Liz.
All right, let's go! Huddle up! All together!
All for Liz! Let's go!
Alright, Smokey!
Enough talking! Do I make myself clear?!
SIR! YES! SIR!
I can't hear you!
Show me your war face!
(War face screaming)
Headquarters tells me you've been getting sloppy, so I'm here to set things straight!
I've got a few brutal challenges lined up to whip your sorry hides into shape!
Whoa! Oh! What the freak?
Has that always been there?
Whoa! Let's go look! Let's go look!
Oh, the freak! Whoa! Wow!
Alright, read the rules!
Here we are. Let's see what it says.
1st Trial: Think Fast, Move Faster!
Rule 1: This is a training exercise for both your brain and your body.
Rule 2: Use the giant keyboard to quickly input the answer to the question shown on the projector.
Rule 3: The trial consists of 10 questions per person. If you're stuck, you can skip and answer it later.
Rule 4: Correct answers with more letters will get higher points.
Rule 5: Let's see who can rack up the most points in 90 seconds!
No whining! Cecilia, you go first! Get in there!
Okay, I'll go first.
Oh, it's okay. Get out of my way! Cecilia, it's up to you!
Watch this guys, don't worry. I got this.
Are you really ready? How ready are you?
I gotta write this email! Let's just start!
Three! Two! One! Go!
Question 1: What is Gigi's last name?
M-U-R-I-N! Enter! Murin!
Wow! Nice! Murin!
Question 2: One of Raora's goals as an idol is to publish an OOO BOOK!
Skip! Oh my god! What?
Question 3: Elizabeth is from GREAT OOOOOOOO!
E-X-A-R-D-I-A! You have one minute!
Whoa! Exardia! Nice one!
Question 4: Who wrote the play "Romeo and Juliet"? Answer with the full name.
Full name! Five points! You can do it! Full name!
W-I-L-L-I-A-M... Go Cecilia!
S-H-A-K-E-S... Just do it! This is too difficult!
William Shakespeare! Almost there! P-E-A-R...
E to finish! Enter!
Whoa! William Shakespeare! That was a difficult one!
Question 5: How many hearts does a fish typically have?
O-N-E! Enter!
One! You have five seconds left! Quick!
Question 6: Granny Smith and Fuji are types of which fruit?
A-P-P-L-E! Yes!
Nice try! Nice try!
Okay, that's the only exercise I'm going to do for today.
How many points did I get? Let me calculate in my brain.
Nine points! Whoa! That's a pretty good score to start on. A good start!
Next challenger, MOVE IT!
I guess I'll tap in now.
Come on, let her show you who's the...
I'll tap in!
Oh, did you just ignore me?
Oh, you're gonna leave her hanging?
Yeah! You can do it!
All right. I, the leader of Justice, shall go next.
Let's get started. Liz, are you ready?
Yes, count me in!
Three! Two! One! Go!
One of Raora's nicknames is BIG OOO!
You know, you know, you know...
C-A-T! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Enter!
Finally someone who knows my questions!
Cecilia likes to drink OOO!
T-E-A!
He likes to drink coffee!
No, no coffee!
Gigi's fans are called OOOOOOOOO! / Gigiのファンネームは何？
Gigi's fans are called OOOOOOOOO! / What are Gigi's fans called?
Gigi's fans are called OOOOOOOOO!
Wait, why is it so long?
G-R-E...
Uh oh.
M...
That's a long... Oh, that's a long word.
L-I-N-G-S! Ah!
Ah, trick question! It's Gremurins! That's the full name!
Oui, oui!
Yeah, 'cause... painted the Mona Lisa! Next question!
OOOOOOOO OOOOOO painted the Mona Lisa! / モナリザを描いたのは誰？
OOOOOOOO OOOOOO painted the Mona Lisa! / Who painted the Mona Lisa?
What do you call a group of lions? / ライオンの群れを何と呼びますか？
What do you call a group of lions? / What do you call a group of lions?
What do you call a group of lions?
A group of...
P... I don't know.
Lion... group of lions... I...
D-E! Huh? Enter! Go, go, go!
Next! Which country is famous for inventing pizza?
Which country is famous for inventing pizza? / ピザ発祥の地として有名な国は？
Which country is famous for inventing pizza? / Which country is famous for inventing pizza?
Which country is famous for inventing pizza? Uh...
I know, I know! Romans! Romans! Empire!
I'm coming! Italy!
I... This is not... Why are the fingers so wide?
I'll just... Enter! What? What?
I think it's the Roman Empire. Roman Empire.
What is the fear of confined spaces called? / 狭い空間への恐怖症は何と呼ばれますか？
What is the fear of confined spaces called? / What is the fear of confined spaces called?
What is the fear of confined spaces called?
What is that? Does it exist?
It's called... Scared!
Next! I don't have enough time anyway, there we go!
Ooh! Good job!
Of course. Yes, of course.
How do you feel? How do you feel?
How do you feel? Are you tired? Tired?
What's my score? What's my score, guys?
I think your score's being calculated.
Okay. What's my score? In my brain! In my brain of brains!
Yes! Good! Go, Gigi! Go, go!
I'm gonna carry the one... It was four!
You got four points!
What the brick?! Ah!
Ah! No way, don't be bad!
That was really good. It's the automaton energy, energy's fine.
No, it's because they tricked you with Gremurins!
Cat girl! Let me see your typing paws!
Okay, I go, I go!
You got this, Raora! Go, Raora!
Let's get started. Okay.
Three! Two! One! Go!
What color is the flame on Elizabeth's chest? / エリザベスの胸の炎は何色？
What color is the flame on Elizabeth's chest? / What color is the flame on Elizabeth's chest?
What color is the flame on Elizabeth's chest?
Don't look! Don't look! Don't look!
Don't look at her! You! You shy!
You! You!
You!
Wait, no, it's E... E...
Enter! You! You!
Yay! Next question!
What is the name of Gigi's mascot? / Gigiのマスコットの名前は？
What is the name of Gigi's mascot? / What is the name of Gigi's mascot?
What is the name of Gigi's mascot?
Wait, again? Oh no!
Gigi's mascot! Hey! Mascot!
Stop! It's P... Oh, don't stop there!
That's it? Enter!
Yay! Okay!
What is Cecilia's last name? / Ceciliaのラストネームは？
What is Cecilia's last name? / What is Cecilia's last name?
What is Cecilia's last name?
I... M... M... E...
Go, go, go!
E... O... She pronounced it in Italian!
Okay. E... Don't be mean!
E... R... What's a QWERTY keyboard? Wait!
Wait, Raora! The second one!
Okay, go, go, go! Enter!
Yay! Okay, okay.
OOOOOOO OOOOOOOO is known as the 'father of modern observational astronomy'. / 「現代観測天文学の父」と呼ばれるのは誰？
OOOOOOO OOOOOOOO is known as the 'father of modern observational astronomy'. / Who is known as the 'father of modern observational astronomy'?
Too many words! Skip, skip, skip!
How many legs do insects have? / 昆虫は何本の足を持っていますか？
How many legs do insects have? / How many legs do insects have?
How many legs do insects have?
Skip!
What kind of reptile is a Komodo dragon? / コモドドラゴンはどんな種類の動物ですか？
What kind of reptile is a Komodo dragon? / What kind of reptile is a Komodo dragon?
What kind of reptile is a Komodo dragon?
Skip! I don't know anything! This is what's...
Is it a lizard?
What is the name of the layer of gases surrounding the Earth? / 地球を取り囲む気体の層は何と呼ばれる？
What is the name of the layer of gases surrounding the Earth? / What is the name of the layer of gases surrounding the Earth?
What is the name of the layer of gases surrounding the Earth?
Skip, skip, skip, skip! They're too long, she doesn't want to spell them!
What is the highest female vocal range called? / 女性で最も高い声の音域は？
What is the highest female vocal range called? / What is the highest female vocal range called?
What is the highest female vocal range called?
Ooh ooh! You got this one! The one Cecilia did!
I know!
I don't know anything! Good job! You did so well!
I'm sorry!
Gigi, score!
Okay. Calculating, calculating...
Ten, right? Is it ten, right? Twenty? Twenty?
It was four!
Why are you sad?
Why are you sad? You tied with me! I got a really good...
Why are you so silent? I got a really good score!
Don't you think Liz did really well? Yeah, don't you think I did well?
I think there is a miscalculation here.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Okay, okay. Next one, next one.
Okay. Oh, yes, I guess it is me. Okay.
What if they ask really hard questions?
I'm scared.
You should be scared. I'm scared of really hard questions.
You've been doing great.
Okay, are you ready, Gigi? I'm ready!
Okay, let's get started. Three! Two! One! Start!
Which flower best represents Elizabeth? / エリザベスを花に例えると？
Which flower best represents Elizabeth? / Which flower best represents Elizabeth?
Which flower best represents Elizabeth?
Skip! Whoa!
Cecilia's signature greeting is 'Spin to OOO!' / Ceciliaの挨拶といえば 'Spin to OOO!'
Cecilia's signature greeting is 'Spin to OOO!' / Cecilia's signature greeting is 'Spin to OOO!'
Cecilia's signature greeting is 'Spin to OOO!'
Skip! What? Oh wait, wait, wait! Keep it!
Uh, no, it's got it.
W!
I!
N, Enter!
WIN! Enter! Yes!
C!
H!
A!
T-T!
I!
N-O! I! Enter!
Ahhh! Okay! Come on!
I!
S! A!
A! C!
N! E!
W! T!
O! N!
Enter!
Give it up! Okay, okay, okay.
This feels way shorter than William Shakespeare.
Skip!
Skip! Only one point!
What the... Oh, you got this, you got this big one!
Skip! I don't care.
Think about it!
Think, Gigi, oh no!
Come on! Come on!
Is it gas or air?
Oxygen!
O-X-Y...
...G-E-N! Enter!
Okay, okay. Isaac Newton versus William Shakespeare...
...and they gave the same amount of points?
That's not... I think that's super unfair.
Smokey's doing Smokey's...
Yeah, I think it's unfair to play a game where we need to read.
That's not... Well, anyways, do you want to know the winner? Do you want to know your score?
What's my score?
I want to know, CC! What is it?
What is it? It's 10 points!
Good job, Gigi! This is why you are a member of Justice!
Smokey: Hmph... Looks like you maggots still need some serious training...
Alright, time for the second trial, you knuckleheads.
I got some special training gear for you!
Gear?
Alright.
Alright. I was just chilling.
Don't hit me! Don't hit me!
Abuse!
What is this?
Ah, yes, we are going to have a duel.
Gigi! Rules!!
Rules! Rule 1 of Dizzy Combat...
...split into 2 groups!
And then one member on each team is blindfolded.
And we have to spin five times. To win.
Oh, man, you're good at this, CC.
And after you spin five times...
...you will face off against each other in an epic sword battle!
To the death? Oh, my...
While being blindfolded! To the death? To the death!
To the death! Me? Me?
To the death! To the death!
And the remaining teammate can guide the blindfolded player...
...using only their voice to help them locate the target.
It's like a co-op game.
It's like a co-op game. Okay, okay.
First, before you pick a team, the points for each target:
Head... 5 points.
Head, okay, okay.
Each arm... 2 points. Each knee, 2 points each.
Okay, that makes sense. Got it.
Elizabeth! Gigi! Time for you dirtbags to beat the snot out of each other!
Ah, yes! Huzzah! Alright, Gigi, let's put on our blindfold.
For... alright.
Do it! Blindfold, blindfold!
Okay, thank you.
Hey, hey, hey, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Okay, you ready? Alright, okay, ready.
Believe in yourself, believe in yourself.
I believe in myself! Okay, no way, I'm gonna guide you.
I'll guide you, yeah, okay, okay. And be careful.
I choose you, Gigi-mon! When do we spin?
When do we spin? We spin?
You can do it, you are the queen, you are the leader! Ready?
Grab... ready? Set?
Spin to win! Okay, one!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Okay, basta, okay, okay. That's it, that's it.
Right in front of you, a little bit more!
Okay, well you have to walk like six steps.
I have the power of anime on my side!
No, that's me, wait, wait, wait.
Don't worry, left, left, turn to the left, turn to the left!
Attack, attack, attack!
There she is, there she is! Yes, you got her!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Roll away, roll away!
Yes, Liz, go! She's on the ground, she's on the ground!
On the ground! Get up! On your left, on your left, on your left!
Okay, on your left! Okay, left!
Okay, okay!
Ready?
Go, go, go, go, go!
Got that! Gracias! Yeah!
You almost got it!
What am I hitting?!
That's one!
That's two!
That's three!
You're doing really well!
What am I hitting?!
You're doing really well! Ow!
What am I hitting anymore?!
Okay, okay!
You did it!
I don't... I don't know...
You did it! You did it! You did it! Yeah!
I think you absolutely destroyed her!
Well well well, looks like you numbnuts managed to scrape up 15 points in round 1.
15 points!
Yeah!
15 points! Definitely a win!
I'm a winner!
So good! Yeah!
15 points! Hey! Amazing!
Yeah, 15 points!
Yeah, 15, not 50!
Oh, alright! 15 points!
Alright, alright, gear up for Round 2!
Okay, okay, okay!
Give us...
...the blue!
Blue!
Wait, is Raora-chi cheating?
What?! No, I'm not!
Turn around, turn around!
Alright, let's put your...
...blindfolds on.
Okay, help me please!
Alright!
Oh, alright, let's put your...
...blindfolds on.
Keep looking at me. Perfect.
Is it on?
Yes, it's on! Okay!
Put your blindfold on.
Okay, can you see anything?
What? Okay, watch this!
I'm ready!
There you go.
Okay, I'm ready!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Took you buttercups long enough. Now square up!
Alright!
We're over here!
Gigi, count us down!
I'm gonna do a countdown!
Three!
Two!
One!
Spin!
And two!
Faster!
Two!
Three!
Faster, faster! And four!
Faster!
And five!
Okay!
Go! Left Raora, left!
Left, left! To your left!
Left! Forward!
Straight! She's bent over, she's bent over!
Stop! On the ground!
Stop! Over that way!
Behind! Okay! Up!
Behind you! Behind you!
Where did she go?! Cecilia! Where did she go?!
Don't follow me!
Raora, straight ahead! Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Going right! Straight! Straight!
Keep going straight! Straight! Keep going straight!
Get her! Get her!
Low, low, low! Go low! Go low!
Go lower! Go low!
Go low! Go low!
Forward! Forward! Stay where you are!
Okay, now, now, now, now!
Get her! Get her!
Oh gosh! Who am I hitting?! Who's hitting?!
I can't understand what you're saying!
Forward! Straight! Straight!
Go! Go! Okay, okay, okay!
Wait, wait! Don't hit me!
Raora, forward! Get her!
Raora, get her! Get her!
Oh, oh my gosh!
That was... that was something!
That was...
Gigi, score!
15 points!
Alright! That was very dizzy, I'm dizzy, I'm dizzy!
I am... I am scared of the darkness!
It is okay. You're still my pretty kitty. You did good, my pretty kitty. Mrow!
Your third trial is behind that door. What's the password?!
Oh really? Let's say it!
All together! All together!
Okay!
Alright!
8-8-0-0-8!
Open!
Fancy! It's very fancy!
Whoa!
Wow! So cool!
So cool! Yes!
So cool! Yeah!
Let's go, everyone! Huzzah!
At attention, you dogs! It's time for your third trial!
Uh oh.
What... what... what?
Oh no, no, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait a second. No one said anything about a life-threat challenge!
Okay, so number one!
Balance the blocks while stacking them according to the color order on the instructions!
There are 5 levels, and you earn the same number of points as the level you clear!
But watch out! The higher the level, the tougher the challenge!
If you mess up the placement, the bomb explodes! It's game over!
So yeah, you lose. Game over.
Whoa!
Alright, who's ready to get SMOKED?
Well, Gigi, do you want to go first?
Die?
I will take the first bomb!
You ready to die?
I will die for Justice! For Justice!
Speed Block: Tick-Tock Takedown! 爆発回避！スピードブロック
Speed Block: Tick-Tock Takedown!
Yeah! Justice for Justice!
Gigi! Justice for Justice!
Let's go, Gigi!
Gigi, you're amazing, look at you!
You got 10 seconds to survive levels 1 and 2, then 30 seconds for levels 3 through 5.
Oh, she's gonna sacrifice for us.
That's so incredible.
10 seconds. Can you count?
That's nine more than one.
You've got this, Gigi! You've got this!
We can count to ten for you, okay?
Ten times one, guys.
Can you, can you count to ten?
You at home, can you count?
One, two...
No, no, not yet! It's not time!
Okay, okay, calm down, let's start.
Gigi, ready?
I'm ready!
Okay, Gigi, go!
Three, two, one, go!
Level 1
Oh, look at... it's blue and you... it's red...
Raora thought she was purple!
I am the purple!
Okay, okay, okay!
Okay, easy, easy.
Ah, good job! Good job!
Level 2
Okay, yellow, blue, green, go!
Oh, oh, oh, look at her go, all that gear!
No way, it's impossible! Four seconds, four seconds!
Oh no! Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh!
They're so far away from each other! What? But we always believed in you!
Level 3
Go Gigi, go Gigi! Go Gigi!
Red! Hey, this one you will have to do like a thingy at the end.
Yellow, okay, okay, okay.
Purple, okay, okay, okay.
She's doing it!
White! Wow!
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!
Oh now pose! Oh! Wait!
Hey, that's pretty good!
Oh! For ten seconds! You gotta keep it!
Keep it! Keep it!
Six, five, four, three, two, one!
Wow! Good job Gigi! That was really good! Beautiful!
Well, good job, good job!
Level 4
Oh, that's a difficult one.
Wait, you put purple on... why'd the ghost do that?
You're doing great, you're doing great.
This is not shape accuracy! Look at her doing it!
That's my Gigi. It's really good.
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
One-one was a race horse, two-two was one too, one-one won one race, two-two won one too.
Oh! She did it! Good job Gigi! Nice one Gigi!
Level 5
Wait, what? Holy moly!
Why'd they put this one so far?
20 seconds is a long time.
You can do it! You can make it!
Can I? What is this?
The... oh, she's doing it, she's doing it.
Oh, she's doing really well! Go Gigi, go!
10 seconds! One more color!
Wait, blue? Okay.
Nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one...
7 x 7 - 7 x 1 x 2 = ?
Wait! Four...
Oh my god! Gigi! Are you okay?
Gigi! Gigi! Are you okay, Gigi?
Yeah, she died for Justice! Gigi no! Gigi!
Gigi? Gigi, are you okay? Gigi?
Don't worry, she's just being mean to you. It's okay. You're gonna be fine.
Wah! Stop! Oh my god! Stop!
What happened to you? Unfair! That's unfair!
How do you do math in two seconds? That's unfair! Quick math! Quick math!
Hey, you did amazing though. You did so well.
Justice for Justice! It's okay, you did... Gigi? Gigi, what are you doing?
Smells like a barbecue in here. You got 10 points!
Ten?! I didn't even count that high! Ten!
Ten times one, that's ten. Wow, that's... Can you? Okay.
Oh, who's next? Someone else is going to get blowed up, right?
That's enough, chatterboxes! You're up, Raora.
Raora! Okay, okay.
I don't want to become a burn mess like Gigi! What? Whatever!
She's clean again! Yeah!
She licked herself clean! Oh, look at Gigi still licking. Look at that.
You're back! So proud of you Gigi. I'm ready to defuse the bomb.
You got this! We believe in you! You got this, Raora! Yay! Hahaha!
First, Level 1! Okay, in three, two, one, go!
Level 1
Light blue, easy, easy. Yellow, purple, got this.
Tada! Ah, good job! Good job!
Okay, easy.
Level 2
Whoa! Whoa, that's a lot of colors.
This is a big one! Gosh! White, yellow, purple...
Oh, oh, blue! Green! Red! Almost there, green!
Yay! Good job Raora!
I knew Smokey was nice. Of course he is.
Level 3
All the colors! Whoa! Purple...
Okay, put it on top, put it on top.
You have a lot of time, don't worry.
Raora, you have a lot of time.
Got this, she got this! She got this, she got this!
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!!
If you had to do a full on...
Way too many for my leg!
You just do the pose.
You can do whatever pose you want!
What? What? What?
Okay!
I was trying to make her do those poses, huh?
Yeah, was it you? Yeah, very cute.
Oh, I'm in the way, I'm in the way.
And time we can huddle.
No! Wrong color.
Wait, that's the wrong color. Wrong color.
Oh, she got this, she got this!
She got this, she got this!
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck,
if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
Pink. We don't need pink
when we're catching criminals.
Oh yeah, that's so many colors.
Okay, that's a lot of color.
Yellow, yellow, black, blue.
You're almost there! Almost did it!
No, dark blue. Wait, dark blue.
5 x 7 + 2 x 3 = ?
35 plus 6 is 41!
Whoa! She got that so quick!
I'm so good at math.
Whoa! My math question was so much shorter.
Big stamina means big brain!
She did it! Ice cream for everyone!
Pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat-pat...
Raora scored 15 points. Not bad for a blockhead.
15! Whoo! 15 points!
Good job, Ra-ba.
Thanks. Yatta! Yatta!
Who's ready to get lit up next?
Okay, I'm all fired up, I'm ready!
Stop fighting, okay!
Okay, okay! You know what, shut up!
I have to huddle down, please.
Three, two, one, GO!
Wait, it's a traffic cone.
Go, Cece, go! Go, go, go!
Whoa, she's so fast!
It's like a candy.
That's hard to balance, it's hard to balance.
Go, Cece, go! Okay, purple.
Candy corn. That's too many.
That's okay. Purple, yellow.
White! You got it! Okay!
Oh, that looks so yummy.
Yeah, this looks like a grave.
Green, yellow, red. Nice blue...
I can't... I'm colorblind!
Cece! You got this! Go!
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!!
Oh, what's your pose?
Pose on the left or the right?
Oh, I'm so relaxed.
Namaste.
Ten seconds! Now breathe in.
Hold it, hold it, hold it!
And now breathe in.
Whoo! Whoo!
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
Red, pink, red, almost,
yellow, I mean, black...
Whoa, you're bringing over every single color!
This strategy, this strategy. Balance, balance.
The big black bug bit the big black bear,
but the big black bear bit the big black bug back. YEAH!
You're stuttering! Big... Go, go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
That was really fast! Go, Cece, go!
She's doing it! White, white, blue...
You win now!
Whoa! It's crumbling down.
Okay, okay, okay, she did it.
Oh, that's black. Oh my god.
Oh my god, it's so over. Oh no!
Colors! I'm colorblind!
I'm colorblind! I'm colorblind!
Whoa! Whoa! Cece!
Wait, you can't see me, right?
I love zombies. Cece!
Did you look... Did you look?
Open your eyes! You've got to face your fear!
Nice and smokey... 10 points!
I got ten! Whoo!
Can you count to ten?
How many fingers am I holding up?
At least four. At least. Twelve!
Cool! Queen!
Lead of Justice, lead of Justice.
Okay, on this chance. Ha!
Justice! Justice!
Show you what I'm made of!
Asazzz!
All right, all right.
Fast. Okay.
I didn't get to the... All right.
We're gonna make it even sooner.
Oh, these blocks are quite far away. Um...
All right, let's let us put them.
I'm ready! Ha! Bring it on! Bring it on!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Yes!
Are you ready, Liz? We're gonna count down for you, okay?
I'm ready!
All right. Level 1.
Yeah. 3... 2... 1... Go!
Ooh, that's easy! Come on, come on! You got this!
Okay, she got it, she got it. She got it.
Oh, the black one... That's so far away.
She got it, she got it, she got it! Woo! All right! Yeah!
Aha! Level 2!
Ooh! Uh-oh.
Okay, okay. No, no, that one's good!
Fast! The blue's! Ahhh!
No, that one's there, that one's there. Oh! Yay!
All right! Yes! Ah! Oh-ho-ho! Yeah!
Level 3! Ooh!
Oh, that... That's a pyramid! That pyramid scream!
You got this!
I'll tell you and then you sell it... Or she's almost got it.
Wait, wait, where? Go! Red! Where's red?
There! There! There! She got it, she got it!
Wait! What are we doing? What are we doing? Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay! Now pose to disarm!
Oh! Yeah!
This pose does not seem fair!
Yeah, this pose... Any cool pose.
Ooh! Ah! Show us your coolest pose.
Oh wow, we get yoga and they just get to do whatever they want.
Yoga? They get photoshoot.
Oh gosh! Why are they so far away? Yeah!
Got it! Okay, she got it, she got it.
Nice, pink! Got it! Oh, she's got it!
Go fast! That's our queen! That's our queen!
Level 4. All right!
Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear.
Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair.
Fuzzy Wuzzy wasn't fuzzy, was he?
Was he?
Whoa! Yay! I'm glad you won, we...!
Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear.
Fuzzy Wuzzy... I can't remember the rest.
Boots and cats and boots and cats
And boots and cats and boots and cats...
Fuzzy Wuzzy, he was a bear, didn't see him anywhere.
Yeah, I'm the Queen of Justice and... uh, what rhymes with Justice?
That's Just! You know what rhymes with Justice? Think about it.
Just... ice. Out of here! Yeah, just ice.
All right! Okay, okay, okay, okay. Difficult.
Ah! This light one!
And then I need the pink one and the blue one...
Wait, no, I don't need this blue one! Get out of here!
Purple! Light blue!
Go, you got it, you got it!
I need this one! I need this one! And I need purple!
No! No! Everything's falling apart!
No! No, it's not falling apart!
No, you can do it, you can still do it!
Did I get it?
No! Get it on! I missed it! No!
Oh! No! Ahhh!
What the freak?
No! Get out of here, get out of here. That's fine.
I mean, yeah, that's fine. Well, whatever.
It's... I got to Level 5.
Kick them, kick them!
Get out your anger! Kick them!
I didn't want to do math anyway. It's fine.
I didn't want to do math anyway, it's fine, it's fine. No.
I got some math for you... 10 points!
Really? 10 points! Yeah!
Woo! Asazzz!
I think that was pretty good, I think that was pretty good.
Simmer down, buttercups! You still got the final trial!
Quizzes and tests? We don't want to do math anymore!
We just want to relax, Smokey.
Oh, I'm getting tired.
Ice cream, ice cream. Let's go. I want ice cream now. Bye!
Wait, what the freak?
Hey! Hey! Hey! I'm the only one still burnt up.
Hey, can I go... can I go shower real quick before the next... next game?
Uh... Hello?
Hello?
Taking you up a load, taking you orby...
Ha ha!
All right, I'm all showered up.
I don't smell like a cheeky chicken... well, burnt cheeky chicken anymore.
Oh, maybe they're hiding. Hehe.
All right, I know a way to bring them out.
Justice... Just... Like... That!
Justice! Justice!
You were hiding this whole time!
Oh goodness. Hello, pretty kitties!
It's time for the final trial, twerps!
Cecilia, rules!
Okay! Yes sir.
The final trial is...
Hammer of Justice! Whack-a-Gnome.
Gnome? Whack-a-gnome.
Okay, here are the rules.
Number one. Defeat the evil gnomes emerging from the wall...
...by striking them with a giant hammer!
Number two. As we've all learned...
...not all gnomes are bad!
Some are friendly, some are nice.
So be careful not to hit the good ones and only hit the bad ones!
And then, if you smash the bad gnomes, you get three points.
And if you hit the good gnomes, you get minus three points.
Okay so we're supposed to hit the bad ones. Right, okay. I'll just know.
Be careful to aim carefully. And then at the end...
How many points can you score in thirty seconds?
They come out of the holes and then you have to hit them.
There's good gnomes and bad gnomes. Are you a bad gnome? I just can't tell.
Here's the bad dude you gotta feed to the worms!
Whoa! Sunglasses inside?
Sunglasses means they're bad ones.
And this is the good one. No friendly fire!
Oh, that's a good one. Okay. So red hat, no sunglasses, good.
Not to be gnomed. That's a good one. Not the sunglasses!
Don't hit this one. Okay, okay, okay.
Alright, put those muscles to work, big cat.
I got this one guys, I got you, I got you.
Oh, come on, pretty kitty, you can't weigh that much.
It's gonna escalate to get you far. Come on, you can do it!
Believe in me who believes in thee!
Let my voice be your strength, pretty kitty! Use your God eyes! You've got this!
I can do it! Raargh!
Ready to roll?
I am ready.
I have the power of justice and cute girls.
I can do it! You got this!
Alright, it's time to Whack-a-Gnome! Are you ready? Yes, I'm ready!
Three! Two! One! Go!
Kill the gnome! Kill the gnome!
Why is there a cucumber?!
Why is there a cucumber? What is the cucumber?!
Oh geez... What was that? That was not a gnome!
Ew. It was a weird green gnome, huh? Disgusting.
Oopsie daisy... I forgot to mention hitting cucumbers give you 5 points per hit.
What?! I feel like you should have said that earlier!
You got so many points then, probably. I hit it a bunch of times!
Total scores will be tallied at the end of the game. Which one of you meatheads is next!? Move out!
Who's next? Who's next? Who's next? Liz, I think it's your turn now.
Oh, well, okay then. Let me just take off my jacket.
Alright. Flame on! Let's go!
Alright, let me go get the hammer over here.
Time to earn your title, "leader"!
Alright, are you ready Liz? I am ready.
Okay. Countdown!
Three, two, one, go!
I feel bad about hitting those gnomes. My grandad has gnomes in his garden.
You did amazing! Destroy them all. No, they're usually quite nice.
Sympathy ain't gonna help you catch Advent! Gigi! Show no mercy.
Okay, Gigi, are you ready? Okay.
Are you ready for this...? Kill all of the gnomes.
Come over here and get the hammer. I left it... I'm gonna do it. There we go.
Man, she was heavy.
She's built for this.
She does this every day.
Oh, uh, I mean it's, you know, not as heavy as Thor's, so...
You can do this! Go!
Come on Gigi! Come on!
Alright, just lift with your legs. Lift with your legs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Let's go! Use your claws! Use your legs!
Well done, well done.
Oh my god, you're stronger than this.
Alright Gigi, good luck! Break a leg, or break a gnome in this case.
Alright, here we go. Three, two, one, start!
Whoa! Oh! No!
Gigi, Gigi, you're doing it wrong! Uh, Gigi...
Gigi, I don't think that's how it works.
Oh no, that's the wrong color! Gigi!
Just the- Just the purple ones! Take out the- The purple ones! Purple one! Just the purple one!
Oh well, she got the cucumber.
Oh, yeah, maybe that evens out.
Eh? Eh? Oh, what? What? Is it talking to her?
I know what I must do. I know what I must do.
Gigi? What are you doing? Why are you looking at me like this?
Gigi? No! Gigi! No, no, no, no, no! Hey, hey, hey! Gigi! No, no, no, no! What are you doing? No, no, no!
Hey! Someone help!
Why can't I hit her?
No! She's so good!
I should learn that. That seems like a good dodge move.
Ew!
Hey, what's wrong with the cucumber?
Disgusting! You must teach me that move sometime.
I will do that. Hey, when it jumps like that, it's- I don't know what happened.
I just lost consciousness.
That cucumber has consciousness. That was really impressive.
Thanks.
Button those lips! Cecilia! Get in there!
Okay, I'm ready!
Avenge me.
Oh wait, I need the hammer.
Let's cheer for Ceci, okay?
Okay, here we go! It's time to whack a gnome! All right! Three, two, one, go!
You know what, Smokey? You know what you are doing to us the entire time? Yeah, you're trying to make us play games.
But I'm not gonna play your games! I'm not gonna hammer up your gnomes! Because I do not discriminate! Bring it all on!
You know what? I don't discriminate! Cucumber! He's on a period! He's on a period!
Oh, he's on a period?
Die! Got it! You got it!
Go, go, go, go!
Sorry, sorry.
I've had enough. I've had enough, Smokey! You're pitting us against each other, but we will not play your games any longer!
We'll happily play your games. No, no it's just- it's just a joke, you know. How funny, you know.
We have humor too, not just strength. But uh... are you okay?
Goin' AWOL, huh? 0 points, you slug!
Oh, I don't want any more! You make us so sport the entire time! I'm sick of this!
Enough of you!
It's okay.
I rock you. It's okay.
Why do you keep bullying us, Smokey?
Silence somehow! Can we escalate this?
Wait, we need to stop this! Stop! Hey, stop, stop, stop, stop!
She hit me!
I'm sorry Smokey! We'll make sure that this is not gonna happen again!
We're sorry! We're sorry! We're sorry! We're sorry!
I'm sorry! Don't work the highest score! Please!
Just tell us! Tell us, Smokey! Come on! Come on, end this pain!
After four trials, one of you clowns came out on top...
The winner is... Raora Panthera! You win, cupcake!
Yay! This is great! I'm a pretty kitty!
Good job! Good job! Good job! Yay!
Good kitty! Good kitty! You're such a good cat!
Zip it! It's time for our winner to make her little announcement.
A sweet little announcement.
We'll be performing the new song right now!
Right now? Yay! A song!
Justice, are you ready?
Yay!
It's gonna be so nice. We've been practicing our singing and dancing really, really hard to perform for everyone today.
So make sure to watch our very first live performance!
Ready!
Yay! Whoo!
RENEGADE
Lyrics: monii / Music: Gimgigam, monii / Arrangement: Gimgigam
Paint the picture and fall before my justice,
final warning you know my rage is limitless,
on the advent of a new genesis
I'm infamous, yeah I get a little villainous.
Look into my eyes, I'll seek you out
reveal the true from lies that you just can't hide.
Flying at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
what do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by your chains, desiring to do it my way
this hurricane of a devastating force is coming
out of the maze, feel my voltage rising and igniting
fire, snuff it out.
Walking the line
on the edge of becoming what I never thought I'd be,
better, this stand is gonna take 'em all out,
renegade.
Walking the line
fell so far into poison and I'm seeing me anew,
gotcha, locked and I'm loaded, take 'em all out,
renegade.
Just, just, just like that, I don't care at all,
up so deep though I can't quit, never gonna stop
cause I don't have a limit.
My moral compass is out of focus,
renegade, I'll make it a little wicked.
The light goes out! Ha!
The light goes out! Ow!
The light goes out!
Make 'em fall down, make your last wish, make 'em make 'em fall down then they crack.
Renegade, I'll make 'em...
Fall by fall, and through the waters flooding,
never blinking, some of the sea go light up the way,
spinning move in the fallout, standing in the ashes,
far from you, snuff it out.
Walking the line
on the edge of becoming what I never thought I'd be,
better, this stand is gonna take 'em all out,
renegade.
Walking the line
fell so far into poison and I'm seeing me anew,
gotcha, locked and I'm loaded, take 'em all out,
renegade.
Just, just, just like that, I don't care at all,
up so deep though I can't quit, never gonna stop
cause I don't have a limit.
My moral compass is out of focus,
renegade, I'll make it a little wicked.
The light goes out! Ha!
The light goes out! Ow!
The light goes out! Yeah!
The light goes out! Ha!
The light goes out!
Paint the picture and fall before my justice,
final warning you know my rage is limitless,
on the advent of a new genesis
I'm infamous, yeah I get a little villainous.
The light goes out!
Yay!
Awesome! Whoo! Yay!
Everyone, mina! What did you think of our performance? Huh?
Yeah! Make sure to stream Renegade!
Let's get us to number one! Yeah!
And also guys, be sure to remember, share your thoughts,
screenshots and favorite moments from today's training
and live performance with the hashtag #Justice3D!
(Alarm sounds) Huh? What? No!
I hate this noise! It's an alarm! Oh no!
Wait, is it an emergency? I need to take a look.
Oh yes, you're right. You're right Raora.
All right, everyone come over. Let's take a look.
What is...?
Huh? Is that FuwaMoco? Advent?
They're dancing and singing! Oh!
Aw, they look so cute! They look so adorable!
No, no, no, they look alright. They look alright.
Oh look, look! They're waving at us!
Yay! Hi! We're on stage!
Oh! Ha! Ha!
What do you think? If we go to the stage,
can we catch them?
Mococo! Mococo!
We want to go to the arena!
All you punks think about is standin' on stage!
Go, get out of my face! And make sure you catch Advent!
We'll give them a taste of their own medicine! Right, guys?
Let's go!
Justice! Just like that!
Justice! Capturing them!
Head of us! Go go go go go! Get out of here!
Ahead of us! Go go go go go! Get out of here!
Huzzah!
Where are they?
I've been here for five hours now.
I've been here for five hours! Huzzah!
Six hours maybe!
We're here!
You're so fast!
You're so quick!
I thought you were here, I had to take a shower, you know.
Oh, Cecilia!
Huzzah! Cucumber Tatsumi!
Well, where are they? They're gone!
I got here on time!
Maybe because you guys are too slow!
What? You see them?
No.
Aha! I see how it is. Well, you know...
Silly.
Maybe we should perform the song we all worked so hard practicing.
Oh! That sounds like a good idea! Right! Okay!
Alright, let's get in positions, everyone!
In positions! Okay, okay, okay!
One, two, three, four, let's go!
手を挙げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, Clap your hands, to the other side of the sea
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so that it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody Clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, so that it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す僕たちの未来
Our future where the light shines
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
All light Justice はじめようか Diving
Alright Justice, shall we start diving?
待っても意味ない Timing
There's no point in waiting for the timing
あの魚みたいに Swimming swimming
Just like those fish, swimming swimming
引き寄せる Rising
Drawing it closer, rising
まだ見えない Oh maybe
Can't see it yet, oh maybe
その先には何があるの？
What is beyond that?
まだ早いよ Tapping
It's still too early, tapping
追いつくまで Shaking
Until I catch up, shaking
でもストレートに Thinking thinking
But straightforwardly, thinking thinking
顔色見て Changing
Watching the expression, changing
飛び出すのさ Stepping
Jumping out, stepping
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ My dream
I'll grab it, my sparkling dream
叶う日まで Story
Until the day it comes true, story
繋ぐからさあ、君に
I'll connect it, come on, to you
ずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to keep watching
手を挙げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, Clap your hands, to the other side of the sea
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so that it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody Clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, so that it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す僕たちの未来
Our future where the light shines
今日はいらない Breaky
Don't need a break today
リセット、イコール、再ブレイキング
Reset, equals, re-breaking
何時でもいいでしょ？四六時中
Any time is fine, right? 24/7
君は何を Feeling?
What are you feeling?
解き放って Sparkling
Set it free, sparkling
暗闇に火を灯せ いざ!
Light a fire in the darkness, now!
The beam 光らせて Stage
Make the beam shine on the stage
作るからさあ、君に
I'll create it, come on, for you
もっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to watch more
手を挙げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, Clap your hands, to the other side of the sea
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so that it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody Clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, so that it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
重なる Wave 世界を揺らせ
Overlapping waves, shake the world
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, do it!
終わりがあることくらい 既に I know
I already know that there is an end
でもまだまだ泳ぎ足りないの
But I still haven't swum enough
Give me crazy
まどろみに
In the slumber
君、混ざり合う 全て塗り替える Boom
You, mixing together, repainting everything Boom
手を挙げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, Clap your hands, to the other side of the sea
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so that it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に
Come on, together
Everybody Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody Clap your hands, to the other side of the sky
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, so that it resonates
...いますように
...I hope.
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光差す
Where the light shines
僕たちの未来
Upon our future
Breaking Dimensions
Lyrics: Steph Music: Carlos Okabe, Masaki Tomiyama
Arrangement: Masaki Tomiyama
Just, sis, just like that
Just, sis, get, get the!
Look at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
Capture the moment that we're clamoring for
An infinite future's right out the door
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just algorithm, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far
Always striving, thriving, higher
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
Because through it all we just keep moving
Now everybody sing
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with good intention
Break conventions, run right through
We're smashing barriers left and right
Soar past the other ways, stay in flight
So get together let's reunite
Reach out, reach out the future's bright
Even though together for it feels like eternity
The times are changing but we're ready for infinity
As far as I think I could go, far with me combined
So look at the horizon and then look beyond
We'll marvel at the sky and the strength of our bond
We're making a vow to the smiling stars
A powerful moment that's all of ours
The seasons change but we keep shining
Now everybody sing
Keep it going!
We're making our way to the next dimension
A million flows in every direction
We'll give every mile our full attention
Breaking tension, breaking through
With endless energy, strong attire
A perfect harmony, reach even higher
So clap along with me, time to rise
The future's bright before our eyes
A new dimension of freedom that we've found
Yeah, we've made it
We're breaking out of the monochrome bound
We're unlimited
We're gonna spring to life and break the chains
Turn up the hype, can't be contained
We're shaking up the status quo
No time to stop, we're good to go
The whole wide world is listening
So everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we've believed in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question, we'll break through
For deep aspiring to excel
It's awe-inspiring, going well
So light the fire and let's rebel
The future's bright as we can tell
Breaking Dimensions
Yeah!
And that's amazing job today!
You’ve conquered all the trials and performed at full force!
Yeah!
And what’s more, for the 3D!
Justice! Just, sis! Just like that!
Just, sis! Get, get the!
Yeah!
But we’re not done yet! We have not one, but two big announcements! Yeah!
First up, drumroll please...
Introducing the official Justice 3D Showcase Celebration merch!
Alright everyone, get into your merch positions!
Oh, merch positions, right!
Okay! First we have Sergeant Smokey’s design multi-case!
There it is! Here!
It’s a multi-case!
And if you also want to be Sergeant Smokey and boss us around...
Sergeant Smokey
Multi Case
And then this is for you.
A handy item to store your favorite goodies.
On the left side, you can keep button badges and keychains.
The right side fits small acrylic stands or postcards.
Yay!
There's also a hook on the back to attach even more keychains.
And we'd be so happy if you show off our merch at events, please.
Thank you so much!
Yay! Yay!
Alright, Raora, your turn. Next.
My turn? Hmm.
Alright everyone, next star, next one is...
...the large-size 3D acrylic stand!
Life-size! Whoo! Life-size, baby!
I don't even know if I'm life-size.
Justice's life-size! I was like whoa.
I don't even know if after I repeated it and I was like, "Wait, life-size?"
Big card means big acrylic!
Oh yeah! Big acrylic! Life-size!
In fact, Justice is coming to life as 3D acrylic stands.
Everyone loves acrylic stands, right?
Yeah, I love them. I love them.
So whether you have a room dedicated to acrylic stands...
...or just starting your collection...
...you are going to need all of Justice, okay?
Get them all!
All of them! All of them! Oh!
Goon! Next one!
Oh, it's me! Okay.
And as we all mentioned during our 3D showcases,
we each have our own merch too. Oh-la-la!
Alright then, I will start.
This right here is the paper knife and acrylic stand.
It's a lovely set inspired by the design of my sword, Thorn.
Yay!
This paper knife can actually be displayed by resting it on the acrylic stand.
It's so cool! You all, you all get your own Thorn!
No, baby Thorn! So cute!
Oh gosh, I can't, I can't!
Oh, it's so cool! Gigi, you go, you go, you go!
And now, a hand-in cushion for Graham!
Do you remember seeing it? Sadly, there is no ojisan...
...to show you how soft and fluffy it is, but it is very fluffy...
...and it's made from a very squishy material...
...and you'll never want to stop squeezing it!
You'll never want to stop squeezing it! I'm gonna squeeze it!
It's so cute! And it's Graham!
Cece!
Check this out! It's Otomo pouch and socks set!
And do you want the socks? Monday, Tuesday, every day of the week,
seven pairs of socks! And then you have your little pouch,
the little Otomo pouch to put in your stuff. Yeah,
oh it's really cute, you can put anything in it of course, not only socks,
but yeah, I really like it. It's little Otomo
and it reminds me of the Otomo pouch I made once. I like it a lot! Yay!
You could put your toes in the Otomo socks!
It's my turn! Ah, and this is Raora's pencil case and keychain set!
It's me wearing a Chattino costume! And I'll be so happy if you fill it...
...so cute! You like it? Yay!
I'll be so happy if you fill it with lots of stationery and use it at school
or in the office or really anywhere you want! And the keychain can be attached
to the pencil case, so you clip it to your bag or anything you like!
Super cute! Yay!
Raora Chattino!
Everything is really cute. I'm super excited to see you guys with it.
I'm very excited to see all of Justice's merch! And if you want to know,
when can we purchase them? Well, they will all be available to purchase
right after this stream! So make sure to get them ASAP! ASAP!
And that's our merch announcement. Yeah!
That was the first one, and...
And as Cece just mentioned, there is one more announcement.
And you all know Justice will be performing live for the very first time at hololive English 3rd Concert!
Whoo!
It'll be taking place at the Radio City Music Hall in New York
on August 23rd and 24th PDT.
And right after this stream, we'll be redirecting you into the music video for All For One!
What? Music video!
Justice also is in there, and of course, and maybe,
maybe you'll see us doing some stuff. Who knows, you'll have to wait!
We'll be moving and grooving, maybe!
So make sure to stay tuned, it's gonna be very, very soon!
It's getting a little sad...
...but it's almost time to say goodbye.
But before we go, let's each share our thoughts
and thank all our fans for their support.
Gigi, you go first.
Me? Me? Okay!
Grems, thank you so much for supporting us all this time!
And can you believe it's been a little over a year now?
And so many more years with Just Chat, Justice, and Grems! Yay!
Gosh! Hello!
Ah, thank you so much!
Gosh, Rosarians, give me a mighty huzzah!
We did it! Oh my gosh!
Thank you so much for joining all of us
on our adventure here at Holo!
I can't... I can't believe it. Oh my gosh, we're 3D now!
And we're gonna be in a concert, and oh, everything's happening!
Like, all our dreams are coming true, and it's all thanks to you guys!
Thank you so, so much!
Onwards and upwards! Huzzah!
Thank you very much, thank you so much everyone, thank you Just Chat!
Thank you all, thank you everyone, thank you Justice, of course!
It's been a lot of fun. We worked very hard, and I'm so excited...
...and happy that you all got to see it finally!
And we're also really excited to be in the ER3 concert!
So yeah, thank you from the bottom of our heart for supporting us thus far!
Please keep supporting us for much, much longer! Thank you!
Hello, ciao-tora, ciao-tora, ciao-tora, Justice!
Thank you so much for supporting Justice for a whole year...
...and many more to come! Yeah!
This... this has been a dream come true for me, being in 3D, dancing with you guys!
So much fun, so I really, really appreciate it!
Thank you so much from the bottom of my heart!
Big Chat-mees, big Justice!
Big Justice! Big Justice!
Once again, thank you all for watching our very first 3D collab stream today!
Please keep supporting Justice!
Justice! Just like that!
Justice! Get-get-get!
Bye-bye everyone! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Ciao ciao!
Ciao ciao! Bye-bye!
Make sure to eat nums, hydrate, and all that jazz!
3D COLLAB