(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
I'm Gigi Murin.
I used to be 14 years old in 8th grade, but now I'm not!
I'm a bit clumsy, crazy and silly, and I may not look it, but actually, I'm a member of Hololive English Justice!
That's true.
...call myself the Fister because I fister people with my big big power glyph, and the folks don't really like that I call myself the Fister...
TWO GREMS AND A SHOEBOX
...literally called the Fister, cause I fist people, you know? You know what I mean?
Today's the day of a very important justice meeting, but I accidentally overslept!
So I have to hurry up and...
...make sure to look both ways before crossing the road, and...
Go! Ah!
GIGI GOES BINTED!
Ah! Ah! Ouch!
Who was that? That was so weird. Wow.
Where am I?
Beautiful 2D fantasy world, I'm so efficient at shipping in my horse car, shipping even bit more than Justice...
I was just hit by a car and it would be really cool... Whoa! What the—
A horse? That's not a truck!
That's dangerous! I could have died!
But whew, that grem sure knows how to drive.
GREMLIN JU—
Ah!
Ah... Ah... My body hurts.
I feel like I got run over by something...
...but I don't know what.
Oh! Is that a statue of a grem?
Looks cool!
Wait a second... I know this!
I've been isekai'd!
What the freak? Gigi, you're here too?
Justice Cardboard.
Huh? Gigi, what's going on?
Where are we?
(Ouch!)
What are you guys doing? Why are you cardboard?
Why does Cece look so sad?
You f***ing c***! How dare you do this to me!
You b****! This is your fault somehow! I don't know how you did this...
...you absolute d***! Oh, you look terrible!
Well, let's go investigate around here!
Let's go.
Okay.
I'm on my way! Wait guys! Wait for me! We can have an adventure together!
We have adventure together and it'll be so fun and and...
Wait! Wait! What's going—
Horses!
Two of them!
Goodbye, leaving heartbreak of the past...
...behind. There's no more tears...
Looking back,
it's time
Moving down our own path
Ever voyaging forward
to make this journey last
Never before in a boundless night
Like a promise found riding the wind
Where a mist begins spiraling outward and up
An inspiring tale begins
We who dare defy changing of times
Us who follow unreachable dreams
Know it's here and right now that we're drawn to somehow
Deep inside a will to live that we'll leave
Echoes of dreams aching
Wandering near and far
Touching lives just like ours
Blinding fires
Till life wastes away
One day
I'll recall these nights
Our relentless odyssey
Pressing onward
We never surrender
To the skies
We can rise again
Again...
If anything else hits me, I don't think I'll survive much longer.
I really need to be more careful.
Thank goodness I'm still alive.
The winds whispered of your coming...
and now, here you are.
Who are you?!
I am the greatest wizard in all of Grem Kingdom.
Wizard Oji-chan.
Wizard Oji-chan?
Are you a wizard or Oji-chan?
Do you have a name?
What should I call you?
So many of Grem's warriors have fallen, one by one,
while we waited for your arrival...
The wait was worth it!!!
You are far more powerful than I ever imagined a hero could be!
He's not responding to me. He's probably an NPC.
It's like this is a game? Like a game?
NPC?!
NPC!? あ！え！？ NPC！？
NPC!? Ah! Eh!? NPC!?
少々お待ちください！
Please wait a moment!
I am the noble wizard,
Oji-chan!
Oh, I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I didn't know you could talk!
You're the key.
Without you, your friend and this world are lost...
What? Lost? What are you talking about?
Gigi,
the world is waiting...
He knows my name?
That's me.
I'm the hero.
I'm gonna save the world from... from being cardboard.
ハッザー！
HAZAH!
Ah! What did you do to me?
It hurts! It hurts!
おかしい...
Strange...
Oh, what are you doing? Why... what...?
ハッザー！
HAZAH!
Wow, I'm so cute and soft and fluffy now. Friends with you. Purchase next time they're in stock.
もうちょっと... ごめん。
Just a bit more... Sorry.
もう一回やらせて。今度ちゃんとやるから。
Let me try one more time. I'll do it right this time.
I don't understand.
オッケー、オッケー。
OK, OK.
ハッザー！
HAZAH!
行くぞ、ジジ！
Here we go, Gigi!
I'm ready!
ジジ！
Gigi!
行こう！
Let's go!
Body!
ハッザー！
HAZAH!
Oh wait.
I think... I think I can move now!
This is...
Hands!
You did it!
You've done it!
Oh my God! Look how cute I am!
Aw! I've always been cute, but now it's even cute...
...now everyone can see how cute I am!
Look at that fat tail!
I can do everything!
I can't do that.
Watch this, guys!
You've never seen this before.
Okay, okay... whee!
Whee!
I can do everything!
Two in a row? Just kidding.
I have a world to save!
Look at that, everyone loves me!
Gigi Murin!
Oh, I'm so dizzy.
Oh, I'm so... I'm so sorry, boss.
What... what should I do to save everyone?
The world is spinning... owie.
Before saving everyone, let's see if you can survive basic chores.
Basic? I can do basic chores!
Let's start with...
Start with what? Start with what?
What? What are we starting with?
What? What?
A bird! Go away! What?
Ouch! Ouch! Wait!
What? What? Ouch! Ouch! What are you doing?
What? What are you doing with him? Wait! Wait! No!
Don't go! Don't go! Please stop! Wait!
Wait! Wait!
No! No!
The birds took him!
I knew I could never trust a bird!
Hey you. Come here! Follow me!
A Grem?
Um... I have to help my friend.
You're scared and lost... Not knowing what to do, right?
I'll show you how to save your friends. Follow me!
Oh, okay.
This place is weird.
This place is dark and it smells bad.
Hey it smells good!!!! Do exactly as I say if you want to save your friends!
Go to the Grem Kingdom and return with the One Ping, a Honkshoe, and a Straw Hat.
Why do you need them?
YOU DON'T GET TO ASK ME ANY QUESTIONS!!! NOW GO GIGI, GOOOOOOO!!
Okay.
Whoa! So this is the Grem Kingdom?
It's so cool! There's so many Grems!
Does this mean this entire kingdom is mine if I save it?
Whoa, there's so many of you.
Oh, not all at once. No, no, no, no.
What?
Oh, I can't hear you.
Let's try this Grem. Lucky little Grem, what's on your mind?
Things aren't going well with my partner... I need your help to fix our relationship.
Aw, that is not my problem.
Ah, okay.
How about this Grem? Do you have anything interesting to say to me?
My tummy is getting very large and I don't know why. Please come with me to the doctor.
Okay, a little secret. Pregnant.
Okay, how about this one?
Make a contract with me, and become a magical girl!
Oh, that is not my problem either.
Oh, no, no, no, no. I will not be doing that.
I know what happens when you sign a contract.
You should never put your name down on things.
Well, these Grems were useless.
I think if I use my RPG knowledge, you're supposed to get information from NPCs...
...at a store.
And there's so many stalls near me.
Let's go to this one!
So cute!
Aw!
Are you a little worker Grem?
How much do you make an hour?
Do you make enough to survive?
Oh, what is this?
For me?
Uh, that's decorative hay, not edible...
Can I ask you something?
Oh, what is this?
- Who's the strongest person around here?
- Where can I get The One Ping?
- Excuse me, where is the bathroom?
...box?
Um...
Where can I get the One Ping?
Oh you are looking for the One Ping?
Then, here is the Quest for you! Take this ring and throw it into a volcano to destroy it.
This cursed ring holds centuries of anger. To purify it, it must be thrown into a volcano...
...but we fear fire and can't go near it.
Okay, yeah, I can do that quest for you.
Don't worry, I am the chosen one!
A ring! Wow!
I don't know what a volcano is.
How is this supposed to help me save Justice?
They're gonna die! They're gonna die if the volcano erupts!
Oh wait, I don't know what a volcano is.
Let's just try to find the One Ping myself.
Wait, this box was a little suspicious.
Hmm... Deliver to weapon shop.
Oh, cool! Is this for a quest?
Okay!
Hey! I got a package!
I got you guys a package! It's a gift from me!
I bought this. I'll just leave it right here.
It looks just like the box of the BL novel set I lost! Thank you!
Your BL novels?
No, no, no. Don't lose sight of the quest, Gigi.
Whoa! This is a really cool sword!
I bet, I bet I could save justice with...
Why is this so heavy for cardboard?
Oh my god. I'm gonna put it back.
This is why List has so much arm strength. Oh my god.
Hahaha! That sword is pretty useless. It can undo cardboardification or something...
This sword's really cool. How much is it?
What's that? Five dollars?
Uh, I can't afford that.
But uh, how about, how about I save them to the power of friendship?
Oh, another... another text box.
Is the One Ping even real?
I present a quest to you! Conquer it, and the One Ping shall be yours!
Would you craft 10 iron bars?
Okay, sounds easy. I can do that.
To craft 10 iron bars, you need to perform a freestyle dance and rap.
Gather 10 Grems with your performance to craft 10 iron bars.
What? I don't think that's how you craft an iron bar.
Ayo, you set, bro? Show us what you've got!
Where'd I get over here? What are these sunglasses?
Grems, this beat's kind of nasty. Who let you have this in the shoe shop?
Oh, okay. I'm getting it.
Okay, I guess we're really doing this. Okay.
Set on a quest to save my friends,
I don't really know what rhymes with friends.
Old man wizard, take it from me,
evil flying birds looking for a treat.
Don't even know if he's alive or not,
But who really cares what the pips that I got.
Horse girls racing my heart racing,
got me by my knees, skill activation.
Then a bunch of Grems surrounded me,
asked me to forge some iron bars you see.
Wait a second, starting to realize what you meant by bars.
But my rap game is fire, and my dance is not desired.
But if there's one thing that I'm not, it's definitely not a liar,
so I hope you don't mind if I twerk up on ya, you see.
There's a promise that I made to Fauna.
Yeah! Oh, I'm twerking. I don't know how to twerk.
I don't want to put in the work.
You see, twerking is a skill you have to, you have to train up for, everyone.
And I ran out of rhymes 30 seconds ago.
All right, um... I got dance moves and then...
Mic drop.
Yo! Yo! That was amazing!
Really? You liked it?
You successfully crafted 10 iron bars!
Yippee! I got that iron bar!
Yippee!
Take this as a reward.
Is that, is that what I think it is?
The One Ping is real!
Oh, what's my gauntlet? Oh.
Oh, is this yours? I found it down in the sewer.
Did I have it?
Did I have them?
If you want it back, throw the ring into the volcano.
Oh cool! Thanks! I'm gonna go now.
That ring is truly cursed. Handle it with care, or something terrible might happen.
If you dare throw it away, a ferocious monster will awaken...
Ooh, my tummy. I'm so hungry.
I can't save Justice like this.
Meat!
For me?
For free?
Hey! Who told you you could eat that?!
Whoa, big ass hat.
You... You don't like my hat?
No, no! I think your hat is lovely. I love it.
Lovely? Really? You can eat as much meat as you want!
Hey, by the way, I'm looking for a straw hat.
Any idea where I could find one?
I'll trade it if you complete my quest.
Ah, here we go again.
I want 26 pictures of giant rats.
Giant rats? Where do I find one of those?
Oh! Here they are!
Take your camera and capture family photos of all 26 of them!
Whoa, is this the family of 26 rats?
I guess I can see why you want pictures of them.
Okay, it's picture time. I'll get pictures of all 26 of them.
Heh, yeah. Get in the frame. Let me get a picture of you.
One of them doesn't even look like a rat. That's a really big person.
How about down here? Oh, right, one more, one more.
That's a Grem!
What are you doing? You're not even a rat!
Okay, how about down here? And look at those!
They look just like Justice!
If Justice were rats, but they're cardboard.
Whoa! Okay, don't worry, I got you. I got every angle imaginable.
That's a computer mouse.
And look at this photo I took, and then this one.
And this one, it's just so cute. All these rats are so cute.
And this is awesome, and this is a yummy looking rat, yay!
How cute!! I love them!!
Please accept this straw hat!
A hat, for me? Yay!
Now I have two items!
Oh, the stables are over there.
Maybe I can get the honkshoe from the stable.
Ah! Ah!
You scared me!
How are you doing?
Is everything going well?
Bad! I'm doing bad!
A few more quests might cheer you up!
You should take the ring to...
It's like no one cares about me.
This cruel evil world...
The stables!
Ah, horses. Ah, hello.
Hi! Hi there!
Hey!
I can share.
Here you go. Eat up.
Is this horse okay?
Oh, no, I think he's sleeping.
Okay, I think I can just... don't mind if I... I'll just take this.
No need for this to you.
I've done it!
I've gathered all three items, by myself!
Yay! I am the hero of this kingdom!
Sewer Grem, you probably didn't think I'd get them all.
But I did. I got everything.
Because I am the hero.
Dozo.
For you.
Oh wow, you really managed to get everything I asked for!
Hold on, wait here. There's something special just for you!
Oh yay!
Ah man, can't believe I got everything.
Oh, does that mean I saved Justice?
Oh, they're gonna be so proud of me!
Eh?
Is there something?
No, no, please! No! Don't do it! No! Ahhh!
Owly...
Ow!
Why does this keep happening to me?
Where am I?
What is this?
This isn't my fantasy life.
House?
Where am I going?
What is- ah!
Hey, what's up, how's it going guys?
Oh my gosh, what's up?
What's up everyone?
My name is Bae!
And my name is Biboo!
And together we are... BAEBIBOO!
Welcome, welcome to our Let's Play!
Yes, today we are playing a new game called...
...what is it called?
Uh, Gimms? The Gimm?
The Gimms? The Gimms?
I don't know how it's pronounced.
Something like that. Yeah.
Um, it's a brand new game with the rat...
...look at my move! The alpha!
We are the first ones to touch it.
Thank you, Sak-chan!
So we've got exclusive footage here...
...for you today. Let's get started!
Thank you so much! Let's get started!
So the premise of this game is we've got our character...
Where are you guys at? What are you doing over there?
...Gigi. Gigi. Is it a Gigi or Gigi?
Biboo!
I probably- I don't know.
And it's kind of like a real-life simulator game.
So if I push this button right here...
...she should be able to sit down.
Let's see. Oh, there we go!
Wait! I didn't do that!
Whoa! The controls!
Let's- let's test them some more.
Let's test out the controls.
Can you make her sit on the sofa?
Um, let's see if she can act like a dog.
You've got that dog in you!
You've got the dog in you! Of course!
Of course people would make me act like a dog.
There's the button! Bar- bar- bark!
Louder!
Whoa, look at those physics!
Oh my god!
Okay, that's enough.
Okay, stand back up.
All right, stand back up.
So this is just the base game, right?
So, you know, there's the- this is the room.
Wait, something weird's going on.
Have you noticed? Something's weird.
So there's four rooms at the moment.
We've got the main living room, the bedroom...
...and the bathroom.
And I think there's a kitchen- attached kitchenette.
Should we go check out the kitchen?
Yeah, let's go see the kitchen! My character!
Move into the kitchen. Come on, Gigi!
I don't want to! I don't want to!
Stop, I don't want to!
Let's see any- anything we can interact with.
Oh look, a knife!
Pick up the knife! Pick it up right now!
What does she have? A knife!
Pick up a knife! Pick up a knife!
Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up!
Why is there so much input lag? I know!
Why is input- oh, there we go! There we go!
Maybe the connection's just a little bit slow.
That's fine.
Now, okay. Now what? You're going to...
...put the knife into the stove?
Yes, into the stove! Into the burning hot stove!
I hope she doesn't stab herself.
Geez, do you think they, uh, accounted for this...
...kind of- oh my god!
Maybe that's something they can add...
...in the next update. That was kind of anticlimactic.
Oh well.
Whoa! Okay, pick up knife again.
Why? Why?
Pick up knife! Always carry a knife.
All right. What are you guys doing to me?
Shall we move into another room?
Yeah, let's check out the other room.
Let's go into door number one! Let's see what's in there.
Whoa!
Walk! Walk forward! Go! Move!
Walk! Walk! Go! Move! Move!
There she goes! Whoo! What is in that door?
Oh, she just clipped through the wall.
Oh, she clipped! Oh, we've got to report that bug.
Oh, clip! Okay, we've got to report that bug.
That's right.
Oh! Oh, there's a bathtub! And there's a toilet!
Oh, there's a bathtub! And there's a toilet!
Oh, oh, there's a- I know, I know!
Have you heard of Skibidi Toilet?
Oh gosh, what is Skibidi Toilet?
All right, I'm going to make the character...
...phase into the toilet...
...with her head sticking out to become...
...Skibidi! Become one with the toilet! NOW!
I don't want to! No! No!
Skibidi Toilet! I learn something new every day.
Skibidi bop bop bop! Yes, yes, yes!
Wow! Okay! Wow!
I don't believe it! Turn on notifications!
Yeah! So you don't miss the next episode!
Yeah! Just spin!
There's gonna be more and people!
Thank you for watching!
Bye!
Thank god.
I don't hear their voices anymore.
Oh thank god.
Oh get me out of this toilet...
...everything is skibidi toilet.
First you take over my body...
...then you make me skibidi toilet.
How do I get out of here?
How could they... how could they torture me like this?
Why did they make me do all those things?
They didn't even feed me.
They didn't even say that I was a good girl...
...after they made me do all those things.
And now I'm poor.
I'm gonna take it out on this canvas.
Oh, if I just paint what I want, then maybe I'll be rewarded for it.
Because I am... karma comes to good people.
So... beautiful woman...
boobs.
Yes.
Yes!
I've done it.
My greatest work yet.
My painting.
Hello?
Gigi?
Hello? Knock knock.
Are you in there?
Okay, I'm gonna come in.
Oh my goodness.
This absolute masterpiece.
One of the lost works of Picasso? Or no?
It has to be Leonardo da Vinci.
It's so incredible. I've never seen anything like it.
I can't believe that something like this is before my own eyes.
Gigi!
Gigi, wake up!
Gigi, are you alright?
Something attacked me...
I don't know what...
Why are you screaming?
Oh, beautiful woman.
Yes, it's me. I came over just like you invited me to.
Nerissa Ravencroft?
Is that you? And not a painting?
No, but did you make this, Gigi?
I made this.
It's incredible. Do you like it?
I do.
In fact, I thought of you while making it. Can you tell?
I can. In fact, if it's so that I'm your muse...
...maybe we could be together?
Really?
Yes. No one's ever said that to me.
I swore... I've never wanted anything quite as much.
After seeing this painting, the fire of my heart has been inflamed...
...and I feel like I cannot live without you, Gigi Murin.
Don't scream now.
You're tickling me.
You know what? I've thought a lot of thinking. Thought thought about thinking.
I've thought of it. And I've come up with a thing.
We should get married.
Oh, I thought you'd never ask!
Really?
Why would you think that?
Do you want me?
I want you so bad.
You have no idea how bad I want you.
Let's go...
...let's go consummate our marriage.
Why?
What?
I don't know if I'm ready for that.
I don't know.
I don't know!
そう簡単じゃないのにずっと
It's not that easy, but forever
揺ら揺ら 散々 消える散々
Swaying, terribly, disappearing terribly
今から 緞帳 下がる 散々
From now on, the curtain falls, terribly
静かな 愛情 あとにサヨナラ
Quiet affection, then goodbye
ロウワー / Lyrics, Music: ぬゆり
Lower / Lyrics, Music: Nuyuri
言いかけてた言葉が一つ消えて
A word I was about to say has vanished
止まらないで またタップダンス
Don't stop, tap dance again.
亡く身失うまで 逆転劇を繰る
Until our bodies are lost, play out the reversal drama.
舌が乾いた心にも 吐き出すように込めて
Pour it into the heart with a dry tongue as if spitting it out.
胸の中 香りのように濁る
Inside my chest, it grows cloudy like a scent.
受け止めた一言が自分さえ
Even the single word I accepted...
抱えられず持て余した それを守っている
...I couldn't handle it, yet I'm protecting it.
掠れた声は空々しく 喉は焼けて埋め尽くす
The raspy voice is hollow, and my throat is burning and filled.
何を言うべきか 分からなくて
I don't know what to say.
感じてたものが 今解き放たれていた
What I was feeling has now been released.
同じ様に違う なんだか違う
It's the same, yet different. Somehow, it's different.
いつまで行こうか 何処まで行けるのか
How long shall we go? How far can we go?
左様かじゃないなら 何を思うの
If it's not "is that so," then what are you thinking?
僕らが離れるのなら
If we are to part...
僕らが望むのなら
...if that's what we desire...
その度に何回も 繋がれるように
...then so that we can be connected many times over.
ここに引き留めるのなら
If I'm to keep you here...
離さず居られるのなら
...if I can stay without letting go...
まだ誰も知らない 感覚ですら割れていく
...then even sensations no one knows yet will split apart.
ナルナルノ
Naru naru no
ラルラルタ
Laru laru ta
いつまで続くだろうと
I wonder how long it will last...
同じ様に同じ様に呟く
...I murmur in the same way, in the same way.
今は忘れないよう 刻まれた空気を
Right now, so I don't forget, the atmosphere carved here...
これから何度も 思い出すのだろう
...I'll probably remember it many times from now on.
僕らだけだ
It's just us.
僕らが離れるのなら
If we are to part...
僕らが望むのなら
...if that's what we desire...
その度に何回も 繋がれるように
...then so that we can be connected many times over.
ここに引き留めるのなら
If I'm to keep you here...
離さず居られるのなら
...if I can stay without letting go...
まだ誰も知らない 感覚僕の
...even my sensations that no one knows yet...
生きてる姿を
...my living form...
確かめて正しくして
...confirm it and make it right.
Oh husband, I'm so happy to be living a domestic life with you Gigi Murin...
...well, in your awesome house, with your awesome kitchen...
...and your awesome floor, and this awesome couch.
Wife.
Husband.
I've never been married before.
Me neither.
What am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed to take care of you?
Take care of me?
You're so sweet, no one's ever wanted to do that.
I want to take care of you.
Oh! I've dreamed of this forever...
...and ever...
Oh my goodness!
Oh! Gigi Murin!
Please, not in front of...
...not in front of the studio audience!
Oh, my beautiful, beautiful wife.
How far does your leg go up?
Oh! As far as you want it to!
I see. That's enough.
Oh, not in front of the studio audience.
Not in front of the studio audience.
I can't believe you did that.
Me?
If you say so husband, I can't believe I'm such a dirty dirty girl...
...in front of this audience and everything.
That's only for me, my dirty dirty girl.
Yes, I wouldn't want anyone else to see me like that but you.
I should do something for you.
That is what a Gigi Murin should do.
Yes, I would love that.
I should make you some toast.
Some toast for me?
Yes, for you!
You're so sweet.
Have you ever cooked before?
No, never.
Never.
Never. I don't even know how to use a microwave.
Really?
Yes, really.
Well, I only have one thing here and it's toast.
Wow, you're so amazing.
Did you make the bread yourself too?
I made it.
Whoa!
Oh, it's been on the floor, that's even better!
You stepped there.
Watch me, watch me flip it, okay?
Yes, yes, I'm watching.
Watch, watch this.
Wait, wait, I have a solution. Okay, flip it!
Yes!
You're amazing!
Oh... Ah, that made me really hungry.
Do you mind if I eat this toast first?
Of course you can.
Really? You're such a sweetheart, why?
That looks tasty.
I have to use the bathroom, my sweet.
Oh, of course.
By all means, anything you need.
If I look through the doorknob hole...
I can see Gigi on the toilet.
Oh Gigi, I just have to tell you...
These last few hours together have been absolute domestic bliss.
I don't think there's any moment in my life that has been as amazing as this.
Are you still in there?
Oh, sorry.
How's the toast?
It's really good, I wish you could try some.
Oh yeah, me too. Maybe next time.
I made this for you so I just had... what if it was poisoned, you know?
So I had to check.
You're so thoughtful.
Well, Nerissa Ravencroft, I've been doing a lot of thinking while I was on the toilet.
Yes.
And I don't...
I don't know...
Yes.
Don't say another word.
I don't know what a family entails.
I completely understand.
Will you be able to teach me?
Of course, I can teach you anything.
Really?
Of course, I'm a ten-thousand-year-old demon. We can do anything you want together.
You can teach me anything?
Anything.
Anything?
Anything your heart desires.
Well, I shouldn't keep my beautiful wife waiting.
Yes.
But I have a tummy ache.
You have a tummy ache.
Will you wait for me?
Of course, I'll wait forever for you.
Okay, hold on.
Okay.
I don't think I should be eating this toast all by myself.
Don't worry.
Let me slide it under the door for you.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Oh wow.
Is it good?
So delicious!
Is it tasty?
It's so tasty!
Skibidi Toilet.
Never has there been bread made this amazing.
I'm glad that I made such a beautiful toast for you.
Me too.
Hey!
I finished it all.
All of it?
All of it, it's all in my stomach.
Was it really yummy?
So delicious.
I'm glad.
Me too. I was really, really nervous, I still am nervous...
...because you're so, you're so beautiful.
And I'm just a little guy on a toilet.
A little guy.
And I have a tummy ache and there's just so much wrong with me.
Well don't worry.
But you, there's everything right with you.
But that's how I feel about you.
Really?
With me everything is wrong, but when we're together, everything is perfect.
My love, why are you crying?
No one's ever said that to me before.
Oh, Gigi.
I'm sick and tired of these walls separating us. Nerissa, come in here!
Let's break them down!
Sit on my lap, Nerissa.
Sit on your lap? I will.
Anything you ask for, I will do.
How about though we move from this porcelain... whatever it is?
My porcelain throne?
Yeah, and we move somewhere a little more comfortable.
Okay, well, I'm done.
Yeah?
I washed my hands.
No.
Okay, it's better this way.
Let's hold hands.
Yes, let's hold hands.
Hold my hand.
I'm holding your hand.
Let's go to the bedroom together.
Yeah, to the bedroom.
Well Gigi, what's the matter?
I'm shy.
Don't be shy.
I've never done this before!
You know Gigi, the truth is... I know I said I'd teach you anything, but I've never done this before either.
Really?
Then how are we supposed to do it if you've never...
Never done such a thing before. Who's gonna teach me?
We're going to learn together.
You can just learn from nothing?
Of course.
That's some... you can just do that?
We'll find it out. How do you think the first humans learned things, Gigi?
I don't know!
Why are you asking me that?
Philosophical? It's pillow talk. Anyway.
Oh, oh, okay. Well...
Shall we?
Well, now that you've brought it up... um...
...the first humans probably learned things by doing them.
Yes.
So let's just do it then.
Okay!
I can't wait another moment.
Nerissa Ravencroft, you monster!
Oh, I'm sorry! I was trying to be really gentle.
You did great.
Really?
Yes, it was amazing.
Well, I'm glad that we could spend our first day in the bedroom together...
...as a married couple.
Yes, but Gigi, there's something strange going on.
Did you transfer your stomachache to me?
I don't think so. You can't just give a tummy ache to someone with the toast.
But it really, it really hurts. Maybe you need to use the bathroom?
I don't think so, but oh...
Gigi!
Wait a moment.
Gigi, your fingers!
No! No!
No, I'm not ready! I'm not ready!
You know...
...you forgot to wear both gloves!
No!
How is it...
I can't... we can't!
We don't have the money!
Gigi, I'm sorry!
Gigi, I can't tell you...
...this house is barely holding together!
Gigi, it hurts!
Doctor!
Doctor! Doctor, please!
My wife, she's in pain! Can you please help her?
Please, doctor! Please!
Please!
Please help me!
What? Hello?
Are you gonna help her?
Hello?
Why are you laughing?
I'm giving birth here!
She's literally... she is literally giving birth...
...and you are just laughing at her!
Yeah!
What kind of doctor... I'm gonna go on the internet...
...and leave bad reviews about you!
Your days are numbered! You're going out of business...
...and you're gonna go bankrupt and...
Gigi! Gigi, the baby!
Oh no!
It won't wait another minute!
Gigi! I got it!
She's safe!
Oh, our child!
It's our baby.
It's a beautiful egg.
It is such a beautiful egg. Wow.
We didn't need a doctor after all. You're a natural.
You're so good at that.
It seems like we're both a natural at a lot of things.
Yes. Wow.
You know, I'm a little impatient.
I kind of wonder, what are you?
What are you in there?
Hello? Hey!
Are you gonna just shake the baby?
Yeah!
Wake up!
Oh my god!
It's our son!
Our son!
Oh, he's so cute!
Let's... let's let them hold the baby. Yes.
Should we name him? Should we name him?
You're not gonna hold it like a mommy?
Should we name him?
Yeah, we should name him.
Maybe we should let them name him.
Them?
Them out there?
Them out there!
Them out...
Yeah! They've been watching us this whole time, you know.
What?
Do you guys have an idea to name our baby?
They've been watch...
What?
...give birth?
They're giving name suggestions. What?
Yeah!
Those are some great suggestions. What do you think?
They're all terrible.
Oh.
I'm going to name it Nerigigi.
Nerigigi.
Yeah, because it's like your name and then my name...
...and together and now...
It's perfect!
It's just a happy family. Just you, me, Nerigigi.
And then now you're a beautiful mother...
...and now I'm also a beautiful father.
What else can we do?
I don't know, maybe you should go somewhere else...
...while I take care of the baby.
Okay.
Yoshi yoshi yoshi yoshi...
There, there, there, there...
Why are you still watching me? Go away!
Go away!
Better get the mail for my wife.
I think giving birth is really expensive.
I'll have to pay the bills.
I don't have any money though.
God, I hope these aren't bills.
Help!
I don't have my—
Hey! What's happening?
Wait. Did you... Did you leave your controller on?
Oh, maybe I like dropped on the floor and the controller like...
Wait, I'm not touching the controller. Wait, um...
Wait, she's going for the ladder. Wait, take it out. Take it out.
No... The liquid of water is filling your lungs.
The air is slowly moving out of your body. You are drowning, honey.
Wait, she's kind of cute though.
Oh my god, wait. What's happening? Oh my god. Did you see that?
Uh, is the house on fire?
My house might be on fire. Oh, whatever. It's fine.
And it's filling your lungs with water. You are slowly suffocating from the inside. Haha.
I hear the inner monologue. Haha.
Bae, help me!
I think there is a... quiz function!
I think it's like if maybe like this character can like answer the quiz correctly...
...the ladder will come back as a prize.
Too much water!
Oh! Hello. Are you ready for the quiz?
Hi! Are you ready for the quiz?
Are you ready?
Let me out!
What is the name of the hypothetical particle that mediates the force of gravity in quantum field theory, and has not yet been observed experimentally?
A. Photon
B. Gluon
C. Graviton
D. Neutrino
What is the name of the hypothetical particle that mediates the force of gravity in quantum field theory...
What are you saying?
...and has not yet been observed experimentally?
What are you saying to me?
A. Photon.
B. Gluon.
Gluon? Help! Gluon?
C. Graviton or D. Neutrino.
I'm drowning in here!
Please answer correctly or else you will die.
Wait, wait! What do I say? It's C! I don't care, it's C!
C! It's C!
The answer was C. Graviton. Womp womp.
What do you mean?
Maybe the next character will know.
Try harder next time.
Oh well.
I'm bored now.
Shucks. Oh well. This is boring.
Oh she did.
Took my ladder away!
Someone help me!
I don't know how to work life!
Morkalify!
Give me a hand!
Morkalify, I'm drowning!
She's flashing me while I'm dying!
Mork, there's a better time for that!
Stop! Stop! I can't look!
Morkalify, put that away! Put—
Hey!
Listen to me.
I'm drowning.
I'm okay.
You made me watch dancing fruits on TV.
You liked it!
You made me dance next to horses.
I liked that.
Fuck you.
Wait! Wait, we can talk about it!
Morkalify, wait!
Die, idiot!
Morkalify!
Someone help me, I'm drowning.
Bae, Mork are killing me.
Bae, Mori are killing me.
They're literally drowning me.
Morkalify, she's killing me.
I'm alive! I'm not drowning!
But my wife, my child...
...my beautiful wife and child, where are they?
Why am I in the Grimm Kingdom? What about Nerissa?
My beautiful wife! No!
Nerissa, where did you go? I love you!
Why is everything on fire?
What?
There's a dragon here?
My friends are made out of cardboard!
They are not fire-resistant. Oh no.
Okay, I see the Grams are doing their best to save them.
Okay, Grams.
What's this one doing? What are you up to?
Oh, you are not helping at all.
It's okay, little Gram. Your arms will reach one day.
These Grems on the other hand, you have magic!
Wow!
Where'd you learn this?
Grems are so talented.
Not you though.
That's okay, one day.
Oh Grems, Grems are working really hard so...
I, me, Gigi Murin the hero, is here to save the day!
Oh!
This must be my hero weapon, as all heroes have a hero weapon.
Okay.
Ooh!
Oh!
POPUPS!
1 million dollars?
Wh... oh, the kingdom can save itself. I am not—
Oh wait, a catapult! Of course!
Of course! Obviously! Okay, I'll help with this.
Don't worry, Grems.
Let me... what ammo is here?
Oh, okay. Let's...
Let's just pick this up.
Mnyaw mnyaw mnyaw...
Hah!
Yay! Let's go Grem! Let's save the kingdom!
Let's save the kingdom together! Yah!
Wait, we're barely scratching it!
I don't know what to do.
Wait, there's just no other choice.
I'm gonna have to pull out that move.
Yeah, yeah that move!
My ultimate move!
All right everyone, are you ready to see my ultimate move?
Okay.
Ikuzo!
Let's go!
Stop!
Oji-chan, you scared me!
Old man, you scared me!
Oh, wait! No!
You took— you took the fire breath, Oji-chan!
You took— you took the fire breath, old man!
Stop it! Stop! You're gonna die!
Stop! No!
O-No, you're getting hurt! Please! I need you!
If you're not here, who's gonna tell me how to defeat the dragon?
No! No! Please! Please!
You're getting hurt! Don't! No!
Are you okay?
Oji-chan, are you okay?
Old man, are you okay?
You saved me!
I must... save...
Wh-What is it?
This kingdom...
The kingdom?
How am I supposed to save it without you?
I'm—
No! Oji-chan, no!
No! Old man, no!
I don't know how else to save the kingdom and destroy the dragon!
It's not taking any damage!
Help! Call the guard!
Wizard graveyard!
Grems come and pray, Gremdal the Grey.
Danger is here, a dragon's appear.
What the...
What the hell?
Come seize the day, fight and we slay.
Gi-gi-mu-rin.
Here at the scene.
Look and behold, legends foretold.
She is the brave, souls will be saved.
Please do not stare, crazy footwear.
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch.
From near and far, hit by a car.
Where did you come from?
Gremurin come outside to pray, oh.
So many of you!
Like... like fifteen of you!
Gremurin, Gremurin.
Wait, what are you singing about?
About me?
Help! Call the guard!
Gigi Murin...
That... wait.
Grems come and pray...
Danger is here, a dragon's appear.
That's right! I am a hero!
Come seize the day, fight and we slay.
Gi-gi-mu-rin.
I can save the day!
Here at the scene.
Look and behold, legends foretold.
Through the power of these children singing for me!
She is the brave, souls will be saved.
Please do not stare, crazy footwear.
I could do anything!
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch.
Yeah!
From near and far, hit by a car.
Yeah, I could do it all!
Okay, okay what should I do? What should I do, Grems?
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing.
What should I do? I don't know!
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here.
I know! Through the power of interpretive dance!
That's the only way we can destroy a dragon.
Because it has not been taking any physical damage.
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh.
So, the best way to defeat this dragon is through mental damage!
Gremurin, Gremurin.
All right!
I've never done a worm before. I'm about to do a worm.
Help! Call the guard!
Grems come and pray...
Is it working?
Danger is here, a dragon's appear.
She is the brave, souls will be saved.
Die, dragon! I'm sorry!
Please do not stare, crazy footwear.
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
I-I'm not an interpretive dancer!
From near and far, hit by a car
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gigi is here!
Don't worry!
Another cartwheel!
A second one even!
Help! Call the guard
Grems come and pray
Yeah!
And then- and then a worm!
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
Is it working?
Is the dragon being cringed out by me?
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
Oh no! I cannot do this!
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
From near and far, hit by a car
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gigi Gigi Gigi Gigi Murin
My name! They're saying my name!
Is it working?
Gigi Murin Acrylic Stand
Tell me, children!
Is the dragon being affected by me?
We'll win somehow, Purchase it now
[emotional vocal solo]
What is this?
It's power I'm feeling.
Oh no! It's surging in my veins!
Oh man! I feel it!
AAAAIEEEE!
Help! Call the guard
They don't call me the Fister for nothing!
Grems come and pray
gremurin, gremurin
Gi gi Mu rin
That's me. The Fister.
Here at the scene, Gigi Murin
Hololive English Justice
Ah! I've done it!
Gigi Murin has done it!
I have defeated the dragon!
Ha! I did it!
Oh, Ojii-chan! It was all thanks to you and the fifteen children!
But it was all thanks to you and the fifteen children that I did it!
Yay!
Ojii-chan... wait...
You're still dead? NOOOOO!
No! I thought-
I thought my power of dance could have saved you!
Ojii-chan! You're okay!
The power of dance does save everyone!
You're okay, right?
You're not possessed, are you?
Oh, what is this?
Oh, what are you doing?
Oh, what is happening?
Oh god! What-
What's happening?
What the heck is happening?
Ojii-chan?
SHOEBOX UPGRADES - NEW ARRIVAL
Ojii-chan! You're okay!
I've done it! Yay!
Behold! The darkness has lifted from the dragon's soul!
My final desperate strike has shattered its cruel memories!
No longer a beast of fury...
...it has been reborn as an innocent baby dragon!
にっこり調査隊！ おはこんばんちわ！
Niccori Survey Team! Oha-kon-ban-chiwa!
How are you? 今日も今日とて最高ぜ！
How are you? Today is the best as well!
Oh, Wonderful!
にっこり^^調査隊のテーマ
Niccori^^ Survey Team Theme
ワンツースリー！
One, two, three!
DJ E・O・六！
DJ E-O-Six!
我ら、世界を笑顔に調査隊！
We're the survey team to make the world smile!
隊長、俺に名案が！ （何だ何だ？）
Captain, I have a great idea! (What is it?)
ってまだ何も言ってないんだが… とにかくあれだ、ほら！
Wait, I haven't said anything yet... Anyway, look at that!
百聞は一見にしかず！ 百聞は一見にしかずだね！
Seeing is believing! Seeing is believing, right!
そろそろ… 虫取りいこうぜ！
It's time to... go bug hunting!
隊長！ 名案があります！ （何だ何だ？）
Captain! I have a great idea! (What is it?)
世界中をひっくり返さなきゃ！
We have to turn the whole world upside down!
とりあえず！ とりあえず！ 出発進行！
For now! For now! Departure!
ちょっと待って！ 旅支度くらいさせろ！
Wait a minute! Let me at least get ready for the trip!
落ち着いて。 持ち物チェック始めます！
Calm down. Let's start the belongings check!
パパパ・パスポート持った？ 着替え忘れた！ （えー！）
Got your pa-pa-pa-passport? I forgot a change of clothes! (Ehhh!)
でもモバイルバッテリー持った？ （はい！）
But did you bring your power bank? (Yes!)
志は持った？ （もちろん！） 胃薬飲んで！
Do you have the ambition? (Of course!) Take some stomach medicine!
仲間がいて！
Friends are here!
私たちがいる！
We are here!
しかも普通じゃない！ （誰のことかな？）
And we're not ordinary! (I wonder who you're talking about?)
僕らには不可能を可能に変える力があるさ！
We have the power to turn the impossible into the possible!
にっこりこりこりこりあんだー！
Niccori-kori-kori-koriander!
あっちもこっちも全速前進！
Full speed ahead everywhere!
千客万来！ 君の笑顔もコレクションさせて！
A flood of customers! Let me collect your smiles too!
イェイイェイイェイイェイ！
Yay yay yay yay!
老いも若きも関係ねえぜ！
Young or old, it doesn't matter!
これぞ一流のエンターテイメント！
This is top-tier entertainment!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって！ We can do it!
I'll make my dreams come true one day too! We can do it!
このにっこりに触れて もっと胸ふくらみ
Touching this smile, my heart swells even more,
満たしたのさ！ グー！
And I'm fulfilled! Good!
はい注目！
Attention, please!
にっこり調査隊！
Smile Investigation Team!
だいたいお茶の子さいさい
It's mostly a piece of cake
保つ調査のていさい
Maintaining the form of an investigation
今だ悪を鉄槌せんさい
Now, hammer down on evil!
理事調査報告その１
Investigation report part 1
ペコは全然違います
Peko is completely different
おバカも全然違います
Stupidity is also completely different
ヤダー！めっちゃ怖～！
No way! That's so scary!
諸君！大変です！
Everyone! It's a disaster!
前前前世が足りてません
We're lacking 'previous, previous, previous lives'!
とりあえず！
For now!
とりあえず待って珍道中だなあ
For now, wait, what a weird journey
だなあ！
It sure is!
お前が言うな！
Look who's talking!
通知追加！
Notification added!
じゃあ持ち物チェック始めまーす！
Then let's start the belongings check!
ほいじゃいつもの！
Then the usual!
パス！パス！パスポート持った？
Pass! Pass! Got your passport?
はい！
Yes!
パンツ忘れた！
I forgot my underwear!
うわぁ！
Whoa!
モバイルバッテリー持った？
Got your mobile battery?
はい！
Yes!
志は持った？
Got your ambition?
もーちろん！
Of course!
お国柄とか
National character or whatever
老若男女
Young and old, men and women
あんまし関係ない
It doesn't really matter
ワールドワイドだぜ！
We're worldwide!
あっちも世界もまだまだ
Over there and the world are still...
捨てたもんじゃないんだってば！
not so bad after all!
にっこりこりこりこりこりお利口さん
Smile, smile, smile, smile, good little kid
陰キャも陽キャもウェルカムウェルカム！
Introverts and extroverts, welcome, welcome!
君の笑顔が
Your smile is...
調査対象さ！
the object of our investigation!
イェイイェイイェイイェイ！
Yay yay yay yay!
ファンダメンタルとかなんとかを
With fundamentals and whatever
景気に一筆入魂エンターテイメン！
as an opportunity, entertainment with a single soul-filled stroke!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって We can do!
Saying that I, too, will fulfill my dreams someday, We can do!
さあにっこり満ち溢れて
Now, overflowing with smiles
もっと胸膨らみましたとさ
My heart swelled even more, or so the story goes
そのしょんぼりもにっこりに変換
Convert that sadness into a smile too
うちらに任せろメイクユアスマイル
Leave it to us, make your smile
揚げの時だって
Even when you're up...
下げの時だってかき混ぜちゃって
...or when you're down, mix it all up
スパイスだって！完璧だ！
even the spice! Perfect!
にっこり！
Smile!
にっこりこりこりこりこりお利口さん
Smile, smile, smile, smile, good little kid
大人も子供も関係なし！
Adults or children, it doesn't matter!
もちろん我々調査隊正座だ！
Of course, our investigation team is sitting at attention!
うぇい、うぇい、うぇい、うぇい、うぉー！
Wei, wei, wei, wei, woo!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって We can do!
Saying that I, too, will fulfill my dreams someday, We can do!
さあにっこり満ち溢れて
Now, overflowing with smiles
もっと胸膨らみましたとさ
My heart swelled even more, or so the story goes
That's not all!
That's right! You didn't expect this!
Oh, you didn't expect this!
There's 3D merch! Yay!
You too, you watching at home...
...can own your very own...
...Grems Hand-in Cushion!
What does that mean? You can put your hands in the Grems!
You can remember all the good times that we had in the Grem Kingdom...
...with Oji-san! Yay! Yay!
...with Gramps! Yay! Yay!
And you can do so many things with this Grems...
...like stick your hands in it, which I said.
You can stick your hands in the Grems...
...and you can sleep on it, and you can squish it...
...and you can cherish it, and you can love it...
...and it's very soft and very squishy.
Just watch Oji-san play with it. Doesn't it look cool?
Just watch Gramps play with it. Doesn't it look cool?
3Dお披露目グッズの登場じゃー！
Behold the 3D debut merchandise!
ヒャッホイ！うぉー！
Hyahhoi! Woo!
見よ！このグレムのもちもちのハンドインクッションじゃよ。
Look! It's this squishy Grems hand-in cushion.
So cute.
ヘッヘイ！いっぱい可愛がっておくれよ。
Hehey! Please take good care of it.
頼んだぞ。イェーイ！
I'm counting on you. Yay!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Thank you everyone for coming to my 3D live today!
I worked really, really hard on it.
And thank you to the staff who is, who is overseeing me...
...and thank you for Oji-san for being here...
...and thank you for the Grems, and thank you for Mori Calliope...
...and Nerissa, and Bae, and FuwaMoco, and Justice...
...for being here, a part of my 3D live!
This was so much fun! Oh, it was so awesome!
Thank you, and I'm looking forward to doing more 3D things for you guys! Yay!
Yippee! And don't forget, there is more 3D debuts next week...
...so make sure you tune in because all of Justice has been working so hard, okay? Okay!
Bye everyone! I'll see you later! Bye-bye!
Grems, thank you for being a part of my journey!
Can you believe it? It’s been 1 year!!
Sometimes it still doesn’t feel real that I get to be here with you all,
and I’ll never take this feeling for granted.
You are my passion! You are my strength!
I will keep working hard knowing that the shoebox will always be by my side.
I could say thank you a million times and it still wouldn’t feel enough.
But for all the times you’ve made me laugh, for the comfort you’ve brought me,
the community we’ve created, the art you’ve shared, the stories you’ve crafted,
the whimsy that you keep alive in your heart,
the shoebox that you take such good care of,
for always supporting me, THANK YOU. stay silly! Gigi