(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
KING
Lyrics・Composition: Kanaria
幽霊だ、行こう、唸る愛に
I'm a ghost, let's go, into the roaring love
幽霊だ、行こう、未熟なラリー
I'm a ghost, let's go, an immature rally
幽霊だ、ストップ、知ってないし
I'm a ghost, stop, I don't even know
勘弁にしてよ、怠慢なラリー
Give me a break, a negligent rally
人様願う欠片のアイロニー
The irony of a fragment that people wish for
だれもが願う無機質なような
Like the inorganic state that everyone wishes for
一掃し、先んじ、始めてタイニーな
Swept away, preempted, starting tiny
ハッとして、笑えない、ハジメテパッパッパ
Startled, can't laugh, first pappappa
パッパッパ
Pappappa
左様なら、おねがいひとつ
Farewell, I have one wish
愛も変わらず、おまけにウォーニンウォーニン
Love remains unchanged, plus warning, warning
左様なら、おねがいひとつ
Farewell, I have one wish
張り詰めた、思い込め
Filled with tension, pour your heart into it
レフトサイド、ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯を剥き出して、パッパッパ
Baring your teeth, pappappa
照れくさいね
It's embarrassing
レフトサイド、ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯を突き出して、パッパッパ
Baring your teeth, pappappa
You are King
無邪気に遊ぶ、期待期待のダーリンダーリン
Playing innocently, the darling of expectation
健気に笑う、痛い痛いの消える
Smiling bravely, the pain fades away
無様にしねる、苦い思いもなくなって
Dying ungracefully, the bitter thoughts are gone
ララ、バイバイバイ、期待期待の最前線
Lala, bye-bye-bye, the front line of expectation
左様なら、おねがいひとつ
Farewell, I have one wish
愛も変わらず、ピックアップのウォーニンウォーニン
Love remains unchanged, pickup warning, warning
左様なら、おねがいひとつ
Farewell, I have one wish
張り詰めた、思い込め
Filled with tension, pour your heart into it
レフトサイド、ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯を剥き出して、パッパッパ
Baring your teeth, pappappa
邪魔くさいね
It's annoying
レフトサイド、ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯を突き出して、パッパッパ
Baring your teeth, pappappa
You are King
KING
#AyundaRisu3D
Hai! You are KING! Wow!
Hi! You are KING! Wow!
You are KING! Wah!
Hai semuanya!
Hi everyone!
Hey, hello everybody! Hai!
Hey, hello everybody! Hi!
I'm, yes, I'm squirrel from the magical forest! Hai!
I'm, yes, I'm squirrel from the magical forest! Hi!
Baru mulai saja sudah berapi-api, oke?
Just started and already fired up, okay?
We just started and it's...
盛り上がってるかな？
Are you guys hyped?
Okay, so, first song is KING.
And uh well because I'm the closing, so I chose KING as the...
...first opening song! Yes!
If you like my performance, yes, don't forget, don't forget there's hashtag above here.
Don't forget, don't forget to post...
...the screenshot, to post your uh uh what is it again? To post your...
...Ayunda Risu experience! Yes, with hashtag #AyundaRisu3D...
...and make it trending! And also don't forget, don't forget, yes, yes...
Don't forget to share this to your whole family, to your friends, to your...
...colleagues, and yes!
How was it? How was it? KING. Oh wait, okay. Yes, yes.
Yes, you can see me! Ah, kawaii! Ah, kawaii!
Yes, you can see me! Ah, how cute! Ah, how cute!
Ah, kawaii! Ah... ah, kawaii! Ah...
Ah, how cute! Ah... ah, how cute! Ah...
Hellow! Oh, I'm finally 3D guys! Yes!
Hello! Oh, I'm finally 3D guys! Yes!
The memer squirrel is finally in 3D! Amazing!
But, but, this is only the beginning alright?
Because there will be more, because this is only the beginning.
So, えとね... Iya iya iya iya iya. Ho ho ho ho ho.
So, well... Yes yes yes yes yes. Ho ho ho ho ho.
Look at me! Look at me all you want before we actually moving, alright?
So after this we're going to check my bedroom. Yes, I think you've seen it...
...previously, just a glimpse of it right?
Jadi habis ini tuh Risu mau mengecek kamar ya. Oke? Oke?
So after this Risu wants to check the room. Okay? Okay?
Yes, are you ready? Oh my god, kawaii! Ah, fluffy tail みたい!
Yes, are you ready? Oh my god, how cute! Ah, looks like a fluffy tail!
Washa washa washa washa... みたい! Ayayayayaya... Okay.
Rustle rustle rustle rustle... it looks like! Ayayayayaya... Okay.
So, you know what? Let's move on to a more comfortable place, to my bedroom, okay?
Let's a-go!
Ulululu... Gamba Risu!
Ulululu... Do your best, Risu!
ハロー　窓を開けて　小さく呟いた
Hello, I opened the window and whispered softly
ハウアーユー　誰もいない　部屋で一人
How are you? Alone in a room with no one else
モーニング　朝が来たよ　どしゃ降りの朝が
Morning, the morning has come, a downpouring morning
ティクタック　私のネジを　誰か巻いて
Tick-tock, someone please wind up my spring
ハロ/ハワユ
Hello/How Are You
Lyrics & Composition: ナノウ
Lyrics & Composition: Nanou
ハロー　昔のアニメに　そんなのいたっけな
Hello, was there something like that in an old anime?
ハウアーユー　羨ましいな　皆に愛されて
How are you? I'm so jealous, being loved by everyone
スリーピー　馬鹿なこと言ってないで　支度をしなくちゃ
Sleepy, stop talking nonsense and get ready
クライ　涙の跡を隠すため
Cry, to hide the traces of my tears
もう口癖になった「まぁいっか」
The phrase "Oh well" has become a habit
昨日の言葉がふと頭をよぎる
Yesterday's words suddenly cross my mind
「もう君には全然期待してないから」
"I don't expect anything from you anymore"
そりゃまぁ私だって　自分に期待などしてないけれど
Well, I don't really expect anything from myself either, but...
あれは一体どういうつもりですか
What on earth did you mean by that?
喉元まで出かかった言葉
The words that were about to come out of my throat
口を突いて出たのは嘘
But what came out of my mouth was a lie
こうして今日も私は貴重な
And so today, I continue to use
言葉を使い分けて生きてゆく
These precious words differently as I live on
なぜ隠してしまうのですか
Why do you hide it?
笑われるのが怖いのですか
Are you afraid of being laughed at?
誰にも会いたくないのですか
Do you not want to see anyone?
それ本当ですか
Is that really true?
曖昧という名の海に溺れて
Drowning in a sea called ambiguity
息も出来ないほど苦しいの
It's so painful I can't even breathe
少し声が聞きたくなりました
I wanted to hear your voice a little bit
本当に弱いな
I'm really weak
一向に進まない支度の途中
In the middle of getting ready, which isn't progressing
朦朧とした頭で思う
I think with a hazy head
「もう理由を付けて休んでしまおうかな」
"Maybe I'll just make up an excuse and take the day off"
いやいや分かってますって
No, no, I know
なんとなく言ってみただけだよ
I just said it for no reason
分かってるから怒らないでよ
I know, so please don't be mad
幸せだろうと不幸せだろうと
Whether I'm happy or unhappy
平等に残酷に朝は来る
The morning comes equally and cruelly
生きていくだけで精一杯の私に
To me, who's doing my best just to keep living
これ以上何を望むというの
What more do you want from me?
なぜ気にしてしまうのですか
Why do you care?
本当は愛されたいのですか
Do you actually want to be loved?
その手を離したのは誰ですか
Who was the one who let go of that hand?
気が付いてますか
Do you realize it?
人生にタイムカードがあるなら
If there were a time card for life
終わりの時間はいつなんだろう
I wonder when the clock-out time would be
私が生きた分の給料は
To whom should the salary
誰に払うのですか
For the time I've lived be paid?
サンキュー
Thank you
ありがとうと言いたいよ
I want to say thank you
サンキュー
Thank you
ありがとうと言いたいよ
I want to say thank you
サンキュー
Thank you
一度だけでもいいから
Even just once is enough
心の底から大泣きしながら
While crying from the bottom of my heart
ありがとうと言いたいよ
I want to say thank you
なぜ隠してしまうのですか
Why do you hide it?
本当は聞いて欲しいのですか
Do you actually want someone to listen?
絶対に笑ったりしないから
I definitely won't laugh
話してみませんか
So won't you try talking to me?
口を開かなければ分からない
If you don't open your mouth, I won't know
思ってるだけでは伝わらない
Just thinking it won't get through
なんて面倒くさい生き物でしょう
What a troublesome creature
人間というのは
Humans are
ハロー
Hello
ハウアーユー
How are you
ハロー
Hello
ハウアーユー
How are you
ハロー
Hello
ハウアーユー
How are you
あなたに　ハロー　ハウアーユー
To you, hello, how are you
Hi! Wah, Hello, How are you?
How are you guys? How are you people?
Oh my God! Woo!
Ini ya guys ya, ada...
So, guys, there is...
...ada satu di mana... orang-orang tuh masih kaget gitu.
...there's one thing where... people are still shocked like that.
Ada kemarin Risu nyanyi "Hello, How Are You"
Risu sang "Hello, How Are You" yesterday,
pas debut dan masih dishare sampe sekarang.
during my debut, and it's still shared now.
So people have actually just discovered...
recently discovered my, what is it... debut video...
...where Ayunda actually showed up singing "Hello, How Are You".
So for me, for me personally though, it's... it's such a...
...life-changing experience. Yeah...
Wow, I'm starting to... to sound old right now, yeah.
It's just that, without that, without that first experience,
I wouldn't be here right now...
...and you wouldn't know Ayunda or even Risu.
And why I chose that song, it's because it has like a...
what is it again... personal attachment, I guess.
So the OG... the OG would know, alright? Yes, right?
So, when I was singing the song, I... I really...
what is it again... I really tried to hold myself
to not become so teary-teary.
And also, I would like to introduce you to my room!
This is where I actually spend most of my time, 24/7.
There's El Mustache! My water bottle that's always been my friend.
Yes, the Mustache. Finally you've seen it.
Also above there, there is a framed Alice and You picture. Yes.
Also, if you like my desktop, you can share it with #AyundaRisu3D!
And also, while singing, I have showed you my bed!
I can actually sit on the bed. Hmm, we can do something nice on bed.
Bed. Bedto. Iine.
Bed. Bed. Nice.
Alright, alright. Just enough shenanigans, alright?
I will let you request some things from me, okay? Pose, pose!
Oh yeah, right! Posing!
See, you can see the tail from every angle, okay?
Look at them hips. Oh my god.
The 3D show is for my tail only, alright? You can see it.
Oh, you want me to pose? Kawaii pose? Gimana?
Oh, you want me to pose? A cute pose? How about it?
Hah... sho sho sho... hah? Are? Ada telepon? Are?
Hah... sho sho sho... hah? Huh? Is there a call? Huh?
Ada telepon guys. Are? Siapa ya? Siapa ya?
There's a call, guys. Huh? Who is it? Who is it?
Oioi, dare darou? E? Oioi?
Hey, who could it be? Eh? Hello?
Halo! Halo! Oh my god! Halo! Awas!
Hello! Hello! Oh my god! Hello! Watch out!
Halo! Ada spoiler! Halo! Siapa ya? Ada spoiler!
Hello! There's a spoiler! Hello! Who is it? There's a spoiler!
Waduh! Aku bisa melihat Anda! Waduh! Ada... ada ini!
Whoa! I can see you! Whoa! There are... there are people here!
Waduh! Bisa dilihat! Waduh! Aku dilihat! Waduh, aku malu!
Whoa! I'm being seen! Oh, I'm being watched! Oh, I'm embarrassed!
Aduh, jadi malu! Oh my god! Aduh, aku malu!
Oh, I'm getting embarrassed! Oh my god! I'm shy!
Oke, ada Ollie, Reine, dan Anya! Makasih sudah datang!
Okay, there's Ollie, Reine, and Anya! Thanks for coming!
Jadi, halo... halo... Bagaimana apa penampilan saya?
So, hello... hello... How was my performance?
Oishou... eh? Bukan... ekornya unyu banget!
The cos... eh? Not that... the tail is so cute!
Pipinya pengen kucubit!
I want to pinch those cheeks!
Berarti kita bagi tiga aja nih! Wah jangan gitu dong!
Then let's just split it into three! Hey, don't say that!
E... mau dibagi tiga? Heh...
Eh... split into three? Heh...
Untuk menghindari pencurian terhadap buntut,
To avoid the theft of my tail,
bagaimana kalau kita bermain game saja ya teman-teman?
how about we just play a game, friends?
Waduh! Dialihkan! Game pengalihan! Boleh boleh apa aja!
Whoa! Diverted! A diversion game! Sure, anything's fine!
リスびじぇスチャーゲーム！ -Charades with Risu!-
Charades with Risu!
Untuk mengalihkan isu, jadi kita akan main gesture game ya!
To divert the issue, we'll play a gesture game!
Pasti udah lumayan ngertilah gesture game ya.
You guys probably understand gesture games by now.
Jadi Risu yang pose nanti kalian yang tebak gitu.
So Risu will pose and you guys guess.
Terus ada kayak time limit-nya gitu lah.
And there's like a time limit.
Oke? Apakah kalian sudah siap?
Okay? Are you guys ready?
Siap dong! Oke kalau begitu, let's go!
Ready! Okay then, let's go!
Ronde pertama! Game starts! Huuu!
Round one! Game starts! Woohoo!
Hai, itu ngapain? Hmm, ngulak ngulak ngulak.
Hey, what is she doing? Hmm, grinding something?
Nyiramin bunga? Balapan balapan.
Watering flowers? Racing, racing.
Nyiramin bunga? Nyetir nyetir nyetir.
Watering flowers? Driving, driving, driving.
Naik odong-odong?
Riding an odong-odong ride?
Vroom tututututututututut.
Nge-drift?
Drifting?
Bajaj bajaj? Pip pip pip pip!
A bajaj? Beep beep beep beep!
Nyetir motor? Isekai isekai isekai!
Riding a motorcycle? Isekai, isekai!
Vroooooom!
Nyetir truk? Supir supir?
Driving a truck? Driver, driver?
Ut ut ut ut ut!
Supir supir? Truk supir truk?
Driver, driver? Truck, truck driver?
Wah bener! Woooo!
Wow, that's right! Woooo!
答え トラック運転手 -Truck Driver-
Answer: Truck Driver
Yey! Mantap!
Yay! Great!
Nah jadi jadi begitu teman-teman cara mainnya.
So that's how we play, friends.
Oke? Udah pada ngerti? Oke, oke.
Okay? Do you get it? Okay, okay.
Sudah? Kalau udah ngerti, siap-siap.
Ready? If you understand, get ready.
Next next... mmm, Risu sedang memikirkan apa ya, next?
Next next... mmm, Risu is thinking about what's next.
Baiklah kalian mau mau mau mau... next next?
Alright, do you want to... go next?
Next next next next! Next next!
Let's go!
Oke next next negis... Waduh, oke.
Okay, next next negis... Whoops, okay.
Round two! Game start!
Tak! Hut! Tatatatatatatatatata!
Hah apa itu? Lari lari?
Huh, what's that? Running?
Itu kayak... larinya itu...
It's like... the way she's running...
Lari lari? Eh eh eh?
Running? Eh eh eh?
Iya kan? Apa?
Right? What?
Apa? Apakah?
What? Is it?
Yang netral, yang netral, yang netral.
Something neutral, something neutral.
Ninja! Iya ninja!
Ninja! Yeah, ninja!
Lari anime? Apa tadi? Raini?
Anime run? What was it? Raini?
Ninja ninja! Yey!
Ninja, ninja! Yay!
答え 忍者 -Ninja-
Answer: Ninja
Ninja... yang netral.
Ninja... something neutral.
Yang netral sekali ya.
It was very neutral.
Wah hebat-hebat. Wah harusnya Risu bikin...
Wow, you're good. Wow, Risu should make...
...yang susah-susah nih kalau gitu.
...it harder if that's the case.
Waduh gimana dong? Wah jangan dong.
Whoops, what should I do? No, please don't.
Masih masih pengen gak liat Risu gerak?
Do you still want to see Risu moving?
Masih ada satu lagi. Mau?
There's one more. Do you want it?
Ayo ayo masih? Mau lanjut? Lanjut gas gas!
Come on, still? Want to continue? Go go!
Round... ketiga! Oke.
Round... three! Okay.
Round three! Game start!
Wush wiuwiuwiuwiuwiuwiu!
Paah!
Wiuwiuwiu... gampang!
Wiuwiuwiu... easy!
Wiuwiu... dia memohon mantra itu?
Wiuwiu... is she casting a spell?
Main layangan? Wiuwiuwiu... Paah!
Flying a kite? Wiuwiuwiu... Paah!
Itu menyihir orang?
Is that bewitching someone?
Iya kayak menyihir orang. Iya bener kayak gitu kan?
Yeah, like bewitching someone. Right?
Iya gak sih? Wush wush wush!
Isn't it? Wush wush wush!
Uuuh sedikit lagi!
Ooh, almost there!
Wizard? Hmm?
Bener! Oh wizard! Yey!
Correct! Oh, wizard! Yay!
答え 魔法使い -Sorceress-
Answer: Sorceress
Jadi yang bener itu wizard! Oh wiiih!
So the correct answer is wizard! Oh wiiih!
Penyihir, penyihir. Wah penyihir. Oke oke.
Sorceress, sorceress. Wow, sorceress. Okay okay.
Aku sihir kamu jadi 3D! Wah!
I'll bewitch you into 3D! Whoa!
Ayo dong ayo dong mau dong! Aku minta Intayago ya.
Come on, I want it! I'm asking for Intayago.
Masih gepeng ya? Kok aku masih gepeng ya?
Still flat? Why am I still flat?
Hmm kalau begitu teman-teman, terima kasih sudah mau bermain...
Hmm, well then friends, thank you for playing...
...bersama Risu dan melihat penampilan Risu malam ini.
...with Risu and watching Risu's performance tonight.
Terima katsy! Muah!
Thank you! Muah!
Lucu banget! Pipinya itu...
So cute! Those cheeks...
...aduh pipinya itu. Muah muah muah!
...oh, those cheeks. Muah muah muah!
Kalau begitu, kalau begitu...
Well then, well then...
Mohon maaf teman-teman, saya usir kalian ya! Hahaha!
I'm sorry friends, I'm kicking you out! Hahaha!
Sampai jumpa! Dadah semuanya! Jenne!
See you! Bye everyone! See ya!
Oke! Good job mantap! Bye bye!
Okay! Good job, great! Bye bye!
Risu-senpai, good luck! Wah wah wah!
Risu-senpai, good luck! Whoa whoa whoa!
Keren keren keren! Wah!
Cool, cool, cool! Wow!
Wah bersemangat guys! Walaupun begini-begini...
Whoa, excited guys! Even though it's like this...
...masih bersemangat ya teman-teman.
...you're still excited, friends.
Tadi tadi udah kan Ninja run?
We did the Ninja run earlier, right?
Kalian kalian udah lihat. You've seen.
You've seen it. You've seen.
I've fulfilled my promise to do Ninja run, okay?
So because I've moved a lot already, I think I'm...
...I haven't got dinner, so I'm actually kind of hungry.
Alright?
So I'm trying to find some nuts, alright?
Ah ada kacang ya? Aduh lapar banget nih aduh.
Ah, there are nuts? Man, I'm so hungry.
Holi! Holi! Holi! Holi!
Ah kacang-kacang! Guys, kalian!
Ah, nuts! Guys, you!
Ini ada kesempatan emas teman-teman apabila kalian ingin...
This is a golden opportunity friends if you want to...
...memberikan Risu kacang tentu saja dengan Super Chat...
...give Risu nuts, of course with Super Chat...
...kalian bisa memberikan kacang yang banyak sekarang juga.
...you can give a lot of nuts right now.
Waktu kalian ya teman-teman! Jangan lupa tagar AyundaRisu3D...
It's your time, friends! Don't forget the hashtag AyundaRisu3D...
...dan berikan kacang lebih banyak biar Risu bisa makan bentar.
...and give more nuts so Risu can eat for a bit.
Lebih banyak dong wey! Masih dikit doang! Eh!
Give more! Still so few! Hey!
Risu tunggu ya, Risu tunggu ya. Satu dua tiga...
Risu will wait, Risu will wait. One, two, three...
...give me more nuts, alright? Give me, give me more nuts please!
Thank you, thank you, thank you! I will, I will eat the nuts now...
...I will eat your nuts, okay? This is from you.
Emm.
Mmm.
This... this nut's from you, alright?
I'ma eat it.
How... how do you feel having
your nuts being eaten by me, alright?
I will... I will start eating.
Wareg!
I'm full!
Wareg apa, guys? Wareg kacang!
Full of what, guys? Full of nuts!
I'm full of your nuts.
That sounds so wrong, oh my goodness gracious!
Alright, alright, alright, I've eaten your nuts, alright?
But... I've seen... I've seen something suspicious right there.
Alright, I'ma... I'ma take you for a while now.
I'ma... I'll take this!
Jadi, jadi ya temen-temen, kemarin, kemarin itu kan Risu kan abis dari tempatnya Moona ya.
So, so friends, yesterday,
Risu went to Moona's place.
Ah, jadi tuh... Risu tuh dapet oleh-oleh yang mana Risu ambil sendiri sih oleh-olehnya ya.
Ah, so... Risu got a souvenir,
which Risu actually took herself.
Jadi karena... sekarang tuh kebetulan lagi streaming 3D ya, jadi...
So because... since this happens to be a 3D stream, so...
Kayaknya tuh... kayaknya tuh seru gitu kalau Risu hitung ya apa sih isi celengannya gitu. Oke? Oke?
I think... it'd be fun if Risu counts
what's inside the piggy bank. Okay? Okay?
Ada berapa banyak ya kira-kira? Mari kita hitung temen-temen.
How many are there approximately?
Let's count, friends.
Satu!
One!
Dua!
Two!
Tiga!
Three!
RISU!
Moona, Iofi! Open up!
Risu-nya lagi nggak ada!
Risu's not here right now!
RISU!
Buka!
Open up!
MOONA!
Ini ada yang maling di sebelah aku kayaknya.
It seems like there's a thief next to me.
Sabar, sabar, Risu buka dulu ntar dulu.
Wait, wait, let Risu open up first.
AAA! TOLONG! TOLONG!
AAA! HELP! HELP!
Nggak boleh gitu!
You can't do that!
Nggak boleh! Sini! Sini!
You can't! Come here! Come here!
Ah... udah... oke, kan bilangnya juga di kamar aku nggak ada.
Ah... alright... I said I wasn't in my room.
Ternyata ini!
It turns out it's this!
Kamu sih aku kan jadi dilabrak sama Moona tahu nggak?
Because of you, Moona confronted me, you know?
Ih... susah-susah maret tahu nggak? Susah-susah maret!
I worked hard saving that, you know? Worked hard!
Kapan kamu ambil celengannya?
When did you take the piggy bank?
Kemarin pas bawa...
Yesterday when bringing...
Parah! Parah!
Terrible! Terrible!
Ini isinya ada berapa? Isinya ada berapa?
How much is inside? How much is inside?
Tadi baru tiga doang sih, tapi masih banyak. Jangan bilang-bilang.
It was only three just now, but there's
still a lot. Don't tell anyone.
Oh gitu ya! Moona lagi bokek!
Oh is that so! Moona is broke right now!
Nih mau ambil? Ambil nggak?
Here, want to take it? Are you taking it?
Aku nggak tahu apa-apa!
I don't know anything!
Nggak tahu apa-apa!
Aku nggak ikut-ikutan!
I'm not involved!
Risu!
Oke, oke, ma-maaf nanti, nanti Risu... oke, kan tadi bercanda, jadi...
Okay, okay, sorry, later, Risu... okay,
it was a joke earlier, so...
Risu akan beli yang lebih bagus. Oke? Yang baru. Iya, yang lebih bagus, lebih gede, iya!
Risu will buy a better one. Okay? A new one.
Yes, a better, bigger one, yes!
Bener?
Really?
Betul!
Correct!
Oke, oke, oke. Sama makanan ya?
Okay, okay, okay. And food too, right?
Oke! Siap! Oke!
Okay! Ready! Okay!
Aman guys, aman, aman.
It's safe guys, safe, safe.
Aduh... harus disogok dulu guys.
Man... have to bribe her first, guys.
Nggak apa-apalah, happy. Sering-sering aja kalau kita nggak bokek.
It's okay, as long as we're happy. Do it
often as long as we're not broke.
Bokek nanti Risu-nya.
Then Risu will be the broke one.
Nggak apa-apa. Kebetulan ya karena kan udah seneng nih, udah seneng ya.
It's fine. Since we're happy now,
we're happy.
Oke, jadi kebetulan kita bertiga, bagaimana kalau kita menyanyikan... Mars kita bertiga?
Okay, since the three of us are here, how
about we sing... our trio's anthem?
Boleh!
Sure!
Oke kalau gitu!
Okay then!
Yuk nyanyi bareng, HI-15!
Let's sing together, HI-15!
Gambarisu!
Moon-moon, Moona desu yo!
Moon-moon, it's Moona!
Yoporya! Obisisa!
HUOOO!
La la la la, area HI-15.
La la la la, bersama selalu.
La la la la, HI-15 area.
La la la la, always together.
Tiap aku jahilin kamu.
Every time I prank you.
Percayalah itu tanda suka padamu.
Believe that it's a sign I like you.
Kau kira ku tak menyadari.
You thought I didn't realize.
Sesungguhnya ku tahu tapi kuikuti mau.
Actually I knew, but I went along with it.
Kita kita semua selamanya bersama kian hari semakin sayang.
All of us, together forever,
loving each other more every day.
Saat air mata jatuh sekejap lagi.
When tears fall in a moment.
Kau genggam tanganku saling memandang.
You hold my hand, looking at each other.
Semua sudah siapkah? Ayo beraksi!
Kasih semangat! Yuk bisa yuk!
Is everyone ready? Let's take action!
Give it some spirit! Let's go, we can do it!
Let's go friends, kita bersama merajut
kisah yang happy happy.
Let's go friends, we're together knitting
a story that's happy happy.
Ku buka semua impian dan keberanian,
ayo maju selangkah jangan sampai menyerah.
I open up all dreams and courage,
let's take a step forward, don't give up.
Walaupun jalannya masih jauh dan gelap,
suatu hari pasti...
Even though the road is still far and dark,
one day for sure...
Perasaan ini kan ku sampaikan kepadamu.
I will convey this feeling to you.
Hingga hari ini...
Until this day...
...menjadi satu
...becoming one
La la la Area 15
Hingga hari ini...
Until this day...
Mimpi yang terwujud
Dreams come true
La la la Area 15
La la la...
La la la let's say cheers
Rasa rindu sehabis menangis
Feeling of longing after crying
Jangan biasakan kerna nanti menyesal
Don't get used to it or you'll regret it
Yo bikin kan sekali lagi
Yo, let's make it one more time
Mungkin saja itu tidak disimpan sendiri
Maybe it's not meant to be kept to oneself
Menari di Wonderland
Dancing in Wonderland
Kita kita semua
All of us
Paling asik di dunia ini
Most fun in this world
Seakan sedih yang datang melanda hati
As if sadness comes and strikes the heart
Lewat layar itu bagi senyuman
Sharing smiles through that screen
Percuma saja tidak masalah dalam dunia penuh masalah u check it out
It's useless but it's okay in a world full of problems, you check it out
Kebahagiaan di hati...
Happiness in the heart...
Wui! Hingga hari ini...
Wui! Until this day...
...menjadi satu
...becoming one
La la la Area 15
Hingga hari ini...
Until this day...
Mimpi yang terwujud
Dreams come true
La la la Area 15
La la la...
La la la let's say cheers
Ayo chat
Let's chat
Ayo song
Let's song
Ayo mimpi
Let's dream
Eh tapi
But wait
Gak jadi
Never mind
Maaf ya
Sorry
Gak apa-apa
It's okay
Sama-sama
You're welcome
Kusayang
I love you
You love me
Sayang kan semua
Love everyone
Ayo mulai tu-wa-ga-pat let's la-la-la
Let's start, one-two-three-four, let's la-la-la
Apabila suatu hari mimpi-mimpiku...
If one day my dreams...
...akan terkabul
...come true
Semoga kita semua lebih banyak lagi
I hope we all get much more
Menangis dan tertawa bersama selamanya
Crying and laughing together forever
Akhirnya mulai terlihat...
Finally, starting to appear...
...hari-hari cerah yang kita impikan
...the bright days we dreamed of
Inilah saatnya daku...
This is the moment for me...
...kusampaikan kepadamu perasaanku
...to express my feelings to you
Dalam hari panas dalam hari dingin...
In hot days and cold days...
...ayolah kita lebih sering bicara
...let's talk more often
Saat hari cerah saat hari hujan...
On sunny days and rainy days...
...ayolah lebih sering bermain
...let's play more often
La la la Area 15
La la la...
La la la Bersama selalu
La la la Always together
La la la...
La la la Area 15
La la la let's say cheers
Wui! Wui! Riri! Riri! Yah! Akhirnya!
Wui! Wui! Riri! Riri! Yeah! Finally!
Oh my god... Akhirnya kita bercanda ria Pargoy!
Oh my god... Finally we're having fun doing Pargoy!
Gimana gimana tadi gimana?
How was it, how was it just now?
Dururururururururururu...
Heh guys! Halo semuanya!
Hey guys! Hello everyone!
Mantap sekali teman-teman terima kasih.
That was awesome, friends, thank you.
Wah ini kita bertiga nih. Yeay! Uhuy!
Wow, here we are, the three of us. Yay! Uhuy!
Kalau begitu, bagaimana menurut kalian kamar Risu?
In that case, what do you think of Risu's room?
Kamar Risu kawaii? Surprisingly...
Is Risu's room cute? Surprisingly...
...it's so rapi. Kok tumben rapi?
...it's so neat. Why is it so neat for once?
Heh, tumben banget rapi.
Heh, it's very neat for once.
Risu saya jauh-jauh ya dari sana...
Risu, I came all the way from there...
...kok gak ada comot-comotnya.
...but there's no mess at all.
Eh, Risu tuh yang paling rapi.
Hey, Risu is the neatest one.
Comot-comotnya gak ada.
There's no mess.
Woi woi woi... Comot-comotnya ilang!
Whoa whoa whoa... The mess is gone!
Comot-comotnya ilang! Woi comot-comotnya!
The mess is gone! Hey, the mess!
Gak ada! Udah udah pulang-pulang udah!
It's gone! Alright, alright, go home already!
Ih kok gitu sih? Hehe... Mau ambil air.
Huh, why are you like that? Hehe... I'm going to get some water.
Ya udah makasih udah datang. Jangan lupa mampir lagi ya guys.
Alright, thanks for coming. Don't forget to stop by again, guys.
See you next time! Don't forget, I love you too!
I love you too! Muah!
Aduh anjay, serem-serem banget guys.
Oh man, that was really scary, guys.
Nah kalau begitu teman-teman, karena sudah ada Iofi sama Moona...
Now, in that case, friends, since Iofi and Moona were here...
...saatnya kita touch the grass.
...it's time for us to touch the grass.
Okay, we're going outside. We're gonna touch the grass for a while...
...because stuck in the room always is not really good, alright?
...because staying stuck in the room all the time is not really good, alright?
So, mari kita jalan-jalan keluar! Ikuyo!
So, let's go for a walk outside! Let's go!
Wui wui wui wui wui... Wah, I'm here now.
Wui wui wui wui wui... Wow, I'm here now.
Yes, we're outside! We're outside! Yes!
Akhirnya guys, kita keluar.
Finally, guys, we're outside.
Jadi tuh, ada tujuannya kenapa Risu mau keluar.
So, there's a reason why Risu wanted to come out.
Jadi Risu tuh mau ngeliatin ya, kira-kira tuh hutan ajaib Risu tuh seperti apa.
So, Risu wants to show you what Risu's magical forest looks like.
Ini tuh kira-kira penampilannya ya mirip-mirip kayak ginilah gitu.
Its appearance is something like this.
So my magical forest looks kind of like this.
I just want to show you the beautiful scenery.
Yes, 私のマジカルフォレストはね...
Yes, my magical forest...
...とっても綺麗なんだけど...
...is very beautiful, but...
...あの、怖いところもあったよ。
...well, there were scary parts too.
あれ？ あれ？
Huh? Huh?
どうしたのかな、こんなところに迷子の小リスさんかな？
What's wrong, I wonder? A lost little squirrel in a place like this?
あれ？ リスザウルス。
Huh? Risusaurus.
いや、私リスザウルスだよ。 え、本当？
No, I'm Risusaurus. Eh, really?
可愛い。
Cute.
私リスザウルス、みんな...
I'm Risusaurus, everyone...
可愛いけど怪しい。なんで？！
Cute but suspicious. Why?!
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
リスちゃんが3Dだって聞いたから、今日は来たの。
I heard Risu-chan is 3D, so I came today.
え、来たんだ！
Oh, you came!
あれ、リスザウルス、ありがとう。
Wait, Risusaurus, thank you.
けど、これはリスザウルスじゃないな、じゃないみたいだね。
But, this isn't Risusaurus, it doesn't look like it.
リスザウルスだよ。
It is Risusaurus.
あれ？ いや、この声はね、この声はね、もしかして、もしかして...
Huh? No, this voice... this voice... could it be, could it be...
オウガさんですか？
Oga-san?
え？
Eh?
オウガさんだよね？
You're Oga-san, right?
え？
Eh?
やっぱりオウガさんだよね！
It really is Oga-san!
なんとか成れ！
Become something!
どうも。
Greetings.
こんばんは。
Good evening.
はいはい。
Yes, yes.
あら、リスちゃん、3Dおめでとうございます。
Oh, Risu-chan, congratulations on your 3D.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロスターズ三期生、荒咬オウガ、
Holostars 3rd Gen, Aragami Oga,
ゲストで参戦です。
joining as a guest.
リスちゃん、どう？
Risu-chan, how is it?
ほら、リスちゃん、これ。
Look, Risu-chan, this.
え、駄目だよ。私、私、あの...
Eh, no way. I... I, um...
私のあの、リスザウルス、ちょっと取ってくるね。
My, um, Risusaurus, I'll go get it.
あら、待って。
Oh, wait.
やあ、あたしリスザウルスだよ。
Hi, I'm Risusaurus.
あたしも生まれたよ！
I was born too!
これ見て！
Look at this!
あ、リスザウルス。
Ah, Risusaurus.
あ、同じ。
Oh, the same.
同じだよ！
The same!
同じリスザウルスが。
The same Risusaurus...
そうそうそう。
Right, right, right.
ね、可愛い。
See, it's cute.
可愛い。
Cute.
え、これ何すんの、じゃあ。
Eh, what are we doing then,
リスザウルスおったら。
since we have Risusaurus?
あ、これね、リスザウルスはね、
Ah, this, Risusaurus is,
あの、オウガさんからのプレゼント。
um, a present from Oga-san.
そうそうそう、可愛いですよね。
Yes, yes, yes, it's cute, isn't it?
とっても可愛い。
Very cute.
ねー。
Right.
あ、そしたらね、あの、この二人が揃ったらね、
Oh, then, um, since these two are together,
あれを歌うしかないよね。
we have to sing that, don't we?
まさか、あれを歌うのか？
No way, we're singing that?
はい、そうそう。あれ、あの、はらぱんぱんぱん。
Yes, exactly. That, um, Harapan Pan Pan Pan.
歌うか。
Let's sing.
はらぱんぱんぱん はらぱんぱんぱん
Harapan pan pan pan, harapan pan pan pan
踊りだしたくなる 摩訶不思議な毎日で
In these wondrous days that make me want to dance
はらぱんぱんぱん はらぱんぱんぱん
Harapan pan pan pan, harapan pan pan pan
めくるめくこの世界で かなえましょう はらぱんぱんぱん
In this dazzling world, let's make it come true, harapan pan pan pan
はらぱんぱんぱん はらぱんぱんぱん
Harapan pan pan pan, harapan pan pan pan
踊りだしたくなる 手を叩きましょう ぱんぱんぱんぱん
Making me want to dance, let's clap our hands, pan pan pan pan
はらぱんぱんぱん はらぱんぱんぱん
Harapan pan pan pan, harapan pan pan pan
めくるめく毎日で また生まれ変わる はらぱんぱん
In these dazzling days, being reborn again, harapan pan pan
Harapan adalah hal yang ada di hati semua orang.
Hope is something that is in everyone's heart.
小さなはらぱん、大きなはらぱん。
Small harapan, big harapan.
神様からみんなに等しく分け与えられたはらぱん。
Harapan given equally to everyone from God.
夢のようなはらぱんも、時には怖いはらぱんも。
Harapan like a dream, sometimes scary harapan too.
例えば私のはらぱんは、歌、いたずら、どんぐり、ナッツ、
For example, my harapan is: songs, mischief, acorns, nuts,
おはよう、コロネ、ほかコロネ。
good morning, Korone, Boga Korone.
そして俺のはらぱんは、美味いもの全般、かっこいいもの全般、
And my harapan is: delicious things in general, cool things in general,
イラストにゲーム、ゲーム、ゲーム、ゲーム！
illustrations and games, games, games, games!
さあ爽やかな願い事 積もり積もって
Now refreshing wishes pile up
世界を丸ごと染め上げちゃおう
Let's dye the whole world completely
私のはらぱん 俺のはらぱん
My harapan, your harapan
二つ合わせてはらはらぱんぱん
Combine the two, hara hara pan pan
願いを叶えて見せましょう
Let's show we can grant the wishes
二人のはらぱん 共にのはらぱん
The two's harapan, shared harapan
ぎゅっとまとめて はらぱんぱんぱん
Tie it all together, harapan pan pan pan
はらぱんぱんぱん はらぱんぱんぱん
Harapan pan pan pan, harapan pan pan pan
踊りだしたくなる 手を叩きましょう ぱんぱんぱんぱん
Making me want to dance, let's clap our hands, pan pan pan pan
はらぱんぱんぱん はらぱんぱんぱん
Harapan pan pan pan, harapan pan pan pan
めくるめく毎日で また生まれ変わる はらぱんぱん
In these dazzling days, being reborn again, harapan pan pan
ねえねえ見て見て！ 綺麗な星はらぱん。
Hey hey, look look! A beautiful star harapan.
はは、本当だね。
Haha, you're right.
そうだ、あの流れはらぱんに3回、はらぱんぱんぱんって言ったら、
Oh, I heard that if you say 'harapan pan pan pan' three times to that shooting star,
はらぱんが叶うそうだよ。
your harapan will come true.
本当？ じゃあ、どんなはらぱんにしようかな？
Really? Then, what kind of harapan should I make?
この先どんな困難があっても、
No matter what difficulties lie ahead,
二人がいつまでも幸せなはらぱんを持てますように。
I wish that the two of us can always have happy harapan.
コロネ、コロネ、コロネ、オカコロネ...
Korone, Korone, Korone, Okakoro...
Ada harapan yang cerah dan ada harapan yang mendung.
There's bright hope and there's cloudy hope.
神様からみんなに等しく分け与えられたはらぱん ぱんぱん。
Harapan given equally to everyone from God, pan pan.
あなたもあなただけの特別なはらぱんを持って。
You too, take your own special harapan.
このめくるめく世界に鮮やかな彩りを。
In this dazzling world, a brilliant color.
本当に大事なのはたった一つだけ。
The only thing that is truly important is just one thing.
はらはら 明日のことはわからないけど
Hara hara, I don't know about tomorrow, but
私のはらぱん 俺のはらぱん
My harapan, your harapan
力を合わせてはらはらぱんぱん
Joining forces, hara hara pan pan
何でもできる気がするんだ
I feel like I can do anything
二人のはらぱん 共にのはらぱん
The two's harapan, shared harapan
ここから始まるはらぱんぱん
Starting from here, harapan pan pan
カリスマ的最高歌姫
The charismatic supreme diva
私のはらぱん 俺のはらぱん
My harapan, your harapan
人生丸ごとはらはらぱんぱん
Life as a whole, hara hara pan pan
君の幸せ また願って
Wishing for your happiness again
二人のはらぱん 永遠にはらぱん
The two's harapan, forever harapan
これからもよろしくね はらぱんぱんぱん
Let's stay in touch from now on, harapan pan pan pan
はらぱんぱんぱん はらぱんぱんぱん
Harapan pan pan pan, harapan pan pan pan
踊りだしたくなる 手を叩きましょう ぱんぱんぱんぱん
Making me want to dance, let's clap our hands, pan pan pan pan
はらぱんぱんぱん はらぱんぱんぱん
Harapan pan pan pan, harapan pan pan pan
めくるめく毎日で また生まれ変わる はらぱんぱん
In these dazzling days, being reborn again, harapan pan pan
はらぱん はらぱん はらぱん はらぱん...
Harapan, harapan, harapan, harapan...
はらぱん ぱんぱんぱん...
Hara-pan pan-pan-pan...
はぁー、はらぱん はらぱん したね。
Phew, that was quite a "Hara-pan" dance.
はらぱん 凄かったよね。
The "Hara-pan" was amazing, wasn't it?
楽しかったね。
It was fun.
楽しかった、いやー。
It was fun, indeed.
あのね、私の3D配信に来てくれてありがとう。
You know, thank you so much for coming to my 3D showcase.
すごく楽しかった。
It was a lot of fun.
今から、本当にありがとうございました、本当に。
I'm truly grateful for everything, really.
でもね、やっとね、3Dなれて。
But you know, you're finally in 3D.
こうやってお披露目できて。
And being able to have this showcase.
本当に良かったなと思います。
I think it's truly wonderful.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
じゃあ、おがしゃんと今日は、あとね、3分ぐらい喋れって言われた今。
Well, today with Oga-shan... Wait, I was just told we have about 3 more minutes to talk.
また遊ぶ、これあげる。
Let's play again. Here, have this.
いや、まだね、もうちょっと喋れるんだって、どうする？
No, apparently we can still talk for a bit longer. What should we do?
もらっちゃったけど、ポーズ？ポーズ取る？
I received it, but... a pose? Should we strike a pose?
はぁー！すごい！
Waaah! Amazing!
待って待って。
Wait, wait.
どうする？どんなポーズ取る？
What now? What kind of pose should we do?
可愛いよね。
It's cute, isn't it?
私も可愛いよ。
I'm cute too!
そうだね、リスちゃんも可愛いね。
That's true, you're cute too, Risu-chan.
ほら、お尻こんな感じ。
Look, the butt looks like this.
お尻、お尻、お尻。
Butt, butt, butt.
リスちゃんも尻尾ふわふわでいいね。
Your tail is so fluffy and nice too, Risu-chan.
おがしゃん尻尾欲しい。
Oga-shan, you want a tail?
尻尾ね、ちょっと欲しいか、つくかなこれ？
A tail... I guess I want one. I wonder if it'll attach?
可愛い。
Cute.
可愛いこれ。リスちゃん嫌がってないこれ？大好き？
This is cute. Risu-chan, you don't hate this, do you? Are you okay?
なんか、なんだよ！
Like, what the heck!
あー、そうか、リスちゃん小さいね。
Ah, I see, you're really small, Risu-chan.
私ほんとに小さいね。
I'm really small, aren't I?
おがしゃんは本当に高いんですけど。
But you're really tall, Oga-shan.
ほら、ホロスターズ一でかいからな。
Well, I am the biggest in Holostars, after all.
どれぐらい高いんですか？
How tall are you?
えーとね、192センチから200メートルまで大きくなります。
Well, I'm 192cm, but I can grow up to 200 meters.
あれ、怖いじゃん。
Wait, that's scary.
ビルよりでかくなれるから。
Because I can become taller than a building.
おがビル。
Oga-Building.
でもなんか不思議な感じするな、リスちゃんとこうやって3Dで並んでると。
But it feels strange, standing next to you like this in 3D.
あのね、3Dもらったら、映画、映画作る。
You know, now that I have 3D, I'm going to make a movie.
映画？ムービー作る？
A movie? You're making a film?
あの、ワールド・ドミネーション・ムービー？
That "World Domination Movie"?
そうそう。
Yes, yes.
いいね、是非とも一緒に撮ろう。
Nice. Let's definitely film it together.
おがは、えっと何だろう、魔神、なんか。
Oga is... let's see, a demon or something.
何だろう、でかいものって何だっけ？名前？
What's that giant thing called? The name?
何だろう、巨人？
What could it be? A giant?
巨人。魔神の巨人になる。
A giant. You'll be the Demon Giant.
そして街にぶわぁーって。
And then go "Bwah!" through the city.
わかりました。じゃあ、一緒に今度ムービー撮りましょう。
Understood. Let's film a movie together next time.
これ可愛い。私なんか一回ぬいぐるみ欲しい。
This is cute. I want one of these plushies for myself.
でもね、それもう家帰りたいって言ってるから。
But you know, this one says it already wants to go home.
あ、これあげる。
Ah, here, have this.
じゃあ、こちらの二つは見てる皆さんにプレゼントするかもしれません。
Then, these two might be given away as presents to the viewers.
というわけで、今日楽しかった。ありがとね。
Anyway, it was fun today. Thanks.
またね、バイバイ！
See you later, bye-bye!
バイバイね。
Bye-bye!
楽しかった。
That was fun.
That was... that was really crazy.
That was really fun, it's...
I can't really imagine that it's actually happening right now.
凄い。はらぱんぱんぱん。
Amazing. Hara-pan-pan-pan.
And then we're going to look at the scenery a little bit more.
I'm sorry because there was an evil being before.
There's a lot of flowers and the...
the look is pretty aesthetic.
And yeah, there's a lot of pretty flowers.
綺麗ですね。
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Daphne
Ficus
Iris
Maackia
Lythrum
Myrica
Sabia
flos
Lyrics / Composition: R Sound Design
拝啓僕の願った未来よ
Dear future that I wished for
絶え間ない後悔よ
Relentless regret
体感八度五分の夢は
The dream of a 38.5 degree fever
やがて散ってしまった
Has eventually scattered away
Daphne, Vitis, Salvia...
Cyanus, Lychnis, Abelia...
Sedum, Felicia, Ochna...
Lychnis
再会　君の想いは　憂は　巡る感情論は
Reunion. Your thoughts, your grief,
the revolving emotional arguments...
半径85センチの
Within this 85-centimeter radius
世界に　囚われたまま
remaining trapped in this world.
本音を挿し　微笑（わら）い合った今日
Stabbing our true feelings,
smiling at each other today,
溢れた色彩に
amidst the overflowing colors.
薪（まき）をくべて風に乗せて
Stoking the fire, letting it ride the wind,
錆びた空を彩る
coloring the rusted sky.
濁った日々を丁寧に
Carefully tending to these muddy days,
飾った花はすぐに枯れていく
the flowers I used to decorate them
soon wither away.
不遇な僕は夢から醒めて
Unlucky as I am, I wake from the dream,
縋（すが）った意味も無い、ない、ない、ない
and there was no meaning in clinging to it,
none at all.
君が僕にくれた声も　色も
The voice you gave me, the colors,
揺るぎない愛情も
and your unwavering affection,
二人きりの空に向かった星も
even the stars we watched in our private sky,
とうに散ってしまった
have long since scattered.
何時の末（すえ）も　温もりの冷えに
At the end of time, in the cooling of warmth,
季節は色褪せて
the seasons fade.
熱を帯びて身を震わせて
Gaining heat, body trembling,
擦れた街に零れる
spilling out into the worn-out streets.
荒（すさ）んだ日々を丁寧に
Carefully following these bleak days,
辿った先に花が咲くはず
flowers should bloom at the end of the path.
不遇な君は夢を見たまま
Unlucky as you are, still dreaming,
悟った振りで水を注いだ
you poured water while pretending to understand.
木漏れ日の中に　柔らかく咲いた
Blooming softly in the sunlight
filtering through trees,
花は雲の上で
the flowers are above the clouds,
散った星で夢の先で
at the scattered stars, beyond the dream,
揺れてる
they are swaying.
濁った日々を丁寧に
Carefully tending to these muddy days,
飾った花はすぐに枯れていく
the flowers I used to decorate them
soon wither away.
不遇な僕は夢から醒めて
Unlucky as I am, I wake from the dream,
縋った意味も無い、ない、ない、ない
and there was no meaning in clinging to it,
none at all.
不毛な日々を丁寧に
Carefully on those barren days,
綴った紙に花を描いた
I drew flowers on the paper I wrote on.
不遇な僕ら夢に当てられて
Unlucky as we are, struck by the dream,
誓った筈も無かった事にしたい
I want to pretend that our oaths
never happened.
Daphne, Vitis, Iris, Maackia...
Lysurun, Melica, Salvia...
Cyanus, Lychnis, Abelia, Sedum...
Felicia, Ochna, Lychnis
Daphne, Vitis, Iris, Maackia...
Lysurun, Melica, Salvia...
Cyanus, Lychnis, Abelia, Sedum...
Felicia, Ochna, Lychnis...
flos
Hooa... flos. flos ni, wa wa wa.
Whoa... flos. flos, wow.
Ayunda! There's a lot of Ayunda in flos, huh?
Ayunda, can you say hi? Hi!
(Laughs) Yes, Ayunda came too, you know?
Wah! Wah!
flos is my, um, like I've explained to you before really back...
flos was my comfort song. And there's a lot of Ayunda in there...
Because the original cover of my flos is full Risu, right?
So I'm giving you more Ayunda. So so so.
D-D-D-Ayunda in action. Here, you want to see? Oh, before that...
I would like to, um... What do you call this? Mic. So so so.
Yes, I want to show you my mic.
This is the mic that I personally designed since my debut.
So this is the "Nut Mic". (Laughs)
I sing on your nuts! (Laughs)
So yeah, this is the mic that I, uh...
Ra-ra-ra-ra-ra, yes, yes, yes!
Yes, that's the... emojis.
Yes, use that. Thank you!
Also, once again, use hashtag AyundaRisu3D.
Don't be as bewitched by my performance, okay?
うわっ、すごい！うわっ！うわっ！
Whoa, amazing! Whoa! Whoa!
うわっ、トレンドになったよ！すごい！
Whoa, it's trending! Amazing!
Jadi trending guys, Ayunda gaming.
It's trending guys, Ayunda gaming.
Wah bahasa gamernya keluar, gila gila gila keren keren.
Wow, the gamer speak is coming out. Crazy, crazy, crazy, cool, cool.
Thank you. Share more #AyundaRisu3D Twitter, alright?
Okay? Okay? Yes, yes, yes.
Also, you want to see Ayunda in action, 3D Ayunda in action once in a lifetime, alright?
はい、どうも。
Hello there.
アユンダです。はーい。
This is Ayunda. Hi.
Hai, hai, hello everybody. I am Ayunda.
Thank you so much for watching us, Ayunda and Risu.
Like until now we kind... we can finally get 3D.
うわっ、3Dすごいね。うわっ。
Whoa, 3D is amazing, right? Whoa.
And also, while being Ayunda I would like to... what is it?
I would like to tell you a little bit of an announcement.
Yes, what is the announcement, Risu?
So, the announcement is... yes...
...later there will be a mini live, yes...
...collab of Gen 1 Hololive Indonesia, alright?
So here's the announcement! Jajannn! Woo!
うわっ、すごいすごい！うわっ！
Whoa, amazing, amazing! Whoa!
I look very safe! So, sugoi ne!
I look very safe! So, amazing, right?
Mini 3D Live Stream, hololive Indonesia 1st Generation
That... that may be Ayunda, right? Right Ayunda?
Yes, I think that's me. (laughs)
ね？うわっ、清楚そうだね。
Right? Whoa, seems so pure.
Mature, you look so mature. I mean, I look so mature. Thank you Ayunda.
You're welcome.
Yes, also the live, mini 3D live will be on...
...20 September, same time, 8 PM.
Yes, don't miss it, alright? Okay?
Yes, that's the announcement. そう、そう、そう。うわっ、すごいね。うわっ。
Yes, that's the announcement. Right, right, right. Whoa, amazing, right? Whoa.
うわっ、すごいね。うわっ。
Whoa, amazing, right? Whoa.
Nggak kerasa guys, ah nggak mau, nggak mau pulang, entar pamer ekor dulu lah.
Time flies guys, ah I don't want, I don't want to go home, let me show off my tail first.
Yes, yes, yes. This is my tail, so you can... you can see it...
...what is it, wiggling, oh to your heart's content.
Thank you so much, oh my god this stream is all about... about tail.
So guys, I'm sorry you need... you need to say farewell to the tail right now.
Not actually the last, but...
Jadi sebelum lagu terakhir itu ada yang ingin Risu sampaikan gitu. Yes.
So before the last song, there's something Risu wants to say. Yes.
The time I set myself here
I've decided to do my best.
All the stories, moments,
and memories we shared
are what's precious to me
The supports I've received
are what keeps me going
and made me who I am today
I can only convey my feelings
through limited words
but this feeling of gratitude
is real...
Thanks for being with me
throughout my journey
This is a beginning of a new chapter
in a path that is forged
by wishes, hardwork,
and lots of support
for you, Risunes,
I've made this song
Let the time
send this song
to more people
as we wished for it
Sing it out together
Our hopes...
Our dream...
Surely...
it will reach the sky.
While my eyes still see nearby
your soul start to fade...
...unleash your magic to me.
Now it's time not to worry, do believe in me.
A journey we have to see.
Lodira lodira incomplete melody.
Sung with a sweet but yet a sad symphony.
An ever-rings spirit that you told me.
How can I do it when you're not even here?
Oh, let me...
...let out all words I could say to you right now.
I can only tell you a bit of overwhelm...
...with your kindest assistance that I could
never ever trade with anything.
Let the time send this song to your ears.
I hope one day you will sing it to me.
Words to the melody that I tried to write...
...for you.
Day by day I will pray my heart keeps on reaching...
...the sky.
In a time full of worries, no light I could see.
Do you want me to be here?
Knowing all the emotions you're supposed to feel...
...even voice I want to hear.
Shalala shalila incomplete melody.
Arriving in your ears like it's destiny.
Lodira lodira incomplete memories.
Showing all the warmth that I have ever feel.
Yeah...
Sing out!
遥かな記憶
Distant memories
空に
In the sky
響き渡る
Resonating
結晶の欠片たちは
The fragments of crystals
今、願いに至る
Now, reach the wish
あなたの喜びを願う
I pray for your happiness
Lodira lodira incomplete melody.
Has been sung in the worlds so far you can't see.
Let the wind, let the sea carry this melody...
...legacy of a song that carry all the wish.
I believe.
All the words I could say right now,
I can only tell you about it to be...
...overwhelmed with your kindest assistance...
...that I could never ever trade with anything.
Let the time send this song to your ears.
I hope one day you will sing it to me.
Words to the melody that I tried to write...
Every day I will sing it loud and now
I will try to shine.
こんな声でも響け
Even with a voice like this, let it resonate
Terima kasih...
Thank you...
...untuk semua...
...for all...
...perhatian...
...the attention...
...yang telah kau berikan.
...that you have given.
A gentle breeze through your soul,
This time I believe,
everything will be fine.
Every day I will sing it aloud,
This is my time to shine!
Thank you for watching my 3D debut!
I hope you enjoyed the show.
Without you, there will be no Ayunda Risu.
Let's do more fun things from now on as well!!
GanbaRisu!
- Ayunda Risu -