(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
今日の3Dお披露目はー？
Today's 3D showcase is...?
ラオーラが3Dで初登場！
Raora makes her 3D debut!!
My tail!
チャッティーニランドにやってきたラオーラが
Raora Arrives at Chattini Land, and...
ジェットパックを賭けてミニゲームで大暴れ！
Unleashes Chaos in Mini-Games for a jetpack!
泣いて
Tears!
Please, please, give me the ticket!
怒って
Rage!
I'm done! I'm so done! I'm leaving!
セクシーなラオーラも見れちゃう！
You can even see a sexy Raora!
もちろん、歌も歌っちゃうよ！
Of course, she'll sing too!
先輩とケンカもしちゃって
Having fights with her senpai,
ジェットパックは手に入るのかな？
Will she get the jetpack?
ラオーラ・パンテーラの3Dお披露目、始まるよ！
Raora Panthera's 3D showcase, starting now!
Ciao-ra!
Are you recording me?
Ah, where should I look? Where should I look?
Hah! What is this place?
Hah! Oh my gosh! That's a...
...that's a giant Chattino in the castle!
Oh my gosh!
And look at the one in the fountain, it's so pretty!
And there's another one over there! Another one!
Hah! Wait a second.
Is this... is this...
...is this Chattini Land?
Whoa! That's so cool!
Ah, hey, hey cameraman! Come here, come here!
How do I look in 3D? Huh?
Hey, you should take a look too...
You should take a look to my Chattino!
Look at him! Isn't he so pretty?
So cute, right?
Ah! And you also should take a look to...
...my tail! Hoo!
Big cat means big tail!
Hah! What do you think? How do I look?
Hey, hey, hey! Whoa!
Ah... oh...
What did you do? Ah...
Come here! I'm gonna use my weapon!
You come here! Ah, now! How dare you!
ちょっと待って！！ 伝えたいことがあるんだ！
Wait a second!! I need to tell you something!
How dare you knock me off like this! Huh?
Eh? You can... you can talk?
Oh, that's impressive.
Well, I'm guessing...
...you need me for something? What do you need?
そうなんだ。 欲しいものがあるんだけど… ミニゲームをクリアしないと手に入らないんだ！
Yeah. There's this thing we want, but... You can only get it by clearing all the Mini-Games!
Eh? Mini-games?
Something you can only get here by clearing mini-games?
Eh, I think I know what it is.
あれ… あそこのやつ！
It's... that thing over there!
Eh? Eh? Eh? Hah!
Ah! I knew it! It's a jetpack!
Oh, the Chattini want one so badly, right?
僕たちだけじゃ無理なんだ。 だからラオーラ、手伝って！
We can't get it on our own. So help us out Raora! Please!
Ah, are you begging me?
Well, you know, little one...
No.
I told you I'm not giving you the jetpack.
So, I'm leaving! Bye-bye! Ciao-ciao!
お願い！ お願い！ おねがーーい！
Please! Please! Pleeeease!
Hey, are you following me? Oh...
Well, I guess it's a special day after all.
Hmm...
You know what? I'll give it a shot.
やったーー！
Yaaaaaay!
Haha, okay! Well then, what should I do here?
ゲームはこのエリアにあるよ。 がんばってね！
The game's in this area of the land, so good luck!
Okay then, I'm gonna do my very best.
Well, I shall go then.
Gamba-Raora! Rawr!
Waaah!
あ、ちょっと待って。 正しい道はあっちだよ。
Oh, wait. The right way is over there.
Eh? Eh? Eh? I mean...
Ah! I'm heading out! Gamba-Raora! Rawr!
この番組は、ご覧のスポンサーの提供でお送りいたします。
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってのん？
Are you gonna do pure, pure things until you die?
Love, bluh-bluh-bluh-bluh-bluh-bluh-bluh-bluh
ラブとライク パーティションはない、ない
Between love and like, there is no partition
君だけが特別じゃないんだ
You're not the only one who's special
反省とか私に求められても
Even if you ask me to reflect on myself
本当、やんわり勘違いしないで
Seriously, don't get the wrong idea
で？で？で？
So? So? So?
どうしてなんで期待の戸締り忘れるの？
Why do you keep forgetting to lock out expectations?
正直なほどやめ時なんてあったじゃん
There was a time to stop as long as you were honest
お嬢様、あちらが出口ですが
Young lady, the exit is that way
やっぱ、帰りたくないですか？
But you don't want to go home, do you?
ホップ ステップ ワンモアチャンス！
Hop, step, one more chance!
もうやっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Anyway, it's fine to show off and rabbit hole
ポップな愛嬌振りまいたらいいじゃん
It's fine to display your poppy charm
みっともないから嫉妬しまいな
Don't be jealous, it's pathetic
発火しちゃうとかぐずぐずすんな
Don't dawdle about catching fire
寂しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone is fine
埋まればいいじゃん 埋めればいいじゃん
As long as it's filled, as long as you fill it
嫌々愛して生きたくなって
Living while reluctantly loving
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん
Being pure-pure until I die
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Anyway, it's fine to show off and rabbit hole
バッドなダンスを待ったらいいじゃん
It's fine to wait for a bad dance
やっぱり好きとかやってらんねーわ
I can't do things like 'loving' anymore
馬鹿じゃない？くっそ、雑魚いわ
Aren't you an idiot? Damn, you're weak
寂しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone is fine
埋まればいいじゃん 埋めればいいじゃん
As long as it's filled, as long as you fill it
嫌々愛して死にたくなって
Loving reluctantly and wanting to die
こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK?
I'm just dizzy here, okay?
バーストからインスタント・ラヴァー
Instant lover from a burst
頭＋身体がバカに絡まる
Head and body entangled in stupidity
ゴーストならアンデッド・マナー
If you're a ghost, undead manners
今だ乱ら今は火花散らせ
It's messy now, make the sparks fly
それがアンサーだ
That's the answer
ヤ ヤ ヤ 悪い子さん
Ya, ya, ya, you bad child
マ マ マ マ お愛顧じゃん
Well, well, it's a draw
さ さ さ さ 始めるよ
Now, now, let's get started
もっとこの穴を愛してよ
Love this hole even more
だっせ！
Lame!
Whoa! Look at this place!
I was not expecting to play a game in such a pretty place.
And I wonder what kind of game it's going to be... Hmm.
Raora!
This is your conscience!
Eh? My conscience? Do I have one?
Oh! Mori!
Yo, it's your turn.
Say something. Say something.
Eh? Is that... Is that...
Is that a ghost? What is that?
Where is...? I can't see anyone.
Raora!
Eh? Is that a dog?
Congrats Raora on your 3D debut!
We're so happy for you.
Oh, thank you so much! I'm so happy!
Well, as you may have assumed by our grand entrance...
...your opponents for this mini-game are, as you see...
Mina-san, Mori Calliope from Hololive English Myth!
Everyone, I'm Mori Calliope from Hololive English Myth!
If you don't know me, now you do!
Konnichi-wa, this is Ouro Kronii from Hololive English Promise.
Hello, this is Ouro Kronii from Hololive English Promise.
And who could this beautiful woman be? Dare desu ka?
And who could this beautiful woman be? Who is it?
どっちこっち？こっち！指、指！指、指！
Which way? This way! Finger, finger! Finger, finger!
ホロライブから来ました戌神ころねです、よろしくね！
I'm Inugami Korone from Hololive, nice to meet you!
こんにちは！先輩、始めまして！今日は来てくれてありがとうございます！
Hello! Seniors, nice to meet you! Thank you for coming today!
お、日本語上手！
Oh, your Japanese is good!
Thank you so much Mori! What kind of game are we gonna play today?
Well, get ready!
Because it's time for one, two, three, say cheese!
Say Cheese! Raora!!
All right.
Now then, here are the rules.
Chattini jump out of the bush holding a camera!
Chattini are gonna jump out of the bushes
at random intervals to snap a photo of you.
え？
Eh?
Strike a pose here!
And when they do so, you gotta enter their frame
and then strike a specific pose for them.
It's okay! It's okay!
Yeah!
Why is she so strong?
She's rejecting all of my pushes!
Oh man, really blocking...
Hey! Hey!
Man, I'm not even gonna try on this one.
No! Arigato!
No! Thank you!
Wow, they're all squabbling!
Calliope takes the lead!
Yes!
That's so tiring!
No! Not every time!
You can't get it every time, Kronii!
Come on! Let me...
...have this one!
Oy oy oy...
Hey, hey, hey...
That's so tiring...
Yo, why are y'all so strong?
I don't get it...
Yeah, good.
We are good.
Oh, okay. So good.
Man, I feel like we just...
...came out of a battle.
Raora!
I'm good.
いい勝負。
A good fight.
That's what I call...
...いい勝負。
...a good fight.
Okay, how was it?
How do you guys think that you did?
I think I won!
いい勝負！
A good fight!
I think I won!
Me too!
No, no, no! Me too!
I think Kronii won...
...with the sheer force of her muscles pushing people out of the way.
I'm so sorry!
But it's the game.
And it wasn't even that. She could not be pushed!
I mean, hey, competitive spirit.
I can't even argue with that.
Well then, well done everyone.
Let's see how that weighs up against the results, shall we?
I bet I am the winner!
No, no, no! No, Raora, no, Raora!
Yes, Kronii! Yes, me win!
Me, me, me win!
Me, me, me!
All right, all right, let's see how we all did then.
Here we go.
Drum roll, please!
And the results are...
Kronii!
That's crazy clutch. She's too strong.
Congrats, congrats!
I knew it was me anyway.
Thank you, thank you.
There was no defeating the Clock of Steel.
This is rigged! It's rigged!
She's too good, Raora. She can't be beaten.
I tried to pick her up and move her, she just can't be moved.
Man, it's really too bad though...
I was gonna give you the ticket if you managed to win.
But oh well, this round's a bust.
Oh boo, so sad. Oh I cry.
No!
Wait, wait, wait! Wait a second.
There must be a way, right?
I need the ticket!
I need to clear three games!
I mean, it's not... it's not up to me...
...but you know what, I feel kind of bad.
You're my cute kouhai.
Please!
ころね先輩、どうすればいい？
Korone-senpai, what should I do?
そうね。
Let's see.
Do you like Japanese TV shows?
Yes, I love Japanese TV shows!
Ah, please, cute "おねだり".
Ah, please, cute "onedari".
Eh? おねだり？
Eh? Onedari?
可愛くおねだり。
Cute onedari.
You want me to beg?
Yeah, おねだり！
Yeah, onedari!
このカメラ、オッケー？
This camera, okay?
Get kind of low.
ちょっと低い、ちょっと低い。
A little lower, a little lower.
Up eyes, up eyes, okay?
Okay, 上目遣い、オッケー。
Okay, puppy-dog eyes, okay.
Do your best!
Cute face, cute face, okay?
おねだり、キュートおねだり。
Onedari, cute onedari.
Please! Please, ころね先輩！
Please! Please, Korone-senpai!
Please, おねだり！
Please, onedari!
Give me the ticket!
Please!
I need the ticket!
Please, ころね先輩、お願い。
Please, Korone-senpai, please.
お願いします！
I beg of you!
Please!
Give me the ticket!
ここまでやるとは。
Doing it to this extent...
All right, all right.
She's done enough!
そんなに欲しいのね。
You want it that much, huh.
All right, all right, Raora, you've done it!
Look at your hand!
チケット、ゲット！
I got the ticket!
Got the ticket!
Excellent おねだり！
Excellent onedari!
やったー！
Yay!
キュートおねだり、オッケー！
Cute onedari, okay!
I got the ticket! Let's go!
Well done!
See, no problem.
Happy ending.
You will receive the Jetpack Chatini if you gather three tickets.
Count 'em, three!
So good luck on the next games as well!
Thank you, senpai!
Yeah, no problem.
Now go do your best!
Thank you so much!
Bye-bye!
This way, go straight!
Go straight!
This way! This way! Go straight!
Bye!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Good luck!
See you!
Bye-bye! See ya!
Chattini Land: Jungle Area
Oh my gosh, this area is really different from the last one!
It's super dark... and what's with all those bars?
It's... it's kind of scary.
What is that?
I hear voices...
Let's go!
What is that?
Oh my god! Chattini!
Please! My time has come! Please take my soul!
I'll just go...
Oh! It's Nerissa and Moona!
Yeah, you're gonna say you don't recognize us?
Of course I recognize you! Hahaha!
Congratulations on your 3D!
Thank you!
Finally!
I think we have to introduce...?
Hmm, of course.
Sorry for me.
Hello everyone! I am Moona Hoshinova...
from Hololive Indonesia Generation 1!
Hi darlings! This is Hololive English -Advent-'s...
devilish diva, the one and only Nerissa Ravencroft!
Thank you for having me!
Thank you so much for being here!
We come here to bring a game.
A game?
Yes! Really! It involves cooperation.
Coop? Oh good!
What are we gonna do? What are we gonna do?
Well, the game this time is...
One, two, three... Limbo Dance Panthera!!
Limbo Dance! Panthera!!
The rules are super simple.
The trio of us are gonna do some sexy limbo dance.
Dancing! Yes, the limbo dance, dancing!
As we make our way towards the stage!
Sexy! Yay!
So excited!
Me too! And once we're there, there's one thing left to do.
We're all gonna sing a super awesome trio song!
I'm so happy!
Sounds simple, right?
Simple! Let's see!
I am born for this! Let's go!
But, you know, are we really gonna be able to do this?
I think we might have not thought ahead too far...
Of course we're gonna do it!
No, but you know, we all have something...
that I feel like will make limbo a little bit difficult.
Oh, don't worry, Nerissa! I can help you!
Something that is really, really hard, but it's fine!
We can help! Save it for the game, ladies!
Okay, let's do it!
First off though, we need to do some warmup.
Oh!
Yes! Yes!
Keep going, girls! Whoo!
Yeah, let's warm up a little bit before the game dance!
Can They Clear It?!
Alright, that gets us ready, all together! Yeah!
I took off my jacket because it's so hot in here!
Can you do me a favor?
Could you jump a little bit more? Just a little bit!
Just a little bit? Why?
Why are you asking? Yes! I love jumping, so let's go!
And look at those shoulders, too!
Show those off! Very nice!
Thank you!
Oh my god!
I'm gonna do my very best in Limbo Dance!
Let's dance! Let's do it!
Get the music going!
GAME START!
Nice music! Do you hear that?
Yeah!
Are you ready?
I'm ready! It's your 3D debut, so get going!
Well, that's too easy for me! Are you guys ready?
Yeah!
Okay, here we go!
Yay! Good job!
Moona! Moona!
Too easy for her!
Nerissa! Nerissa! You can do it!
Oh my goodness! Easy peasy!
Who's next? Who's next?
Same order!
Same order! Let's keep it going!
Wait, that's a little bit unfair!
Well, I'm gonna do it then!
Show us how it's done!
Good job!
I can do it! Easy, easy!
Oh! Look at you go!
Nerissa, Nerissa... Oh!
Easy game!
This is a little bit more difficult.
Maybe same order? Maybe same order! Let's go!
Senpai order!
I can do it for you guys.
Oh, look at her go! Look at her go!
[GOOD!]
Nerissa, your turn!
Watch how it's done!
Show me, Queen!
That's so clean, girl!
Let's go, my turn!
Come on, kohai!
[GOOD!]
Okay, maybe switch it off, I'll go first.
Yes, you go first!
[PERFECT!]
Are you gonna be able to do it, Muna?
You can do it, Muna!
I believe!
This is a really tough one!
[SUCCESS!]
All right, my turn!
Let me show you all my skills!
[FAIL?]
I'm good, I'm good!
You're okay, you're okay!
No, we have to keep going! You've still got two more!
[Sexy Pass!]
Oh my god, I'm too old for this!
Come here, grandma! Come here!
We have two more to go, right?
Wait a second... you dropped your...
I think I still can do it for now.
Time to get serious, so I'm gonna lock in.
Yeah, it's a little bit low, but I think we can do it.
[Amazing!]
No, I think I have an idea.
[GOOD?]
The power of brain, Muna!
You did so good so far!
I think I'm too tall for this one.
I'm gonna hold you!
I'm gonna fall! I'm gonna fall!
[Sexy Pass!]
I'm going to follow their way.
She's getting serious!
[Sexy Pass!]
What to do...?
Well, I'm a big cat, so...
[Too Cute to Fail!]
Nya nya nya!
Well, I still think we have one more obstacle yet before us.
Look at this slope!
Don't forget our limbo dance!
Oh yeah, limbo dance now!
Let's go to the stage!
Are you guys excited?
I am so ready!
[Singing Next!]
I don't know what I'm doing, but let's do it!
Cutie Panther
Lyrics: 畑亜貴 Music: 佐々木裕
Lyrics: Aki Hata Music: Yū Sasaki
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
(どこにいるの？)
(Where are you?)
(ムリよムリよ)
(It's no use, no use)
(どこにいたってムリよ)
(No matter where you are, it's no use)
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
(だれといるの？)
(Who are you with?)
(ダメよダメよ)
(No, no)
(わたし以外はだめよ)
(No one else but me)
甘いよ甘い
Sweet, so sweet
そんな装備じゃ
With that kind of gear...
逃げられるわけ無いじゃないか
There's no way you can escape, is there?
狙いをつけて密かに
I'll take aim and quietly...
背後から
from behind...
I love you
私のことを好きになるはず
You're bound to fall for me
I love you
そこに正義があるの
There's justice in that
何度言わせるつもりなの？
How many times are you going to make me say it?
おや おや
My, oh my
抵抗するならしてみてな
If you're going to resist, show me what you've got
意外と
Surprisingly...
我が儘だと知ってるけれど
I know I'm selfish, but
私の方が上手なようね
I seem to be the more skillful one
冷たい言葉
Cold words,
優しい視線
a kind gaze...
獲物は…君だよ！
My prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 私
Cutie Panther, it's me
どこでも行くよ
I'll go anywhere
君の 君の
For your... your...
心盗んでみせるよ 心を離さない
heart, I'll steal it away. I'll never let you go.
熱いよ熱い
It's hot, so hot
愛のルールは
The rules of love...
破られるため在るんだよ
are made to be broken
ずるい罠へと誘う
Luring you into a sly trap...
微笑みは…
my smile is...
I miss you
好きのせいだし悪くないでしょ
It's because I love you, so I'm not to blame, right?
I miss you
それが重度の恋よ
That's what a serious love is
絶対全部をいただくよ
I'll definitely take everything
おや おや
My, oh my
抵抗するならしてみせな
If you're going to resist, show me what you've got
意外と
Surprisingly...
偽りだって疑うよりも
Rather than doubting and calling it a lie...
私のこと信じてみてよ
try believing in me
優しい言葉
Kind words,
冷たい視線
a cold gaze...
獲物は…君だよ！
My prey is... you!
捕まえちゃう!
I'll catch you!
どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ
どこにいたってムリよ
Where are you? It's no use, no use
Wherever you are, it's no use
捕まえちゃう!
I'll catch you!
だれといるの？ ダメよダメよ
私以外はダメよ
Who are you with? No way, no way
Anyone but me is no way
Whoa! How was that, Raora?
It's really nice!
That's how Raora does it.
So cool, right?
So together. Nice! So happy.
Thank you for dancing and singing with me.
And also, since we already finished our session,
so here's your ticket.
Oh my god! I got it! Look at you! CLEAR!
Got the Ticket!!
Congratulations, Raora!
How's that! One more left now.
Let's go!
Thank you so much! I'm so happy. It was so fun!
Thank you for having us.
Good luck getting that final ticket too!
Yes, it's true.
I'll do my best.
I promise!
Thank you girls!
You can do it!
Well, as for us, we should take our leave now.
Bye bye!
We must leave you.
No! Don't leave me, girls! I need to go!
Nooooo!
No! Oh...
The limbo dance was so hard that it became
their default walking state instead.
Whoa! What is this place?
Oh my god, this seems like this came out of
a science fiction movie or something like that!
But now I'm curious...
what kind of game they got prepared for me this time? Hmm...
I smell something... dog smell!
I know who you are!
Come out! Come here!
Oh, come here, come here! Oh wow! Yeah!
There, there...
I'm so excited, I'm so nervous, I'm so happy!
Your tail's looking really happy too!
No no no no no no!
Okay let's talk about it. There's a game to the right!
And I'm not the game, right?
Okay, okay. Well, why don't you guys introduce yourselves?
I'm not Bau Bau! I'm Fuwawa Abyssguard!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo Abyssguard!
Together we are FuwaMoco! Bau Bau!
And I'm not FuwaMoco! Bau Bau too! I'm...
Koseki Bijou, sparkling gem of hololive English -Advent-!
Kira kira! Koseki Bijou!
And then... Raora!
It's still me, Raora Panthera from hololive English -Justice-!
This time in 3D!
Wait, have you introduced yourself before? Maybe.
Oh well, always good for a second time! It's okay!
So, what's the last game gonna be?
Ready for this next game?
Actually Raora, you're the only one in this challenge!
But what do you mean?
But we have a very important role too, right?
What are you guys gonna do?
We're gonna stop you!
No no no no no! You guys gotta let me win!
We're gonna beat you!
No no no no no no! You gotta let me win!
It's my debut and it's the last ticket! I need it!
No! No I don't think so!
We're gonna put you through the wringer, yeah!
Are you ready to hear what the third final game is?
One! Two! Three! Run! Run! Raora!!
Oh! Okay, okay... what's the rules?
Are you curious?
I'm very curious!
Take a look at the conveyor belt behind you!
Whoa! What is this? Huh? There is nothing on it.
Oh, silly me, there IS something on it. Bring it out!
What is that? Huh?
Eww! What the heck! Eww!
Is that a pizza?
Pineapple pizza!
Broken up spaghetti! Oh get out of here!
Eww! No thank you!
Pasta with ketchup! No no no!
I'm done with this! I'm so done! I'm leaving!
I'm leaving! I'm not gonna play this game!
No, I'm not gonna play this game! It's too much!
No! Basta! No no no no no!
No! Stop! No no no no no!
It's too much for me! I'm done with this!
Well, do you notice that everything we brought
out here is everything you hate?
Do you hate us just a little bit, Raora?
To clear the stage, Raora must dodge all
incoming obstacles during the time limit!
And avoid everything... I've got it!
You! You! You!
No, no, no!
You can do it! Do it!
Wait a second, why are you guys here then?
Hey, what are you guys gonna do?
Well, we'll be using certain things...
...to make life more difficult for you, Raora!
Oh, you can't do this to me!
It's impossible!
Yeah, you are really a criminal!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
No, you're not gonna do this to me!
Wait, let's go grab her!
Yeah, yeah, okay! Hold on!
We'll be right back! We'll be right back!
No, no! Come back!
Hey, what are they gonna do?
No, no, no, no, no!
RAORA! RAORA!
Wait, wait! Okay, I will play the game!
I will play the game!
Did you like that? Because there's more where that came from!
No, not that! That's me with that onion!
It's bigger than you, Pinky!
What is that to me? I'm bigger than this onion!
This is not a normal sized onion, hey!
Cucumbers are good! Yum!
Ooh, yum! Wow!
Now then, let's get going here!
Let's go! Goodbye!
Alright, let's go! Onion! Yeah!
Are you okay? I'm fine, I'm fine!
Okay! You ready, Raora?
Uh... I'm not so sure... Eh, guys? Guys?
Can we play another game?
Okay, the timer...
If you can keep dodging for 60 seconds, you'll level up, okay?
Okay, okay... Okay, I'm ready!
There's a total of three levels,
so try to escape to the very end without getting hit, okay?
Okay, okay! Okay!
Okay then! I'll do my best this time!
GAME START!
FAILED!
Level 1 Revenge!
GAME START!
CLEAR!
Mamma mia!
Yatta! Level 2!
Yay! Level 2!
Oh yeah? Okay, we're gonna make it harder then!
Let's get ready for Level 3!
Oh boy! This is not fair at all!
You guys are cheating! This is not fair!
FAILED!
I disagree with that!
Well, you know guys, today is my 3D debut, right?
So maybe, you know, senpais... give me the pizza?
No. No. No.
You failed, panther!
We have prepared a special stage for you!
We kind of want to see your cool side!
My cool side? Really? Show it off to everyone!
Maybe put those angry feelings into your next song!
Sing? Okay! Let's go!
恋は戦争 / Lyrics, Music: ryo (supercell)
Love is War / Lyrics, Music: ryo (supercell)
もう行き場がないわ
I have nowhere left to go
この恋の熱量
The intensity of this love
Ah...
灰色の雲
Gray clouds
モノクロの喧噪
Monochromatic din
日差しはかげり
The sunlight fades
The sunlight casts a shadow
夕暮れは色を変えていく
The twilight changes color
嗚呼 世界がにじんで
Ah, the world blurs
それでも好きでいられるかなんて
Even so, will I still be able to love you?
わかってる
I know
けどどうすればいいの
But what should I do?
どうしたら どうすれば
What should I do? What should I do?
バカだな わたし…
I'm a fool, I...
始めるのよ
It's starting now
これは 戦争
This is war
嬉しそうなキミをみるなんて
I see you looking so happy
切なる恋
This painful love
それは罪
It's a sin
見せてあげる わたしの想いを
I'll show you, all of my feelings
叫んでみたメガホンは壊れてたの
I shouted, but the megaphone is broken
どれだけ背伸びしたって
No matter how much I stand on my tiptoes
君の視界に入らない
I'll never enter your world
嗚呼 いつのまにか晴れた空
Ah, before I knew it, the sky cleared up
全然似合わない
It doesn't fit at all
気持ちが抑えられなくて
I can't hold back my feelings
どうしたら どうすれば
What should I do? What should I do?
泣いてなんか ないんだからね
I'm not crying, you know
大好き
I love you
たたかうのよ
I'll fight
ハートを撃て
I'll shoot my heart through
手段なんて選んでられない
I can't choose my methods
スカートひらり見せつけるのよ
I'll show off my fluttering skirt
君の視線奪ってみせるの
I'll steal your gaze and show it to you
迎撃 用意
Battle stations, ready
戦況は未だ不利なのです
The war situation is still unfavorable
恋は 盲目
Love is blind
君の口づけで目が覚めるの!
I'll wake up with a kiss from you!
Oh... I'm sorry Chattini... I tried my best...
...but I only got two.
Noooo... my jetpack...
Ah! The jetpack exploded!
I'm sorry Chattini.
Actually, I have a present for all of you!
Present? I wonder what it is? Is it a cucumber?
Ah, mmm-mmm. Let me tell you.
That's the best! It's not a jetpack but it's really nice!
Hehe! Thanks Chattini!
Well then, before I reveal the best present ever...
...I've got an announcement to make!
Tada!
Raora Panthera Pencil Case & Keychain!
Yes, this is a cute pencil case with me in a Chattino costume.
So I hope you guys can bring it everywhere. School, in the office, literally everywhere.
So please don't miss it out, okay?
Ah, that was such a fun 3D showcase with a lot of things happening.
Did everyone have fun? Chattini, did you guys have fun?
Ah! Thank you! I'm so happy to hear that. Thank you!
Since you guys had a great time with me today, I'm so happy. Thank you!
I'll keep doing my best to bring fun streams and more 3D live performances like this one today, okay?
I appreciate you guys so much. Thank you Chattini for all your support.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Ah... That was so much fun!
How did you like it, Chattini?
Did you like it?
Thank you for watching and listening!
Today was so much fun!
Thank you so much everyone for all your support!
Thank you, thank you, Chattini! Thank you!
I can't wait to see you all again!
Until next time...
Ciao ciao!
Bye-bye!
RAOOOO~!
Big CAT means...
BIG TROUBLE!
Thank you Chattini for all your support!
I still can't believe this day finally came!
BIG CAT means BIG DREAMS!