(
"ai_sub_version": "3.2.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-11T01:51:14.062765",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 17,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Greetings, CC, my fated rival!
Greetings, Cece, my distant rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Woohoo!
Remember, if you want a chance
for your wish to be featured...
...on the Otomo or the Takodachi
that we made...
...post about it with #WishUponTakoTomo.
Yay!
Thank you, AmiAmi, for supporting!
...rivalry.
And for supporting Serendipity,
be sure to check out their booth at...
...Anime Expo!
Yay!
Hey pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
Pebbles!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me,
all 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round 1 USA locations nationwide...
...starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates.
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
[The concert will be starting soon.]
[Attention For Visitors]
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
[On-Screen: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
[On-Screen: Acrylic Stand]
[On-Screen: Button Badge & Acrylic Panel]
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
[On-Screen: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
[On-Screen: Acrylic Stand]
[On-Screen: Button Badge & Acrylic Panel]
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
[Merchandise: Acrylic Stand]
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
[Merchandise: Button Badge / Acrylic Panel]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へお願い
Attention For Visitors
ライブグッズ2次販売受付中！
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Sing a bold duet again
Continuing this odyssey
We'll start this new refrain
Brimming with memories
And when the clouded skies become bright
Let's reunite!
What's up, everyone? Welcome to Hololive EN's Serendipity!
Wah! And we are back!
Let's kick off the show with a Myth-ic medley!
Woo!
Ready? Set? Three!
Showtime, baby, I would say / Today's breakfast was slightly delayed
Revving up the engine, is it really enough? / Smoke above brewing endlessly, why?
Take it easy, what did we learn?
Set a fire in the heart and the PC burns
Uh, optimistic, folks out for a quick fix
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks
But we're growing stronger than ever / And never saying die
And I'm aware it's ironic, but where's the freaking lie?
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers to senpai
Not losing to you young people / In our hearts, a myth that's priceless
And spanning new dimensions
We can bring another mystery to light
Blending our ascension, dancing inside
We ignite!
Join us while we're celebrating / In the myth that we're creating
There's another story waiting
Through this world and beyond
Our distant dreams have brought us here
A strong, unyielding bond
Guiding us endlessly
Will bring us moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on
And though these winds may scatter us
We'll keep this promise
When the moment's finally right
We'll always find a way to unite!
One, two, three!
Light up, light up, let's begin
We'll start, stage right, and shuffle on in
Stage is ready, steal the show
Jumping with joy, let's go!
Four tunes of some cute band / We'll keep on entertaining hand in hand
It's our greatest moment yet
A spectacle they'll never forget
All your worries, cast them down / The show will go on and on
Tell them that we're here to stay
And spread the news from Tokyo to Broadway!
Gleaming spotlight
Gather, gather together, we're boogying all night
Beaming so bright
Now we're feeling all right
Since the day we met, we've fallen / Going strong
And we'll keep moving right along
So keep on dancing on your feet / Nothing can stop us, we're a perfect quintet
In harmony, no matter where we go / Like it's meant to be, don't you know?
We're gonna feel so alive when we're all free
Ready to put on another show!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper truth or dare
My hands are full, I'm ready to roll
But no one's keeping score
Set course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, we're all in
I'll play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheel of fortune circles back around
We'll turn it in the betting ring
With these outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread
I see what's up ahead
A wild chase, a straight face
I've got to try my luck, keep spinning, spin
La la la la la...
I'm always spinning
Oh, yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round, hopping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
The game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on
Our threads unbroken
Cord, life, by flex and string
Casting lots together
At the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I swing back round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
And whether it's black or red
I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance, a daring dance
I'll spin this wheel of fate with my own hand
La la la...
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoa, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Blazing fire!
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
Tension rising to the top, won't look back, I'll never stop
Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot, it's your fault, baby
Fever burning up inside, it can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
Come on and come on I wanna confess, baby oh baby I'm gettin' obsessed
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter, gonna be wanna be ready for more
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch, it's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm bearing my soul
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play; a dangerous game
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
Look at me, look at me turnin' to ash, breakin' me shakin' me makin' me crash
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
Drivin' me drivin' me drivin' me crazy, tellin' me tellin' me what do you mean
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire love, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire love, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire
I'm getting started
Blazing fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fuel my delusion
I want you burning for me
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me closer, if you dare
Fire love, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire love, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire
[Gigi Murin]
[Cecilia Immergreen]
[AutoFister]
Yeah! La la la la...
Go, Gigi! Go, Cecilia! AutoFister!
We've been performing our absolute best, but the lines in LA are so long!
No, Cecilia, just speak Japanese!
Arretez, arretez! Ah! Fine, let's speak German!
On this day, you are cast to cope
And keep it in your memory
Oh come on, you're supposed to hope
And let our brand-new madness run its course
Take our hand, let's fly away
Break a leg, now challenge me
Quick, before your time is up
Give in and be our playmate
Puff, snap, jump, our dreams away
Love yourself, don't be afraid!
Find just one condition, give in
Release your soul, in eight, five, seven!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, mate!
Cecilia, Cecilia, Cecilia, Cecilia, AutoFister!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, mate!
Cecilia, Cecilia, Cecilia, Cecilia, come on, let's play!
Come on, LA! We want to hear you shout!
Say something, Gigi!
Oh my god, why don't you say something?!
Oh come on, can you feel that hope
To lose your heart in reverie
There's no way to avert this trope
So laugh, our brand-new madness run its course
Take our hand, let's fly away
Make a way, now choose the day
Quick, before your time is up
Give in and be our playmate
Puff, snap, jump, our dreams away
Love yourself, don't be afraid!
Live up your ambition, come on
Let go of all inhibition!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, mate!
Cecilia, Cecilia, Cecilia, Cecilia, AutoFister!
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, mate!
Cecilia, Cecilia, Cecilia, Cecilia, come on, let's play!
Wait, Gigi! Did we do this part?
No, we're doing the dance! Oh, wait, we're supposed to dance?
Yes! Shake your hips!
Shake your hips? I can't even move my hands!
Yes, you can! Wave them around!
Stop trying to hit me!
I'm not hitting you, you're hitting me!
Oh my god, your dress is tickling my nose!
Well, stop putting your nose there!
All nice fun must come to an end
But at least you found a friend
So let us fly and stay...
...or rather...
One, two, and!
Take our hands, let's fly away!
Turn around and let us play!
Find just one condition, come on!
Tonight, safe adventure, fly away!
Hello, hello, hello!
Hello!
Hololive English's very first...
...and chat's greatest threat!
My butt's too big for this seat!
Ah!
Wow, look at it! It's so big and juicy! How impressive!
Hello, everyone!
It's me, Cecilia Immergreen!
It's me, Gigi Murin!
And together we are AutoThrust!
Well, L.A., we wanted to do some L.A. call-and-response.
So I'm gonna say something, and you cheer if you like it, okay?
Okay?
The beach!
Hololive in L.A.!
Sitting in traffic!
Boo! Whatever.
CCGG in L.A.!
Okay, everybody, excited to be here at Hololive...
...Serendipity!
Please all stand. It is the Fourth of July weekend. For the flag...
Please stand up, everyone!
O say can you see...
...by the dawn's early light...
...what so proudly...
Okay, okay, okay, shut up, shut up! That's enough, enough.
Enough of that. Enough of that shit. Okay.
How about we do a CCGG chant?
Oh, no, no, no, not yet, not yet, not yet!
Not yet! USA is not yet! No, no, no, no.
Okay guys, since you are standing, we want you to do our chant of our chorus plus...
...stomping!
Stomping to the beat.
Okay, so the left side, we want them to be green.
And this side...
Orange!
Green!
Orange! Do it now!
Quickly.
Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect.
Orange, good.
Okay, okay, okay, stomping...
...and you stomp...
...and then we say, "CCGG CCGG."
CC! GG! CC! GG! CC! GG! Madness!
CC! GG! CC! GG! CC! GG! AutoThrust!
CC! GG! CC! GG! Come let's play!
Issho ni, together.
Everyone together really fast though.
So impress us, okay?
Okay.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
CCGG CCGG CCGG Madness!
CCGG CCGG CCGG AutoThrust!
CCGG CCGG CCGG Come let's play!
Really impressive, guys.
That was really, really good.
Maybe America is awesome.
U-S-A! U-S-A! U-S-A!
Yeah, they freaking love us again.
In America.
Well, for those at home...
...this is sadly the end of the free section.
Wait, there's one more song actually. The song after this.
Oh, one more song. One more song, sorry, sorry, sorry.
But there's the tickets for the streaming... tickets down below, so please check them out.
In the description, check out the streaming tickets, okay?
AutoThrust forgot to do this today, okay?
And...
無料配信は次の曲で最後になります！
The free stream will end with the next song!
ライブの続きはぜひ配信チケットを買って見てね！
Be sure to get a stream ticket to watch the rest of the show!
買って見てね！
Make sure to buy it!
お願いします！
Please!
Or you freaking haters, okay?
Haters, don't be a freaking loser.
Don't hate us for the very last part.
Since this is the very first MC, we want you to be as loud as possible, okay?
Okay!
So... thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you!
Thank you!
We will become a bowling ball and a bowling pin,
and we need you to chant "Serendipity", right? Okay?
Keep chanting until we leave, okay?
Keep chanting until we're gone!
Don't stop until we're gone.
Don't stop!
Okay. Well, one time together, everyone.
Serendipity!
Wheee!
Weee!
I'll be your exit route
pound the gavel and sentence me to doom
even though I'm just doing what you do
decide which lies become the truth
no, you never really thought about it that far
judging me when I can see you've got the same scars
that's the price that I pay, it's a deep mark
come, pick your sacrifice
nail me to your crucifix
nothing else can fix this
so I'll take the blame
see yourself reflected
and not corrected
one request, it's:
don't be gentle
don't be kind when you
murder, murder, murder the martyr
poke their eyes out
leave them blind
murder, murder, murder the martyr
one request, it's—
hypocrisy
I've seen what you do in private rings
all your friends, yeah, they know what you really think
to your glory, the masses keep on singing
point at me in a hurry
pick a scapegoat for the new controversy
even when I'm buried, hidden, silent, you'll be wary
please, dear God, show them mercy, uh
nail me to your crucifix
nothing else can fix this
so I'll take the blame
see yourself reflected
and not corrected
one request, it's:
don't be gentle
don't be kind when you
murder, murder, murder the martyr
poke their eyes out
leave them blind
murder, murder, murder the martyr
break me now
take me down
me down
one request, it's:
I see your sins
and they're in your soul
consume and ignore
decay to your core
I'll never win to you
but within, you'll...
break, break, break, break, break
and when I
break, break, break, break
you will
and in your hands, the hammer pounds the nail in
don't be gentle
don't be kind when you
murder, murder, murder the martyr
poke their eyes out
leave them blind
murder, murder, murder the martyr
one request, it's—
do you love me?
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました。
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！