(
"ai_sub_version": "3.2.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-09T01:33:07.258702",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 17,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. / Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Light Stick / T-Shirt / Acrylic Keychain / Sticker
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales:
Light Stick, T-Shirt, Acrylic Keychain, Sticker
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales:
Button Badge, Acrylic Panel
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. / Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Light Stick / T-Shirt / Acrylic Keychain / Sticker
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales:
Light Stick, T-Shirt, Acrylic Keychain, Sticker
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales:
Button Badge, Acrylic Panel
Greetings, senpai, my fated rival!
Greetings, kouhai, my destined rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity! Woo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made...
...post about them with hashtag #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay! Thank you AmiAmi for supporting our rivalry!
And for supporting Serendipity! Be sure to check out their booth at...
...Anime Expo!
Yay!
Hey, pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me. All 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round1 USA locations nationwide, starting this September!
So come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
[hololive English 4th Concert: Serendipity]
[The concert will be starting soon.]
[Attention For Visitors]
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Concert Merch Sales: Acrylic Stand
Concert Merch Sales: Button Badge & Acrylic Panel
hololive English 4th Concert -Serendipity- Fan Messages
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Concert Merch Sales: Acrylic Stand
Concert Merch Sales: Button Badge & Acrylic Panel
hololive English 4th Concert -Serendipity- Fan Messages
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment until the start of the performance.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
A-D-V-E-N-T
Everyone, let's light the fire!
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire!
Higher, higher, as you desire!
Chasing all that we aspire!
Spreading out like wildfire!
Never ever, have I ever...
...been a sinner, been a dreamer!
Take the chance and with my lighter...
...start the fire!
Don't burn me out
I know the secret
That is over, these sad stories wearing me down
Snap out of the system
Break out, give it everything
This is our time...
...we are starting to shine!
Hello brand new world
Would you welcome the light?
And free us...
...from the night?
Fire, fire, light the fire
Higher, higher, as you desire
United we march
Jump into the stream of light!
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump into the end of time!
次元の向こう側連れてってあげる
I'll take you to the other side of dimensions
Fleuria!
I know that I can still be...
...the future of this story
I know that I can be free
The one and the only
They tell me that I'm crazy
I'll never let them stop me
With this, our final ticket
Time to get this party started!
Never ever, have I ever...
...been a sinner, been a dreamer!
Fire, fire, light the fire!
United we march
Jump into the stream of light!
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump into the end of time!
次元の向こう側連れてってあげる
I'll take you to the other side of dimensions
Jump into the stream of light!
それぞれのステージへ
To our respective stages
Jump into the end of time!
奇跡の向こう側連れてってあげる
I'll take you to the other side of miracles
Fleuria!
Time to get this party started
Fire, fire, light the fire
Higher, higher, as you desire
Time to get this party started
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below, takin' you all be—
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below we go
They think they want it? (Huh?)
They wanna ge-get down
We take 'em down (down, down)
Queendom in the borderline
Run it, no surprise
You ain't gonna win, but you can try
Told ya, you got no luck
End up in my lineup
Listen, listen
Run, oh, hide and scream out, already locked ya up
Fool's games you always play
Call me corrupt, won't hear anything
Aiming my sight down right on your heart
Throwin' the keys out, shut down, I—
(Justice, just like that)
Love it, the forbidden
You're never forgiven
(Justice, get, get that)
Not one to just forget
We got 'em
The higher I rise, down further you dive
Standin' on the edge
don't know me, unpredictable, typical you
Got nowhere to go
Show you somethin' real
my level no you'll never know
as above so below, you should know
Dudurudurudu
(We got it!)
Run in the light, oh my dio
What's wrong, what's right?
Rush in' in a fantasy
Rushin' in a fantasy
Wannabe disease
Sure that you won't ever make it out
Eyes follow now, do it, do it
New target locked on it now (now)
New target locked on it now
Enemies? Girl, I lost count (uh)
Enemies? Girl, I lost count
See your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop, it's just the start
Ooh~
Get down, get darada
(Like it like that? Run it like that)
Get down, get down, down, down (hey!)
Get down, get down, down, down
Takin' me up, up, up, let's go
Goin' above, go below
Told ya, you already know
Don'tcha? They know it!
Run in the light, oh my dio
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night, oh my dio
Come take a bite (never ending, endless sky)
Come take a bite
(never ending, endless sky)
Love it, the forbidden
You're never forgiven
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't get stuck
We rise
Yeah! Yeah!
Standing on the edge
Just that little more unpredictable, typical, you
Got nowhere to go
Show you something real
Real mind, next level, no, you'll never know, up above, so, below
You should know
So let's go!
Just that little more unpredictable, beautiful
Just that, look up, look up!
Next level, on the criminal, up above
So, below
준비!
Ready!
That's the game, what a shame, players they all complain
Why need no knight again and shout out, tatarata, burn!
In due time, so dry those eyes
Look around, who's satisfied?
The broken and bruised, I've got something to prove now
Abracadabra, let's go, watch 'em, like dice, as they fall
끝까지 가보는 거야
I'm going to go to the end
나는 내 멋대로 해 (Hey! Hey!)
I do whatever I want (Hey! Hey!)
Double, double, double, double, in, I'm leaning to the ladder we drew
All day, we hit that high
Snake, eye, snake, eye, come on now, don't be shy
Snake, eye, snake, eye
뜨겁게 타올라
Burning up hot
All day, all night
Don't turn it off, can't stop, won't stop reaching, who said the sky's the limit?
Show them that we're in business, we are the young and vicious
Snake eyes, they never lie
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
지켜봐 우린 이미 판을 바꾼 Party
Watch us, we are already the party that changed the game
Play 어떻게? 완전 Safari
Play how? Totally safari
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me, giddy, giddy, 받아
Go, go, go Baelz! Acting on this, 다 벗어던져
Go, go, go Baelz! Acting on this, data beoseodanjeo
머리 찰랑
Shake your hair
Shake it off, what goes around
Shut your mouth, what will come down
Ready to fight, ready, screaming!
Abracadabra, let's go, watch 'em, we ripping it up
걱정하지는 마, 너를 다 던져버려 Play
Don't worry, throw yourself entirely into it and Play
Raise up, demons! Believe in the beat and just wait and see
We hit that high
Snake, eye, snake, eye, come on now, don't be shy
Snake, eye, snake, eye
뜨겁게 타올라
Burning up hot
All day, all night
Let me hear you, NY! Let's make some noise!
Yeah, we go hard!
이 어둠 속에 전부를 걸어볼게, Go!
I will bet everything in this darkness, Go!
We go hard, I want it all!
죽지 않아 전부 골라
I won't die, pick them all
맞서 싸워, 시작이야
Fight back, this is the beginning
끝까지 달려가
Run to the very end
We'll hit that high
Snake, eye, snake, eye, come on now, don't be shy
Snake, eye, snake, eye
끝까지 전부 다 버려 이렇게
Throw it all away to the end like this
멈출 수 없어 끝까지, Burn! Burn!
I can't stop until the very end, Burn! Burn!
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just a new beginning
Look at the clouds we're reaching
Sometimes it takes a villain
Snake eyes, the time is nigh
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
Cut you off at the thighs
This ain't the only battlefield that can tell of lies
Ego is enormous, so put the camera down and face it
They went and got complacent
Come and run with me
You say you stand for nothing, no one else can relate
Just know the company you keep is in the business of hate, are you...
Wait... Wait, I'm close to...
I've been dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Go on shoot, shoot, shoot, oh baby, did you miss?
Ricochet, ricochet
You can think about me any time, any time
So get your street fight!
This is trench war!
I'll make you mosh, mosh, mosh till you hit the floor!
Gettin' thirsty for collision, let them wonder what they're missing
In the front row
Now here we go!
See the white line, it's a call to arms
Become the witness, the unforgiven
Make a decision, as you look for permission
To riot, your body rots
Think about it, your identity
Click, clack, now you're alone
Step up or nothing, play the coward
Step up or someone will devour
It's a dead end quest, unless we head west, big success!
Oh...
Step up or nothing, play the coward
Step up or someone will devour
It's a dead end quest, unless we head west, big success!
Let me say this... WOAH!
さあ 牙剥き出し この子に決めた
Now, baring my fangs, I've decided on this one
角度調整 角度微調整
Adjusting the angle, fine-tuning the angle
聴き慣れたボイスから Please send me message
With a familiar voice, please send me a message
Decide, special and discard the rest
Can't play by their picture, chips are stacked
We some lonely animals until we crack
サイコ サイコ パスみたいなエゴイスト
An egoist like a psycho, psycho, psychopath
あっち向いて こっち向いて ピーポー
Look that way, look this way, people
Always starving, 時間の無駄無駄
Always starving, it's a waste, waste of time
やっちゃいな ちゃいな
Go ahead and do it
I can tell you're not a friend
さあ どん底から 息吸い込んで 吐き出せ...
Now, draw in a breath from the very bottom and spit it out...
吐き出せ 吐き出せ どん底から 息吸い込んで
Spit it out, spit it out, draw in a breath from the very bottom
舞台傷だらけの Lonely, Lonely
On a stage covered in scratches, lonely, lonely
自分を買い被る奴を 踏み潰して見下してやれ
Trample and look down on those who overestimate themselves
AWA, AWA, AWA
WOAH!
さあ 牙剥き出し 貼り付けたプロファイルを...
Now, baring my fangs, tear away the pasted profile...
サッと破り捨て
In an instant and throw it away
How's that? Special, and you're out of luck
How's that? I'm the one who's not impressed
さあ どん底から 息吸い込んで
Now, draw in a breath from the very bottom
吐き出せ 吐き出せ
Spit it out, spit it out
どん底から 息吸い込んで
Draw in a breath from the very bottom
吐き出せ
And spit it out!
I gotta tell you
I never lied to you
Never lied to you
Let me knight you
My, my, my, take control
By finding ways of avoiding your death toll
It's a story of your after-life with me
Underrated everywhere we go
Pick a name, but it doesn't make a difference at all
Got a million different enemies I can't recall
You're showing up to a battle when you know that you'll fall
Here's the benediction, watch it all burn
I gotta tell you
I never lied to you
Never lied to you
Let me knight you
When thunder crashes down
When the world breathes under my pressure
There will be no one to save
Where is your precious human will to survive?
Was it just empty words for your grave?
I'll reach inside this soul
Now all that remains is delusion and decay
And decay...
'Cause of you, I live this way
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
Lately, I realize I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know, do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree?
I can feel the rain wash...
over us
yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
And I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side, my heart is beating in double time
And every moment you make me feel alive, it goes like
I can feel the rain wash over us
yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
And I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hello! Hello!
Hello! Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello!
Hello! Hi!
Hello up there!
Hello down here!
Hello, みなー！
Hello, everyone!
Hey, who are you?
Hiya darlings! This is Hololive English -Advent- devilish diva...
Hiya darlings! This is Hololive English -Advent-'s devilish diva...
...the one, the only, Nerissa Ravencroft!
And with me...
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue!
Also known as the Scarlet Queen, the Harbinger of Order, Leader of Justice...
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you...
Lovely!
Wow! What a setlist so far, huh?
I know! We're starting off really strong!
We had...
Snake Eyes! Snake Eyes!
Whoa!
Oh my god!
And we had Mori...
rocking it out!
Seriously!
And then Kronii coming in with her new song, so good!
Yeah! Such cute dance moves!
And we had Advent and Justice, of course!
Yes! Yes! Did you enjoy?
Did you enjoy?
Couldn't hear you! Did you enjoy?
Wow! You know what? We didn't have solos yesterday.
No, no.
So we must be having them today, right?
Ah, yeah! For mine, I want to practice something, okay?
Oh, okay. Go on.
A little chant from Great Ersardia!
So when I go 'Oggy oggy oggy', you go 'Oi oi oi!'
Are you ready?
Okay! Here we go!
Oggy, oggy, oggy!
Oi, oi, oi!
Perfect! Kanpeki!
Kanpeki!
How about you? Any sneak peeks about your solo?
Hmm... would you guys really like a sneak peek?
Well... I think I have to remind you all...
...no matter how you identify, no matter what you are...
...you, in this audience today...
...are my wives! Can I hear from my wives?!
What the freak?! Everyone here is your wife?!
Including you!
What...
I sing too!
You guys know I like harmonies?
Yes!
So we're going to split you into different notes, okay?
So we have...
...you guys over here,
...and all of you at the top.
So...
...we're gonna start off with you guys here.
Yeah.
We want you to hold this note.
Ah...
Perfect! You guys...
...up there!
Ah...
All right, everyone together!
Oh! Beautiful! Beautiful!
Oh my gosh, we have a choir!
So good!
We gotta do that more often. That was cool!
I like hearing you all sing for us.
Aww!
Hey, that reminds me of a song, doesn't it? You know that first note?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Something like...
Three, two, one...
It's wondrous...
...somehow we met along the way.
Now here you are beside...
...me, embracing serendipity!
Wow, that was great, wasn't it?
Harmonizing! Yeah!
It's wonderful harmonizing with you.
And I just want to say thank you so much for being my friend.
I love you!
Anyway...
We're gonna sing together!
I got too excited! I got too excited!
I'm just too happy!
I'm so happy too!
Wee-woo, wee-woo...
Oh, I spammed too fast. There we go.
Anyway...
無料配信は...
The free stream...
...次の曲で最後になります！
...will end with the next song!
ライブの続きは、ぜひ配信チケットを買って見てね！
To watch the rest of the live concert, please buy a stream ticket!
The YouTube free sneak peek is only until the next song, which is...
...a duet.
If you want to continue watching, click the link in the description and get your tickets now!
All right, everybody.
After three, we all say 'Serendipity'. Got it?
Yeah.
Thank you so much! We love you guys so much!
All right, here we go!
Yes!
Three, two, one...
Serendipity!
Performing Units
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Nerissa Ravencroft
Bloodraven
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ 神話になれ
boy, become a legend.
蒼い風がいま
Even though the blue wind
胸のドアを叩いても
is knocking on the door of my heart,
私だけをただ見つめて
you are only looking at me
微笑んでるあなた
and smiling.
そっとふれるもの
Gently touching things,
求めることに夢中で
so engrossed in searching
運命さえまだ知らない
that you don't even know your destiny yet,
いたいけな瞳
with those innocent eyes.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう
But one day you'll realize
その背中には
that on your back
遥か未来 めざすための
are wings to take you
羽根があること
to the distant future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A cruel angel's thesis
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
will soon fly from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
With a gushing, hot pathos,
思い出を裏切るなら
if you betray your memories,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く
embrace this universe and shine!
...この宇宙を抱いて輝く
...embrace this sky and shine!
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a myth!
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
もっと声出して行こう！
Let's hear your voices more!
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
Back to you, Kronii!
ずっと眠ってる
Sleeping forever,
私の愛のゆりかご
inside the cradle of my love.
あなただけが 夢の使者に
Only you are summoned by the messenger of dreams,
呼ばれる朝が来る
as the morning comes.
細い首筋を
Upon your slender neck,
月あかりが映してる
the moonlight shines.
世界中の時を止めて
I want to stop time all over the world,
閉じ込めたいけど
and lock you in, but...
もしも二人会えたことに意味があるなら
If there is a meaning to us having met,
私はそう 自由を知るためのバイブル
then I am, yes, the bible for knowing freedom.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A cruel angel's thesis,
悲しみがそして始まる
sorrow will soon begin.
抱きしめた命の形
The shape of life that you held tight,
その夢に目覚めたとき
when you awaken to that dream,
誰よりも光を放つ
shining brighter than anyone else,
少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, become a myth!
人は愛を紡ぎながら歴史をつくる
While weaving love, humans create history.
女神なんてなれないまま私は生きる
Unable to become a goddess, I live on.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A cruel angel's thesis
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
will soon fly out from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
With a surging hot pathos,
思い出を裏切るなら
if you betray your memories,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く
embrace this sky and shine!
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a myth!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.