(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
But, yo, time's wasting
Show me what you really wanna do
Now it's my turn to show you how Orpheus can lead
Sometimes it feels like you'll play that guitar for me and only me
Oh, so not so predictable, they can see what I can see
Let's write a track!
Let's just crash!
吐き出すメロディ 弾丸ボルト
The melodies I spit are lightning bolts
Let's just crash!
塞いだ手を解いて 叩き割って行くだけ
Just loosen those closed hands and break on through
こんな世界
A world like this...
笑い飛ばせ
...laugh it off!
不完全な 虚しい世界で
In this incomplete, empty world...
ステップ重ねて
...taking steps over and over,
光を
towards the light.
脈打つ鼓動 誰にも止められない
A pulsing heartbeat that nobody can stop,
言葉を紡いでよ
weave your words together.
Fade to black
We fall
We break
We're drowning in fire
Lost inside this dark desire
Sorrow 溶かす未来の Mercy
A future mercy that melts our sorrow...
願うのは飾らない最小の愛
...all we pray for is an unadorned, simple love
戻って
Come back
Show me what I'm trying to say, what's your problem?
通り雨、遠回り、私が迷う
A passing shower, a detour, and I lose my way
And when the world crashes down
When the world keeps turning
Under my pressure, there'll be no one to save
巡る巡る 運命に逆らって
Spinning and spinning, defying our destiny...
出会い 思いを 通わせた
...meeting each other, our feelings connected
The strangers I followed with stars in...
Sorrow, keep on waiting... Wanting, seeking...
Seeking for someone you're not reaching
Longing, chasing...
Why, why can't I be someone else?
Despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape, or hoping in the dark, but still...
くらくらするでしょう
You'll feel dizzy, right?
くらくらくるでしょう
You'll get dizzy, right?
ほんのほんのトークショー
Just a little, little talk show
そうでしょう FLASH BANG
Isn't that right? FLASH BANG!
In this moment, we gotta open up
Not knowing if I never try
I'm wondering...
夢を見るたび
Every time I dream...
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
...I end up thinking about the meaning of my birth
あぁ 美しい 青い日
Ah, beautiful blue days...
We fall
We break
We're drowning in fire
Lost inside this dark desire
What's up, all you dead beats?
Welcome to DISASTERPIECE Release! ようこそ！
Welcome to the DISASTERPIECE release! Welcome!
たくさん楽しもうね！ Let's go, come on!
Have a lot of fun, okay? Let's go, come on!
Ha! You got eyes and ears, but you don't look or listen!
In other words, you're useless, every last one of you!
And that's why I'm gonna send you all to hell!
All of humanity!
So yes, yes, yes...
I'm just so yes, yes, yes...
I'm just the type you forget, so don't waste your time
Yeah, check it, keep kicking the chain, going insane, somebody's gotta pay
While I live with the pain, laugh with me now, I'm one you can't contain
低俗で最低の天才 そう言うんでいい
A vulgar and low-life genius, just let it be like that.
思いが募る場所に
Where longings pile up...
花は咲くから
...flowers will bloom.
Let's riot!
Get back, you're trash! 掃き溜めで希望を
Get back, you're trash! Finding hope in a dump...
Let's just crash 積み上げていくんだ
Let's just crash, I'll pile them up...
頂から高らかに笑え
Laugh loudly from the top!
Lose control!
美しき理想を
That beautiful ideal...
Heads will roll! 汚してくる奴は
Heads will roll! The bastards who dirty it...
誰だ一体？ 誰だ一体？
Who is it? Who is it?
誰だったとしても
No matter who it is...
この理想は無理だろって
Even if someone says this ideal is impossible...
誰が言ったとしても叶えてこうぜ
No matter who says it, let's achieve it!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
正解不正解の解答
Correct or incorrect answer...
どうだっていい
...doesn't matter.
そんなとっくのとうに超えた場所に俺は立っている
I am already standing at a place far beyond that.
Meaningless problems, everybody's got 'em
And they can't be satisfied until somebody's at the bottom.
So what? You think you're special 'cause you got some grit and hunger?
We ain't getting any younger, thinking 'let's just crash'.
心が通う時に
When hearts connect...
魂が叫ぶ
...the soul screams.
Woo!
Get back, you're trash!
どぶねずみのように
Like a sewer rat...
Let's just crash 気高く生きるんだ
Let's just crash, living nobly.
俺が通る今すぐにどけ
I'm passing through, get out of my way now!
Let's riot!
Get back, you're trash! 掃き溜めで希望を
Get back, you're trash! Finding hope in a dump...
Let's just crash 積み上げていくんだ
Let's just crash, I'll pile them up...
頂から高らかに笑え
Laugh loudly from the top!
Lose control!
美しき理想を
That beautiful ideal...
Heads will roll! 汚してくる奴は
Heads will roll! The bastards who dirty it...
誰だ一体？ 誰だ一体？
Who is it? Who is it?
誰だったとしても
No matter who it is...
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves
under my pressure,
there'll be no one to save.
Where is your pride,
your human will to survive?
Was it just
empty words
for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
Now all that remains is
delusion and decay
'Cause of you, I live this way
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
You're just confused!
Lightning never strikes twice in the same spot
So, go ahead and run up on me 'til you get your shot
I see the weapon that you're hiding, come on, ready or not
Another life and you would never give a second thought
Thinking your pride's different than mine
Ticking all your vital signs off
But we still gotta protect all our friends from our enemies
Wouldn't you agree?
Forged in fires of hell, God can't betray you
If I'm a fallen angel, what does that make you?
I'm not debasing myself to see the same view
When it's your pride on the line, no one can save you from mine
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
Thank you for coming today everyone, it's over!
No, we're back, we're back.
Just some technical difficulties.
Staff-san's on the beats.
Everyone calm down, it's fine, it's fine. We're okay.
Welcome, welcome!
Hey, you know what? It fits... It fits the theme of the show.
That there would be some technical issues.
So it can't be perfect, right? But I'm looking at your comments...
And thank you, by the way, to Shiori for the raid as well.
Hope the outfit reveal went super good.
Hi, Dead Beats!
Hello!
We're here, we're here!
We're finally at the Disasterpiece venue.
And I'm reading your comments, but...
...there might be a little bit of lag, so sorry about that.
Anyway, check it out. I've got a special...
...I've got my own special mic that is definitely what I'm using to talk and not the headset.
But check it out!
Oh, I'll show it... I'll show it to you closer later.
I've got... Oh, hello! Liz is here too! Amazing senpai! Woo-hoo!
Thank you!
Welcome to Disaster Show, everyone.
Disasterpiece is out at long last!
Hooray, we did it! We finally got here.
And now, I'm going to do some songs for you guys.
Wow, akasupa came... I can't read it right now, but I'll have to read them later. Thank you so much.
The new art style is so nice.
This is some Unreal Engine powered, Dead Beats. Unreal power.
It's stunning, isn't it? I bet you want to get a closer look.
And maybe get some screenshots of Mori Calliope's face.
So let me show you. Staff-san is holding a special camera.
よろしくお願いします！ おー！
Nice to meet you! Oh!
Hey hey! Hold on, I think this is my normal hand.
All right, I'm gonna take some... I'm gonna get some good...
some good reactions for you guys. Hold on a second,
here I go. Check this, check this shit out.
Huh?! Ah!
I'm being silly. I'm being silly because I need time to chill right now.
You sound amazing, Calli. I'm doing my best.
Whew! And the outfit, too! Look at how shiny... shiny.
It just... it looks so good. And my face, my face looks good too.
Oh gosh, I'm still not used to holding the camera though, so I'm trying to make it perfect,
but I might have to edit things... a little bit. You might have to edit it later.
Hold on. No, I got this. Okay.
RTX on.
Very realistic... I can wink. Hold on, here... here I go.
Wait, hold... hold on. I got... I...
I suck at this. That's okay though, that's okay. It's fine if it's not perfect.
I think I can wink. Check this out.
がんばれ！
Do your best!
Close enough!
It looks good. And look behind us! We've got the track from the 'Let's Just Crash' MV.
And we've got Challenger's car behind me.
And we've also got King's car as well.
And then... well, you Dead Beats, you're all on your way to the next stage, so you're not there yet.
But let me show you my mic. マイク見せたいから。ありがとうございまーす。オッケー。
But let me show you my mic. Because I want to show you my mic. Thank you very much! Okay.
Check out the mic. This is the special Mori Calliope mic that was made specially for me. Isn't it cool?
Look at how sick. The red and the roses. I'm obsessed.
I'm obsessed with it. So anyway, that's what's going on, Dead Beats. This is the actual future of Hololive. Well...
I mean, the technology will only get better and better, so... anyway, this is exciting.
You guys want to see some more songs? Um, also buy the album!
I'm all out of shape. I feel like MCs, I'm like good when it's an actual live, like, in a venue,
but then if it's like this, I screw up a lot, so... oh well. New merch?
Not neces- well, I mean, this... Oh, you're talking about the mic? You want the mic as merchandise?
I'll think about it.
Not a bad idea. I think Peace-san is listening to that, so I'll have to talk to her about it later.
Welcome to the future.
Anyway, Dead Beats, I gotta do a quick costume change and scene change.
So let's get out of here, and I'll sing some more songs...
and meet up with you hither and thither. That's probably the wrong word to use in that situation, but thank you, Staff-san!
All right, I'll catch you guys there. Time for a 変身！ 行くぞ！
All right, I'll catch you guys there. Time for a transformation! Let's go!
不確かな物語に
In an uncertain story,
勝ち獲るはアイデンティティ
what I will win is identity
荒れ果てた手札を
The ruined hand of cards
しまい込んで
I'll tuck them away
時に止まらない愛を捧げきっちゃう
And sometimes dedicate my unstoppable love entirely
感情はノンフィクションで喜怒哀楽
My emotions are non-fiction, with ups and downs
一進一退 際どい勝負
Back and forth, a close battle
失敗も 絶望も 味わえばワンダフル
Even failure and despair, if tasted, are wonderful
ゴールド・アンバランス
Gold Unbalance
意味なんてないような世界で
In a world that seems to have no meaning,
偶然を重ねた光
the light piled up from coincidences
脈打つ鼓動 誰にもなれない防壁
A pulsing heartbeat, unable to become anyone else
言葉を紡いでゆく
I will spin my words
なめんじゃないよ
Don't underestimate me!
小さな勇気と覚悟があれば十分
A small amount of courage and resolve is enough
強気で行こうよ
Let's go strong!
ハートをセッション ２人ならやれるさ
Our hearts in a session, if it's the two of us we can do it!
Back to back no matter what's
俺達の無敵なラッキースポット
Our invincible lucky spot
世界中を止めてたってパス
Even if the whole world stops, we pass
シャットアウト 誰も邪魔できないこのルート
Shut out, nobody can get in the way of this route
何回だって何万通りだって
No matter how many times, in tens of thousands of ways
上がるから ルーザー
We rise, loser
うざいくらいどん底に這いつくばって
Crawl on the bottom, annoyingly deep
這い上がって地獄から勝ったら
Climb up, and if we win from hell...
ループに馴染めないルートを無限に
An infinite route that doesn't fit the loop
ありふれた道じゃない
It's not a common road
選んだ道を歩むの僕らと
Walking the path we chose, with us
冷めない夢を笑えばいいさ
You can just laugh at the dream we won't wake up from
最大のアンバランス
The ultimate unbalance
どうせなら狂おしいほどにしてよ
If anything, make it maddeningly so
初めての涙より狂った覚悟を
More than your first tears, show me a crazy resolve
敗者と勝者のドロー、ドロー、ドロー！
A draw, draw, draw between winner and loser!
かき消された不条理なノイズ
Drowned out, unreasonable noise
振り払い Don't worry
Shake it off, don't worry
覚悟さえあれば消えない
As long as you have resolve, it won't fade
２人ならやれるさ
If it's the two of us, we can do it!
...手を替え品を替え
...changing hands, changing goods
感情はノンフィクションで
Emotions are nonfiction
喜怒哀楽 一心同体
Joy, anger, sorrow, and pleasure, one heart, one body
一切合切の衝動
All impulses
失敗も成功も味わえ
Taste both failure and success
我らゴールデンバディ
We are golden buddies
エンタメライダー
Entertainment rider
人生賭け駆け抜け
Betting life, racing through
絶望も栄光も
Despair and glory
Lemme see you fight back
どうなったって何も変わらないんだって
No matter what happens, nothing will change
ミームされた現実に囚われて
Caught in a meme'd reality
This life where we're stuck taking chances
飽き飽きしてんでしょ？
You're fed up, aren't you?
We're living in a world with no direction
Reach out with our light 'till we make a connection
Tearing the walls apart
Facing it all, side by side
Once again, it's us against the world
舐めんじゃねーよ
Don't underestimate me
本能をヒリつかせて
Letting instincts tingle
本物見せつけろ
Show the real thing
圧倒絶頂 アンバランスを
Overwhelming, climax, dance in imbalance
踊れ
Dance
So just how far can I go?
I think I already know
That view that I want to see
A place in history that's mine
I don't know why we're always side by side but worlds apart
I don't know why we're always side-by-side but worlds apart
It's trial by fire
I'm fighting for a place where we can breathe
When fight takes over, I might just take it out on you
'Cause you're too good to be true
Struggling but carrying on
I'll go where nobody has gone
I'm searching again and again and again
For something only I can do
Asking why I can't be someone else
Despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark
But still in my heart
Your words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go but I can't erase you
I'm falling behind but I won't chase you
I'm swallowing my pride until the time that I can face you
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
It's never been enough but I'll keep on writing a story that's evolving
From the day that I decided I'm alone
I don't belong anywhere anymore, it was my decision
I'm gonna break down the door to your heart without your permission
There was nothing that could make me stay
Remember it like it was yesterday
Hanging on every word you'd say
What if I walked away?
How can I still carry on?
Someday when you're finally gone
I'm searching again and again and again
For something only I can do
The truth is I can't be someone else
Despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark
But still in my heart
My words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go and you can't erase me
'Cause I'm the only one that could ever replace me
Igniting every line until the time that I can face me
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
It's never been enough but I'll keep on writing a story that evolved me
Since the day that I'm deciding I'm alright
So just how far can I go?
I think I already know
That view that I want to see
I still could make it in time
あ、皆さん、Welcome to the next stage!
Ah, everyone, welcome to the next stage!
パチパチ、thank you for the パチパチ。Thank you so much、どうでしたか？
Pachipachi, thank you for the pachipachi. Thank you so much! What did you guys think?
見て、このアウトフィット...
And check it out! We got this outfit...
おどけてみせてるよ、ごめんね。
Now I'm being goofy, I'm sorry.
パチパチパチパチ、本当にありがとうございます！
Pachipachi pachipachi, thank you so much!
あれ、Odaいる？またラグがあったらごめんなさい。
Oh, is, is Oda here? Sorry if there's like a, again, just lag.
私たちが使ってるこのマシン、超高品質だから...
This is a very high quality machine we're using...
...broadcast to all of you, so there might be a bit of lag.
But I'm happy that I can read some of your comments in real time.
Thank you so much, you guys. Makes me very happy. Pachi pachi pachi, thank you.
Oh, but we might, we might need to refresh the chat because now it has stopped moving.
Anyway, in the meantime... Oh, there it goes, there it goes. Oh wow, I think it just exploded when Dad entered the chat, anyway.
Thank you so much, you guys. I hope you guys have been liking the new songs.
MOMENTO was one of the new songs that I wrote.
I wish I could go into it in a longer MC or talk more about it, cuz there's so much I want to say...
...about that song. Um, but it's, it's, it's... Oh, oh, hold on, hold on. I'm frozen.
I'm frozen in place!
Okay, we're good, we're good!
大丈夫。Sorry, ZA WARUDO! No problem, no problem.
I'm okay. Sorry, ZA WARUDO! No problem, no problem.
Here, for now though, instead of going into talking about the lyrics...
...which I'll probably do during the next, during the next stream.
We'll find some time before or after I play a game, and then I'll talk about the songs.
Until... hang on, hold on a second. You know, Kenty couldn't be here for Gold Unbalance,
but you know what I've learned from Kenty's song is that fan service is very important.
I used to be really like nervous about doing some fansa and stuff like that...
...cuz like, I'm, I'm an embarrassed person. But, but Kenty so easily is just like...
...'Oh like chu chu' to the fans, like wink...
...and like, I don't know, he's so good at the fansa...
...and like, with no shame whatsoever. I thought to myself, 'I need to try and do some of that too.'
So, um, I'm going to do that. So... Chu!
Probably not very good at it, but... Chu!
Hold on, I'll start... no, it's perfect because ZA WARUDO!
ZA WARUDO, it stopped it for you so that you could get a little picture.
Watch where you're pointing that camera. Hold on a second, I'm not pointing it anywhere suspicious.
What are you talking about? Can I do... Can I do a funny face now?
Ahhh! Ahhh!
Oh no. Anyway...
...so here's this outfit, and it looks so high quality.
And hey, you notice something about the stage?
This is the coin from the beginning of Gold Unbalance! Dead Beats, look!
意味なんてないような世界で
In this world that seems meaningless
不確かな物語に
In this story full of variables
Anyway, check it out. Hold on. Look at how cool the stage is, by the way.
Are you checking out the stage? Look at those... the roses, the moon!
It reminds me of when I debuted from Universal Music Japan,
and I had the moon in the background of, what was it, I think it was one of my debut albums.
So cool, looking very respectful. Oh, I know. You don't need to tell me.
I already know. Of course, as always.
I wish I could put it as high as possible. Whoa, my eyes are glowing in the darkness!
What about the effects? The effects are also so cool for this show, I can't believe it.
We have some even more amazing stages coming up. But if you guys haven't checked out the album yet,
it's full of brand new songs.
Um, one of them I composed myself, and then all the songs, all the English in my songs is written by me.
...except for maybe Cult Following, and that's it.
But that's in a different album, so it's safe to say all the English lyrics are mine.
And then for Japanese lyrics, I basically tell the lyricists what I want it to be about
and give them my lyrics too so they know what to write about. But yeah,
so it's full of my thoughts and my feelings. I'm going to put this one... I really don't need to keep holding this. ありがとうございます！
so it's full of my thoughts and my feelings. I'm going to put this one... I really don't need to keep holding this. Thank you very much!
But yeah, it's full of my thoughts and my feelings about the world and the world around me.
And, uh, this time it's a bit darker, a bit more emotional, but...
you guys know that I have a lot of emotions inside of me, and...
I feel like the best way to deal with those is to put them out in the world in like a productive way.
I love Shuden... 終電, last train. That's what it means in Japanese.
I love Shuden... Last train, last train. That's what it means in Japanese.
I can't wait to talk more about that song too, that's also very close to my heart, that song.
I want to say so much more but I probably need to wrap it up.
Amazing per usual, thank you! That's nice, I dig it. Thank you so much.
The lyrics are all amazing. Thank you, Dead Beats. I appreciate, I appreciate all of you.
Thank you, we'll have... we have some more to do here, so I can't go on forever. This is a very long MC.
So, let's do another...
変身...
Transformation...
And... 行くぞ！
And... here we go!
So just how far could I go
Find...
Don't look back, look forward
Don't look back
I was tripping and falling and kept on looking for something to bring me up
Others guess there's no such thing as hope, hold me down or what
Walk the thin ice and it shatter to pieces
More than a reach it seems so my chances decrease
A spinner, a cynical, as I just might be
Our endless, unwritten, I think I'm about to break free
My limits closing around me, they're sounding less and less real
Because my heart is beating louder than the fear that I feel
My mind's already made up, not afraid of unrealistic dreams
Looking for my spring, sixteen, so I can walk on water
Used to look for perfection, now it's progress
Every dues paid part of the process
And this moment, maybe it's our last
Not knowing if I never try
Changing faces, enveloped in moonlight
I can see stars now
Running through an endless sky
Find, find, find what you need to live life how you want it
Don't look back, look forward
Find something you can move toward
Don't look back
I fight another day, these battles inside and outside
Have all that I wanted, why am I still not satisfied?
Lost taxi signs and street signs, the city mirrored in my mind
Alleys to level, to forever defy
Yeah the world decline, I was always dope but they were like 'nah'
Now it's up to me to rise, keep them little surprised
My mind never slides, always riding high
Thrive on this lovely hate, my view's the sky
A warning, all my shadows still in worn-out shoes
With everything to gain, even more to give up and lose
This time you gotta choose, no excuse, tired of sleeping, gotta move
Envisioning tomorrows that I have the guts to refuse
Red skies, rain, but I lost my aim
More things change, the more they stay the same
Burning strife and shame
This pain will be my strength
And this moment, maybe it's our last
Not knowing if I never try
Changing faces, enveloped in moonlight
I can see stars now, guiding me to fight
For this moment, we're no longer broken
Never leaving love behind
This morning, I wake up to sunrise
Living with resolve now, running with a fearless stride
Find, find, find what you need to live life how you want it
Don't look back, look forward
Find something you can move toward
Don't look back
雨は上がった 君がため
The rain has stopped for your sake
花咲いた 明日は雨
The flowers bloomed, but tomorrow it will rain
為せば成るなら何だって 惜しみのない pain
If anything is possible, then let it be; this pain without regret
Falling on and on 惜しむなよ
Falling on and on, do not regret it
メッセージ宛てて喰らえば 妄想ねじよるお払い
If you receive a message, it's a delusion-twisting exorcism
混成抽出 救い出すとお通り トラブルキープアライブ
Mixed extraction, pass through when saved, trouble keep alive
気は上がり気味に達して 空中急に Infinity
My spirit is rising, suddenly reaching infinity in mid-air
気に病んで本当かい？ 本当に？
Are you really worrying about it? Really?
上昇してくモノは消去したって死に...
Even if what rises is erased, it won't die...
And underneath the blue sky, still choose to sing 'cause I refuse to die
Grit teeth and try to look past the pain, but these flowers are watered in acid rain
And I can't change, believe that I tried and tried, my grief is a scene that I left behind, if I could find a place to rest out of mind that can live for a lifetime
Since day one, I've sung all I needed to say
I've got a feeling that I'll still sing anyway
さぁ、遠く霞む未来の向こうに
Now, beyond the hazy, distant future
照らされた道に 大惨事の愛
On the illuminated road, a disastrous love
焦げ付くほどの奔流を浴て
Bathed in a burning torrent
Hello, hello, 声を上げて daydream
Hello, hello, raise your voice, daydream
Let's maintain
名シーン chapter 苦楽を経る
Famous scenes, chapters, through joys and sorrows
要 妄想 燃料 酔っ払う
Needing delusion, fuel, getting drunk
今世中 達成する 成し遂げる
Achieving in this life, accomplishing
トラベル トラブル 闊歩ライフ
Travel, trouble, strutting life
I said goodbye to false gods
But even cats hide their claws
Nobody's ever truly what they seem
With the limelight gleam to conceal the flaws
I can't escape the scroll and it takes a toll on me
Dead-end thoughts still loop and hold on me
Did it even matter in the end that I held out?
Sorry, I could never be the god I was sold to be
So to speak, an idol in fool's gold
Living out the role I was told to be
I'll be old and free in a matter of centuries
Wondering if there was a point to me
Was thinking for sure I'd be long gone by now
But I found a place to belong
People I can't live without
Follow me, please この渡り廊下
Follow me, please, this corridor
暗闇からの園へ
To the garden from the darkness
トゲすり抜けて 辿り着く
Slip through the thorns and reach it
Hello, hello 今宵も insomnia
Hello, hello, tonight's insomnia too
Let's maintain
In a world where nothing is certain
Except that someday we will say goodbye
I wanna keep my eyes off the sky
砂漠みたいな味 desert
Taste like a desert, desert
Desert!
Sorrow 孵化する未来の mercy
Sorrow, hatching future's mercy
微動だにしない異彩の愛に
To a unique love that doesn't budge
焦げ付くほどの hold you 抱擁と
Hold you with a burning embrace
Hello, hello 今宵の day dreamer
Hello, hello, tonight's day dreamer
Let's maintain
Shoutは changing 喝采
Shout is changing, applause
邪魔させん bashing
Don't let them interfere, bashing
Chanceは起死回生
Chance is a revival
エッサエッサ fire
Essa essa fire
Shoutは changing 喝采
Shout is changing, applause
邪魔させん bashing
Don't let them interfere, bashing
Chanceは起死回生
Chance is a revival
エッサエッサ fire
Essa essa fire
みなさん！
Everyone! Woo!
どうでしたか？「天誅 & mercy」。
How was that? 'Tenshu & mercy'.
あの曲を書くことで思い出したんですけど、そう、私は今でも...
Writing that song reminded me, yes, I still can...
ライブでのパフォーマンスがめちゃくちゃ難しい曲を書けるんだって！
...write songs that are extremely difficult to perform live!
いこうぜ！
Let's go!
変わらないものもあるよね、Dead Beats。
Some things never change, Dead Beats.
でも、このライブの技術はどう？ちょっと待って。
But, hey, how about the tech for this concert? Hold on.
みんな私の後ろの桜見えてる？ディテールがさ。
Are you guys seeing this sakura behind me? Like, the detail?
あ、ちょっと待って。もう一回、この桜の木めちゃくちゃパワフルだよ！
Oh, hold on. Sorry, again, the sakura tree is very powerful!
すごく大きなアイテムだし、めちゃくちゃ詳細だし。
It's such a- such a big item and so detailed.
たまに動きを止めるけど、大丈夫、大したことじゃない。
Sometimes I stop moving, that's okay, it doesn't matter.
うおー！パチパチパチパチ！
Woo! Clap clap clap clap!
10点中1000点だったよ。完璧、いこう。
That was a thousand out of ten. Nailed it, let's go.
ありがとうございます。完璧ですね。水を飲みます。
Thank you very much. That was clean. Drink water.
それは本当にいいアイデアだね。
That's a really good idea.
水、水、水、水...
Water, water, water...
大丈夫、大丈夫。見えない水ね。
It's fine, it's fine, the invisible water.
でも、みんなPhantomimeの時のことを思い出すと...
But, I mean, if you guys think back to Phantomime...
みんながプロダクションとか品質がヤバいって話してるのをよく見かけるけど。
I see a lot of you guys talking about, like, oh, the production, the quality is so crazy.
このあたりは本当にパワフルなことが行われているんだ。
It's very, very powerful stuff going on around here.
スタッフは本当に大成功を収めてくれたよ。スタッフには本当に感謝してる。
And they really knocked it out of the park with this. I just have so much thanks to give to my staff.
最後にちょっとしたクレジットロールが流れるから、スタッフのみんなに大きな拍手を。
Uh, be sure- we have a little credit roll at the end that will play, and, you know, that's my staff, and big up to them.
でも、Phantomimeのコンサートを覚えている？
But, remember the Phantomime concert...
Phantomimeのリリースに合わせてやった、あの小さなミニライブ。すごくクールだったよね。
you guys, that we did, the little mini live for the release of Phantomime, which was really cool.
あれはすでに、これらのショーのためのさらに優れた品質の始まりの余韻があったよね？
That already had, like, the- the echoes of the beginning of even better quality for these shows, right?
じゃあ、次はどうなるか想像できる？
Well, can you imagine what the next is gonna look like?
だって、今すでにこんな感じなんだよ。
I mean, if this- if this looks like this right now,
ここからどこへ行くか想像できる？考えるだけで本当にワクワクするよ。
I mean, can you imagine where we go from here? I mean, it's really exciting to think about.
今から20年後のDead Beats。20年後はどうなってるかな？誰にもわからないね。
20 years from now, Dead Beats, 20 years from now, who knows?
たぶんあの桜の木くらい詳細になってると思う。でも心配しないで、私らしさは残るから。
I'll probably be as detailed as that sakura tree. But- but don't worry, it won't be too much, it'll still feel like me.
それだけは確実にするよ。
I'll- I'll make sure about that.
これはもうギリギリのラインを攻めてると思うけど、もっと顔を動かしたりしたいな。
This is already kind of toeing the line, I think, but I'd love to, like, move my face a little bit more and stuff like that.
葉っぱが舞い散る方が劇的かな？それはいい指摘だけど、もし...
Would be more dramatic if leaves were scattering around? That's a good point, however, Dead Beat, you say that...
もし今桜が散っていたら、このスタジオのすべてのPCが火を噴くと思う。
...if sakura was falling right now, I think that- I think that every PC, uh, in this studio would catch on fire.
いいアイデアだけどね！
Great idea, though!
自撮りタイム！
Selfie time!
よし、いくよ。またこのカメラを使うよ。おっと、よし。
Okay, here we go. Now I'm using this camera again. Whoa, okay.
下がってるよ、下がってる。
You guys can get- I'm backing up, I'm backing up.
少し近くで見てみよう。後ろの桜の木、あれは3Dなんだ...
A bit of a closer look. That sakura tree behind, that's- that is 3D...
ちょっと待って、いける、これならいける。
Hold on, I got- I got this.
あれは3Dなんだよ。
That- that is 3D.
みんな笑ってる、笑ってるよ、私を笑ってるな！
They're laughing, they're laughing, you're laughing, you're laughing at me!
やめて！
Stop it!
ストップ！
Stop!
いつかみんなにもっと怒った顔を見せられるようになるから、楽しみにしててね。
Someday I'll be able to make an angrier face at you, so get ready for that.
モリ・カリオペがもっと怒った顔を見せられるようになる、それも楽しみの一つだね、Dead Beats。
That's another thing to look forward to, Dead Beats, when Mori Calliope can make an angrier face at you.
talking to you.
Ooh, check out my nails.
Ah. Even cats hide their claws.
claws.
Hey. This is a cute little screenshot, too. I heard from...
...my Pi-san. My Pi-san showed a little piece of paper...
...to me that said that hashtag Disaster Show entered, entered the trends in USA!
Thank you so much for that!
Dead Beats, keep it coming, and some folks are like,
"Mori, I can't believe that this is free!" Of course it's free, 'cause I know,
I know that the majority of you guys bought the album, so
might as well be free.
And if you didn't buy it, you at least have been streaming it.
So it just, it feels, it just feels right, I guess, to do...
...what I can to make it worth it to you guys...
...even more. Even more so.
Hi. You guys remember this outfit?
It's a little on the older side, but check it out.
You guys remember, right, from my very first solo show,
New Underworld Order.
Looking good, right?
I'm looking good?
Hi. Hi.
Trying to get as much camera screen time as I can.
Buy the album, buy the album, say the Dead Beats.
おねがいします！
Please!
If you could, I'd be very happy.
Woah, this is kind of a cool shot with the sakura.
Woah, this is kind of a cool shot with the cherry blossoms.
My eyes are glowing in the darkness. Hey there.
Hi.
うわぁ！
Whoa!
I'll keep trying to make silly faces though.
That's something that will never change about me.
This is a screenshot moment.
Whenever it stops, it means it's a screenshot moment.
Maybe. Anyway, it's time to move on because I still have a couple songs...
...to sing for you guys.
I think this one will end up being longer than Phantomime, which is a good thing.
I get to sing even more for you.
What songs will they be, I wonder?
ありがとうスタッフさん！
Thank you, staff!
And, yeah, so...
I guess it's about time that we move on to the next spot.
Looking good!
Thanks, Dead Beats. You want to see my high kicks? I've been working on them.
おいしょ！
Heave-ho!
And...
おいしょ！
Heave-ho!
My high kicks.
おいしょ！
Heave-ho!
Next year, I'm going to kick even higher, you'll see.
Anyway, that's some randomness right there.
Let's go.
Next...
変身。
transformation.
行くぞ！
Let's go!
I put my lust and illusions to bed
Still, you're creeping through my thoughts tonight
Now I know it's only skin deep
Drawn like a moth to flames inside your heat...
...heat, heat, heat
Consider myself fine,
but I'm crossing every line,
drunk on love that's not mine.
Heaven sent you, way too late,
kiss of death and take the bait.
Past lives and loaded dice, white lies and alibis,
fingers tracing a design,
a medicine I never swallowed right.
Still no enemy to fight, not in this light.
Stolen whispers, don't ask and don't tell,
step in my world, welcome to hell.
Sinking down in your deep black...
We fall,
we break,
we drown in fire,
lost inside this dark desire.
No love,
no faith,
just you and I,
dancing to the end of time.
Ba-la-la-la-la-la-la
End of time, end of time, end of time
Ba-da-da-da-da-da-da...
I still blame myself for this hate,
stream that overflows, never dissipates.
I let words unsaid rot slowly, tainted and unholy,
and though...
watch,
wait,
cold steel pressed against your neck.
Ba-da-da-da-da-da-da...
End of time, end of time, end of time,
one last breath before we die.
The sight of you intoxicates.
when it takes us to rest
Six feet under, side by side
We fall
We break
We drown in fire
Lost inside this doctor's desire
No love
No fate
Just you and I
Dancing through the end of time
Bye, la-la-la-la-la-la-la
Ashes fall from blackened skies
All that's left is you and I
Drown inside this love of mine
Da-ra-ra-ra-ra-ra-ra
End of time, end of time
End of time
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though, my heart's beating to your song
Oh yeah?
Thinking hurry up, Orpheus, time's wasting!
Another late night, aimless dreaming
Then the day starts to call
Still got like a million deadlines to beat
In a red one, my back up against the wall
I got my headphones on, walk home is long
Dragging feet like I'm born to lose
Till somehow they're tapping along
To you-know-who's song, a melody I can't refuse
I'm walking on the street, you on my mind, can you feel the shame?
I know I get a little carried away, but we got music when there are no other words to say
See my heart has sparked when you look this way, can you send me some of the stage when you feel the same?
Now I'm in distress, you got me possessed, I might be obsessed, so let me get a little something off my chest, look...
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though, my heart's beating to your song
Oh yeah?
Thinking hurry up, Orpheus, time's wasting!
Tonight it's my turn to show you how I feel
Inside can be so, as long as you keep playing that guitar
Critics so loud, so predictable, they can see what I can't see, gonna wind up a star
Just discard my fear, my wonder, I wonder if it's enough
'Cause I'm in the line when I'm implying you're all that I've been thinking of
Maybe they'll call me delusional, but baby this could be real love
Give me one chance and I'll take... dance the night away
Now it's a game that I played before, but with the way the scene changed there is nothing you can blame me for
I'm talking TV screens, magazines, seen you in a couple of dreams, pictures up on every padded wall and floor
Always talking bad notes, time to desire a lover, so why'd you paint your nails up in my favorite color?
I got an attitude, just when it comes to you, see, our reality is kind of slipping out of view...
Never lost in the groove of somebody new, if it's devotion you're after, stay true
So are you noticing me, noticing me, noticing me? An illusion, but there's not a lot I guarantee
See my heart has sparked when you look this way, can you send me some of the stage when you feel the same?
You're strumming next to me, and I'm in ecstasy, and for the rest of the week, I'm depression free.
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though, my heart's beating to your song
Oh yeah?
Thinking hurry up, Orpheus, time's wasting!
Tonight it's my turn to show you how I feel
Inside can be so, as long as you keep playing that guitar
Critics so loud, so predictable, they can see what I can't see, gonna wind up a star
Never lost in the groove of somebody new, if it's devotion you're after, stay true
Just discard my fear, my wonder, I wonder if it's enough
'Cause I'm in the line when I'm implying you're all that I've been thinking of
Maybe they'll call me delusional, but baby this could be real love
Give me one chance and I'll take... dance the night away
Hey! Hey! Come on!
So let's blow this joint, and if the feeling's right, then we can make a little music of our own tonight, come on!
Hey! Hey!
Why you walking away? I got a lot to say, guess I'll save it for the next one!
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though, my heart's beating to our song
Oh yeah?
So hear me out, Orpheus, thinking next time, I'll show you what I really wanna do
I'm back deadbeats! Where'd the cats go?
Hey wait a minute, where're the cats at?
They were just here a second ago.
Deadbeats, check out what I can do. Hold on, get ready.
Are you ready? Check it out.
I'm obsessed with how this dress moves!
Deadbeats!
Almost... let me, let me back up a little bit. Look at how it moves!
Moves! Ooh, so scandalous!
Ah, don't look!
The physics are crazy!
How about those weird cats though, doing the dance?
It was so cute, the creature. Nice moves, thank you.
Thank you, Dead Beats. Whew!
Oh, that was fun. That was fun, Dead Beats.
I had such a good time with you guys today.
Actually, I mentioned to you guys my family...
My family came to glorious Nippon!
And actually, we kind of celebrated the release together.
I was, like, sneaking around some places that were selling the album...
...and then hearing my own music blasting on the speakers.
They were playing 'Orpheus',
they were playing... uh, 'Golden Balance', they were playing 'Let's Just Crash'.
And for the first time ever,
Dead Beats, walking around the store, I didn't feel like...
...embarrassed.
Which is a step in the right direction.
I feel like I've been getting better.
Dead Beats, I hope it was fun. It was so fun.
Dead Beats, I can't even explain...
...being able to be so proud and say, 'Look, that's my thing, they're playing my song
on the speaker.' It's so cool.
I mean, I went to karaoke with my little sister.
She told me that 'Die for You' was her favorite song of mine,
and 'Meta Meta', which made me very happy.
Those are her little sister reap favorites, and I sang...
I sang it for her and her friends because they really wanted to hear,
and they were like, 'Woah, free concert!'
It was really cool.
So yeah, there was that.
What else did I want to talk about?
I feel like, even today with today's show,
I feel like I'm getting more confident to do more things with my voice,
and I can do more things with my voice.
It's still a little rough and unpolished, but like, that's the point of Disaster-Piece
in general, right?
I'm working towards my masterpiece.
And maybe, um, it will take some time to get things exactly the way that I want.
Maybe I'll never get there, you know? But...
...I'm doing more with my voice, and even though it's new stuff and it needs polishing,
um, I'm really happy with it.
'What's my favorite song?' ask the Dead Beats.
Oh... I don't know, I like them for different reasons.
The one that maybe I'm proudest of is maybe 'Rivals and Equals',
because I still... I listen to that and I'm like, 'Yeah, that's really good.'
But then I also really like 'Shut In' for the lyrics as well.
...probably my favorite lyrics I've written in a long time.
Yeah, that's right. That Dead Beat says, 'It's about the journey.' Exactly.
I'm running out of time here, so let me get this jidori camera really quick, hold on.
Ah, yes. My eyes are glowing in the dark right now,
because we're in a dark area. But now I'm going to show you the skirt...
...let's get on the red. Can I get on the red?
Okay, I'm moving my chest, chest piece, which is myself, to the red. Look at the skirt.
It's kind of hard to see. Sorry, sorry!
Doing my best over here. Maybe it's better to view from the other side.
So look, this is the stage from 'Die for You' MV.
And then you can see, if we look this way, it's darkness...
...and then if we look this way, it's darkness!
But it's still really cool. Whoa, what was that?
It kind of looks like the wall that maybe leads to the hospital, I don't know.
Respectfully, of course. Peace.
It's so... it's so dark in here. Peace. Peace.
I'll... I'll make it work. Hi. Hello.
It is I, Mori Calliope, and I just...
...released a new album. It's my best work so far.
And in Japan, we got number one...
...album on iTunes ranking, yay! For alternative music.
So let's see how much further we can push. Last time I checked in US, it was climbing...
...it was getting high up, but you know there's a lot of stiff competition there.
So, it's all good. If we don't reach number one, that's fine.
But I'd love for you guys to keep pushing for me,
if you would like to. Spread the word and keep listening in all your favorite places.
Keep enjoying the album, and I will keep making...
...I'll keep doing stuff that only I can do,
like writing Mori Calliope lyrics!
So, yeah. I guess that's about it.
I want to give a special thanks to Dead Beats and to staff-san. Itsumo arigatou gozaimasu.
My staff is the best. Please look at the credits so you know who to say thank you to.
Dead Beats, um, and yeah, post it everywhere.
Thank you, thank you, Dead Beats. I'm reading y'all's comments. 'Eat the camera'?
I think that's a bad idea. I think they'll get mad at me if I do that.
I think... I think it's going to break things. So, anyway, that's the end of the jidori camera.
Um, anyway, we are back here.
So I guess that's... oh, wrong microphone. Like I said, I'm using a headset.
No, no, no. Really, microphone. Trust, trust.
But you know, with the technical stuff, there's always a little bit of magic...
...involved, right? In order to get the level of quality that we've got.
Thank you guys always for cheering for me and being excited about my work.
Now, there is no encore because life has no encore. So sorry about that.
I know there are a lot of songs you guys want to hear me sing.
The good news is, I will be singing them soon for you on my streams.
So tune into my streams, and...
My karaoke streams and streams where I'm singing my stuff
and, uh, future shows.
If there's a song that you really want to hear, like I know a lot of you probably wanted to hear Shuten, for example. So...
If you want to hear it, you got to stay tuned and come to the next one.
Like I said, life has no encore.
So, um...
what I want you to do now is just rewatch the live.
And then go listen to the music. Links in the description.
Thank you, Dead Beats, always for cheering for me.
Thank you for supporting what I do.
I'm strange, but you know...
this is really fun. I'm glad I get to do this every day.
And I put my whole heart into the new release. So...
I'll see you guys tomorrow. We're playing a game.
There's, there's a game stream tomorrow.
See you guys around. Thanks again, everyone!
I'm Mori, hope you'll remember me.
Peace!
[Title: DISASTER SHOW - Mori Calliope]
[Title: DISASTERPIECE - Mori Calliope]
Orpheus, time's a wasting...
Tonight, it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
Sometimes it feels like you're playing that guitar for me and only me
Critics so loud, so predictable, they can't see what I can see
Let's ride, yeah!
Get back! Get back!
Pack your dummy, pack your bomb, bomb!
Let's just crash!
So get out of the way!
くだらねぇキャラばかりに
All these useless characters
笑い
laughing
殺して
Kill them
美しく
beautifully
歪な世界で
In this warped world
ほら ぶつけ重ねた光
See, the clashing, overlapping light
脈打つ鼓動 誰も止められない
Pulsing heartbeat that no one can stop
言葉を紡いで
Spinning words
We fall
we break
we drown in fire
lost inside this dark desire
Sorrow 孵化する未来の mercy
Sorrow, mercy of the hatching future
Mercy! Mercy!
微動だにしない異彩の愛に
In this unbudging, eccentric love
偽物だって
Saying I'm a fake
Tell me what I'm to not say
What's your problem?
夜を一人
All alone in the night
あたしが迷う
I get lost
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure
There'll be no one to save
巡る巡る 運命に抗って
Resisting the revolving, revolving fate
出会いを 迷いを 酔わせた
Making encounters and hesitation drunk
The strangers I followed with stars in...
So I keep on waiting
Wanting...
Faking you're someone you're not
Reaching... Longing...
No, I can't be someone else
Despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape, we're hoping in the dark
but still...
クラクラするでしょ？
You feel dizzy, right?
ほら、ホラ、溶けそう
See, see, about to melt
そうでしょ？ FLASH BANG
Right? FLASH BANG
In this moment
Maybe eyes open wide
Knowing if I never try
夢を夢見る度
Every time I dream a dream
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I end up thinking about the meaning of being born
あぁ 美しい青い日々
Ah, beautiful blue days
We fall
we break
we drown in fire
lost inside this dark desire
No love
no faith