(
"ai_sub_version": "2.6.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 13,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Kikkerikii!
Thank you all so much for coming to
Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis'
first concert, Day 2, Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara, and next to me is...
Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening everyone!
This is Ninomae Ina'nis!
That's right, it is finally time to start Day 2!
Is everyone hyped?!
Hype, hype, hype, hype!
All right, before we kick things off, of course,
we have some important safety rules
and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of
recording equipment are strictly prohibited...
...during the performance. However,
if you are watching from home,
screenshots are allowed.
Please take lots of screenshots.
スクショはOKですよ！
Screenshots are okay!
Also, the venue is smoke-free,
so please refrain from smoking inside.
Unless you're smoking hot like me!
We've heard that one before.
If you start, un-feeling well...
(I'm feeling well...)
Unfeeling well!
If you start feeling unwell at any point,
please don't push yourself.
Just reach out to the nearest staff member
for help, and drink water.
For everyone's safety, please avoid any
dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This once again, no matter how hyped it is,
includes moshing, diving...
...sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively,
or throwing objects towards the stage.
Climbing onto the stage, intentionally
blocking the aisles,
or rushing towards the front is not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting,
erratic lightstick movements,
or any extreme motions that might interfere
with the experience of those around you.
Be considerate.
If you don't follow the instructions of
our staff, you may be asked to leave.
Yeah, please keep in mind that the venue,
organizers, performers, and staff...
...cannot be held responsible for accidents,
equipment damage, or trouble
caused by failing to follow instructions.
So you stumbled over the same words.
It's hard, okay? I'm trying my best here.
I can't read.
Additionally, any costs for damage resulting
from ignoring these rules
will be the responsibility of the person.
There are cameras in the venue for filming
and photography today,
and you might appear in the footage.
These may be used for promotional purposes,
so please keep that in mind.
And finally, just like yesterday,
the concert will be in two parts.
There's a part for Wawa and a part for me,
so please look forward to them!
And yeah, that is it for the rules.
The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Have fun!
See you soon, bye bye!
INA! INA! INA! INA!
Enlightened by the powers that be
The ruler of a world run on INAsanity
It’s clear to me they still can’t see
I’m just a normal girl
Empowered by the Ancient One's call
We’re gonna be pun-stoppable, we’re not a cult
Nonsensical and nautical
Adventures lie in wait!!
Gimme a ONE EIGHT!!
ICHI! NI! SAN! SHI!
ONE! TWO! THREE! FOUR!
INA! INA! INA-INA-INA!
Sing with me!
世界を守るために タコになろう
To protect the world, let's become Takos
ICHI! NI! SAN! SHI!
ONE! TWO! THREE! FOUR!
INA! INA! INA-INA-INA!
良いタコになれますように
May you become good Takos
皆さん一緒に踊りましょう
Everyone, let's dance together
Let's talk about the future to be
Rewriting all of history in urgency
With cookies as our currency
This place can finally heal
Insubordination won't fly
Or else I'm making takoyaki
Gimme a ONE EIGHT!!
ICHI! NI! SAN! SHI!
ONE! TWO! THREE! FOUR!
INA! INA! INA-INA-INA!
私の命は 運ぶためで
My life is for carrying things
You could use some more
愛を感謝を ありがたい
Love and gratitude, I'm thankful
ICHI! NI! SAN! SHI!
ONE! TWO! THREE! FOUR!
INA! INA! INA-INA-INA!
ICHI! NI! SAN! SHI!
ONE! TWO! THREE! FOUR!
INA! INA! INA-INA-INA!
Am I into my song? Am I striking a chord with you?
String you along so that I can make a board of you
80 million strong and we're set to do some more to do
Everybody shout! DOMINATION!
Can I tap into your emotion? Do I have you in my best?
I don't want to hear you say that you're not in the rest
That your favorite devotion isn't all I request
Can you dare you to become our greatest creation?
Oya oya...
Oh my, oh my...
A cute little Tako has stumbled way down here
Experimentation might be necessary
Takos, we have to cook!
ひっくりかえして 丸くして
Flip it over and make it round
コロコロまわして 焦がさずに
Roll it around and don't burn it
外はカリっと 中ふわふわ
Crunchy on the outside, fluffy on the inside
Like the power to be
the ruler of a world run on insanity.
It's clear to me they still can't see,
I'm just a normal girl
empowered by the Ancient Ones' call.
We're gonna be unstoppable,
we're not a cult.
Nonsensical and illogical,
adventures lie in wait.
So talk about the future to be,
rewriting all our history.
In emergency, with cookies as our currency,
this place feels finally real.
Enough of the Ina-tion's won't lie,
or something-something-something,
takoyaki or takos
before they die-die-die.
Dimensionality!
Welcome to my world!
私のもの　そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine.
洗脳！　ごぼう！　数百年の財宝
Brainwashing! Burdock! Hundreds of years of treasure
この船に眠る
lie dormant in this ship.
Hey everyone! Get ready to dance off for day 2! Are you ready?!
古びた伝説は
The ancient legend...
呪われた幽霊船に
...is on the cursed ghost ship.
綴る夜の帳
Bound in the curtain of night.
そこに富みが残る
The wealth remains there.
海賊の夢があるのなら
If you have a pirate's dream,
確かめないでしょう
surely you'll go check it out?
海の仲間よ　若き娘よ
Comrades of the sea, young maidens,
命を賭して　後悔に繰り出してやろう
stake your lives and set sail on the voyage!
止まない　雨の弾丸で
With a ceaseless rain of bullets.
眩しいほど　この瞳焦がす
Dazzling enough to scorch these eyes,
生命の炎　茜の色彩
the flame of life, the color of madder red.
払う　宝石なのなら
If it's a jewel to be paid...
私のもの　そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine.
命の証を
The proof of life,
あなたの求める全てを
everything that you seek.
輝くはず　全て錆びついて
It should shine, but everything rusts,
それでも土塗れに　染み付くなら
yet if it remains covered in dirt,
泡沫と共に　鎮め
let it sink along with the bubbles.
暗い海底に蓄える
Stashed away on the dark seabed,
独唱の海賊の秘宝
the treasure of the soloist pirate,
惨憺　笑う
laughing miserably.
満月の金銀珠玉
Gold, silver, and pearls of the full moon,
七つの身の宝玉に
in the seven jewels of the sea,
滾る無念共
along with seething regrets.
綻び富みを狙う
Aiming for the fraying wealth,
愚か者の身も知らず
not knowing the state of the fool,
騒がし珍味を
a noisy delicacy.
胸に当たる　黒い魂の群れ
Striking the chest, a flock of black souls,
影の底で　忍び寄る亡者の渦
a vortex of the dead creeping at the bottom of the shadows,
まるで　開かずの箱
just like an unopened box.
手放したいわ　諦めたいわ
I want to let go, I want to give up,
悪夢の中から　逃げられるのに
even though I could escape from this nightmare,
まだ　戦ってる　夜を思い出したら
I'm still fighting; when I remember the night...
私のもの　そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine.
自分自身を　信じ込ませてしまって
I've made myself believe in it,
縛り付けて　待って　気付いた
bound myself to it, and wait—I realized.
夢の出口　永久の夜の鍵
The exit from the dream, the key to the eternal night,
目を覚まして　あなたの憧れ
wake up to your aspiration.
風に吹かれて
Blown by the wind,
誰も気づかぬよ
without anyone noticing,
区別がつかない
I can't tell the difference
モノクロの世界
in this monochrome world.
色を足しても
Even if I add color,
何も見えなくて
I can't see anything,
まるで私は
as if I had...
息を止めていた
stopped breathing.
もういいよ 遠くても
It's okay now, even from afar,
叶えたい 私は
I want to make it come true.
この世界を 今も
This world, even now,
抱きしめていたいのに
I want to keep holding it tight,
夢のキャンバスに
yet on the canvas of my dreams,
描き続けていく意味を
the meaning of continuing to draw
この胸に 輝いている
is shining in this chest.
ストーリー
Story
ありふれることに
There's no meaning
意味などないけど
in things being ordinary,
拾い集めた
but the fragments I gathered
欠片失うの
are being lost.
そして夜は その冷たさを
And the night, it melts that coldness,
溶かして手を伸ばした
as I reached out my hand.
もういいの 遠くても
It's okay now, even from afar,
届けたい 私は
I want to reach it.
埋め尽くす 涙も
I'm releasing these tears
抱きしめていたいのに
even though I want to hold them tight,
夢のキャンバスに
yet on the canvas of my dreams,
心込めるのは
what I put my heart into
この空に 描き出していく
is beginning to be drawn in this sky.
ストーリー
Story
そして夜は その冷たさを
And the night, it melts that coldness,
溶かして手を伸ばした
as I reached out my hand.
もういいの 遠くても
It's okay now, even from afar,
叶えたい 私は
I want to make it come true.
この世界を 今も
I'm wrapping this world,
言葉で包んだ
even now, in words.
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of my dreams,
色を足していく
I'm adding colors,
この胸に 今輝いて
shining in this chest now.
強くなくてもいい
It's okay if I'm not strong,
壊れかけてもいい
it's okay if I'm falling apart,
この心は永遠に羽ばたいて
this heart will take flight for eternity.
響くように
So it may resonate,
塗り替えていく 鮮やかな
I'm repainting it into a vivid...
ストーリー
Story
Hello everyone!
It is Day 2 of Drawn to Dawn!
Yes, yes, welcome to Day 2 of Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis's first concert, Drawn to Dawn!
Are you guys enjoying the show so far?
You know, I was really...
I want to talk about TakoTako first because...
...yesterday, I heard you guys sing along to the instrumental...
...and I was like, "Uh... ooh, I feel bad for not singing on Day 1."
But you know, I knew I was opening for, you know, Day 2...
...so I couldn't have thought of a better song to open than TakoTako.
Hope you guys had fun singing it!
Thank you again!
And of course, I sang two of my senpais' songs...
...Sencho's "Dead Man's Chest"...
...and Towa-sama's "Palette".
I specifically wanted to choose their songs because...
...they're senpais that I really look up to...
...and I always feel like my journey here wouldn't have been possible...
...if I didn't discover my senpais many, many years ago.
And I always wanted to pay respect to the path they paved for us.
So, yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed it!
I'm so nervous again!
And, you know, I of course didn't really tell you guys...
...specifically what penlight colors to use...
...but I knew that you guys would get my message...
...because we share a brain cell, right? Right?
And yeah, so... well, um...
...now going by the different setlist...
...because we have different setlists for Day 1 and Day 2...
...so, going by the process of elimination...
...we have a couple of songs from my new EP left, actually.
Who here bought my EP?
Yay! Thank you so much!
I hope you were lucky to get an autograph. I tried to sign as much as possible...
...but I knew, you know, sometimes you can't be lucky.
Thank you, thank you!
But yeah, I want you guys to have even more fun than before today!
I mean, you always have fun, so that's good.
But um... yeah! Sing along, have fun...
...and I always think that a live stage is where not only me performing...
...is creating the performance, but you guys as well.
You really help everyone with that special experience.
So let's create an unforgettable memory together today, okay?
Nyah!
Anyways, I would also like to shout out...
to those watching at home and at the live viewing in the cinema.
Hello, hello to you again!
And also, to the lovely girls doing a watchalong right now.
Hi guys! Thank you!
IRyS, EN, and everyone else doing the watchalong.
Thank you, thank you! You know, I'm always amazed by everyone's support.
And really without the support of Holo EN members as well...
...I wouldn't have had the confidence to stand here today.
Thank you, I love you!
And of course, I would like to remind you guys about the hashtag...
...for today's concert as well, #TakoTori1stConcert.
As usual, post your thoughts about it, post the screenshots.
No videos, no videos!
Post the screenshots and, you know, Kiara and I...
...whenever we have time, we've been checking the hashtag.
And of course after as well, I want to hear what you guys thought about the live.
So, yeah! Thank you, thank you!
And unlike yesterday, first MC means...
...I unfortunately have to bid farewell to those watching the sneak peek on YouTube.
I'm sorry!
But if you want to keep the party going...
...head to the streaming site via the description or the comment.
I don't know where the comment is!
But I know that some of you guys won't get a chance...
...to see my new outfit that I revealed yesterday.
So, I thought maybe I'll do something...
...maybe you guys can help me transition into the new costume here...
...so that even those of you...
...and YouTube Tiramisu can see!
All right, so I'm gonna count down from three.
Count down with me, okay?
And I will switch into the new outfit for you guys to see.
Ready?
Ready? Give me a "wah" if you're ready!
All right, all right, all right.
All right, here we go.
Three!
Two!
One!
Hah!
Tada!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
All right, it's time to move on to the next song.
And I think this song also fits the starry stage perfectly.
Not that one yet, but...
But this one is from one of my favorite franchises.
So I hope you guys listen.
Anyways, the song will fit the starry stage perfectly.
Please, give it a listen.
無料パートの放送は終了しました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!