(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-24T01:07:04.264612",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
CCGG劇場
CCGG Theater
曖昧3センチ そりゃぷにってコトかい？ ちょっ！
An ambiguous 3 centimeters, does that mean squishy? Wait!
らっぴんぐが制服…だぁぁ不利ってこたない ぷ。
Uniform wrapping... It's not like that's a disadvantage, pfft.
がんばっちゃ？やっちゃっちゃ
Do your best? Just do it, do it!
そんときゃーっち＆Release ぎょっ
Then catch and release! Whoa!
汗々の谷間に Darlin’ darlin’ F R E E Z E!!
In the valley of sweat, darling, darling, freeze!
なんかだるー なんかだるー あいしてるー あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Kind of sluggish, kind of lazy... I love you! Wait, one of those is different!
なやみん坊ー 高鉄棒ー おいしん簿ー いーかげんにシナサイ
Worrywart, high horizontal bar, Gourmet Craze... Cut it out already!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって 所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
That guy who flew away with a flushed body is what you'd call a normal girl.
驚いたあたしだけ? 豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Another bowl of extra-firm tonkotsu ramen!
BON-BON おーえんだん
BON-BON cheer squad!
Let’s get! チェリーパイ
Let’s get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN かんげーかい
RAN-RAN welcome party!
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation!
あい！存在感・てん・てん・てーしょん！
Yes! Presence, ten-ten-tension!
MAX！使って・溶けました・当然！
Max! I used it and it melted, of course!
おい！おい！だって・知れんじゃん？
Hey! Hey! After all, you know that, right?
もっていけ！最後に笑っちゃうのは私のはず！
Take it! The one who laughs last will be me!
セーラーふくだからです
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform,
結論！
that's the conclusion!
月曜日なのに・機嫌・悪い・の・どうするよ？
Even though it's Monday, my mood is bad, what should I do?
まず・服が・いい・のです
First of all, the outfit has to be nice,
かわいい！
so cute!
1、2、3！
One, two, three!
生まれてチュー、チュダヨン！
Born to kiss, kiss dayon!
がんばって！
Do your best!
はりきって！
Get pumped!
My Darling, Darling, please！
My Darling, Darling, please!
もりもり・もりさがり・もいしたり・まだ・内緒・にしといて・りん・りん！
Completely, completely down, or doing... keep it a secret for now, ring-ring!
あまえんぼう・ようじんぼう・つうしんぼ・ちょうしこいて・玉砕！
Spoiled baby, bodyguard, report card, getting cocky and shattered!
プレッシャー・アイスクリーム・会いたい・たい・たい・たい！大げさ・散らかり・クリーニング！
Pressure, ice cream, I want to meet, meet, meet, meet! Exaggerated, messy, dry cleaning!
ぜったい・残留・いっちゃん・なまいき・する・気が・おねだり・た・た・た・た！
Definitely staying, most cheeky, feeling like begging, ta-ta-ta-ta!
ぽぽん・ぽーん・ぺん！
Po-pon, pon, pen!
ごー！ぱぱぱぱーん！
Go! Pa-pa-pa-pan!
や、や、いーすとらんど！
Ya, ya, Eastland!
すぽーつ・あ・あ・てんしょん！おい！
Sports, a-a-tension! Hey!
そ、そ、し、した、たたた、アルバイト！
So, so, sh-sh, ta-ta-ta, part-time job!
探したら・見つかって・当然！
If you look for it, you'll find it, of course!
人生・まるごと・ケレンナシ！
Life, in its entirety, no gimmicks!
やってみーの！新規に狙っちゃうのは私の挑戦！
Give it a try! Targeting something new is my challenge!
セーラー服着替えても、私！
Even if I change out of my sailor uniform, it's still me!
週末は・どうよ？
How's the weekend?
チラ見せ・なんて・ありきたり！
Showing a little is so ordinary!
セーラー服は簡単よ！
A sailor uniform is easy!
らくちん！
Comfy!
4、5、3！
Four, five, three!
抱きついて・コマンド！
Hug me, command!
これ、どっち？
Which is this?
あれ、どっち？
Which is that?
シュガー、シュガー、スイート！
Sugar, sugar, sweet!
ぽぽん・ぽーん・ぺん！
Po-pon, pon, pen!
1、2、うー、うー、あー！
One, two, woo, woo, ah!
らら、ちょちょ、きー！
Lala, cho-cho, kee!
るっく・あっぷ、ふふ、はー、はー、はい！
Look up, fufu, ha, ha, yes!
えでゅけーしょん、とび、ABC！
Education, tobi, ABC!
なんか、なんか、なんか、晴れて、晴れて、綺麗なし！
Something, something, something, clearing up, clearing up, beautiful!
もっていけ！最後に笑っちゃうのは私のはず！
Take it! The one who laughs last will be me!
セーラーふくだからです
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform,
結論！
that's the conclusion!
月曜日なのに・機嫌・悪い・の・どうするよ？
Even though it's Monday, my mood is bad, what should I do?
まず・服が・いい・のです
First of all, the outfit has to be nice,
かわいい！
so cute!
やっぱり、最後に笑っちゃうのは私のはず！
Just as I thought, the one who laughs last will be me!
セーラーふくだからです
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform,
結論！
that's the conclusion!
あい！まい！さん、せっつ！
Ai, mai, sun-sets!
そりゃ、食い切ったことない、わーお！
I've never finished eating that, wow!
トッピングがセーラー、よし、凝り切ったことない、ぼー！
Topping is a sailor, alright, never been fully stiff, bo!
がんばっちゃ、やっちゃっちゃ、あ、とっちゃ！
Do your best, do it, ah, take it!
ぽっちゃ、ぽっちゃ、おしゃ、しゃして、は、せ、は、せ！
Potcha, potcha, osha, do it, ha, se, ha, se!
そして、My Darling, Darling, please！
And, My Darling, Darling, please!
(yawns)
Now, *this* is what I'm talking about.
That's what we need!
We need... we need another hit show!
We need an anime opening!
No, no! We need... No, we need a show! We need... we need something with substance.
I just thought that our show was failing because we didn't have an anime opening.
No, our show is failing because it's *really* bad.
It's... it's not *that* bad.
It's *really* bad. Have you seen the reviews?
They're wrong, though.
Ugh...
I cannot, friends.
Really? What else do we need? Um...
We need to sell out.
We need to sell out. / We need to sell out.
Ah, I'm so tired from all this thinking.
I think we need to explore other genres, to save the Immergreen.
Like what?
Every genre.
I think that's the only way.
You're boring me...
What?
Oh, a sympathetic sleeper!
Huh? What? / Huh?
Where... where are we, Gigi?
What is this?
What is this? Are we... are we in my head?
Wait, are we in your head? / Are we in my head?
Wait, what? / This is just like...
This is just like [bleep]!
Does this mean we're gonna steal people's ideas?
No, they're our ideas. We're in my head. / No, this is my head.
I'm gonna steal your idea.
You can't steal my ideas.
I could.
Wait, what if I see every single idea in your head, and then I take them from you?
Stop!
If you go too deep into my brain, you'll get to the yaoi parts!
Oh, oh. Maybe we should start with my brain. It's okay, it's okay.
Wait. Wait. / What's in your brain?
Nothing.
Um, actually, there's a lot in my brain. For example...
Your brain is full of bad romance novels! We can't put that in our show!
Ah, yes we can! We can put it in our show!
Let's put it in our show! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Romance? Hm, romance.
Romance.
I guess we need to break free out of this place.
DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL
[Title: DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL]
THE FOLLOWING SCENE IS AS FOLLOWS:
CROY AND GIBRIELLA ARE AT A PARTY.
CROY LOVES BASKETBALL
AND GIBRIELLA IS NOT LIKE OTHER GIRLS...
A FICTIONAL TALE OF SONG AND BASKETBALL.
I don't want to sing. I'm just a normal boy.
I just want to play basketball with my friends and get my head in the game.
I can't sing. I'm just Croy.
Get it together, Gibriella.
We don't have time for extracurriculars, we have to get into college.
I'm not like other girls. I just want to stay at home and read books.
ばかみたい
I've been a fool...
子供なのね
...such a child, aren't I?
夢を追って傷ついて
Chasing after dreams and getting hurt...
嘘が下手なくせに
Even though I'm terrible at lying,
笑えない笑顔みせた
I showed you a smile that couldn't even laugh.
I love youも ろくに言わない
You rarely even said "I love you,"
口下手でほんまに不器用
So clumsy and truly bad with words...
なのに なのに どうして
And yet, and yet, why did...
サヨナラは言えたの
...was "goodbye" the only thing you could say?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, it's no use, it's just no good...
あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you way too much...
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink is,
歪まない思い出が
The memories won't blur...
ばかみたい
I've been a fool.
ばかみたい 本当バカね
I've been a fool, a total fool...
あんた 信じるばかりで
Always just believing in you...
強い 女のふり
Pretending to be a strong woman...
切なさの夜風浴びる
Bathing in the sorrow of the night wind.
一人になって
Now that I'm alone,
3年が過ぎ
three years have passed,
街並みさえも
and even the city streets
変わりました
have changed.
なのに
And yet...
なのにどうして
And yet, why
未練だけ
are only lingering attachments
置き去り
left behind?
ほんまにロクな男やない
You really are not a good man.
揃いの指輪
Our matching rings...
外します
I'll take them off.
ざまあみろ
Serves you right.
せいせいするわ
I feel so relieved.
いい加減
No matter
待ってても
how long I wait...
ばかみたい
I'm such a fool.
だめだね
It's no good.
だめよ
No good.
だめなのよ
It's no good at all.
あんたが
I love you,
好きで
I love you...
好きすぎて
way too much.
どれだけ
No matter how much
強いお酒でも
strong alcohol I drink,
歪まない
these unyielding
思い出が
memories
ばかみたい
are just foolish.
ほんまにロクな男やない
You really are not a good man.
揃いの指輪
Our matching rings...
外します
I'll take them off.
ざまあみろ
Serves you right.
せいせいするわ
I feel so relieved.
なんなのよ
What's with
この涙
these tears?
ばかみたい
I'm such a fool.
Whoa, yeah, yeah! Musicals is where it's at!
I think... I think this could really be...
This is gonna get us the big dollars!
Yeah, hopefully the big mouse is not gonna shoot us in the head.
Ten billion dollars!
What big mouse?
Ten... don't worry about it.
Ten billion dollars! Yeah, it's really good.
We might need like a different type of show too, you know?
Just for variety, so they can't shut us down.
A variety show?
Yeah!
Like a variety game show?
The Autofister Games!
The Autofister...
...physical games!
Physicals!
One hundred and five!
But first, a word from our sponsors!
Whoa! Slow down there, partner!
Hold your horses! Don't you think you're scrolling a little too fast?
Yeah, put down the phone and full screen our video instead because...
...we are about to show you the new hottest thing in town!
Introducing the...
Autofister...
...Network!
Get it? 'Cause it's Autofister Network, but this is our merch!
We wanted to take this opportunity to show you all of our cool, fun merch before it goes live!
We've got Cemimis!
Gimimis!
Grems!
Otomos!
And this neat acrylic stand of the both of us!
Yay!
And if you hurry up, you'll even be able to get...
...the limited set with a postcard signed by both of us!
Woohoo! It will be live at these exact...
...times, so make sure to check it out then!
Coming soon to a stream near you!
And we're back from our commercial break!
Thank you everyone for waiting!
Yeah! Welcome back to the official...
...Autofister...
Physical Autofister!
100!
And with us, we have our lovely contestants!
BAE!
Okay, I'm gonna win!
KOBO!
Kobo is comfortable.
TOWA!
Towa-sama!
Today, as said before, we are here to find out who is the ultimate winner of...
...Physical Autofister 100!
As explained before...
...commercial break, each contestant will have to compete in our physical obstacle course of FUN!
FUN!
If you're just now tuning in, here is a quick recap!
Everyone starts in a line, you have to run to the other side while avoiding all obstacles, and do a quick little physical activity!
Grab a question from a dragon, who telepathically gives it to you in your brain, run back and answer a question! Yeah!
We'll do four rounds, and the person with the most points at the end of four rounds is the winner!
Okay, well everyone get into position!
What is this?
So, so, as said before, of course...
...since a lot of these questions will be in English, Bae has a handicap.
She has a handicap, very difficult question.
What is this?!
Nice! Nice, nice!
Okay, okay, okay, everyone in position?
Yes, we have the first round. The first round is, you run over there...
...and you do five jumping jacks! Five jacks.
Okay, jumping?
走って、5ジャンプやって、質問取って、走って帰る。
Run, do 5 jacks, grab the question, and run back.
オッケー、オッケー。いいですか？オッケー。
Okay, okay. Ready? Okay.
Three, two, one, GO!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
I was betrayed!
Please read the question out loud.
Okay. えっと、うんと、I like...
Okay. Um, well, I like...
...うんと、strawberry!
...um, strawberry!
Strawberry! Yes! Name a fruit! Strawberry!
One point!
You can give your questions over here.
Well, next round!
Next round! Is everyone ready?
No, no, the crab walk like this!
Crab walk like this! Crab walk!
Crab walk and five squats!
5スクワット？クラブウォークand 5スクワット？
5 squats? Crab walk and 5 squats?
Wait, do they have to jump?
No, we can walk.
Jump? They have to jump? Okay, okay!
帰る時もこれ？
When returning, this too?
帰る時もな。
Returning too, right?
Okay, everyone ready? Three, two, one, GO!
これスクワットかね？これ？
Are these squats? This?
Okay, come on. Oh, I ripped the mind telepathy...
Hey, you can't rip our telepathy paper!
13 times 6... 78!
Yes! Oh, she's actually really good at math! She's good at math! Wow!
バナナ。またバナナなんだけど！
Banana. It's banana again!
2回連続バナナなんだけど。
Two times in a row banana.
Two banana questions!
おい、日本語書いてるじゃねえか！
Hey, it's written in Japanese, isn't it!
What?! I was given a handicap because the questions were in English, they are written in Japanese!
Hey, but the questions are in English...
Okay, okay, we got to keep it rolling, guys! Keep it rolling!
Do I still have to go around and around?
Those are the rules by our producers, who are not us.
On my telepathy paper, the next one is... sexy walk!
Sexy walk! Sexy, sexy!
Do we get disqualified, do we have to start again if it's not sexy enough?
Hot, please make up your mind! We'll see, we'll see!
And, three push-ups! Three!
腕立て伏せ3回？オッケー。
3 push-ups? Okay.
And sexy walk! Sexy walk!
セクシーウォークね。
Sexy walk, right.
セクシーウォーク、セッキシージャンプ。そのセクシーさが足りなかったら万が一やり直しって言われてるから。
Sexy walk, sexy jump. If the sexiness is not enough, we might have to do it again.
えええ！？セクシーが足らん！？
Eee!? Not sexy enough!?
任せろ、任せろ！
Leave it to me, leave it to me!
オッケー、見てみよう。
Okay, we'll see.
Everyone ready?
Ready? Three, two, one, go!
セクシー、ベイビー！
Sexy, Bae!
You try to be sexy!
いち、に、さん、し！
One, two, three, four!
トワ様！
Towa-sama!
おお、セクシーセクシー。
Oh, sexy, sexy.
それ、歩き方じゃない。
That's not how you walk.
セクシー？
Sexy?
あれ、セクシー？
Wait, is that sexy?
私セクシー。
I'm sexy.
もう一回？
Again?
セクシーじゃない？
Isn't that sexy?
セクシーじゃないよ。
It's not sexy.
You try running like...
Bae, you only have to do it on the way there.
On the way back, you can go straight.
いやいや、助けないで！
No, no, don't help!
待って。
Wait.
Name a flower!
ええと...
Uh...
パンジー！
Pansy!
おお、イエス！パンジー！
Oh, yeah! Pansy!
知ってる？
Did you know?
イエス！オッケー！
Yes! Okay!
Gigi, have you been counting the points?
Yeah, one, one, one.
Oh, tie-breaker!
Tie-breaker! Okay, okay.
最後のポイントは？
What about the last point?
One hundred points?
Can I get rid of this?
No! Last round!
You have to do this well.
Lunge walk.
ええー！きっつ！
What?! So hard!
ヤバい！
This is crazy!
きた、きた、きた！
Here they come, here they come!
3回！
Three times!
How many times?
3回！3回！
Three times! Three times!
And then, three...
Wow, you're so good!
がんばろう、がんばろう。
Let's do our best, let's do our best.
わかりましたか？
Do you understand?
オッケー、わかりました。
Okay, I got it.
死にそう、なんか。
It looks painful somehow.
Can I just do this?
No, no! Our buttocks will get cut.
Bae, fighting!
がんばる！
Let's do it!
Ready, 1, 2...
...1, go!
Gigi, you're touching it.
Towa-sama is fine. She's doing her best.
いち、に、さん！
One, two, three!
うおお！オッケー！
Whoa! Okay!
よいしょ、よいしょ！
Go, go!
トワ様、すごーい！
Towa-sama, you're amazing!
Let's wait for Bae to come back.
Bae, come on, we can answer.
This is not the winner until you get over here.
はい！はい！はい！
Go! Go! Go!
You need to high five.
Squad over here.
Here is your question.
Say a French word!
French? French?
ボンジュール！
Bonjour!
オッケー！
Okay!
Towa is the winner!
Winner for today!
Contestants have something to complain about anyway.
Yeah, we did our best.
The last level was like, insane.
一週回って、結構しんどいよ。
Try one lap, it's really tiring.
Stop, stop, Bae only.
Bae only? Yes, please.
Security, security! We got her.
Can we give our winner her crown?
Yay!
This is not fair! Tie-breaker!
This is Bae!
This is Kobo!
This is Towa-sama!
And you're watching the Autofist Network!
The rat sucked.
Yeah.
She should go back to the gym.
She should go back to school and retake PE.
Yeah, but Towa-sama was strong. She got the crown.
And Ceecee is so cute! So cute!
Yeah, also the hosts were amazing.
Really, they were so beautiful. Every time they were on the screen, I was electrified.
I think this is what's going to get us the funding.
Yeah, I think we're going to get $10 million for this one.
And the more budget they have, the more difficult the challenges can get, and then the death...
...penalty can be even greater.
Anyways, what if...
...anime, but live action?
I don't feel so good.
Ah, I'm so tired, Gigi.
Me too. I'm so tired because I'm working so hard.
I've been working so hard with making so many shows. I'm so sleepy.
And I don't want to record, and I'm at the studio every single day.
I always wanted a tea party! If only someone would invite me to their tea party.
Actually, I have been preparing something.
Is it this background? This really, really realistic background that you probably stole from the internet?
Who said I stole it? I stole it.
Yeah, and this is my tea party, so welcome in! It's...
But yeah, I have one more surprise.
You have a surprise for your tea party?
Yeah, we're models.
Where's me? Where's me?
You know what? We got some graphics update.
A graphics update?
You want to see?
You want to see? I want to see me!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's me...
...Cecilia Immergreen from Hololive English Justice!
Spin, twirl!
You look...
...great! Oh, thanks!
You look freaking amazing! I guess I'll go sit down real quick.
Oh my god, I look so good. Look at my shoes! I look so good.
Wow!
Hey, Gigi, come on, come on in. It's okay. Oh, I get one too?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Gigi Murin, everyone! It's Gigi Murin...
...from Hololive English Justice! I'm so happy to be here.
Wow, you look good too! You look great. I guess it's time for me to sit down also.
Yeah, look at my shoes too. Wow, wow, wow.
Wow, they look good. Those look kind of hard to walk in actually. That's crazy.
No, I'm a natural. Let me sit down.
Sit down, sit down. Sit down already.
And together, we are Autofist! Autofist! Yay!
Finally, we get some time to relax. Wow, you look really good.
Ah, thank you. You look really good too. Oh, we're hugging again?
Oh, I just can't... I really like hugging you.
I can't help that I keep hugging you. Oh, my hood came off, it's fine. I'm so excited!
So excited! Hey, are you hungry?
I'm really hungry. Will you feed me? Okay, I'll feed you, I'll feed you.
Say 'ah'.
Ah! Wait, accident, accident!
Oh, wait. Oh, I'm really hungry too.
Oh my god. Oh, you're getting this all over me. It's getting really messy.
Oh, why is it getting on your face too? Ew!
Mm, it tastes really good.
Really? Let me feed you again.
Do you mind if I got my spit on it? You don't mind, do you?
Wait, wait, wait, let me wipe that off. You got something on the side of your mouth, let me just get that for you.
Hehehe, are you so...
...dirty? Let me get it off of you too. Oh, you have something on your mouth.
Okay, okay, that's enough, that's enough. Oh, yes. Thirsty?
I'm thirsty. I'm really thirsty. Okay, I'll pour you some tea.
Glug, glug, glug, glug. I'm really excited.
Here's your tea. It's really hot.
Oh, be careful, be careful. Oh my god, it's really... Oh my god, it's really hot! Oh, it's really on my cowl! Oh god, oh!
It's all over my body. Oh no, you spilled it!
Oh my god! Oh my god, it burns! Atsui, atsui. Oh my god.
Oh no.
I feel like I got a third-degree burn just now.
Why did you do that to me? You're freaking... I'm sorry, let me wipe it off of you.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that, I just got really overzealous. Mm, but it's really good now it's cooled down.
You like it? What type of tea is it?
It's like a note... a little floral note on it. Here, try some. Try from my finger, try from my finger.
Nom, nom.
How does it taste? Yummy.
That's really good. Okay. Okay, that's enough.
I finished my cup. It was really, really delicious.
You know, if Elizabeth was here, she would tell us that after having a really good meal, we should work out.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, so let's get up.
Let's go stand over there in this corner. Yeah, let's stand by the horse.
That horse is really amazing. Oh! You kicked me!
making so much noise!
Sorry! My my my shoes are just really big and clunky.
Sorry! My shoes are just really big and clunky.
You know what? I think it'd be really cool
if we were to do 50 push-ups right now.
I, I want to do...
You know what? I want to do 50 push-ups!
- I want to do 50 push-ups!
Me? I really want to...
No, no. I really wanted to do 50 push...
Okay, okay, wait. I changed my mind.
Oh, you changed your mind?
I want... I want, um, 50 lunges.
50 lunges?!
Oh, oh, oh! Oh, your knee hurts?
Oh... Ah, I think, yeah, I got into an accident
about 200 years ago.
Did you get hit by a car?
- I got hit by a car 200 years ago.
Oh, okay. I guess that's just how it is.
You know what, Chichimurin?
Don't touch me!
Stop touching me.
- Stop touching me!
Stop touching me! What? Oh my god!
Why are you always doing that? Why are you...
You're just... Ah, you fight so much! No, no!
I hate you! I hate you! I hate you so much!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! What about your hair?
- Look at your hair!
Hey hey hey hey hey hey...
- Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I got... Sorry, I was getting mean.
I was acting out.
Will you forgive me?
I... I guess so.
I'm sorry for yelling.
- I'm sorry for yelling at you.
I didn't mean to. Can you kiss my knee, please?
I guess, oh... I feel really good now.
Do you feel better?
- I feel better.
And I feel really sleepy all of a sudden.
Oh, me too, actually. Oh...
Yeah, so sleepy.
- I'm so sleepy.
Ah, but there's only one bed. What should we do?
Should we... get into it together?
I guess, I guess so. I guess we'll get into...
Let me just take off my shoes.
Oh yeah, I think it would be really, really weird
to get into bed with shoes on. - Yeah, that would be strange.
But let me help you. Let me fluff this pillow
for you. Oh, you look so... Here you go, Princess.
Princess?
Okay, let me... let me just lay down.
- Oh, let me get into bed. I have to take my shoes off, too.
I'm already getting so comfortable.
- Please, please don't go to bed without me!
Oh, I'm so tired. If someone doesn't get into
bed quick, I'm just going to fall asleep without you.
Oh, no, don't, don't! It's just my... my achy,
achy bones. I'm trying to get into bed. Please!
I guess your knee really hurts still.
- It does.
Oh, I feel so comfortable.
- Thanks for coming to my tea party, Chichimurin.
Thanks for inviting me, Cici.
- Good night. - Oh! We're holding hands.
It's because I... I get scared in the dark.
- Oh, of course. Yeah.
So, I'm glad that we have each other. Good night, Cici.
- Good night, Chichi...
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah. Good night.
I'm Cici!
- And I'm Jiji!
And you're watching...
- The Autofister Network!
Ummm... mmm.
I don't know if that's going to make us any money.
Well, on to the next idea!
みんなが大好きっ！！
I love everyone!!
延々続行 ルララ Miracle Sing Time
It goes on forever. Lu la la miracle sing time.
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
I sing and sing to convey my love the best I can.
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even if the song sucks, even if the lyrics are questionable,
届けたい 精一杯のsoulを
I want to deliver my soul with all my heart.
どうしよう オートマティックに決められてる
What should I do? Things are being decided for me automatically.
時間割じゃ追っつかない
I can't keep up with the schedule.
の！ 夢無限 したいこと怒涛
No! Wanting to dream infinitely is an angry wave,
廊下もダッシュで集まるよ
we'll get together with a dash down the hallway.
お行儀悪かったらsorry！
Sorry for the bad manners!
でもなりふりも構わずに
But regardless of how I look
どっぷりハマっちゃうplay
I get too immersed in playing.
キラリっ もしかこれが青春
A "sparkle". Perhaps this is youth.
ever ever… Forever Shine
ever ever... forever shine.
ほんとに大好きっ！！
I really love it!!
テンション上昇 ルララ Powerful Gig Time
The tension keeps rising. Lu la la powerful gig time.
ハートって ハートって ワクワク探す天才
The heart, the heart is a genius at searching for excitement.
アレっ！？って言われても ミス連発でも
Even if they go "Huh!?", even if I keep messing up,
放ちたい 湧いてくるbraveを
I want to release my overflowing bravery.
仕掛けるトレモロ 応えるフラム
I'll start a tremolo, a flam will respond
いいじゃんいいじゃんノリノリでいいんじゃない
It's great, it's great. Isn't it great to be high-spirited?!?
ハッピーはいつだってね “今”感じるもの
Happiness is something we always feel in the present.
生きろ乙女 本能で、裸の
Girls, live strong with your bare instincts.
本能で、裸の
With our instincts, bare...
どうしても ホームワークよりも重要課題
No matter what, this is more important than homework.
放課後のお茶 おしゃべり 練習
After-school tea, chatting, and practice!
ユーモア ナチュラル
Humor, natural...
めくるめく 笑い ウケ過ぎでお腹痛い
dazzling laughter, laughing so hard our stomachs hurt!
呼吸(いき)ぴったりexcellent! でも苦手なリフまだあったの
In perfect sync, excellent! But there's still a riff I'm bad at.
特訓つきあってくれる?
Will you practice with me?
もう少し門限まで だって帰りたくない
Just a bit longer until curfew, because I don't want to go home yet!
never never... can't say good-bye
めちゃめちゃ大好き!!
I love you all so incredibly much!!
超絶 ぞっこん ル ララ wonderful show time
Extremely, head over heels, lu-la-la, wonderful show time!
音楽って 音楽って もう私達まんま
Music, music is just exactly who we are!
スタンディングオベーション賞 オーディエンスなしでも
A standing ovation, even without an audience!
奏でたい 瞬間(とき)のrealを
We want to play the reality of this moment!
昨日の後悔って 明日の心配って
Regrets from yesterday, worries about tomorrow...
ぶっちゃけ ぶっちゃけ 誰得?何得?
To be honest, to be honest, who does that help? What's the point?
ラッキーはいつだってね “今” つかむもの
Luck is always something you grab in the "now"!
欲張れ 乙女 与えられん、さらばだ
Be greedy, girls! If nothing is given, then farewell!
どんな本も書いてない
It's not written in any book,
授業じゃちょっと教わらない
and not taught in classes,
けど一生忘れない
but we'll never forget it for the rest of our lives!
この世にないと思ってた奇跡
A miracle we thought didn't exist in this world...
一緒にね歌えば
If we sing together,
信じられるんだ 強くなれるんだ
we can believe in it, we can become stronger!
みんなが大好き!!
We love you all!!
延々続行 ル ララ miracle sing time
Endlessly continuing, lu-la-la, miracle sing time!
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
Singing, singing, the ultimate way to convey love!
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even with a clumsy song, or awkward lyrics,
届けたい精一杯のsoul 等身大のlifeを
we want to deliver our full soul and our real-size life!
今日は昨日みたい? 明日は今日みたい?
Is today like yesterday? Is tomorrow like today?
大丈夫大丈夫 楽しかったら大正解
It's okay, it's okay, if you had fun, that's the perfect answer!
ロッカーはいつだってね “今” やんちゃ盛り
Rockers are always in their prime mischievous phase "now"!
進め 乙女 抱きしめて、希望を
Move forward, girls! Embrace your hopes!
大好き
We love you,
we love you,
大好きをありがとう
thank you for all the love!
歌うよ
We'll sing,
we'll sing,
心こめて 今日も歌うよ
from our hearts, we will sing today as well!
大好き
We love you,
we love you,
大好きをありがとう
thank you for all the love!
歌うよ
We'll sing,
we'll sing,
愛をこめて ずっと歌うよ
with all our love, we'll sing forever!
Please hold.
We will soon be changing the channel.
We are about to switch the channel.
Please wait.
The channels will be changed soon.
Please stay seated,
as the channels are about to switch.
Don't change the channel,
because we'll do it for you.
Do not touch the remote,
coz we will be doing it.