(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.2",
"generated_at": "2026-06-30T00:33:13.627671",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey, why were you looking at my Raora?
No, I wasn't.
Raora already has my love. It's first come, first served.
What are you even talking about?
No, she's mine!
Mine!
She's mine now!
Don't take her! No, it's mine!
Raora's mine now! No, mine! Mine! Mine!
Mine! Mine! Mine! No...
Jay! What on Earth are you playing over here?
The jealousy game.
The jealousy game?
And shouldn't you play something more appropriate for a five-year-old?
Mom, I'm five, and this is what five-year-olds do. And I thought this was funny.
Oh, you and your daddy are definitely having a conversation about this later.
All righty, it's time for your favorite thing: Justice!
Justice!
They are Justice.
They make loads of trouble.
What?
Oh! Is that it?
Justice! Justice!
How to Protect JUSTICE!
Members of JUSTICE! are expected to possess strength,
sound judgment,
and an unwavering sense of justice.
In this training video,
you will learn the fundamental skills and exercises required of every Justice member.
Now, join us and say it together!
FOR JUSTICE!
[身体検査訓練]
[Body Search Training]
The first training is a body search conducted immediately after securing a subject.
Even the slightest oversight can lead to serious incidents or the destruction of evidence,
making this one of the most critical police procedures.
Can Justice keep their emotions in check under any circumstances
and carry out a precise body search to completion?
[Officer: Elizabeth / Suspect: Raora]
Stop, ma'am! No further, no further. It is...
...policy, and I'll be conducting a body search.
Come here, madam. Yes, body search you here.
If you really insist...
Over here, over here, over here, ma'am.
Okay, okay!
Do you have any electronics, tablets, laptops, devices?
Turn around here, ma'am.
Arms up! All right.
Straight arms, there we go. Wonderful, wonderful. All right.
What is this?
Oh... You know, Totini is... See, my Totini...
...they are always hungry and they really want some food, so sometimes I always have...
...an emergency cucumber.
Emergency rations, I see, I see, I see. We can't have that on these premises, I'm sorry.
No? I... I take care of them.
All right. Spread your legs, ma'am, over here.
No, no!
Over here, ma'am. Over here, right here.
What are you going to do if I don't do it?
Uh, probably arrest you, put you in jail for many years...
...take you to court.
Really? You're going to arrest me? What are you going to do?
Oh! What if I... What if I check on you instead?
No, no. It's my job, ma'am. My job. Over here, ma'am.
All right, stand there. What is...
...this?
Oh... I like cooking.
Would you like something? Maybe I can cook something for you?
Ma'am, I'm a professional. No dating on the job.
Do you want a little bit of pasta? I'm so good at making pasta.
Pasta... I am a bit hungry.
Hey, hey, hey! Stop trying to tempt me! Stop trying to tempt me!
Okay, okay!
All right. Stand here.
Stand here, ma'am! Right here now!
She's kind of hot when she's...
Three, two, one, arms out!
All right. And what is...
...this?
Oh... That's a...
That's a Totini jetpack!
Oh, no one should see this. Let's get out of here.
Ma'am! You just threw that small... little creature!
Don't worry about it!
All right, anyway, what is this?
Oh... Well...
You have a lot of food-related items on you, ma'am.
Yes, please, please eat that before you go.
Do you want a little bit, too?
No, ma'am, I'm on the job! I'm on the job!
Anyway, ma'am, arms up! Come here, come here, over here.
What are you going to do if I don't do it? Are you going to punish me or something?
Uh, maybe, if you don't come here right now. I'm behaving!
Not going to do it. What are you going to do about it?
Going to make you do 10 push-ups, outside of this training.
Maybe I can do some squats for you. Ah! What is this?!
No! Not this one!
Anatomy Book?! No! I can... I can explain.
You know, anatomy is... uh...
All right, and what is... anatomy book... I can explain!
That's my anatomy book! Ah...
Ma'am, you are way too suspicious! You are under arrest!
And also for having... Really?
...having Totinis with jetpacks! That is unbelievable!
You are a bad, bad kitty! You are a bad kitty! Come here!
All right, you are under arrest! Oh, yes I am!
Yeah, yeah, that was really good, Raora. That was... that's it. Yes.
Are we going to jail? Are you going to bring me to jail?
That's it for the training. That's it for the training.
Maybe we can share a cell together? Raora, no!
We're done with the training! We're done! Wait! Wait! Let's go together!
[Officer: Cecilia / Suspect: Gigi]
All right then! Officer Cecilia Immergreen.
We'll be conducting a...
Conducting the body search.
Stop right there! Hands up in the air!
I didn't do anything wrong!
Don't move. Do I have your consent to do a body search on you?
No, no, no, no! Do I have your consent?
Do I have your consent? Do I have your... Okay, okay.
Let us see.
Let us see what you have here. On what charges?!
What... What's this?
What is this?!
A maraca? Hey, that's mine! Why did you take that from me?
Why did you take that from me?
It is not. We never met before. Why would I take something from you?
No, I can't believe you would steal! You're a thief!
I did not steal it. It was given to me.
Stand still. Hands up in the air! No!
No, ah, ah, oh, ah!
No, ah, ah, ah!
Girl, girl... what, what's this then?
There's nothing wrong with having that in my pocket! It's a gremlin buddy! We're buddies, we're friends.
Does it live under a humane living condition?
Yes! It lives in a nice little shoe box and it's really happy there! So that's why you should not arrest me, Officer.
Okay, okay, okay, I believe you. Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
What's this?! Ah!
Wait, it's Otomo! Why do you have Otomo?
No reason! They are...
Are they friends? They're friends!
He was on a playdate, obviously. He came to visit the shoebox, so that's why. Am I free to go, Officer?
I'm starting to think that maybe, maybe it's okay. Let me see one more time.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
What... What's this?
Nothing... Oh? It's nothing?
Oh, oh...
Can't a girl have some BL in her pocket?
Kimi ni Dunk?
Can't a girl have some hobbies?
Can't I read? Am I not allowed to read?
Ah! Ah!
Stop making those noises!
What's this?
Another one?! This one is a cat boy, and then the other...
Have you heard of that really, really awesome manga where whenever they... they...
Okay, okay, ground...
On the floor! On the floor! Get on the floor! On the floor?!
Get down! On the floor?! On the floor?!
Ah! Ah!
What... Ah!
Stop making those noises!
What's this?
What's this one then?
So, so this is the one that I really, really like this one because these, these two men right here...
Uh-huh. ...one of them is an Omega, another one is an Alpha.
It's called the Omegaverse. And then, uh, they don't actually turn into wolves here, it's just...
...it's called pack dynamics, and one of them is really, really dominant, and the other one is really submissive,
...and then one of them can get pregnant. Do you like... Hello? Are you listening, Officer?
Officer? Officer? One of them gets pregnant, it's really, really...
The next training is apprehension training.
This is a critical close-quarters task in the field...
...requiring officers to approach and subdue a target swiftly.
However, unexpected behavior on site can sometimes shake one's judgment.
Can Justice successfully and reliably subdue the target?
Gigi and Raora's apprehension training, you have three minutes. Begin!
Yeah! You're going down, criminal scum!
Ah, no! Ah! Ah! No, wait, wait, wait!
Put your arms behind your back! Put your arms behind your back!
You can't do that! Get her, get her!
Get over here, criminal! Get over here!
Look at my tail, look at my tail! Don't you like my tail?
Don't fall for it! Don't fall for it!
I'm unsure who's winning. Hey, Gigi, don't fall for that!
You know, it's kind of hard for you. You want justice!
Show me your back! Get her!
What's wrong with it?
Oh, no, you have the right to remain silent!
You don't want to hurt me, do you?
You're a criminal, so I'm gonna have to touch you!
She's gonna do that?
I'm gonna have to put you in jail!
Why would you put me in jail, Gigi? Oh, stop! Oh, stop!
Apprehend her!
Help! Help! Help! Get her, get her, get her!
Get her! Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, Gigi, why would... why do you want to touch my tail? Hey!
Touch my tail! That's my tail!
Show me your tail! Stop!
You're a criminal! You're a criminal! You're a criminal!
You're a criminal!
Down, Raora, down.
Don't look. Don't look.
Whoa!
Get down! Where are you going?
You're never gonna touch me, right?
No, I would touch you. I will touch you.
I will touch you. I will hurt you.
Lie down. Lie down. Lie down, you're a criminal!
You're a criminal, so you have to lie down.
Oh, wait, I have something here. Hold on.
Oh, my clothes... my...
Ah!
Stay down! Stay down! I'm trying! I'm trying!
Get back on the ground!
Oh, you wanna be here next to me?
Oh, you want this? Get off! Get off!
Both of them are useless. You got me...
Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me!
I win! Guys, I win!
Okay, okay, okay, that's enough, that's enough.
I win. That's enough.
That was... That was apprehension. Did I win?
Who do you think won? Wow, and the winner is...
This is about apprehension training, there's no winner.
Did you do a good job? I am still free.
In the end, you apprehended her.
Yeah, yeah. I got her in a leg lock and everything.
I think she's correct. You definitely interlocked...
Hey! Hey! Hey, hey!
Get off! You know what, I disqualify. Gigi is the winner.
Yes! Well done, you apprehended the...
Actually, I think you won.
I think you won too. You won.
Hey, hey. Not without my consent!
Okay, okay.
SUSPECT / Officer Cecilia
Elizabeth and Cecilia, apprehension training!
You have three minutes. Are you ready?
One, one second. Flame on!
Flame on! I'm ready.
Flame on. Flame on!
Are you ready now? We're ready. Okay, three, two, one, start!
Suspect! Suspect, stop right there!
I am Evil Elizabeth!
And I have chewing gum in everyone's hair!
How evil am I?! Hands up in the air!
Oh! Oh! Hands up and...
Oh, yeah, yeah! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh!
Help! Help!
My god, Liz, you should kill her. She's so strong.
Oh... Liz! Liz, I've fallen!
Oh! Come on, up. Up, up.
Come on, up again. It's okay, it's okay.
You did great. You want another go?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. Whoa!
Oh, no, I have fallen.
I'm doing it! I... Okay, okay, all right.
Did I win, Liz? Did I win?
Are you willingly going to come with me to the police station?
Oh, no, because I'm evil!
I'm going to go burn a village! Okay. Whoa!
Wait, stop! Huh? Look at this!
Oh my goodness!
I am evil, and she's evil. She's the most evil.
Oh my god, is that a signed picture of the evil, evil, evil Nerissa?
Yes. Give it! I need it!
If you come with me, I'll give this to you!
Yes! I will, yes, yes, yes!
Okay, hands behind your back, hands behind your back.
Okay. I get the picture though, right?
Yes, of course, of course. Here you go. Yes, yes, yes!
You were playing dirty! You just humiliated Liz!
No, I am a smart-smart cop,
and instead of using violence, I used my brain.
Justice loses! Oh, my god, look at her!
Oh, I don't know, I don't know what you're on about.
Yeah, you did really well. I think you did great.
You used a weapon against the suspect
to apprehend them.
And, yeah, so I think you did great.
Great job, Cecilia.
I think Cecilia has done the best out of everyone, personally.
She cheated! See? Justice's greatest weakness.
No! No! You weren't supposed to win!
Justice is caught!
We're never gonna catch them like this!
Oh... Huh.
How to Protect JUSTICE! Interrogation Training
Where even the slightest inconsistencies in a statement
must be detected to get closer to the truth.
Can Justice remain unaffected by the situation
and accurately draw out the information?
Yeah, I'm the best, actually.
I have a gun, and I know how to use it, so...
Easy! Don't worry about it, I have my ways. I've been here for so long...
...it's going to be the easiest case of my life.
No, I don't think so.
Because my heart is too pure, and my ass is too fat...
...and I'm not a gaslighter like Cecilia Immergreen.
I'm not very confident, but I'll do my best.
Well, well, well, Elizabeth the criminal! We are about to begin your interrogation!
Wait a minute, I'm not a criminal!
Why me? I haven't done anything. What exactly have I been accused of?
Th-That would be the... suspected identity fraud, and...
...and the unlawful acquisition of personal...
Come on, Gigi!
...of Nerissa Ravencroft!
I don't know anything about that. I'm innocent. Who is Nerissa Ravencroft?
Have you ever seen Nerissa Ravencroft?
You know who Nerissa Ravencroft is!
No, I've never seen her in my life.
Blue, black, long hair? Red eyes?
If I ever saw such a maiden, I would call her a princess.
She sounds like one.
Well, we have evidence, we have evidence, we have evidence.
Does the name "99_X3XD" ring a bell to you?
Oh, yes! Because 99_X3XD is me.
Huh!
I knew it!
You are the prime suspect in the stalking incident!
Of Nerissa Ravencroft!
We have it on paper right here!
And we have all the chat logs that you put in Nerissa Ravencroft's channel right here.
I don't know, I watch a lot of virtual entertainers.
Nerissa Ravencroft, I'm outside of your house right now.
Nerissa Ravencroft, I see you from the window.
Nerissa Ravencroft, take off your shirt.
Whoa, now...
That was also you!
I don't know about that. I think you're mistaken. I would never speak that way to a princess.
Tell her that we're never going to give her donuts ever again.
And you will never have donuts ever again.
And I would have never... Donuts? How did you know I like donuts?
No more donuts! No more donuts.
But, if you just confess, we have an in with Nerissa Ravencroft.
Yeah, offer a good deal, Gigi!
We can give you what you want.
A date with Nerissa Ravencroft!
Okay, now you guys switch roles. Gigi is the bad cop...
Look, I admit it. I know her.
Answer us right now! Answer us right now!
Go crazy! Go crazy on her!
I'm scared!
Hey, you! Whoa!
A third woman, it is my lucky day.
Chief Raora! Oh, Chief Raora!
What do you guys think you're doing, huh?
I was doing what you were saying.
You useless! You don't do anything in this place!
Why did I hire you, huh? You're so useless!
This person, we have all the evidence, and you still didn't manage to make her tell the truth!
Chief, we are trying our best, okay? We are underpaid, overworked!
You're embarrassing us in front of the criminal.
Well, maybe you should do better than this!
You're humiliating us. You're not even listening to me, are you?
You never fixed our coffee machine! And we never get free time off, Raora!
Well, if you work more, maybe you will deserve your coffee machine!
Do you like coffee?
No.
Why? What do you want from me? I like tea, please!
And you, write! Silence!
You know, one of my favorite virtual entertainers, Cecilia Immergreen, she does not like coffee.
Do you remember what did you do in that record?
Um, I... I mean, I... I make up my own stories in my blog.
Well, your own story with Nerissa Ravencroft, by any chance?
Get her, Boss! Get her, Boss!
Boss, I think... I think you're all perfect at this task. Yeah, I think you're doing great.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank thank...
So you do know Nerissa Ravencroft!
I know that her name spelled backwards is "Assiren."
How do you know that? How do you know that?
Ah, I know many Nerissas because I'm very popular with the ladies.
Oh! What about the photo collection she has in her room?
We have some things that I want to show you, okay?
See this paper right here?
Can you loosen my shackles, please? No, no.
These are all the photos that we found in your room that you have taken of Nerissa Ravencroft.
Do you recognize these?
These photos, do you recognize these photos of Nerissa Ravencroft?
Well, you took them. We found them on your camera.
I think my mother really, really liked Nerissa Ravencroft.
It was not your mother!
Oh!
There's a selfie right here!
That's you right there!
What do you think? - It's you, it's you.
So, what do you have to say? Is that you, or is that not you?
I think there's an imposter here.
Is that you, or is that not you?
So, about the evidence that we have, the bra, which is the wrong size, so it's not hers, it's from Nerissa Ravencroft because it's also signed by her.
We found a bra in your room.
And it's the wrong size.
I checked your breast size when you came in, and it's not this size. - Not that one.
It is Nerissa Ravencroft's. And it's also blue.
She never wears blue!
And we know you don't wear blue bras.
I do! - Are you sure?
I checked.
I think you guys... I think you guys... - Stop it, criminal! I mean...
We can... we can give you more than a bra from Nerissa Ravencroft. - Help me!
We can give you way more than a bra from Nerissa Ravencroft... - Help me! I need help.
These photos... - These photos...
It's me!
These photos. - These photos.
What are you doing to her?!
What did you offer just now?!
I was doing... - You offered to give her stuff from Nerissa Ravencroft?!
You offered her! She offered her! - He forced me! It was all her!
I was only doing what you were telling me to do!
I'm going to get away. - What are you talking about? - She was talking about...
She was trying to bribe her! - You are trying to bribe her?
We are not police officers trying to find a new victim!
She told me to do it...
What are you doing? Why am I even paying you right now?
I just... I just kept getting yelled at.
It's my first day on the force, and I just really wanted to be a good cop.
And then 99, 83, 83... she's just so good! We had all the evidence and all, she bribed...
...us, and she got away!
I've never seen such a thing.
99 83 8D was just so cunning.
It was kind of attractive, actually.
Those long hairs, and those curves...
Actually, I should go find her.
Oh, they are totally useless. They can't do anything.
I... I need to find new... new people for this job. They don't have the guts for this.
But 99 83 8D... she said she likes ladies and stuff.
Maybe she would like me? Maybe she could work with me, who knows?
Where is she anyway?
Heh, they didn't see it coming.
They didn't know I was... well, they didn't know I was 99 83 8D.
But they didn't... they didn't catch me one bit!
For I am too good, I am too cunning. I am... too powerful, as they say.
Can I get out of this?
The next training is Firearms Training!
What's required is precision and split-second judgment.
A moment's hesitation can greatly impact the outcome!
Can Justice remain unfazed by the situation and deliver highly accurate shots?
Firearms training, let's go! - Let's go!
Yeah! Let's go!
First, let's go over the rules.
Rules!
A variety of targets will appear one after another.
Your job is to quickly decide whether to shoot or hold your fire.
If it's a valid target, take it out with your revolver.
But be careful, not every target is meant to be shot.
Out of the ten targets...
Three are no-shoot targets!
So don't let your guard down.
Okay! Okay!
Wait, what do you mean? I wasn't listening, I wasn't paying attention.
Alright, so you shoot everything.
No! No!
Shoot everyone! - You shouldn't listen to what she said!
Most importantly, shoot your friends! - What?
Huh? What the freak?!
Alright, Cecilia, you're up first!
Justice! Justice! Just like that! Justice!
She should shoot that! She should shoot that!
Cecilia, are you feeling confident?
Really good, look at my trigger... Oh, it's not... Oh, yeah, I'm really good.
I'm gonna shoot everything, and I'm gonna win!
Ready, set, go!
お、そこだ…うわ！
Oh, there it is... Whoa!
当たった！
I got it!
よし！やった、やった！
Yes! I got it, I got it!
彼女イカれてるよ！
She is crazy!
うわ…おお！
Whoa... Oh!
嘘でしょ、魔法のノーム…？
Oh my god, is that a gnome with magic...?
しかも死んだ！
And it's dead!
ノームを殺しちゃった！
You killed a gnome!
めっちゃ…魔法の妖精キノコ？
Very... magic fairy mushroom?
魔法の妖精ノームだよ。
Magic fairy gnome.
あれってピザ？ / そう、ピザ！ピザを撃て！
Is that a pizza? / Yeah, pizza! Shoot the pizza!
ピザを撃て！ピザ！
Shoot the pizza! Pizza!
ピザって悪者なの？
Pizza's a bad thing?
待って、ピザを撃つべきなの？
Wait, we're supposed to shoot the pizza?
おお、おお…ダメ、ダメ！
Oh, oh... No, no!
待って、ダメ！あの子はただの幼い女の子だよ！
Wait, no! She was just a little girl!
ダメ！ただの女の子だったのに！
No! She was just a little girl!
死ね！
Die!
違う、違う、違う、ロイヤルガードだよ！
No, no, no, that's a royal guard!
リズ！セシリア！
Liz! Cecilia!
ちょっと！うわ、彼女人殺しだよ！
Hey! Whoa, she's a killer!
待って、見て！運転中にメールしてる！
Wait, look! He's texting while driving!
死んだ！
He's dead!
いいね、いいね！犯罪者を一人駆除できた！
Good, good! We got rid of a criminal!
そう、あいつは紛れもない犯罪者だ。
Yeah, that's a criminal right there.
ちょっと、それ私の年金！
Hey, that's my pension!
ああ、そう、それ撃て！彼女の年金を撃ち抜け！
Oh, yeah, shoot that! Shoot her pension!
そうだ！彼女の年金を撃て！
Yes! Shoot her pension!
あら、こんにちは、ちっちゃなジェットパック。
Oh, hello, tiny jetpack.
すっごく小さいね。
Very tiny.
よし！ナイスショット！
Yes! Nice shot!
ピクルス…見て、見て…きゅうり…
Pickle... look, look... cucumber...
きゅうり、きゅうりだ…
Cucumber, cucumber...
きゅうりは撃っちゃダメ！
Don't shoot the cucumber!
きゅうり！
Cucumber!
よし！ナイス！ / イェーイ！
Yes! Nice! / Yay!
待って…そう、私たちは…
Wait... yeah, we...
あ、クッキー食べてるノームを見て！
Oh, look at the gnome eating cookies!
クッキーだ！よし、よし！バイバイ！
Cookies! Yes, yes! Bye-bye!
本当に？
Really?
できた！
I did it!
全部撃ち抜いたね！ / イェーイ！
She shot everything! / Yay!
セシリアの最終スコアは…
Cecilia's final score is...
…7ポイント！ / え、7？ / 7。
...seven points! / Oh, seven? / Seven.
6、7？なんで7？
6, 7? Why seven?
8、9？ / まあ…
8, 9? / Well...
正直なところ…
Honestly...
きゅうりはマイナスだと思うんだけど、プラスだと思ってたの…
I think the cucumber was a minus, and I thought it was a plus...
だってきゅうりを処分すれば、彼女が食べなくて済むから。
...because we want to kill the cucumber so she doesn't have to eat it.
私はきゅうりが嫌いだからね、そうだ。
I don't like cucumbers, right.
それに、時には撃っちゃいけないターゲットを撃っちゃったとしても…
And I think even if I shot the ones that weren't meant to be shot sometimes...
このおバカさん…
You idiot...
危機的状況では、たとえ間違っていても決断を下さなきゃいけないんだよ！
...in a crisis situation, you just have to make a decision, even if it's the wrong one!
撃て！それはどうかな…
Shoot! Not sure about...
よし、いくぞ。フレイムオン！
All right, let's go. Flame on!
フレイムオン！いいぞ。
Flame on! All right.
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, go!
イェーイ！
Yay!
よし、撃て！撃て！
Okay, shoot it! Shoot it!
撃て！いいね！
Shoot! Good!
あら、チアリーダーだね。
Oh, she's a cheerleader.
撃て！撃て！撃て！
Shoot it! Shoot it! Shoot it!
ふう！仕留めたぞ！
Phew! Got that one!
私の頭が…やらなきゃ…
My head... I must...
なんで自分を撃っちゃうの？！
How could you shoot yourself?!
待って、明らかに違う…
Wait, it's obviously not...
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ！あれは鳥だよ！鳥！
No, no, no! That's a bird! That's a bird!
可愛い鳥なのに！
That's a nice bird!
ああ、そうね、ハハ。
Oh, yeah, haha.
うわ、うわ、うわ…また？
Whoa, whoa, whoa... again?
なんで自分を撃ったの？
Why did you shoot yourself?
そんなつもりじゃなかったんだ。
I didn't mean to do that.
わかった。
Okay.
よし、見てみよう。
Okay, let's see.
あら見て！撃たなかった！わあ、ハハ。
Oh, look at that! She didn't shoot! Wow, haha.
地面に落ちてるのは1ペニー？
Is that a penny on the ground?
待って、これ撃たないの？なんで？
Wait, she's not shooting this one? Why not?
ダメ、私の年金！リズ、それが必要なの！
No, my pension! Liz, we need that!
年金？ダメ、必要だよ！
Pension? No, we need it!
そうだ！正義のためにそれが必要なんだ！
Yeah! We need that for justice!
お願い！
Please!
私のピザ！ああ、お腹空いた！お腹空いた！
My pizza! Oh, oh, I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
よし、仕留めた！やった！
Yeah, she got it! Yes!
ピザが食べたい！
We want pizza!
オッケー。
Okay.
お金！お金！お金！
Money! Money! Money!
撃て、撃て！お金が必要なんだ！
Shoot it, shoot it! We need money!
お金、お金、お金！お金が必要！なんで？！
Money, money, money! We need money! Why?!
なんで？！嘘でしょ、リズ…
What?! Oh no, Liz...
あ、猫ちゃんを見て！
Oh, look at the cat!
殺せ！殺せ！殺せ！
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
ダメ！殺して！
No! Kill it!
でも、あいつすごく面白いよ！
He's so funny, though!
よし、最後だ。「私を撃って」！
All right, last one. Shoot me!
撃て、撃て！
Shoot it, shoot it!
その調子！ふう、仕留めた！
Like that! Phew! Got them!
イェーイ！すごい！よし、終わりだよ！
Yeah! So good! Okay, you are done!
ああ、やった！よし、私のスコアは？
Oh, yes! Okay, what is my score?
あなたの得点は…ドラムロール…
Your points are... drumroll...
No, that's bad!
Oh! Kill it! Kill it!
I can't... I can't hit it.
Oh, God.
You're lucky. You're lucky. You're so lucky right now.
Kill it! Kill it! / No, don't kill it!
I can't kill it. I looked into its eyes and I can't kill it!
I looked right into its eyes and I couldn't do it!
Pizza!
Yeah! Good job!
No more pizza. / No more pizza diet!
Whoa, he's stealing the cookies! Kill him!
My gun... it doesn't work!
He's texting while driving! We have to put him down!
That was so good!
Okay, I think you are done. / You've run out of bullets.
Gigi, point it away from yourself. / Oh, no, no, no!
Okay!
Wait, it's time to reveal Gigi's score!
They're real, they're real!
Okay, the final score for Gigi... / Do it!
You...
I'm so tired! / Eight! You got eight!
Yeah! Eight!
It's your turn, Raora Panthera! / It's me!
Yeah, big cat means... / Big gun? Me?
Yeah, let's go. Let's face the gun!
It's not real, you're not gonna die. / I practice...
Wait, what? What do I do again?
You shoot those targets, and you shoot the ones that are bad.
Bad ones? / How do I know which one is bad?
That's up to you to decide as a member of Justice.
Ready? / I'm ready! / Ready, set, go!
Go, go, go, get him!
Okay, okay... shoot, shoot, shoot!
Behind, Raora, behind! A little to the left!
You were supposed to shoot this one! / Oh, really?
Oh, look, he's texting while driving! / Where?
Get him! / I can't... I can't hit it.
He's texting! Oh God, that guy is a menace!
Liz? Liz? / No, don't kill Liz! / I shot Liz...
I'm right here, that's an impostor! / You killed Liz!
Don't kill him! / Kill him! Kill him!
Did you get him? / No! That's a 'No Shoot'!
Raora with the god eyes, huh? He's stealing cookies!
Get him! Kill him! He's stealing the cookies!
Hey, but he's gone! / Why didn't you kill him?!
Oh right, next... Come on, get the next one!
Oh, cute! / No, he's stealing fairy mushrooms!
Get him, get him, get him! / Hey, I shot...
Ah, that's a 'No Shoot'.
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
Yeah! Kill it!
Oh, that's bad! / Raora, get the piggy bank!
Get the piggy bank! Yeah, shoot it!
Ah! He's on the loose! / It jumps real fast.
Wait, no, don't shoot it! / No?
Yay, cucumber for dinner! / Yeah!
Oh, money! / Do we want money?
This is the Gigi texting. / What's wrong with that?
Yeah!
That was great, Raora! That was really good!
Really good for a kitty. / Can I shoot something else?
Can I go after criminals? / Gigi, save the score.
Do you want to know how much? / I want to know!
I want to know! / Hold my hand, I need to tell you.
Your score was... four! / Four?
You did it on purpose, because there's four of us!
Justice! / Justice!
And the training is complete! Huzzah!
And the winner is... all of us! Yeah!
At the loser! Loser! The loser! Loser!
Oh, it's okay, Gigi, you're the freaking loser.
Hey, I just wanted to make you win because I'm the strongest with my god eyes, so...
Also, Elizabeth, what's that behind your back?
What's behind my back?
What's behind your back?
You can't do that!
You can't do that! She's mad!
She's mad!
Cecilia! Cecilia!
Cecilia!
Traffic Enforcement Training
[Title: Traffic Enforcement Training]
The next training is Traffic Enforcement Training.
This duty requires accurately assessing the violation
and processing it correctly.
However, in the field, unexpected behavior
can sometimes shake an officer's judgment.
Can Justice stay unfazed in any situation
and carry out the appropriate response?
We did it, boys. Good job, my goons.
Oh no, a cop car. Run!
Oh no!
My goon, goon, do the voice, do the voice.
Okay, boss.
Buonasera.
Good evening.
Good afternoon.
What's all this then?
You know what? I pulled you over... That was really cool.
Oh my god, you did it again. Oh cool.
Silenzio!
Silence!
Don't act like you don't know anything!
You blew right through the stop sign!
We are just really in a hurry right now.
My husband, he's pregnant.
Can I see your driver's license, please?
Oh yes, yes. Do you have your driver's license?
Driver's license? We don't have time.
He's really pregnant. I am so pregnant.
His water just broke!
Oh, we have to go to the hospital!
We have to go to the hospital right now, please!
I think they are liars.
We are not, we're not lying.
He's like really pregnant.
Look how big he is.
I think she's not pregnant, officer.
Excuse me, my husband is really pregnant. He's really big right now.
I'm really pregnant. Please.
Let me feel the baby.
It's kicking!
Can you not feel it?
My son!
I feel you!
Your ear!
Silenzio!
Silence!
Please!
What do you think? Those two, those two are acting a little bit...
suspicious.
Mamma mia!
Are you alright?
Do you think? Could it be?
Yes.
See, this is exactly what I was thinking.
My son!
No, no, no! Why are you stopping us?
Because I am pregnant? It was the baby! It was the baby!
Oh, there was a horse there.
No, it was my baby! It was our baby! It was our baby!
Recently?
No, no, no, it's still our baby!
I heard a hoof sound coming from the trunk.
Hey, you can't say that about my baby!
Mind if we take a look?
I do mind! I mind!
Wait, wait, wait, wait! No, no, no! Okay, okay, okay.
Just a quick look, just a quick look.
We're just going to take a look at the trunk.
Please, please!
You are definitely guilty!
No, you can't! Please, officer, stop! Officer, please! Officer, police!
You'll stop me?
It's our officer!
A horse?
It's a horse! It's a horse!
It's my son! No, it's our son!
Gigi Murin, Cecilia Immergreen, you're under arrest.
No! Please! You are arrested. Wow.
I can't be under arrest. I have too much to lose.
Yeah, you're under arrest. Give me your hand. No!
You are arrested, officially.
Wait, what? Boss! Boss! You can't leave me! Boss!
Yes, yes, yes, under arrest.
See you later, officer.
Hey! We're going to get her! Get her!
Let's get her!
I can't drive!
It's just you and me, baby.
National Museum
[Title: National Museum]
All right, the place is empty. Got about ten minutes before the guard's next patrol.
So, this is the YAGOO trophy? The Giga-Mega National Treasure.
I'm going to make a fortune on this.
This is Justice. Is this an emergency?
Help! Help! Please! Please! Please, is somebody here right now? I don't know what to do, please!
Calm down, and take a deep breath.
Can you tell me exactly what happened?
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Uh, calm down, calm down...
Leave it to us. Leave it to us.
Justice is on the way right now!
Everyone, we have a case!
The Ultimate National Treasure has been stolen! Head to the scene immediately!
The Ultimate National Treasure?
You mean the YAGOO statue?
Who even wants that? Just let 'em keep it.
Gigi Murin
Gigi, that is disrespectful!
It is still the Ultimate National Treasure!
We're counting on you.
Fine, I'm on it.
Ah, wait! Lilith!
The super limited edition Sweet Kitty Plush drops in just three minutes!
It's limited quantity, okay?
That... That means I absolutely have to buy it!
Uh, okay, so only two minutes left now...
Just go already!
Ah! No! Oh, mio dio! Porca miseria! No! No!
Ah! No! Oh my god! Damn it! No! No!
Raora Panthera
Cecilia, did you get any information?
Cecilia?
Who the hell changed my keyboard to Dvorak?!
Cecilia Immergreen
Glad you love my present, Cece!
This was you?!
You! You little piece of [bleep]! You absolute garbage can! When I get to you, I'm going to [bleep]!
Cecilia, every second counts here.
I know, I know. All right.
Found a backdoor in the telescope. Cracking the encrypted protocol via brute force, enforcing a security patch overdrive...
In English, please!
Uh, fine. I'm in!
The suspect is a woman dressed entirely in black.
Height looks around 168 cm.
She really likes people wearing helmets...
Ah, she's fleeing north! If you move now, you can still catch her!
You all heard her! Let's move out and apprehend the suspect!
For Justice!
Raora, what are you doing? You don't know how to drive a car?
What? What?
Put your foot on... on the gas pedal!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
What?
There is a horse in front of us!
There's no freaking horse!
Oh my god, there is a horse!
Oh, a horse is right there! Oh my god!
No way, it's real!
Oh, we must... we must get out of here now!
Hurry, Gigi! We might be able to buy...
No, we might miss the limited edition Satini!
If I missed it, I'm gonna die!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Horses like vegetables, right?
I think there's a cucumber in the trunk.
What?
A cucumber.
A cucumber in the trunk.
Hold on, Gigi Murin.
Why do you have a cucumber in your pocket right now?
Gigi Murin, I...
You know I hate cucumbers!
You know why?
What?
Gigi Murin, you know I hate cucumbers.
Why do you have cucumbers right now?
Ew! Get out of here!
You know where I'm going to put that cucumber?
Where?
Get out of here right now! I don't want to see the cucumber.
Ew!
What about the... what about for the horse?
No.
What about for the horse?
Oh, you hate me! Don't you freaking hate me?
No, you hate me! So you hate me?
So you hate me? Just say it! Tell me!
You know how I feel! Why did you bring cucumbers?
Why do you have cucumbers right now?
I hate cucumbers! I hate the taste! Everything about cucumbers!
Stop laughing! Stop laughing!
Haaah...
Those two are away with the fairies.
Cecilia!
Do you have any updates on the suspects' location?
Cecilia?
Cecilia Immergreen!
No!
I missed! Look what you did, Liz!
You ruined my perfect score! I was so close!
Not you too!
Did I fail them as a mother?
My heart breaks as their big sister.
I've done everything in my power to look after those three...
...those three wild, eccentric little sisters...
...and guide them to this very day.
I gave them my all!
Oh, what did I do to deserve such cruelty?
Where did I go wrong?
Where did my guidance stray away from the path?
You guys are still... still there, huh?
We're sorry, Mommy...
I promise I'll be a good girl.
We're sorry.
Big sister... Big sister...
It's just allergies. I'm not crying, you're crying.
We love you! Big sister! We love you!
Happy ever after.
Justice, just like that.
Guys! Everyone!
It's the thief who stole the Ultimate Justice Statue!
We're going to kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
Hey, you! Hold it right there!
Because of you, I missed out on unlimited editions of Satini and I didn't even get to eat my delicious pizza!
How are you going to take responsibility for this?
That sounds like a 'you' problem. Go eat your pizza now.
Oh, by the way, there's a shop nearby famous for its cucumber pizza. It's to die for.
Agh! Cucumber pizza?
Ew!
Even I've had it before. Absolutely exquisite.
Oh, this is... Haaah... This is such an insult!
Impossible!
It's okay, it's okay, Raora. Please, relax, relax.
Doom!
Doom?
JUSTICE SHOPPING!
Whoaaa!
And now, it's time to introduce Justice's 2nd Anniversary Merch!
Yay!
First, take a look at this!
The Premium Acrylic Message Board!
Ooh!
We spoke with someone who actually used it.
Oh, you want to meet...
You talk about the premium acrylic message board?
You want to talk about the premium acrylic message board?
Ah, yeah, yeah, sure. Oui, oui!
This artwork is so cool! I love it so much.
Ah, using acrylic instead of paper was such a good choice!
And it makes it feel really special.
And the foil-stamped replicated messages?
That's honestly the best part! I can't stop looking at it.
It just looks that much good, you know? Oui, oui!
Ah, please support Justice and buy our merch, oui?
Thank you. Merci!
Wow, that's some pretty high praise!
We've still got lots more merch to introduce.
So let's move on to the next item!
Here it is.
Embroidered Patch Keychain!
So cute!
The illustrator behind this artwork...
...is none other than Raora Panthera!
And guess what?
We've received a special message directly from her!
Tada!
This is Raora Panthera,
the artist behind the embroidered keychains!
Raora!
You know, I'm... I'm so happy
I got the chance to draw for my Justice girls!
Greetings from some of my friends always feel really special,
...and... and I hope... I hope you're gonna love them as much as I do!
Yes, yes, yes!
And you know, they took all my adorable illustrations...
...and turned them into those cute embroidered keychains.
And you know, since they... since they are keychains,
you can attach them to your bag
and take them with you wherever you go!
Yeah!
A little bit extra cuteness for your everyday life.
Hehe.
So make sure to pick one up!
And trust me, the cuteness is guaranteed!
Yes!
Look at that! They're so cute!
Adorable!
What a wonderful piece of merch!
Anyone would love to have that one in their home, including me!
Oh right, let's move on to the next piece of merch.
Take a look at this!
The Medal-Style Badge!
Cool!
We caught up with Justice's leader, Elizabeth, to get her thoughts.
Hm?
You wanna hear about the badge?
Hehe, of course!
My sweethearts, my Justi-cheris, hehe.
This badge was designed with the image of law enforcement and authority in mind.
The weighty, prestigious look fits Justice perfectly, don't you think?
I think it looks absolutely... fan-tabby-dozy! It looks fantastic!
Very cool.
Anyone who strives for justice should definitely get their hands on one.
Oh, and it also comes in a beautiful display box,
so it's perfect for displaying and admiring as well.
I hope when you guys look at your... your medal or wear it...
...that you will remember how...
...us, Justice, are... and we're so proud of you all and we all really appreciate you so, so, so much.
So I really hope that comes to mind every time you wear or look at this medal, yeah?
Mwah! Hehe.
And that was a message from Elizabeth.
And now, for the final item we're introducing today...
...here it is!
The Double-Zip Patch Hoodie!
Woah!
We spoke with a fan who actually got their hands on the merch.
Wait, a Justice show?
Oh, oh my god, oh my god! I'm so excited!
You wanna hear my thoughts on this merch...
...as the biggest Justice fan in the world, that has nothing to do with Justice, I'm just a random fan passing by?
Of course! Ask me anything!
Q: What do you think about this item?
Oh, I absolutely love the design!
The patches inspired by all four members of Justice are so cute and stylish!
And I love how each one of them reflects their personality.
And... and the logo and text on the back give us such a cool, premium look!
It's the kind of hoodie that instantly makes you think, "Mm, yes, this is Justice!"
Q: How is it when you actually wear it?
Oh, it's amazing!
The brushed fleece lining makes it super warm and comfortable.
Not only does it look great...
...but it's also really practical.
And the fact that it comes in both L and LL sizes is fantastic!
I think a lot of fans will appreciate having different size options.
So make sure to buy the Justice merch, okay?
Wow, jolly good!
Now that's a passionate fan!
And that's it for Justice Shopping!
Hooray!
So, how was it?
It was awesome!
Oh, and what did you like the most?
The horse!
Ah, the horse...
And there's just this news flash!
We interrupt your regularly scheduled programming to bring you this breaking news.
We have just received an exclusive update from Justice, the global guardians of peace.
Rumor has it a brand new track from the iconic four-piece is about to drop at any second.
I repeat, new music from Justice is imminent.
Do not touch that dial.
We will be right back with the world premiere.
This is Ouro Kronii, signing out.
Yeah
Are you there?
You're a SUPER GIRL
(Justice just like that)
(Justice get get that)
If you're feeling trapped, send out a signal right above!
(Gesundheit!)
We'll find you, set you free then you can sign up for the club!
(Hit it!)
Danger, fun fun fun
Soul shine like the sun
(Minna Happiness, Minna Happiness)
The frig? I'm big! My strong strong muscle
They see me run, it's no miracle
You are shining
SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing
LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL
I'm the SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA) (SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA) (SUPER GIRL)
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun <3 it
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit
I'm the SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA) (SUPER GIRL)
I always want a pizza, stack those fries up to the sky
Ciao ciao!
You lot say whatcha think about us hittin' town tonight?
Feeling happy time, no sad, say bye bye
(MOTTO MANIAC, JUSTICE JUST LIKE THAT)
So stomp, stomp, stomp your feet to this beat
Cuz we are space, no no gravity!
You are shining
SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing
LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL
I'm the SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA) (SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA) (SUPER GIRL)
I know you're feeling so super bad
You don't have depression, you're just super sad
We are change the world, that's hope!
If you doubt, hope you explode!
Justice loud, Justice proud and we keep telling you!
We are SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA) (SUPER GIRL)
SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA) (SUPER GIRL)
Justice we are justice, make the baddies go boom!
Come on, come on, baby, rocker ship to the moon!
I'm the SUPER!
DUPER!
(SUPERNOVA) (SUPER GIRL)
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
And that was SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL, our brand new song!
Yeah!
And just like that, our second anniversary stream is coming to an end.
So, what did you all think? We'll start with Raora this time.
Who, me?
Yeah, you first this time.
Ah, it was really fun! It was amazing! I can't believe it's been already, like, two years!
I know! Wow!
And thank you so much, you guys, as well, for being... the best... the best companions ever, you know?
Yay! I'm so grateful to you guys and thank you...
...and thank you to Justice chat for supporting us since two years now! It's insane! Thank you!
Thank you, Justice chat! Thank you so much!
Hello! Thank you very much, everyone, for being...
And hello... Oh, sorry!
Oh, sorry!
Let's do it with green! Do it with green!
Thank you very much for being here today, everyone!
Thank you for choosing Justice!
Please keep supporting us and listen to our song!
Yes!
Stream Supernova Super Girl!
Yeah!
Elizabeth is going to talk!
What I think? I think...
...the stage is very cool! Look at the stage! Woah!
And look at this amazing team. I couldn't ask for better.
I love you girls. I love you all very much.
And Justiciar, we love you all very much, too.
Thank you so much for supporting Justice. Thank you so, so, so much.
I love you so much.
So many kisses because you are so spoiled.
Okay, Gigi.
Are you eating them? She's eating them! Oh my god!
Thanks Justiciar, thank you for supporting us for... two... years?
Two! We didn't even know we could...
I didn't even know Raora could count to two!
But we made it to two years! Thank you for supporting us!
Please stream Supernova Super Girl! Learn the...
...chants! Chants? Chants.
For our song?
For some reason, maybe you should learn the chants.
I wonder if there is a lyric somewhere for you to learn...
...when we go "Supernova..."
"...Super Girl!" Or...
...'Minna Happiness!'
Minna Happiness! Yeah!
We all feel like Super Girls because of you guys. Thank you so much!
Yes!
And don't forget to grab the merch!
Purchase our merch!
Yes, thank you, thank you, thank you all so much for celebrating with us today.
Please keep supporting Justice, please, going forward as well.
Now then, let's all say goodbye together...
...with our own chant!
You ready? I'm ready. All right.
Justice, just like that!
Justice, get, get, get down!
Minna Happiness!
Minna Happiness! Bye-bye!
Stay tuned for the premiere of Justice's new MV "SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL" right after this!