(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
はぁー...
Haa...
Cerah sekali hari ini.
It's so bright today.
Ya, langit yang sangat biru.
Yeah, the sky is so blue.
うわぁー... うわぁー...
Uwaaa... Uwaaa...
Langit biru, memerah hati.
Blue sky, blushing heart.
Putih awan, setulus cintaku pun bersemi.
White clouds, as sincere as my love blooming.
Kurang ngeteh aja nih.
Just missing some tea.
Ha? Bentar, kita baca chat dulu ya guys,
Huh? Wait, let's read the chat first guys,
kita absen dulu.
let's do a roll call.
Bu intro, bu intro... Eh, saya bukan Kobo ya.
Intro lady, intro lady... Eh, I'm not Kobo.
Panggil aku Cebo.
Call me Cebo.
Ya, sama-sama "Bo" sih.
Yeah, both are "Bo" anyway.
Tapi di sini saya bukan Kobo ya, tapi oke...
But here I'm not Kobo, but okay...
intro dulu ya guys.
intro first guys.
Abocceboccebo...
Cebo Kanaeru siap menghujani hatimu
Cebo Kanaeru is ready to rain on your heart
dengan petir cintaku.
with my lightning of love.
Anjay...
Damn...
Oke, mari kita lihat live chat lagi.
Okay, let's look at the live chat again.
Kak, itu ada gitar di belakang. Coba mainin dong.
Sis, there's a guitar back there. Try playing it.
Aku dan keluargaku sangat ingin mendengar
My family and I really want to hear
Kak Cebo bernyanyi.
Kak Cebo sing.
Oh iya, ada gitar ya? Oh.
Oh right, there's a guitar? Oh.
There's guitar here. そうですね。
There's a guitar here. That's right.
Tapi... mana ya? Aku nggak pandai nyanyi guys.
But... well? I'm not good at singing guys.
Plis Kak, suara Kakak ganteng banget,
Please Kak, your voice is so handsome,
pasti bagus kalau nyanyi.
it must be good if you sing.
Aduh iya iya...
Ouch, okay okay...
や udahlah しょうがないわ。
Well, it can't be helped.
Tapi satu lagu aja ya, oke?
But just one song, okay?
Only one song okay?
Maaf ya guys kalau sedikit gimana gitu,
Sorry guys if it's a bit like that,
soalnya aku emang nggak pandai nyanyi.
because I'm really not good at singing.
Ya udah, let's go.
Alright, let's go.
丑三つ時に隠れて
Hiding in the hour of the ox
終わらないベンドーテン
An endless overdose
電池はもうこの部屋にはない
There's no more battery in this room
顔も知らない一人と
With someone whose face I don't know
目が合う今日この頃
Our eyes meet these days
何かを必死にして
Desperately doing something
動き始める歯車
The gears begin to move
私の耳を劈くような音
A sound that seems to pierce my ears
ないものねだり夜が明ける頃
Asking for the impossible as dawn breaks
誰かの寝言が終わる頃
Around the time someone's sleep-talk ends
あぁ、なんて傑作だ
Ah, what a masterpiece
このままじゃ生きられない
I can't live like this
ダディマミ私いい子じゃない
Daddy, Mommy, I'm not a good kid
...誰にも私を確かめられない
...no one can verify who I am
強がりも起こしちゃう 一人きり
Acting tough all by myself
奈落の日々も悪くないでしょ？ Help!
The days in the abyss aren't so bad, right? Help!
流れる雨の数が増えていくから
Because the amount of falling rain is increasing
たまに走るリズムに合わない
It doesn't match the rhythm I occasionally run to
名前も知らない人と目が合うこの頃
Lately, I've been making eye contact with people I don't know
何かを必死にして震える
Desperately doing something while trembling
夢見る時間に限りがあること
That there's a limit to the time spent dreaming
期待してた 剥がれてくそこ
I was expecting it; it's peeling away there
私じゃなきゃいけない理由はどこ？
Where is the reason why it has to be me?
なんて失敗作
What a failure
踊るを歩きたい
I want to walk the dance
誰にも私を確かめられない
No one can verify who I am
臆病も魔がさしちゃう 一人きり
Cowardice tempts me when I'm all alone
奈落の優しさ Oh yeah
The kindness of the abyss, oh yeah
Help! Please go away! バカげた呪文待つのよ
Help! Please go away! I'm waiting for a silly spell
必死こいて格好つけたって 夢を見たい
Even if I try my best to look cool, I want to dream
けど 瞳そらしちゃう 特等席から
But I look away from the best seat
負け惜しんだプライド半分 足んない自分の不備を...
Admit your half-hearted pride and your own shortcomings...
このままじゃ楽しくない
It's no fun like this
誰にも私をさらけ出したい
I want to reveal myself to everyone
面倒なんて全部台無しにしたい
I want to ruin all the bothersome things
でも これも好き放題 私は叶えるの
But I'll do whatever I want; I'll make it happen
このままじゃイキれない
I can't live like this
私じゃいられない だから
I can't be myself, so
今だけを見つめてたい そう 今だけを
I want to focus on just right now, yes, just right now
壊さないように
So as not to break it
疲れたー！ はあ...
I'm so tired! Haah...
Wah, keren banget nggak sih?
Wow, wasn't that really cool?
Syuuush!
Suara Kobo, eh Cibo maksudnya.
Kobo's voice, I mean Cibo.
Aku keren, suara keren, ya nggak? Rawr!
I'm cool, my voice is cool, right? Rawr!
Dah sorosoro jikan da, jadi gimana ya?
It's almost time, so what should I do?
Udah disemangatin sih, kinchou suru demo ya...
I've been cheered up, although I'm nervous...
disemangatin sama Bang Natori jadi aku mau jadi lebih keren. Yeah!
cheered on by Natori-san, so I want to become even cooler. Yeah!
Uoryaaaa!
Lah tapi bentar, kok mendung gini?
Wait, why is it getting cloudy?
Kalau hujan gini kan nggak jadi keren.
If it rains like this, it won't be cool anymore.
Ni timing ujan nya nggak bisa di-delay apa? Hmm...
Can't the timing of this rain be delayed or something? Hmm...
Nggak bawa payung lagi.
Didn't bring an umbrella either.
Kasa... kasa pake gitar apa nggak ya? Jangan-jangan. Haah, shikata ga nai.
Umbrella... should I use the guitar as an umbrella? No, don't. Haah, it can't be helped.
Ya udah, shikata ga nai.
Oh well, it can't be helped.
Tanpa payung pun aku pasti bisa.
Even without an umbrella, I can do it.
見て！この雨シャーマンのパワー！
Look! The power of this rain shaman!
うああああ！痛い！
Uaaaaakh! It hurts!
Bangun bangun! Bangun!
Wake up, wake up! Wake up!
Hello! Help!
Kobo! Kobo come on! Eh, bangun bangun!
Kobo! Kobo, come on! Hey, wake up!
Gugu gaga.
Gugu gaga?!
No no no no! Chotto matte!
No no no no! Wait a second!
No! We can't do this again! I'm here for your anniversary,
not to raise you from a baby up again!
Gugu gaga!
hoho! usu usu~ むにゃむにゃ~
hoho! usu usu~ munya munya~
Eh? What is she saying now?
Usu~ むにゃむにゃ~
Usu~ munya munya~
Oh, oh, there's subtitles below! Wonderful. Hmm...
the blue kid has been suspended by the sky, the sky ang-yyy!!!
blue kid has been suspended by the sky, the sky angyyy!!!
青い子供が空に吊り下げられている、空が怒っている！
A blue child is being suspended by the sky; the sky is angry!
Oh, why would the sky be angry about my sweet child?
She had treat the sky roughly!!
空を荒っぽく扱っていた！
She had treated the sky roughly!
I believe there's a misunderstanding here.
Please, bring her back to normal, I beg you!
hoho~ in order to bring her back to normal, is to train her to be an idol!!!!!! Good luck
元に戻すには、ここでアイドルになるための訓練をすることだ！
In order to return her to normal, you must train her to be an idol! Good luck.
Eh? Idol?
Wait, wait, wait... no, no, no... okay.
Okay, Bokobokobo, come on.
Let's just go inside first, okay? And we'll talk about it. Come on.
Can you stand up and walk normally?
I know you can.
Just try, try, here, here.
We've done this before many years ago.
There you go! Wheee!
Kobo! Are you okay?
Oh no! No, no, no...
Okay, okay. You know what?
If you ganbaru and do your best to walk on your own,
If you do your best and try to walk on your own,
then I will make your favorite food at home.
Kuso gaki. Not again.
Brat. Not again.
Let's go, Bokobokobo.
Let's go home, okay?
Here we are back...
At home!?
Oh my god!
What's going on? This is so chaotic!
Attention! Attention!
Ai, ai, attention please.
Aye, aye, attention please.
Time for your first lesson, because apparently we're here with a lot of kids,
but I think I would like some introductions first, okay?
So we have some order here. Let's try.
Okay, let's begin with...
Hmm, you! Are you... tell me your name.
Yippee! Yippee!
Yippee! Your name is Yippee? Yippee! Okay, tada!
Very good, baby!
I go next to you.
I'll go next to you.
Who are you? Huh? Introduction!
Biboo! Biboo!
Biboo!
Okay, good job. Thank you!
And who are you, cutie patootie? Hmm?
Lu-na! Lu-na!
Okay, okay. And now, because I seem to not be able
to recognize my own child today, who are you?
Abababa! Abababa!
Okay, I guess it was Kobo after all.
Good job everybody! Well done, you did so well!
Kobo, do you remember who I am?
Mama! Mama! Mama!
Yes, Mama! But also known as Kiki-Riki,
I'm Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth,
and today I seem to be the babysitter of this group.
But, but, but, chotto matte!
But, but, but, wait a minute!
Why are these babies here anyway? What's going on?
I thought I made only Kobo into a baby
Koboだけを赤ちゃんにしたつもりも、
I thought I made only Kobo into a baby,
it seems that all the girls on this island have become babies!
この島にいた子みんな赤ちゃんになっちゃったみたい！
Kiara, I asked you to babysit!
キアラ、子守り頼んだよ〜
Kiara, I'm counting on you to babysit~
Did you understand?
Babu?
Yeah!
わかった？
Understand?
わかった？ Okay!
Understand? Okay!
Okay, doesn't matter.
Everybody, I think we should play a game, yeah?
No problem.
I have an idea.
We're gonna draw something over there.
I'm gonna draw something...
...and you all will guess what it is.
Babu? Yeah?
And if you get it right...
...you will get a big cake! How about that?
Are you ready?
Babu?
Yes!
Okay, we will start with Round One!
While I draw, you will behave, okay? Stay there?
Okay? Start!
Sit, sit, here, sit, sit, sit, sit, sit.
Okay, it's finished.
Everybody, please take a look!
見て、見て！
Look, look!
What is this?
What is this, think!
Okay, I will ask you now.
Babu? What is this?
Nya! Nya! Nya! Oh!
ねこ！
Cat!
Oh!
I wonder...
Maybe it's a potential answer.
もしかしたら、そうかもしれない...
Maybe it might be so...
What does Kobo-chan think that this is?
Wait, I don't think so.
But we will see. We will see.
Pi-po-chan?
うんち！ うんち！
Poop! Poop!
Eh? Is my drawing that bad?
そんなに？
That much?
そんなにひどい？
Is it that bad?
Oh, Kobo! Not unchi, right?
Oh, Kobo! Not poop, right?
What is this? Tell me.
い、い、い、い、いぬ！
D-d-d-d-dog!
いぬ！ いぬ！
Dog! Dog!
りんご！ りんご！
Apple! Apple!
いぬ？
Dog?
Yes! いぬ！
Yes! Dog!
Yes!
Okay, Round Two!
Start time!
Okay, please behave, okay?
Shhh... Start!
I've finished, I think. Oh, I finished.
Okay, babies...
Look at this! Ta-da!
Let's think, what could it be?
This doesn't look nice?
Does it look like an animal?
Does it look like... hmm, let's see.
Luna, what do you think that that is?
ドリアン！ ドリアン！ ドリアン！
Durian! Durian! Durian!
Maybe!
Ollie-chan, babies, what is this? What is this?
くさい！ くさい！ くさい！ くさい！
Stinky! Stinky! Stinky! Stinky!
Kusai? So also Durian?
Stinky? So also Durian?
Oh, maybe, maybe, could be.
What do you think, people? What is that over there?
Think, think, think.
バナナ！ バナナ！ バナナ！
Banana! Banana! Banana!
You know banana is yellow.
Okay, okay, Ollie-chan, please save me!
What is this?
Ah!
Eh... ah...
An-ning! An-ning!
Ah! An-ning!
What is an-ning?
An-ning! Ai!
Okay! An-ning, okay!
Calm down! One more round! Last round!
Okay? Start!
Finish! Finish! Okay, please look!
Ta-da!
Oh! Abu!
It's not so difficult, right?
You know, right?
How about this time, we ask Kobo first?
Hmm? What do you think that is?
You know it.
O-ga-ga!
O-ga-ga?
Okay. Probably...
I'll ask them too, okay?
What do you think that is?
Wa-wa! Wa-wa!
A-bu-bu! A-bu-bu!
Wa-wa! Wa-wa! Wa-wa!
Mama! Wa-wa!
And what do you think it is?
A-bu... A-bu...
Tomato!
Hey, hey, hey!
Kobo was correct!
Eh?
O-ga-ga! Kobo's correct!
O-ga-ga!
Kids, how about we get along better together,
仲良ししましょう、
let's get along,
by singing a song!
Do you want to sing a song?
Ya! Ya! Ya!
You too, Kobo!
It's okay, come back up!
They will not bully you anymore, okay?
We'll have fun now! Fun time!
Okay! Singing time!
Ya! Ya! Ya!
チ・チ・チ・モチ・モチ・モチ・モチ・モーシー・キモチ　ウレシッテマジ
Chi-chi-chi feelings, feelings, feeling so happy, for real!
チ・チ・チ・モチ・モチ・モチ・モチ・モーシー・キモチ　タノシイキモチ
Chi-chi-chi feelings, feelings, such a fun feeling!
アメフッテジカタマルケド　コオルバイトジョウケンガナイ
After the rain, the ground hardens, but there's no condition for freezing.
ハレモッテイイコトガアル　ソレキョウノハイテジョウケンガナイ
When it clears up, good things happen, and there's no condition for that today.
チ・チ・チ・モチ・モチ・モチ・ピンチガキテ・チモチガハイテ
Chi-chi-chi feelings, feelings, a pinch comes, and feelings crawl in.
チ・チ・チ・モッ・チョ・ロンサ・マジマッテ・ロッ・テマカセテ・シーモチ
Chi-chi-chi, of course, for real, wait, just leave it to me, feelings.
ヨツバノクローバートレバ　ソレハハッパーイエスハッピー
If you find a four-leaf clover, that's a leaf, yes happy!
シーモチッタラ・オモシロイ・アトヤサシイ・ッテマジ・メーモチ
If you have these feelings, it's interesting and kind, for real.
アッチコッチバッチマチ　カワルウンキヤッホッホー
Here and there, everything's perfect, changing luck, yoo-hoo!
フムフムデモスモスモ　ニチモサチモイカナイダラケ
Hmm, hmm, but still, we're stuck in a rut.
チ・チ・チ・モチ・モチ・モチ
Chi-chi-chi feelings, feelings, feelings...
毎日もちもち
Every day chewy chewy
ちちちもしも
Chi chi chi if
君のきもち
Your feelings
まみむめみも
Ma mi mu me mi mo
雨のち晴れて
After rain, it clears up
なんかちょっとファンシー
Something a bit fancy
ちちちもしも
Chi chi chi if
ピンチがきてちもしがいて
When in a pinch, Chimoshi is there
ちちちモチベあげみてる
Raising my motivation
手も持ってるだけで
Just by holding hands
みんなドラマ大好きなら
If everyone loves drama
そうさもうハッピー
Then it's already happy
ちもしは公平だし
Chimoshi is fair
君狂おしな感じ
A feeling of going crazy for you
あっちこっち毎日
Here and there every day
晴れる天気予報は
The weather forecast says it'll clear up
まじまじとふむふむ
Staring and humming
とにかくこにかくしてあげましょう
Anyway, let's do something or other
ちちちもしも
Chi chi chi if
道のちもし
Chimoshi on the road
ちちちもしも
Chi chi chi if
罪なきもち
A sinful feeling
まみむめみも
Ma mi mu me mi mo
みんなのラブキャッチ
Everyone's love catch
立てアイドルだし
Stand up, it's because I'm an idol
Yay!
Good job everybody!
Now we can eat some cake!
Cake! Cake! Cake! Cake!
Stinky.
Kobo-chan? Stinky!
So stinky!
Kobo has to take a shower!
Shower! Shower! Shower!
Ah, better.
Cake! Cake! Cake!
Mandi Biar Wangi ☆ Washa Washa!
Shower to Smell Nice ☆ Washa Washa!
Habis bermain, keringat bercucuran
After playing, sweat is pouring out
Rambut jadi lepek, juga berminyak
Hair becomes flat and oily too
Tapi ku lelah, ku ingin tidur saja
But I'm tired, I just want to sleep
Memang cuci muka tidak cukup kah?
Is washing my face really not enough?
Bau badan tak tertahankan
Unbearable body odor
Mami Papi pun kewalahan
Mom and Dad are also overwhelmed
Di tengah mereka, ku harus pergi mandi secepatnya
In their midst, I must go take a shower as soon as possible
Washa washa washa washa rambutku
Washa washa washa washa my hair
Washa washa washa, cuci rambutmu
Washa washa washa, wash your hair
Washa washa washa, gosok badanmu
Washa washa washa, scrub your body
Sish sish sish sish, sikat gigi
Sish sish sish sish, brush your teeth
Sekarang sudah wangi
Now it's already fragrant
Shapo shapo shapo, keramas rambutmu
Shapo shapo shapo, shampoo your hair
Washa washa washa, keramas badanmu
Washa washa washa, shampoo your body
Pakai baju, empuk tidurnya,
Put on clothes, sleep comfortably,
bersiap ke kasur
get ready for bed
Selamat malam Mommy Pappy
Good night Mommy Pappy
Selamat pagi, tapi masih di kasur
Good morning, but still in bed
Tangan dan kakiku malas bergerak
My hands and feet are lazy to move
Masih ngantuk, ku ingin tidur saja
Still sleepy, I just want to sleep
Memangnya nggak bisa bentar lagi kah?
Can't it wait a little longer?
Heh
Perut sakit kelaparan
Stomach hurts from hunger
Mommy Pappy ku kewalahan
My Mommy and Pappy are overwhelmed
Katanya mereka, ku harus pergi mandi dulu
They said I have to go take a bath first
Maka...
So...
Washa washa washa, cuci rambutmu
Washa washa washa, wash your hair
Washa washa washa, gosok badanmu
Washa washa washa, scrub your body
Sish sish sish sish, sikat gigi
Sish sish sish sish, brush your teeth
Sekarang sudah wangi
Now it's already fragrant
Shapo shapo shapo, keramas rambutmu
Shapo shapo shapo, shampoo your hair
Washa washa washa, keramas badanmu
Washa washa washa, shampoo your body
Seragam yang lengkap, bersiap ke sekolah
Complete uniform, get ready for school
Sampai jumpa Mommy Pappy
See you later Mommy Pappy
Mimpi indah menjadi nyata
Beautiful dreams become reality
Membuka nakas satu per satu
Opening the nightstand one by one
Kelap kelip bintang di langit
Twinkling stars in the sky
Semua habis aku lakukan jika sudah mandi
I've done everything once I've bathed
Jika aku rajin mandi, aku bisa menjadi putri yang sesungguhnya.
If I'm diligent about bathing, I can become a true princess.
Washa washa washa, cuci rambutmu
Washa washa washa, wash your hair
Washa washa washa, gosok badanmu
Washa washa washa, scrub your body
Sish sish sish sish, sikat gigi
Sish sish sish sish, brush your teeth
Sekarang sudah wangi
Now it's already fragrant
Lari lari lari kawan ayo mandi
Run run run friends, let's take a bath
Jaga kebersihan bersama
Maintain cleanliness together
Cintai dirimu
Love yourself
Ayo mandi, ayo mandi
Let's take a bath, let's take a bath
Cintai dirimu ya!
Love yourself, okay!
Ah...
Gugu gaga!
Babu babu!
Gugu gaga, tada!
Hmm...
Gugu gaga!
Washa!
Gugu gaga! Gugu gaga!
Esh!
Gugu gaga!
Aga go, gi gu go, gu gu...
Gugu gaga! Gugu!
Hey, Kobo! I've been waiting for you here. Congrats on your third anniversary!
Gugu gaga!
Huh? Wait, why "Gugu Gaga"?
Babu babu! Babu babu!
Gugu!
Okay, okay, I get it. You've been cursed. Well, I'm actually familiar with curses, okay? So what's up?
Babu babu! Babu babu! Asho!
Okay okay, I see. You're in training
so that you can be an idol so that you can talk normally.
Gugu gaga...
Naruhodo, okay. So you can still dance
I see, okay. So you can still dance
and like sing just fine, but no talking?
Ah... gugu...
Oh... okay. Well, maybe you need to perform with Dada?
Dada... ts-ts-dada...
Oh, okay, okay. Say... Dada.
Ts... na... tsu...
Okay, all right, all right. You know what?
Let's just... let's take it slow, okay?
Let's take it slow.
Ah... gugu gaga...
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ Lyrics, Music: 宮下浩司
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Lyrics, Music: Koji Miyashita
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ みんな食べるよ
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Everyone's gonna eat!
ツル・ツル・テカ・テカ 明日も 入るかな？
Slippery, shiny, will it fit tomorrow too?
ダバ・ダバ・デュ・ア ダバ・ダバ・デュ・ア
Daba daba du a, daba daba du a
大きくなったらお空に声が届くかな
When I grow up, I wonder if my voice will reach the sky
いつまででも一緒だよ
We'll be together forever
マル・マル・モリ・モリ！ みんな食べるよ
Maru Maru Mori Mori! Everyone's gonna eat!
ツル・ツル・テカ・テカ 明日も 入るかな？
Slippery, shiny, will it fit tomorrow too?
悲しくて 泣いていた ひとり歩く 帰り道
I was sad and crying, walking home alone
こんな時 ほんわかな みんなに会いたいな
At a time like this, I want to see everyone who makes me feel warm
マル・マル・モリ・モリ おまじないだよ
Maru Maru Mori Mori, it's a magic spell
ツル・ツル・テカ・テカ にっこり笑顔
Slippery, shiny, a beaming smile
いちにのさんしで ごましおさん
One, two, three, four, sesame salt!
たくさんだとおいしいね
It's delicious with a lot of it, isn't it?
マル・マル・モリ・モリ プカプカお風呂
Maru Maru Mori Mori, floating in the bath
ツル・ツル・ピカ・ピカ ゴシゴシブラシ
Slippery, sparkling, scrubbing with a brush
皆さん今晩は また明日
Good evening everyone, see you tomorrow!
朝ご飯は何でしょうね？
I wonder what's for breakfast?
ダバ・ダバ・デュ・ア ダバ・ダバ・デュ・ア
Daba daba du a, daba daba du a
大人になっても 虹色の夢を描こうね
Even when we grow up, let's draw rainbow-colored dreams
指切りして テレリンコ
Pinky swear, tererinko
お星様 綺麗だね 手を繋いで 願い事
The stars are beautiful, aren't they? Holding hands and making a wish
たとえ遠くにいても 心は一つだよ
Even if we're far apart, our hearts are one
マル・マル・モリ・モリ 幸せ元気
Maru Maru Mori Mori, happy and energetic
テク・テク・トコ・トコ 前に進むよ
Walking along, step by step, moving forward
いちにのさんしで ホームラン
One, two, three, four, home run!
愛がいっぱいランドセル
A backpack full of love
マル・マル・モリ・モリ 大きくなるよ
Maru Maru Mori Mori, I'm going to grow up
ドキ・ドキ・ワク・ワク ドアを開けるよ
Pounding heart, exciting, I'm opening the door
皆さんしっかり また明日
Everyone stay strong, see you tomorrow!
もっと素敵な日になる
It'll be an even more wonderful day
Dada! Anjing!
Oh yeah, you like anjing too? That's nice.
大好きだよ
I love you
マル・マル・モリ・モリ さあ歌いましょう
Maru Maru Mori Mori, now let's sing
ツル・ツル・テカ・テカ にっこり笑顔
Slippery, shiny, a beaming smile
いちにのさんしで ごましおさん
One, two, three, four, sesame salt!
たくさんだとおいしいね
It's delicious with a lot of it, isn't it?
マル・マル・モリ・モリ プカプカお風呂
Maru Maru Mori Mori, floating in the bath
ツル・ツル・ピカ・ピカ ゴシゴシブラシ
Slippery, sparkling, scrubbing with a brush
皆さん今晩は また明日
Good evening everyone, see you tomorrow!
朝ご飯は何でしょうね？
I wonder what's for breakfast?
いつもいつもありがとう
Always, thank you so much
ダバ・ダバ・デュ・ア ダバ・ダバ・デュ・ビ・ドゥ・バ
Daba daba du a, daba daba du bi du ba
よくできました Good job!
Well done! Good job!
Uh, so, so how was that? How is it now?
Gugu gaga... gugu gaga...
Ah, mou... still baby, huh? This is weird.
Ah, geez... still baby, huh? This is weird.
The curse should be lifted
because you did really, really...
Well, you're very like...
アイドルみたい、可愛い、可愛い。本当。
You're like an idol, you're so cute. Truly.
Right?
Calliope needs a little bit of work though.
Wait, what is wrong? I need to talk to that curse.
I will visit whoever did this to you now,
and I will boko-boko their ass.
and I will beat their ass.
So keep yapping while I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get out of here.
My work here is done. がんばれ、がんばれ！ Bye-bye!
My work here is done. Good luck, good luck! Bye-bye!
ウグガガ...
Gugu gaga...
ググガガ ググガガ...
Gugu gaga, gugu gaga...
ブブブ
Bububu
ブブブババ ブバブバブ
Bububaba bubabubabu
ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ
Gyu Gyu Gyu Gyu
ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ！
Gyu Gyu Gyu Gyu Gyu!
ステキな日曜日～Gyu Gyu グッデイ！～
Lyrics：浅利進吾、渡辺なつみ Music：浅利進吾
Lovely Sunday ~Gyu Gyu Good Day!~
Lyrics: Shingo Asari, Natsumi Watanabe Music: Shingo Asari
燦々と お日様 笑顔の日曜日
The sun is shining on this smiling Sunday
（ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ！）
(Gyu Gyu Gyu!)
お出掛けしましょう はぐれないように
Let's go out together, so we don't get separated
（ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ！）
(Gyu Gyu Gyu!)
しっかり 仲良く 手を繋いで
Let's hold hands tightly and get along
手を繋いで
Holding hands
ずっと ずっと 一緒にいようね
Let's stay together forever and ever
明日も 明後日も 大人になっても
Tomorrow, the day after, even when we grow up
大好きだよ
I love you so much
夢いっぱい ギュッギュッギュッ
Full of dreams, Gyu Gyu Gyu
みんなでおにぎり モグモグハッピー
Eating rice balls together, munch munch happy
幸せをギュッギュッギュッ
Squeeze happiness, Gyu Gyu Gyu
愛情たっぷりでお腹いっぱい
Full of love, my tummy is full
ニコニコほらね 心が躍る
Look at that smile, my heart is dancing
ステキな日曜日
What a lovely Sunday
ギュッギュッギュッ！
Gyu Gyu Gyu!
ザアザアと 雨が降ってる日曜日
The rain is pouring down on this Sunday
（ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ！）
(Gyu Gyu Gyu!)
でも平気だよ 傘さして
But I'm okay with an umbrella
（ギュッ ギュッ ギュッ！）
(Gyu Gyu Gyu!)
長靴履いて 出掛けよう
Let's put on our boots and go out
おしゃれをして
Dressing up nicely
ちょっと ちょっと 寂しい時でも
Even when I feel a little bit lonely
水たまり跳んで 君と遊んだら
If I jump in puddles and play with you
忘れちゃうよ
I'll forget all about it
ハートいっぱい ギュッギュッギュッ
Full of hearts, Gyu Gyu Gyu
明日もまた会おう 約束ハッピー
Let's meet again tomorrow, happy promise
思い出をギュッギュッギュッ
Squeeze memories, Gyu Gyu Gyu
心のポケットに ウキウキしまおう
Let's store the excitement in our heart's pocket
雨が止んだら 虹が見えたよ
When the rain stops, I see a rainbow
ステキな日曜日
What a lovely Sunday
ギュッギュッギュッ！
Gyu Gyu Gyu!
おんなじ気持ち 一つ増えたら
When one more shared feeling is added
笑顔も一つ増えるから
One more smile will surely follow
捕まえようよ たくさん集めよう
Let's catch them and gather many
たくさん集めよう
Let's gather many
宝物！
Treasures!
ね！
Right!
夢いっぱい ギュッギュッギュッ
Full of dreams, Gyu Gyu Gyu
みんなでおにぎり モグモグハッピー
Eating rice balls together, munch munch happy
幸せをギュッギュッギュッ
Squeeze happiness, Gyu Gyu Gyu
愛情たっぷりでお腹いっぱい
Full of love, my tummy is full
ニコニコほらね 心が躍る
Look at that smile, my heart is dancing
ステキな日曜日
What a lovely Sunday
グッデイ！
Good day!
ギュッ！ギュッ！ ギュッギュッギュッ！
Gyu! Gyu! Gyu Gyu Gyu!
ギュッギュッギュッ
Gyu Gyu Gyu
弾む心とピュアなテンション
A bouncing heart and pure energy
さあコネクトしよう
Now, let's connect
I'm me, no more hiding now
Hey hey!
Changing, so I'm trying now
あれ今こう思っていて
Wait, I'm thinking this now
あ そうじゃなくて
Ah, no, that's not it
えと あの、言わないほうがいいなって
Um, well, I thought it's better not to say it
だけど どうするんだっけ
But wait, what should I do?
沈黙がみちびきくる 鳴り止むオリオン
Silence leads the way, the fading Orion
コントロールZ 効かないし
Control-Z doesn't work
ブツブツカスタマイズ 足りない何か
Muttering about customization, something's missing
いっそ溶かせたらいいのにな
I wish I could just melt it away
不完全不完全で
Being imperfect, being imperfect
正解はなんだって
Whatever the right answer is
不完全不完全で
Being imperfect, being imperfect
答えは僕だって
The answer is me
名称なんてないよねまずは
There's no name for it yet, but first
始めてみようかな
I'll try starting it
違う形 違うカタチ
Different shapes, different forms
なのにどうして同じ気持ち
Yet why do we feel the same?
繋ぎ合ってる時間
The time we spend connected
解け合うぬくもりありがとう
Thank you for the warmth we share
思い切り伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you with all my heart
カラフル笑顔 届いていいな
I hope my colorful smile reaches you
繋ぎ合ってるみんなと
With everyone I'm connected to
ここが私の好きな場所
This is my favorite place
弾む心とピュアなテンション
A bouncing heart and pure energy
今コネクトしよう
Let's connect now
I'm me, no more hiding now
Hey hey!
Changing, so I'm trying now
一生懸命頑張ってみたって変われないって
Saying I can't change no matter how hard I try
諦めトライしてみるって前段を無視して
Ignoring the fact I'm trying after giving up
平然な顔して デタラメなままで
With a calm face, staying nonsensical
思ったようにいかなくて
Things didn't go as planned
ポッキリ折れてた
I was completely broken
心もう一度躍らせていきたいな
I want to make my heart dance once more
不完全不完全で
Being imperfect, being imperfect
今を信じたいんだ
I want to believe in now
不完全不完全で
Being imperfect, being imperfect
僕は僕なんだ
I am who I am
正解と届かなくても一歩
Even if I don't reach the answer, one step
踏み出してみようかな
I'll try taking it
違う色と 違う夢で
With different colors and different dreams
進む未来糸解いて素敵
Unraveling the threads of the future is lovely
見えない糸感じてる
I'm feeling an invisible thread
温かい優しさありがとう
Thank you for your warm kindness
思い切り歌いたいんだ
I want to sing with all my heart
ハッピー振れ笑顔 届けていいな
I hope I can deliver happy smiles
出会ってくれたオリジナル
The original version of us that met
みんなと大切な場所
A precious place with everyone
一人でちゃんと自立してんだ
I'm properly independent on my own
みんなと一緒に第一歩を踏み出せることが
But being able to take the first step with you all
見つけていくから
I'll keep finding it
Ah--
違う形 違うカタチ
Different shapes, different forms
なのに本当だ同じ気持ち
Yet it's true, we feel the same
繋ぎ合ってる時間
The time we spend connected
解け合うぬくもりありがとう
Thank you for the warmth we share
思い切り伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you with all my heart
カラフル笑顔 届いていいな
I hope my colorful smile reaches you
繋ぎ合ってるみんなと
With everyone I'm connected to
ここが私の好きな場所
This is my favorite place
弾む心とピュアなテンション
A bouncing heart and pure energy
さあコネクトしよう
Now, let's connect
I'm me, no more hiding now
Hey hey!
Changing, so I'm trying now
あああああああああ！
AAAAAAAAAA!
あ、痛い、痛たたた...
Ah, ouch, ouch ouch ouch...
え？ 痛い。お！
Eh? It hurts. Oh!
I can speak! Woah!
Congrats, you have now gotten back your power!
おめでとう！これでまた力を取り戻したね！
Congrats! You've regained your power!
うわ！
Woah!
I've gotten back my power now!
And my, my dress... my, my huku is changed!
And my dress... my clothes are changed!
Why do I have mic?
Why do I have a mic?
Ah, but anyways thank you! Thank you Cielos!
Now I can talk normally! Yatta!
Now I can talk normally! Hooray!
You're such a good friend!
でもなんで？
But why?
Kenapa bajunya baru sekarang bikinnya?
Why did they only make the dress now?
What is this mic for? Huh?
I hope you have a great day, Happy 3rd Anniversary!
うん！今日もいい日になるといいね！3周年おめでとう！
Yeah! Hope today becomes a great day too! Happy 3rd Anniversary!
Okay, sekarang waktunya...
Okay, now it's time for...
Jowat Cilus!
Yeah! Jowat Cilus apaan tuh Kak Kobo?
Yeah! What is Jowat Cilus, Kobo?
Ya jadi Jowat Cilus ini maksudnya...
Well, Jowat Cilus means...
Merch kali ini adalah... Tadam!
The merch this time is... Tadam!
Boneka Cilus! Cilus Plushie dayo!
Cilus Plushie! It's a Cilus plushie!
Kawaii desho? Eh...
Cute, right? Uh...
安い！ハハハ！
It's cheap! Hahaha!
ええや、これ安い！絶対買ってね！
Yeah, this is cheap! You must buy it!
可愛いだからね！
Because it's cute!
Jadi kalian harus punya Cilus sebagai teman tidur kalian,
So you must have Cilus as your sleeping buddy,
teman mandi kalian, teman motoran kalian,
your bathing buddy, your motorcycling buddy,
bisa menjadi teman kalian yang nggak punya teman. Ahahaha.
it can even be a friend for those who don't have any. Ahahaha.
Anyways, tolong dibeli karena bisa habis.
Anyways, please buy it because it might sell out.
Iya, jadi jangan sampai kehabisan
Yeah, so don't let it run out
karena nggak apa-apa, harus aja beli pokoknya. Oke,
because it's fine, you just have to buy it. Okay,
kalau gitu, udah nih kita jual Cilus udah.
then, we're done selling Cilus.
Promo Cilus udah nih jual plushie Cilus. Oke
The Cilus promo is done, selling Cilus plushies. Okay
selanjutnya apa? Udah selesai kita.
what's next? We're finished.
Kita udah di penghujung acara, guys.
We're at the end of the show, guys.
Ya udah deh kalau gitu, see you next time ya.
Alright then, see you next time.
Kobo mau ngucapin makasih udah ngikutin
Kobo wants to say thanks for following
perjalanan Kobo, perjalanan Gugu Gaga ini.
Kobo's journey, this Gugu Gaga journey.
見てくれてありがとう。
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for accompanying me in this baby Gugu Gaga journey.
Ja, Otsu-Kobo! See you next time,
Well, Otsu-Kobo! See you next time,
bye bye!
Eh?
Halo? Eh?
Hello? Eh?
Ini di mana ya?
Where is this?
Arsy? Arsy Widianto?
Iya, halo. Kita udah kenal?
Yeah, hello. Have we met?
Hah? Kobo, pawang hujan 8 tahun,
Huh? Kobo, rain shaman for 8 years,
sudah punya pengalaman 3 tahun.
with 3 years of experience.
Ini pengalaman ke-3 tahun, penggemar ringan Arsy Widianto.
This is the 3rd year experience, casual fan of Arsy Widianto.
Selamat, Happy 3rd Anniversary ya, Kobo.
Congratulations, Happy 3rd Anniversary, Kobo.
Aaah! Thank you so much! Tapi BTW
Aaah! Thank you so much! But BTW
bukannya kak Arsy sibuk ya orangnya,
aren't you a busy person, Arsy?
kok bisa tiba-tiba di sini?
how come you're suddenly here?
Nggak tahu. Tadi aja tiba-tiba kayak aku
I don't know. Just now suddenly it was like I
ditarik dibawa terbang sama awan, gitu aja.
was pulled and flown away by a cloud, just like that.
Hah? Sama awan?
Huh? By a cloud?
Iya.
Yes.
BTW, aku tuh sebenarnya udah kenal kamu, Bo.
BTW, I actually already know you, Bo.
Hah?
Huh?
Arsy Widianto-kun?
Aku cuma pura-pura lupa aja.
I was just pretending to forget.
Jangan-jangan kamu beneran lupa ya, Bo?
Don't tell me you really forgot, Bo?
Hah? Aku... banyak yang sudah terjadi hari ini.
Huh? I... a lot has happened today.
Kepala aku sedikit sakit.
My head hurts a bit.
It's okay, Kobo. Nggak apa-apa.
It's okay, Kobo. It's fine.
Tapi kenapa ya perasaan ini familiar?
But why does this feeling feel familiar?
Seakan kita sudah saling kenal
As if we've known each other
satu sama lain sebelumnya.
before.
Seberat itu trauma kamu, Bo.
Your trauma is that heavy, Bo.
Maaf Arsy.
Sorry Arsy.
Sebenarnya aku ingin dekatmu
The truth is I want to be close to you
Namun kusadari ku tak bisa
But I realize that I can't
Tak boleh ku di sini
I shouldn't be here
Bahaya ku makin cinta
It's dangerous, I'm falling more in love
Ku tak ingin jauh
I don't want to be far away
Tak ingin berpisah
I don't want to part
Mengapa semua selalu indah
Why is everything always beautiful
Saat denganmu
When I'm with you
Sayang untuk diakhiri
It's a shame to end it
Andai engkau bisa mengerti
If only you could understand
Betapa beratnya aku
How hard it is for me
Harus aku tetap tersenyum
I have to keep smiling
Padahal hatiku terluka
Even though my heart is hurting
Adakah arti cinta ini
Is there any meaning to this love
Bila ku tak jadi denganmu
If I don't end up with you
...memang ku harus pergi. Yakinlah...
...that I must go. Believe that...
...hatiku kamu.
...my heart is yours.
Bukankah semesta yang pertemukan kita?
Didn't the universe bring us together?
Harus kau sampaikan...
You must tell...
...pada bintang.
...the stars.
Mengapa bukan kamu yang memiliki aku?
Why it's not you who has me?
Andai engkau bisa mengerti...
If only you could understand...
Betapa beratnya aku...
How hard it is for me...
Harus aku tetap tersenyum...
That I must keep smiling...
Padahal hatiku terluka.
Even though my heart is wounded.
Ada tak hati cinta ini...
Is there any love in this heart...
...bila ku tak jadi denganmu?
...if I don't end up with you?
Jika memang ku harus pergi...
If I indeed must go...
Yakinlah hatiku kamu.
Believe that my heart is yours.
Mengapa cinta pertemukan...
Why did love bring us together...
...bila akhirnya dipisahkan?
...if in the end we are separated?
Dan mengapa ku jatuh cinta...
And why did I fall in love...
Pada cinta yang tak jatuh padaku?
With a love that didn't fall for me?
Harus aku tetap tersenyum...
I must keep smiling...
...padahal hatiku terluka.
...even though my heart is wounded.
Ada tak hati cinta ini...
Is there any love in this heart...
...bila ku tak jadi denganmu?
...if I don't end up with you?
Jika memang ku harus pergi...
If I indeed must go...
Yakinlah hatiku kamu.
Believe that my heart is yours.
Kamu...
You...
Harus aku tetap tersenyum...
I must keep smiling...
...padahal hatiku terluka.
...even though my heart is wounded.
Ada tak hati cinta ini...
Is there any love in this heart...
...bila ku tak jadi denganmu?
...if I don't end up with you?
Jika memang ku harus pergi...
If I indeed must go...
Yakinlah hatiku kamu.
Believe that my heart is yours.
Yakinlah cinta...
Believe that this love...
...untukmu.
...is for you.
Eh, gimana Mas? Cocok nggak kita jadi pemeran film?
Hey, what do you think? Do we fit as movie actors?
Bisa, bisa nih kayaknya nih. Cocok nih.
We can, it seems so. It fits.
Ini super mega bintang nih kayaknya...
She'd be a super mega star...
...kalau main film nih kayaknya nih.
...if she were in a movie.
Ayo, kapan nih collab next collab kita?
Come on, when's our next collab?
Ayo dong, ayo dong.
Let's do it, let's do it.
Ayo dong, ya nggak sih?
Come on, don't you think?
Gas!
Let's go!
Atau yang satunya juga, eh...
Or that other thing too, eh...
Eh apa itu yang satunya? Spoiler ini guys!
Eh what's that other thing? Spoiler, guys!
Eh enggak enggak enggak.
Eh no no no.
Eh gimana gimana? Senang nggak?
So? Are you happy?
Terima kasih loh udah mau diundang.
Thank you for accepting the invitation.
Aku yang harus berterima kasih.
I should be the one thanking you.
Aku happy banget.
I'm very happy.
Ini salah satu pengalaman yang berharga banget,
This is one of the most valuable experiences,
...terindah banget buat aku.
...most beautiful for me.
Especially ada kamu di sini menemani aku.
Especially with you here accompanying me.
Ya aku sih yang nemenin kamu sebenarnya.
Well, I'm the one accompanying you, actually.
Aku senang banget.
I'm very happy.
Saling menemani.
Accompanying each other.
Ini pengalaman yang best banget.
This is the best experience.
Jadi terima kasih banyak Kobo, makasih banyak.
So thank you very much Kobo, thank you so much.
Iya, makasih kembali.
You're welcome. Thank you too.
Tapi sayangnya cuma bentar.
Unfortunately it's only for a short while.
Aku sebenarnya masih pengen lebih lama sih sama kamu.
I actually still want to spend more time with you.
Nih, ini emang Ardhito Pramono emang sepinter ini ya...
See, is Ardhito Pramono always this good with words...
...kalau ngomong ya? Kalau berkata-kata?
...when he speaks?
Emang itu pinter? Aku mah...
Is that being smart? I'm just...
...ini dari hati aja apa adanya.
...speaking from the heart, as it is.
Eh tapi pantesan lagu-lagunya tuh...
But no wonder your songs are...
Aku tuh nggak bisa tau. Aku tuh pernah nulis lagu...
I can't do it, you know. I once tried writing a song...
...romantis gitu, cuma tuh nggak bisa.
...romantic like that, but I couldn't.
Aku tuh harus ngebayanginnya tuh fake gitu loh.
I had to imagine it being fake.
Membayangkan keadaan yang fake gitu.
Imagining a fake situation.
Bisa, semua orang tuh bisa.
You can, everyone can.
Bicara cinta semua orang pasti memiliki...
When it comes to love, everyone surely has...
...jalan cintanya sendiri. Kamu juga pasti punya.
...their own path. You definitely have one too.
Dengan apapun, dengan hal-hal indah.
Through anything, through beautiful things.
Jadi kamu akan menemukan sendiri jalannya.
So you'll find your own way eventually.
...nanti.
...someday.
Makasih advice-nya.
Thanks for the advice.
Banyak sekali pelajaran yang bisa diambil dari stream ini.
There are so many lessons to be learned from this stream.
Terima kasih ya, Bang Arsy Widianto-kun.
Thank you, Arsy Widianto-kun.
Aku juga berterima kasih banget.
I'm also very grateful.
Aku happy banget.
I'm so happy.
Jadi aku lanjut ya.
So I'll continue now.
Ini enggak ilfeel kan ya diundang sama anime?
You're not turned off being invited by an anime, are you?
Enggak lah.
Of course not.
Kalau buat kamu mah apa sih yang enggak.
Anything for you.
Udahlah, tenang aja.
Come on, don't worry about it.
Ayo kita... kita kayak...
Let's... let's like...
Coba di pat-pat bisa enggak? Kita kecil ya.
Can you try patting me? We're small, aren't we?
Kok kayaknya pendek banget sih aku?
Why do I seem so short?
Kayaknya aku enggak sependek ini deh harusnya.
I don't think I'm supposed to be this short.
Parah banget.
This is bad.
Ayo kita fist bump.
Let's do a fist bump.
Oke, fist bump.
Okay, fist bump.
High five!
Ya udah deh.
Alright then.
Oke baiklah, terima kasih banyak sekali lagi.
Okay then, thank you so much once again.
Kobo makasih banget.
Kobo, thank you so much.
Jangan ke mana-mana.
Don't go anywhere.
Ikut ini enggak? Makan-makan dulu kita.
Want to join us? Let's go eat first.
Iya mau ke mana? Mau makan apa?
Yes, where to? What do you want to eat?
Ayo mau makan apa?
Come on, what do you want to eat?
Buseti, cowok softspoken gini buset guys.
Damn, such a soft-spoken guy, damn guys.
Ya udah nanti di belakang ya.
Alright, later behind the scenes.
Ya udah, oke.
Alright, okay.
Aku lanjut ya.
I'll continue now.
Kamu jangan capek-capek juga ya.
Don't get too tired either.
Arigato, bye bye.
Thank you, bye bye.
Owari mashita ka na?
Is it finally over?
Netai...
I want to sleep...
Yasumitai...
I want to rest...
Gimana surprise-nya? Kalian suka enggak?
How was the surprise? Did you guys like it?
Kalian suka surprise-nya enggak?
Did you guys like the surprise?
Eh, Cirus!
Oh, Cirus!
Cirus, ini dia yang akan kita obrol nanti guys.
Cirus, this is what we'll talk about later, guys.
Kawaii... kamu nanti bakal dijual banyak ya Cirus.
So cute... you'll be sold a lot later, Cirus.
You will be sold by many many customers.
So please be a good Cirus.
Kalau gitu kita beneran closing-nya.
With that, it's our real closing.
Semoga kalian senang sama...
I hope you guys are happy with...
...surprise itu, performance tadi.
...that surprise, the performance earlier.
Hai, ja... Bu-kobo-kobo Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Alright, then... Bu-kobo-kobo Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day.
Bye bye semuanya!
Bye bye everyone!
Yokoso, bye bye!
Capek.
I'm tired.
So tired.
Mou owari da.
It's finally over.
I'm friend... I'm friend with the curse.
I'm sorry, I don't know English but I write it.
I'm fr... wait a minute.
Dari pagi kayak gini.
It's been like this since morning.
Berapa hari kayak gini?
How many days has it been like this?
Tiga hari berturut-turut.
Three days in a row.
And you look too shocked on the chair.
Say Dada!
Enggak bisa.
I can't.
Tadi enakan karaage.
The karaage was good earlier.
Enggak tahu kamu mengambil yang mana.
I don't know which one you took.
Karaage, terus omurice.
The karaage, then the omurice.
I just fumbled... gaga gaga.
Gi sana tidur.
Go to sleep.
Bye.
Kobo Baby Party! #Kobo3rdAnniversary