(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ #BreakingDimensions
Official Hashtag / #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 開催までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRyu
Starting around JANUARY 2025 at ROUND1 across the US!
PUPPET PLUSHIES
LYING DOWN PLUSHIES
hololive plushies up for grabs in ROUND1 CRANE GAMES!
FuRyu
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRyu
Starting around JANUARY 2025 at ROUND1 across the US!
hololive plushies up for grabs in ROUND1 CRANE GAMES!
Further updates will be posted on ROUND1 website,
be sure to check regularly!
hololive campaign at ROUND1 starting October 2024!
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
Official Hashtag #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive English 2nd Concert Made-to-order merch
T-shirt, Face Towel, Folding Fan
Mutual Items: Penlight
Penlight colors: 12 colors
Made-to-order merch
Original Keychain, Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand
Acrylic Panel, Laptop/Tablet Case
Breaking Dimensions / hololive English 2nd Concert
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ / #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 公演開始まで、いましばらくお待ちください
Official Hashtag / #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive English 2nd Concert / Made-to-order merch
T-shirt: ¥4,000 each / Face Towel: ¥2,500 / Folding Fan: ¥2,200
Mutual Items / Penlight: ¥4,000
Made-to-order merch
Original Keychain: ¥990 each / Random Button Badge: ¥550
Made-to-order merch / Acrylic Stand: ¥2,200 each
hololive English 2nd Concert / Acrylic Panel: ¥4,400 / Laptop/Tablet Case: ¥4,950
Breaking Dimensions / hololive English 2nd Concert
フワモコちゃんへ
デビューしてから追い続けてるよ！
To Fuwamoco,
I've been following you since your debut!
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRyu
Starting around JANUARY 2025
at ROUND 1 across the US!
PUPPET PLUSHIES
LYING DOWN PLUSHIES
hololive plushies up for grabs
in ROUND 1 CRANE GAMES!
フリュー
FuRyu
Further updates will be posted on ROUND 1 website,
be sure to check regularly!
hololive campaign at ROUND 1
starting October 2024!
ENigmatic Recollection Launch Party
August 30th 19:00 PDT
ENigmatic Recollection
ENigmatic Recollection Launch Party
August 30th 19:00 PDT
NOW AVAILABLE GLOBALLY FOR PRE-ORDER ON HYTE.COM
holoplus+ hololive production's Official App
The concert will be starting soon.
Official Hashtag #BreakingDimensions
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of
flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.
Made-to-order merch: T-shirt, Face Towel, Folding Fan
Mutual Items: Penlight (12 colors)
Original Keychain, Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand (15 designs)
Acrylic Panel, Laptop/Tablet Case
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRyu
Starting around JANUARY 2025
at ROUND 1 across the US!
hololive plushies up for grabs in
ROUND 1 CRANE GAMES!
FuRyu
Further updates will be posted on ROUND 1 website,
be sure to check regularly!
hololive campaign at ROUND 1
starting October 2024!
NOW AVAILABLE GLOBALLY FOR
PRE-ORDER ON HYTE.COM
ohmonah Breaking Dimensions Collection
Order Online
holoplus+
hololive production's Official App
holoplus+ hololive production's Official App
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a while.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
Made-to-order merch: T-shirt, Face Towel, Folding Fan.
Mutual Items: hololive STAGE World Tour '24 Penlight.
Made-to-order merch: Original Keychain, Random Button Badge.
Made-to-order merch: Acrylic Stand.
Made-to-order merch: Acrylic Panel, Laptop/Tablet Case.
[Fan Message Montage]
Breaking Dimensions -hololive English 2nd Concert-
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ #BreakingDimensions
Official Hashtag #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 公演まで今しばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a while.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive English 2nd Concert Made-to-order merch
T-shirt, Face Towel, Folding Fan
hololive STAGE World Tour '24 x hololive English 2nd Concert Mutual Items
Penlight (12 color variants)
Original Keychain, Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand
Acrylic Panel, Laptop/Tablet Case
Breaking Dimensions -hololive English 2nd Concert-
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive English 2nd Concert
Made-to-order merch
Sales period: 10 PM August 10th -
5 AM September 17th (EDT)
Mutual Items
On sale now!
BREAKING NEWS !!
from FuRYU
Starting around JANUARY 2025
at ROUND 1 across the US!
PUPPET PLUSHIES
LYING DOWN PLUSHIES
hololive plushies up for grabs in
ROUND 1 CRANE GAMES!
フリュー
FuRYU
Further updates will be posted on ROUND 1 website,
be sure to check regularly!
hololive campaign at ROUND 1
starting October 2024!
ENigmatic Recollection Launch Party
hololive English Official YouTube Channel
August 30th 19:00 PDT
ENigmatic Recollection
ENigmatic Recollection Launch Party
August 30th 19:00 PDT
hololive x HYTE Breaking Dimensions merchandise now available
ohmonah BREAKING DIMENSIONS Made-to-order merch
holoplus+ hololive production's Official App
#BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait for a moment.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive English 2nd Concert Made-to-order merch
Breaking Dimensions Fan Messages
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRYU
Starting around JANUARY 2025 at ROUND1 across the US!
PUPPET PLUSHIES
LYING DOWN PLUSHIES
hololive plushies up for grabs in ROUND1 CRANE GAMES!
FuRYU
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRYU
hololive campaign at ROUND1 starting October 2024!
NOW AVAILABLE GLOBALLY FOR PRE-ORDER ON HYTE.COM
Order merch online from OMOCAT.
All about your Oshi, One app: holoplus+
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
Made-to-order merch: T-shirt, Face Towel, Folding Fan
hololive STAGE World Tour '24 Mutual Items: Penlight
Made-to-order merch: Original Keychain, Random Button Badge
Made-to-order merch: Acrylic Stand
Made-to-order merch: Acrylic Panel, Laptop/Tablet Case
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ #BreakingDimensions
Official Hashtag #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
Made-to-order merch: T-shirt / Face Towel / Folding Fan
Mutual Items: Penlight
Made-to-order merch: Original Keychain / Random Button Badge
Made-to-order merch: Acrylic Stand
Made-to-order merch: Acrylic Panel / Laptop/Tablet Case
Breaking Dimensions
hololive English 2nd Concert
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
Made-to-order merch
T-shirt / Face Towel / Folding Fan
On sale now! Mutual Items:
Penlight (12 colors)
Made-to-order merch
Original Keychain / Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand (Design Variants: 15 designs) ¥2,200 each
Acrylic Panel ¥4,400 / Laptop/Tablet Case ¥4,950
BREAKING NEWS !! from FuRYu
Starting around JANUARY 2025 at ROUND1 across the US!
FuRYu
hololive campaign at ROUND1 starting October 2024!
ENigmatic Recollection Launch Party / August 30th 19:00 PDT
ENigmatic Recollection
NOW AVAILABLE GLOBALLY FOR PRE-ORDER ON HYTE.COM
ommonah BREAKING DIMENSIONS
holoplus hololive production's Official App
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a while for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.
T-shirt ¥4,000 / Face Towel ¥2,500 / Folding Fan ¥2,200
Mutual Items Penlight ¥4,000
Original Keychain ¥990 each / Random Button Badge ¥500 each
Made-to-order merch: Original Keychain & Random Button Badge
Made-to-order merch: Acrylic Stand
Made-to-order merch: Acrylic Panel & Laptop/Tablet Case
Breaking Dimensions: Fan Message Compilation
hololive English 2nd Concert: Breaking Dimensions
Breaking Dimensions
hololive English 2nd Concert
Fan support board
BREAKING NEWS !!
from FuRyu
Starting around JANUARY 2025
at ROUND1 across the US!
PUPPET PLUSHIES
LYING DOWN PLUSHIES
hololive plushies up for grabs
in ROUND1 CRANE GAMES!
FuRyu
Further updates will be posted on ROUND1 website,
be sure to check regularly!
hololive campaign at ROUND1
starting October 2024!
NOW AVAILABLE GLOBALLY FOR
PRE-ORDER ON HYTE.COM
holoplus+
hololive production's Official App
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ
#BreakingDimensions
Official Hashtag
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors
hololive English 2nd Concert
Made-to-order merch
Fan support board
I am supporting Breaking Dimensions!
GO KIARA!
BAU BAU, Fuwamoco! Rock the stage!
Official Hashtag / 公式ハッシュタグ #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
Official Hashtag #BreakingDimensions
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
Made-to-order merch
hololive English 2nd Concert T-shirt / Face Towel / Folding Fan
hololive STAGE World Tour '24 -Soar-
hololive English 2nd Concert Penlight
Original Keychain / Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand
Acrylic Panel / Laptop/Tablet Case
I am supporting Breaking Dimensions!
Ahahaha!
Roses are red,
the fire of my heart is blue.
Also known as the Scarlet Queen,
the harbinger of order, leader of Justice.
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see ya, to see you lovely!
Gigi Murin! It's Gigi Murin!
But today, you can call me "The Beaster"!
And I'm Cecilia Immergreen, the ancient automaton.
Spin to win!
Ciao-at-tsu-ni-ni! This is Raora Panthera!
And we are...
Justice!
Just-ice! Just like that!
Just-ice! Get-get that!
Whoo-hoo! Oh yeah!
We're finally here!
We're so excited to witness
hololive English history with all of you!
Are you ready to join a new chapter in hololive English history?
The concert starts now!
Get ready and remember to enjoy until the very last moment!
Yippie! Here we go!
Is everyone ready?
Three, two, one!
Breaking Dimensions!
Breaking Dimensions
Mori Calliope
Takanashi Kiara
Ninomae Ina'nis
Gawr Gura
Watson Amelia
MYTH
IRyS
Ceres Fauna
Ouro Kronii
Nanashi Mumei
Hakos Baelz
PROMISE
Shiori Novella
Koseki Bijou
Nerissa Ravencroft
Fuwawa Abyssgard
Mococo Abyssgard
ADVENT
hololive English 2nd Concert - Breaking Dimensions -
Breaking Dimensions
Breaking Dimensions - hololive English 2nd Concert -
Sing out boldly again
Continuing this odyssey
We'll start this new refrain
Brimming with memories
And when the clouded skies become bright
Let's reunite!
What's up, New York!
Welcome to Breaking Dimensions Day 1!
First off, isn't it...
Showtime baby, I would say
Today's broadcast holds no delay
Pulling out the stops isn't really enough
So we're buffering endlessly... why?!
Take it easy! What have we learned?
Start a fire in their hearts when the PC burns up
Optimistic, focus on the quick fit
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks
Still going stronger than ever, never saying die
And I'm aware it's ironic but where's the freaking lie?
Dreamers to dreamers
Together we survive
Must seem to you people
Like a mid-day crisis
Searching new dimensions
We can bring another mystery to light
Planning our ascension
Dancing in flight
We ignite!
Join us while we're celebrating
In the myth that we're creating
There's another story waiting
Through this world and beyond
A distant dreams of prophecy
Our strong and moving bond
Guiding us endlessly
Will bring us moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on
And though these winds may scatter us
We'll keep this promise
When the moment's finally right
We'll always find a way to reunite!
Hello, New York!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'm diving in again now
It's time to sink or swim
I'll pledge to try the deeper end
But could you hold my fin?
Vibing with every end
Let's kick back and ponder, ponder
Tacos primarily
Then let's get cozy and have fun
Nobody escapes death
And I know that it's morbid
Years come and go, I still pretend
That God is killing things sorted
Listen I wanna look cool
But I keep on tripping and falling
Guess I'll stay playing the fool
To hold up the combat calling you back
Countless moments
Led us to this day
Triumph and sorrow, hope for tomorrow
We'll always find our way
Come what may
New York! Make some noise!
In every universe
We were always meant to meet
Our little boundless search
We will never know defeat
My wings will guide your hands
As the fateful days go by
We will catch the path
Through a never ending sky
Drawing us together
I can sense another wish is coming true
Each typhoon we'll...
Where strengths are true, me and you.
Sing out again, the cloudless skies give way to clear.
We'll start this new refrain, brimming with memories.
Another story starting right here.
We'll keep forging ahead
to make a saga all our own.
Whichever paths we tread, steadily journeying,
We know we're never really alone.
If we believe, wherever fate may find us,
Our love will find us,
every after-chapter we write
Will set us on the path to reunite.
Are you ready?!
A certain love I thought I'd never understand,
couldn't help it when you took my hand.
Bright side never before, you left me wanting more,
destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead.
Life flies by in zip-code reality,
Not sure of much but I know I'm ready,
soaring these streets make me complete,
Full throttle, come give me your all.
Engines on, keeping up with the beat of my heart,
just can't get enough.
Revving up make it fast, only us make it last
'til the sun's up.
A shot in the dark, take me away,
Fizzing up in my heart, it's okay.
Accelerate me until I'm there,
you and I reach the line, marking a view.
Keep it going until the bubbles fade,
I don't care if I don't see another day.
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got,
wheeling down, don't hesitate a minute more.
Time is not enough, fill it up, and don't look back again.
Carbonated love.
A settled love is better than I could have dreamed,
look at what we've done, we're too extreme.
Pour me your favorite drink, so much until we sink,
down to the bottom, don't want to miss a thing.
The track we're on might crash, oh what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring all avenues.
Race to the night, my guiding light, sparkling I'm right here with you.
Engines on, keeping up with the beat of my heart,
just can't get enough.
Revving up make it fast, only us make it last
'til the sun's up.
A shot in the dark, take me away,
Fizzing up in my heart, it's okay.
Accelerate me until I'm there,
you and I reach the line, marking a view.
Keep it going until the bubbles fade,
I don't care if I don't see another day.
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got,
wheeling down, don't hesitate a minute more.
Time is not enough, fill it up, and don't look back again.
Carbonated love.
A glass of empty company without you,
make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm a fool.
Another night let's speed up, let's make it new,
love me despite the way I'm crazy just for you.
A shot in the dark, take me away,
Fizzing up in my heart, it's okay.
Accelerate me until I'm there,
you and I reach the line, marking a view.
...feel alive and be what we will
Keep on going until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Bring us down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush we shouldn't, don't give up and never again
Our time is up, not enough, fill it up then begin
Carbonated love!
Thank you New York!
フワフワ
Fuwafuwa
モコモコ
Mocomoco
魔界の番犬シスターズ
Underworld guard dog sisters
この世界に爆弾バウドールです
In this world, we're the bomb BAU dolls
BAU! BAU!
Fuwafuwa!
Mocomoco!
Fuwafuwa! Mocomoco!
Fuwafuwa!
Mocomoco!
Mococo!
FUWA + MOCO = FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO
BAU BAU!
1, 2, 姉妹 君の隣
1, 2, sisters by your side
入念に身嗜み整えて
Carefully grooming our appearance
ドキドキ
Thump thump
右、左
Right, left
BAU BAU BAU!
悩んでいてもグズグズフューチャー
Even if you worry, it's a dragging future
まずは目の前の道 ステップして
First, take a step on the path before you
ハッピー
Happy
パッピー
Pappy
一緒に歩こうよ
Let's walk together
ドーナツの穴の向こう側には
On the other side of a donut's hole
きっと
Surely
夢が詰まってるから
Dreams are packed inside
フワフワ
Fuwafuwa
モコモコ
Mocomoco
魔界の番犬シスターズ
Underworld guard dog sisters
二匹が揃えばもう 大騒ぎ
If the two of us are together, it's already a big fuss
モアモア
Moamoa
ハローハロー
Hello hello
迷わずに ゴー・マイ・ウェイ
Without hesitating, go my way
君の絶対味方 バウドールです
We're the BAU dolls, your absolute allies
BAU! BAU!
フワフワ!
Fuwafuwa!
モコモコ!
Mocomoco!
Fuwafuwa! Mocomoco!
フワフワ!
Fuwafuwa!
モコモコ!
Mocomoco!
Mococo!
FUWA + MOCO = FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO
BAU BAU!
一人じゃないよ Always together
You're not alone, always together
明日もガッツリ君とチャットして
Tomorrow too, I'll chat with you a lot
ハッピー
Happy
パッピー
Pappy
一緒に歌おうよ
Let's sing together
ドーナツ リングに誓って
Swear on a donut ring
きっと
Surely
君が待っているから
Because you're waiting
Hey!
Ruffians!
Step you can hop!
Can I get a HELL YEAH!
Let's shout BAU!
BAU! BAU! BAU! BAU!
モコちゃん、この曲は可愛く歌おうねって言ったでしょ！
Moco-chan, didn't I tell you to sing this song cutely?
バウバウ。
Bau bau.
じゃあ、Bメロから！せーの！
Then, starting from the B-melody! Ready, go!
ドーナツ リングに誓って
Swear on a donut ring
ずっと
Always
笑顔を守るから
I'll protect your smile
フワフワ
Fuwafuwa
モコモコ
Mocomoco
魔界の番犬シスターズ
Underworld guard dog sisters
二匹が揃えばもう 大騒ぎ
If the two of us are together, it's already a big fuss
モアモア
Moamoa
ハローハロー
Hello hello
迷わずに ゴー・マイ・ウェイ
Without hesitating, go my way
君の絶対味方 バウドールです
We're the BAU dolls, your absolute allies
この世界に爆弾バウドールです
In this world, we're the bomb BAU dolls
BAU! BAU!
フワフワ
Fuwafuwa
モコモコ
Mocomoco
Fuwafuwa! Mocomoco!
フワフワ
Fuwafuwa
モコモコ
Mocomoco
Mococo!
FUWA + MOCO = FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO
BAU BAU!
Thank you!
Hello, everyone!
BAU BAU!
Welcome, everyone...
...to hololive English's second concert...
...Breaking Dimensions!
BAU BAU!
Thank you for all your BAU BAUs, everyone! Thank you!
All those BAU BAUs!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
You know, we've been worried that you wouldn't know...
...who we are because we're still new.
Yeah, but I don't think we have to worry, right, Mococo-chan?
No! Thank you! Thank you!
BAU BAU! Thank you!
But just in case, Mococo-chan, let's introduce ourselves.
Okay! Hmm...
I'm not a chihuahua...
...I'm Fuwawa!
BAU BAU! Thank you!
And me now! Oh, oh!
I'm not Fuwawa...
...I'm Mococo!
BAU BAU!
Together we're hololive English -Advent-'s twin demon guard dogs...
...we are FUWAMOCO! BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! Thank you!
Thank you for all your BAU BAUs!
BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
Wow! That song that was just performed...
...is our original song...
..."Born to Be"!
BAU BAU! Thank you so much! Did you have fun?
BAU BAU!
Mococo-chan, did you hear that?
Right, I know! BAU BAU!
Thank you! Thank you!
Well, today a big dream of ours came true.
Yeah! And that was being here together with you...
...at our first-ever 3D concert!
BAU BAU! You know, I...
...if it's okay...
...I'd like to be a bit selfish.
Selfish?
Yeah, is that okay? I have another dream.
Can we grant it all together?
Hmm? Mococo-chan, what kind of dream?
Well, I would like to hear you BAU BAU...
...your biggest BAU BAU you've ever BAU BAUed!
BAU BAU! Can you do that for us?
Okay! Okay, well...
...everyone over here first! Okay?
Over here! Okay!
Everybody over here!
On three, a big BAU BAU, okay?
Yeah!
Three, two, one, BAU BAU!
Thank you! Okay, and this way!
Okay, everybody over here now! Once more!
Okay!
Three, two, one, BAU BAU!
Thank you! Okay, and one more time!
Now, everybody all together, okay?
Three, two, one, BAU BAU!
Thank you! BAU BAU!
Wow! Thank you so much, everyone!
With that, another dream came true! Yeah!
BAU BAU! You know...
...today is all about Breaking Dimensions, yeah!
And to us, Breaking Dimensions...
...is all about breaking into you! Yeah!
Breaking into you! Yeah, that's right!
We want to be able to break into your heart, you know, like... roar!
Roar! I would like to break in!
Yeah! I'm breaking into your heart!
We're going to break in, we're going to protect that smile!
And you know, Breaking Dimensions...
...it also means being here all together...
...and getting pumped up to make a night you'll never forget!
Are you ready? BAU BAU!
Well, actually, I know it's a very exciting night...
...but there's... there's been a misunderstanding.
There's been a misunderstanding! I know!
It's Breaking Dimensions, but... everybody joining us on YouTube today...
...well, the end of the sneak peek is right here.
Yeah, but you can join us over at SPWN or Streaming Plus!
So please get your tickets! Okay?
Okay, get your streaming tickets, please! Thank you!
BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! Thank you!
Well, actually... if it's okay, I have one more thing...
Mococo-chan moe! I'm being so selfish.
Is that okay?
Yeah! Thank you!
Just today, okay? Just today.
So when...
...we say yellow, all together...
Bau Bau! Up to today's concert, hey!
Are you ready? We're gonna do that a lot tonight, okay?
Uh-huh!
Okay, here we all go then!
Breaking...
...Dimensions! Bau Bau!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.