(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Sing out boldly again, continuing this odyssey
We'll start this new refrain, brimming with memories
And when the clouded skies become bright, let's reunite!
Ready? Set?
It's showtime, baby!
I will save this broadcast on slide delay
Ramping up the stuff is really enough
Talk about the lore endlessly, why?
Take it easy, what did we learn?
Start a fire in the hearts of the PC burns
Always optimistic, focus on a quick pitch
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks
Still going stronger than ever and never and never say die
And I'm aware it's ironic, but where's the freaking lie?
Streamers to streamers to entertainers to senpai
Not losing to young people
Ignorant, it's a Myth, don't mind us
Gura! Ame! Kiara! Ina! Calli! Myth!
Spanning new dimensions,
we can bring another mystery to light
Planning our ascension,
dancing in flight, we ignite
Join us while we're celebrating in the Myth that we're creating
There's another story waiting through this world and beyond
Our distant dreams have brought us here
A strong and unyielding bond
Guiding us endlessly,
will bring us moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on;
and though these winds may scatter us
We'll keep this promise;
when the moment's finally right,
we'll always find a way to reunite!
I'm diving in again,
now it's time to sink or swim
Let's try the deeper end,
but could you hold my fin?
Vibing with everyone,
let's kick back and ponder puns
Taco party anytime,
let's get cozy and have fun!
...escape death
and know that it's morbid.
Years come and go,
I'll still pretend
that I've got this killed and sorted.
Listen, I wanna look cool,
but I keep on tripping and falling.
Guess I'll keep playing the fool
to hold up the commerce calling yatta-yatta.
Countless moments
led us to this day.
Triumph and sorrow, hope for tomorrow,
We'll always find our way.
Trouble may...
In every universe,
we were always meant to meet.
I'll lead a boundless search,
we will never know defeat!
My wings will guide your hands
as the fateful days go by,
We will carve a path
through a never-ending sky!
Drawing us together,
I can sense another wish is coming true.
Each typhoon we weather
strengthens our crew, me and you.
Sing out again,
the clouded skies give way to clear,
We'll start this new refrain,
brimming with memories,
another story starting right here.
We'll keep forging ahead
To make a saga all our own.
Whichever paths we tread, steadily journeying,
We know we're never really alone—
If we believe,
wherever fate may find us,
Our love will bind us.
Every epic chapter we write
will set us on the path
to reunite!
Journey Like a Thousand Years ~千年の旅~
A song in snow, enchanted by rhyme...
Painted in wishes, granted by time...
Our longest hopes connecting yet those...
Be like echoes of ages gone by.
Made a splash,
but found I'm not free,
A fish out of water
bound to the sea.
Then a reckless high tide brought you right by my side,
I bet this moment's a wave we can ride.
Connecting songs across the sky.
Take off and fly,
the longer we wait,
The stronger it makes us
as we fight every fate.
Strength to finally defeat
this journey of a thousand years
to meet.
Witness the fire of minds burning inside,
Resonating from the ashes,
every bruise and scratch makes us feel more alive.
We never give up, never give in
no matter what's ahead,
instead we'll crush all our worries aside.
If there's no world
for us to touch or to see,
We'll make it ourselves
and make memories.
There ain't a mystery
our brains cannot solve,
We just shine brighter
and tighter evolve.
Connecting songs across the world.
Take off and fly,
the longer we wait,
The stronger it makes us
as we fight every fate.
Strength to finally defeat
this journey of a thousand years
to meet.
At the end of this world, where's our fighting chance?
Nothing's changing, it's always the same story
stays with a different dance.
We've got a happy end
For me and my friends and those who've loved us up until now
I wanna see you smile
Find my way to you somehow
Take off and fly
The longer we wait
The stronger it makes us as we fight every fate
Strength to finally defeat
This journey a thousand years to meet
Let's try!
It can't be denied
The wish in my heart is you right here by my side
Strength is all that we'll need
I'll hope wait a thousand years to meet
To meet...
Done!
Yeah!
Good work everybody! Let's hype!
Yatta, yatta!
Yeah! We did it once again!
And once again, hi guys!
Hi guys!
Yeah, we're off to a flying start already but...
...to properly kick things off, welcome everybody
to hololive English -Myth- 4th Anniversary Live:
The Show Goes On!
Welcome everybody!
Yeah, yeah! Thanks for coming!
Yeah, well, well done. Let's start off with
a round of introductions.
So, who will be first?
Me! Me! Me!
Let's do it first! Come on!
You know the rules and so do I.
Oh, okay, so it'll be me.
Alright. Kikiriki! Hello everybody, I'm Takanashi
Kiara from hololive English -Myth-.
You'll hear that a lot today.
So, who's next?
A-do-mo-do-mo-do-mo! Same desu!
Gawr Gura desu! Chark-kun, oh no!
Chark shark, Gawr Gura desu!
Keep 'em coming, keep 'em coming!
Water? Oh me? Okay.
(Clears throat) Minna-san! Hi, I think you guys
maybe know who I am.
My name is Mori Calliope from
hololive English -Myth-.
I am a virtual singer, artist, creator,
I stream, I play games too.
Nice to meet you if we have already met,
if we haven't, if we have... hi.
Someone take the mic away from me, I'm so bad
at these, I'm always so bad, someone else do it.
Who's next? Ame? Ame, perhaps?
Okay! I'm Amelia Watson, number one detective
from hololive English!
Yeah, yeah! And last but not least... Wah!
Wah! Wah! Wah!
Wah! Good morning, afternoon, evening everyone!
I'm Ninomae Ina'nis from... oh wait.
I'm Ninomae Ina'nis and together we are...
hololive English -Myth-!
We did it! Told you you'll hear it a lot.
So with our introductions out of the way,
feast your eyes on the venue we have today!
Check it out! Whoa! New stage!
Look, a brand new stage made for our
4th anniversary!
Look at our songs! Our songs are everywhere!
Our originals!
Finally! It was... pretty high!
Look, some Valentine's stuff! Cute!
Yeah, I love it. We're stars!
That's really, really nice. This stage...
So... um, I'm sure it's obvious, right everybody?
We've got a full divine exquisite...
for 'The Show Goes On'.
Can you guess what the theme is?
Anyone? Anyone?
Hai, sensei! Tropical island vacation!
No, no, no.
Okay, I got it. Underwater sea adventure!
Are you for real?
What? You asked me! It's definitely that one.
Okay, no. I don't think they'll have
good answers either, so...
Those two boneheads. Okay, drumroll though.
Come on! Brrrr...
It's Broadway!
I knew that.
Yeah. And it's not just, you know, a Broadway,
it's also a red carpet!
Do you like to do a catwalk? Ina? Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Let's go ladies, let's go!
Let's go! Wow! Model walk! Fashion, baby!
Nice, that's what I really wanted to do, thanks.
Alright.
That was pretty cool too.
So, along with the stunning backdrop, you guys,
I hope you will enjoy our grand performance.
But it's not just any live concert...
We've got a fun surprise waiting for them,
don't we ladies?
Oh yeah!
Surprise!
Hmm.
Wait, Ina...
Ame, Ame, Ame!
We have a surprise?
Yeah. Wait, did you forget already, Ina?
Didn't hear it?
About the surprise?
I mean, it's not a surprise if we don't-- if we know about it.
Play along, play along!
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah!
We have a surprise, guys! Yay!
Yay!
Oh, we know about it, of course.
Well, if you keep on watching until the end, you will indeed find out.
So, in the meantime, everybody, I ask you to use the hashtag...
...that is at the top right corner of your screen...
...to let us know what you think about our cute performance tonight!
And... where should they post the screenshots?
My fridge!
Ah... Your fridge?
Post them on X...
...formerly known as Twitter.
Yeah! Yeah!
Not-- not the Fridge-gator.
Hey! Spelling bee ladies.
Oh god.
They know.
(Ahem)
Everybody, hololive English -Myth-...
...now presents our 4th anniversary live...
...The Show Goes On in...
SHOWTIME!
(Cheering)
3, 2, 1, come on!
Full Color
Lyrics: WUNDER RIKU
Music, Arrangement: Snail's House
Hey! Alright!
Come on Dead Beats!
And Chumbuds!
All together now, come on!
Something that lasts, buried long ago
But soon I'll forget, in the gray boring road
But I thought I might drown, then I see a butterfly
Headphones on I hear that song and open up my eyes
And I know...
世界はまだ
The world is still...
なくなってないから
...not gone yet
今もずっと
Even now, always
Deep breath and fly away we go, each step we take a common show
When hope is lost I'll let you know, se-no!
Ev'ry melody just needs a place to start
And ev'ry dream needs a refrain
Each neon light illuminates your heart
So let the rhythm guide your way
And dance away with me
You'll see
夢と現実は同じ
Dreams and reality are the same
Something I found, sparkle of life
Rainbow of sound, it lives deep inside
My heart wants to beat for so long
Knocks loud and now I know it, now I'm right where I belong
十色の世界を
Casting off the...
脱ぎ去り
...ten-color world
Deep breath and fly and then just be, reality is what you believe
Listen with me and then you'll see
Ev'ry melody just needs a place to start
And ev'ry dream needs a refrain
Each neon light illuminates your heart
So let the rhythm guide your way
And dance away with me
You'll see
夢と現実は同じ
Dreams and reality are the same
That's right, I'm not just a phoenix...
...I'm a TENTOU!
Look at this!
Woo!
When we first met
I wonder what you think of me
Do you imagine set
That was a perfect merrier day
Well the time went by
I forgot to hide
The laughs that came so naturally
Through lows and highs
I wonder why
I ever thought you would leave
Now no matter where or when we are
I know it's you I can count on
Magical
Mythical
Nothing can stop us now
Let's go!
Chikutaku worth the tango
Wakuwaku how should I know
Why it seems when you're here with me
The clock won't stop spinning
Waku waku waku waku
Doki doki hearts beat faster
Tomodachi friends forever
It's clear to see
That this mystery was solved immediately
Jiku no yugami
Distortion of space-time
It's been so long
Since I laughed so hard I cried
Now you came along
It happens almost every time
That I hear your voice
I'm left no choice
But to let you know what you mean to me
Spiraling, time skipping
Through treasured memories
Now no matter where or when we're from
Our friendship's elementary
Case closed
Now you know
Nothing can stop us now
Let's go!
Chikutaku worth the tango
Wakuwaku how should I know
Why it seems when you're here with me
The clock won't stop spinning
Waku waku waku waku
Doki doki hearts beat faster
Tomodachi friends forever
It's clear to see
That this mystery was solved immediately
Jiku no yugami
Distortion of space-time
Which day we're old
What the future holds is
Knock knock knock for us to know yet
Go go go before we know it
So let's solve the question
We can make each second
Chikutaku last forever
Wakuwaku now or never
Chikutaku worth the tango
Wakuwaku how should I know
Why it seems when you're here with me
The clock won't stop spinning
Waku waku waku waku
Doki doki hearts beat faster
Tomodachi friends forever
It's clear to see
That this mystery was solved immediately
Jiku no yugami
Distortion of space-time
That's right! I am the Phoenix! I'm KFP! Look at this!
Eclogo alos, egveni lagos
水面に映る自分がいた
I saw myself reflected on the water's surface.
ああ 私は悪いサメです
Ah, I am a bad shark.
ずっと逸れていた
I had been straying away the whole time.
赤く光るその目
Those eyes glowing red.
海の底 暗闇に消えていく
They disappear into the darkness at the bottom of the sea.
どうして泣くのよ
Why are you crying?
Your tired eyes begin to fall
欲しいものなら全部手に入れて
Get everything you want.
教えて私は
Tell me, did I...
Your darkest thoughts unleash them all
望んでいた私になれたかな
...become the me I wanted to be?
嘘はつかない でも本当じゃない
I don't lie, but it's not the truth either.
本音は言わない 方が楽じゃない
Isn't it easier to not speak your true feelings?
いつかは分かり合える時が来るの？
Will the time ever come when we understand each other?
A time, a place for darker days
分かり合える時来るの？
Will the time to understand each other come?
Look at this so-called "gem of the sea,"
I'll unscramble you, know what I mean?
But who're you watching now?
It ain't much of a now, it shows.
私はあんな奴とは違うの
やめてよ 決めつけはもう
I'm not like that person.
Stop it, I'm done with the assumptions.
大嫌い (大嫌い)
I hate it (I hate it).
理想の姿じゃなくていい
私らしくあれば
It's fine if I'm not the ideal figure.
As long as I'm true to myself,
ただ分かってほしいだけよ
I just want you to understand.
理想通りじゃなきゃ意味なんてない
If it's not as ideal, there's no meaning.
希望も夢すら無くたって
辛い 辛い 辛い 辛い
Even without hope or dreams,
it's painful, painful, painful, painful.
あなた居場所はあるのかしら？
Do you even have a place where you belong?
諦めて楽になるわ さぁ
Give up and you'll be at ease, come on.
ずっと追い求めた
Chasing it all this time,
私なりの答え
The answer in my own way.
自分にだけは嘘はつきたくないの
I don't want to lie to myself at the very least.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
One story ends 今まで
One story ends, until now.
Begin again (Begin)
気づかなかったことがあるんだけど
Begin again (Begin),
though there are things I didn't notice.
While hand in hand どうして
While hand in hand, why?
Until the end (Until the end)
いてくれたから今の私がいる
Until the end (Until the end),
I am who I am because you were there.
過去はいらない？ そんなことはない
Don't need the past? That's not true.
未来は見えない方がマシじゃない？
Isn't it better not to see the future?
ここから No matter where
静かに Watch over me
From here, no matter where,
quietly watch over me.
私を見守っていてね
Please keep watching over me.
So, you think that's all, huh?
Just gotta leave like it's nothing?
Going without me?
I don't know what you're thinking!
Return to the sea,
a shark is all you'll ever be. さよなら。
a shark is all you'll ever be. Farewell.
One story ends ありがとう Begin again
One story ends, thank you. Begin again.
隠していた私はもういらない さよなら
I don't need the hidden me anymore. Farewell.
Once hand in hand ありがとう Until the end
Once hand in hand, thank you. Until the end.
すべてを受け入れて生きていくから
Because I'll live accepting everything.
海の底はつまらないけど
The bottom of the sea is boring, but
あなたの言葉 忘れないから
I won't forget your words.
いつでも No matter where
どこでも Watch over me
Anytime, no matter where,
anywhere, watch over me.
私らしく生きていこう
I'll live as myself.
不退転の覚悟、曲がるかな？
Does the determination of no retreat bend?
Time to die, bird!
No!
It's your time to go!
I'm gonna get you finally!
Get over here! Get over here!
You stupid bird!
Sorry! I thought whatever I did!
Dogeza, dogeza, dogeza!
That's what I thought. Kneel!
What did I do?
You guys forget that I'm a killer.
Actually, sometimes I forget that I'm a killer.
Whoops. That was fun though!
How did you guys like Reflect?
That was dramatic, right?
Dramatic!
Yes! I got to make up for my
lack of dancing skills...
...with drama.
What do you lack?
You did so well!
I-I don't know! It was really tough.
And with the scythe, right?
It is very heavy.
It looks like it's not very heavy,
but it actually weighs a ton.
I'm just really strong, you see.
But the way you're dancing around with it
is kind of dangerous.
Yeah, sorry about that if I accidentally hit you.
It would be curtains for you,
but maybe that's what I secretly want.
Hmm? So we did Reflect together!
We did! As our duo song.
And what did you do?
I did "Full Color" by... Gura!
I love that song so much.
Still unreleased! Oh, so unreleased.
Where is it, Goombus?
But I will say that that was probably the
hardest choreography,
the solo choreography that I've learned,
aside from maybe Go Getter.
Maybe that... that was the hardest.
That's good, you have to challenge yourself!
I was happy to challenge myself to learn that.
And I still know the movements.
You know, the hip sway is so fun!
Yeah, I can imagine.
What about you? What did you sing?
I did "Ame-Ame-Chiku-Taku"!
Well, you know, actually originally when they were like,
"Okay, so we're gonna do the switcheroo,"
"you sing whatever whose song you want to sing,"
And I said, "Ame, Ame, please let me do Chiku-Taku!
I want to sing Chiku-Taku!"
I was like the first, I think, to shout out, so...
I know how much you love that song.
And I loved your bouncy movements to it.
And "Aree!" I like that you changed the lyrics too.
"I'm not just a phoenix, I'm a Tencho"?
Yeah, something like that. Something like that.
It was cute.
そうですね。
That's true.
And we finished it off with our Reflect, which I think is
made for... you know, to be a duet after all.
It's a duet after all.
And we make a really good duet.
So there seems to be a theme, right?
There is a theme here.
Of doing each other's songs.
It seems so. Interesting.
Well, I wonder what will be next!
Because of that...
What are your guesses? Who will do who and like what song?
Hmm, what you thinkin'?
Naruhodo, chat.
I see, chat.
Okay.
So, maybe your wish will come true.
Well, it's not over yet. まだまだ!
Well, it's not over yet. Not yet!
全然ですね。全然!
Not at all. Not at all!
So we gotta pump up the energy just a little bit more, you guys.
Pump!
Keep it going, because there's so much more left. Let's enjoy together... or else.
Well, just remember I'm a killer.
Take her seriously guys, I'm so scared.
People forget that I'm the reaper. I'm crazy!
I'll come after you, I promise. I'm crazy.
As you just saw.
Anyway... okay, how should we end it?
Get excited! TakaMori! Yeah!
TakaMori!
Bye-bye!
See you later!
See ya!
気儘な海に浮かぶ島エッグヘッド
A selfish island floating in the sea, Egghead
世界変えられる未来一番のラボ
The world's leading laboratory for a changing future
最高の頭脳叶えるよ願望
The ultimate brain will grant your wishes
未来のお宝探したお
I've found the treasures of the future
天才が引き起こす初の発の奇跡
The first of many miracles brought by a genius
脳内でも終わらせない夢のファンタジー
A dream fantasy that doesn't end even in the mind
世界がひっくり返るテクノロジー
Technology that turns the world upside down
サイコー叶えちゃうラボラトリー
The best laboratory that makes it all come true
釈迦、リリス、エジソン、ピタゴラス
Shaka, Lilith, Edison, Pythagoras
アトラス、ヨク、録、身のサテライト
Atlas, York, Roku, Mi, the satellites
湧き出すアイデア止まらない
The ideas keep flowing, they won't stop
忙しすぎて猫の手も借りたい
So busy I'd take any help I can get
海も波も越えていく海賊王
The Pirate King who crosses seas and waves
常識変えていく発明を
Inventions that change common sense
そんなやつらに憧れてきた
I've always looked up to those people
次は誰かが王になる
Next, someone else will become king
無限の夢
Infinite dreams
未来の知恵
Future wisdom
ひらめきを巻き起こせ
Let a spark of inspiration arise
無限の夢
Infinite dreams
未来の知恵
Future wisdom
過去も世界も飛び越して
Jumping across the past and the world
ベガパンク
Vegapunk
生み出すよアイデア
Producing ideas
ベガパンク
Vegapunk
革命はここから
Revolution starts here
ベガパンク
Vegapunk
どん！
Don!
This mind's undefeated.
Unto my cosmos' completed.
Let's keep on searching for the treasure under dome.
Genius, a miracle, I make a world and set it free.
Mysterious, fantastic dreams are burning up inside of me.
We turned the world around with technology.
A laboratory cast upon the sea.
Shaka, Lilith, Edison, then Pythagoras of mine.
Atlas, York, and knowledge, fierce, six satellites.
Ideas can't stop flashing, always thinking they might.
Who needs a hand when I'm busy working through the night?
The pirate king who braves the ocean in search of elevation.
A ruler of invention that can modify all reason.
Once watched in jealousy, now someday I gotta be.
Next up the throne, I know what I've gotta do.
言うこと聞かなきゃ振りかざす正義
If you don't listen, I'll brandish justice
世界守る軍団の大義
The cause of the army that protects the world
秘密巡る怪しげな企み
Suspicious plots surrounding secrets
過去の記憶に隠された狂気
Madness hidden in memories of the past
信じておけ、危険な遊戯
Believe in it, a dangerous game
望みに満ちたりその夢のエネルギー
Full of hope, the energy of those dreams
天才が見せる世界の形
The shape of the world shown by a genius
どこへ向かう未来の島エッグヘッド
Where are we headed? Future island Egghead
Oh no, fell into the abyss unknown.
Left me bleeding heartless all alone.
Ayo, ayo, no control.
Ayo, ayo, don't you dare apologize.
Trauma in the pitch cold night.
Listen up cuz here's some advice.
You're out of time, way out of line.
It's taking over like a renegade.
It's taking over, like a renegade
Eye for an eye
I'll make you cry
Tearing it down just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Chimerediediedia
Got me twisted
Such a misfit
Taking the crown you're calling me king
You're gonna hear a monster sing
Chimerediediedia
Now sing it!
Louder like that!
Chimerediediedia
Make 'em buzz
Don't back it up, don't back it up
Keep that aim
I got thoughts that'll drive you insane
Come over if you like
We'll have a lot of fun
But I got a lot of bite
I do but I want
Make sure you don't forget it
An army on my back
Say I'm sick I'm a sadistic
Not living in a lie
Pariah in the light
I want to see the way you bleed
It's taking over, like a renegade
Eye for an eye
I'll make you cry
Tearing it down just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Know ya think so
Chimerediediedia
Got me twisted
Such a misfit
Taking the crown you're calling me king
You're gonna hear a monster sing
Chimerediediedia
Now sing it!
Louder like that!
Chimerediediedia
Make 'em buzz
I want it all so give me some more
Blaze me up down into my core
Oh you wish that I stay down
But then I just rise
You're not my enemy
Baby you're dead to me
Hear my voice screaming out loud
No doubt
Chimerediediedia...
Tearing it down just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Know ya think so
Chimerediediedia
Got me twisted
Such a misfit
Taking the crown you're calling me king
You're gonna hear a monster sing
Chimerediediedia
Now sing it!
Louder like that!
Chimerediediedia
Make 'em buzz
Ha ha ha...
花が寝る夜に 映った星
Stars reflected on the night when the flowers sleep
唸る月が 足をくすぐる
The growling moon tickles my feet
流れる光に 沿ってみてたら
As I followed the flowing light
耳に囁いた 君に届かな
Whispered in my ear, will it reach you?
今手を繋いでも 精一杯抱きしめても
Even if we hold hands now, even if I hold you as tight as I can
それは君に 散るんだ
It will scatter to you
指先でゆらゆらと その動きが
Swaying with fingertips, that movement...
止まった時計の 針に踏み込んだ
...stepped onto the hands of the stopped clock
固まった願いさえ 離れた今は
Even the hardened wishes, now that we're apart
その笑顔を 知ってるよ
I know that smile
Listen, Let me in, Fade, Tear it, Let it out, and Phoenix
光を問う夜に 映った空
The sky reflected on the night questioning the light
爽やかな香りが 鼻をくすぐる
A fresh scent tickles my nose
足音合わせて 歩いてみてたら
As I tried walking in step
私を見ていた 君に届かな
Who was looking at me, will it reach you?
ずっと手を繋いでも 君に吸い付いてみても
Even if we hold hands forever, even if I try to cling to you
それは雨に 染まるんだ
It will be dyed by the rain
君を呼び出した 声の形が
The shape of the voice that called you out
乾いた色を 濡らして
Wetting the dry colors
強く叫んだ声が 散らばった今は
The voice that shouted strongly, now that it's scattered
その言葉を 知ってるよ
I know those words
君が分かってるかな
I wonder if you understand
教えてくれた
You taught me
もう戻らない
That never again
その幸せは
Will that happiness return
花が寝る夜の　海に映った星
The stars reflected in the sea on a night when flowers sleep
光った月が　消えてゆく
The shining moon fades away
指先でゆらゆらと
Swaying at your fingertips
その動きが
That movement
止まった時計の針に踏み込んだ
Stepped onto the hands of a stopped clock
雲が描いた列車
A train drawn by clouds
そよぐ髪
Fluttering hair
その笑顔を
That smile
知ってるよ
I know it well
We'd run
right through
those nights
I'll never find my way back to you
inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness
in the meaning
never laughless
we were screaming at the
top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died.
I'll fly
no proof
those heights
I'll never find another chance to say
hey, thanks for saving my life
i was hopeless
it was stinging
running roadless
we were singing at the
top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died.
what was the root of it all?
...I couldn't say.
I used to jump and then fall,
rugged and cliched.
Would shrug it off without complaint, not a sound
No use in trying to find friends, cuz in the end nobody sticks around
It's when you shoved yourself into a crowded place
that you turned around and found yourself in love in outer space
Cue the reckless nights, no strings,
laughing at our own dreams...
Just what the hell was so funny?
Bark up the wrong tree, stumble, used to falling great heights
amidst a concrete jungle, singing cuz it felt right
we mixed the ennui and troubles rhyming our discontent
and though it's history, I can't forget the time that we spent
convinced that this could mean another end
exists between real and pretend
a twisted alter-fiction where I missed my chance, did not ascend and
Disappearing into the mist of "never happened"
is the me that I can never befriend.
...I let it go.
fade in, fade out
this crazy dream
without a direction, floating aimlessly
there's nothing left back there for me
breathe in,
but it won't stop the rain from pouring
We'd run
right through
those nights
I'll never find my way back to you
inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness
in the meaning
never laughless
we were screaming at the
top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died.
but was there ever a soul inside?
chasing fireflies between the soaring high-rises
left a trail behind defined it "wasted time of our lives"
silent singer, overworked and underpaid
thinks an office is a coffin until off is where you're laid
yet a thought persists, an optimist who ought to be afraid
saw the "nothing wrong" in writing songs behind the lonely shade
is the world a sadder place without the words that you conveyed?
when the ladder fell and shattered every bar that we had played?
Does it matter in the end the sound diminished and decayed
and your friends grew tired of fantasy you're wishing they had stayed?
You don't get to say "I miss you"
you watched your heroes fade
into the rear view-mirror of the villain you portrayed
Stop the pity party, listen, you don't get to be dismayed
you don't get to be emotional, feel blessed you got it made
these the best of years of life because you chose to make a trade
recollect the days you hoped and you prayed for this
What is there to miss?
fade in, fade out
this hazy dream
without a direction, roaming aimlessly
there's nothing left back there for me
pretend it's the end of a made up story
I'll fly
no proof
those heights
I'll never find another chance to say
hey, thanks for saving my life
i was hopeless
it was stinging
driving roadless
we were singing at the
top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died.
I'll say goodbye to the soul inside
somehow there was romance in our self-hate
we've got no chance in this light maze
I'll keep on dancing...
...through the night haze...
...it was so fast to this cold jump...
...tell the truth now...
...you know it's time we're the same ones...
...waking up now to the real life...
...lemme daydream 'til the next night...
I'll keep waiting...
I'll keep waiting for you
Waking up now...
...to my real life...
...lemme daydream 'til the next flight...
...drowning so long...
...I got older...
...now the crowd's gone...
...is it over?
Is it over...
(Exhales)
Hello everyone!
Thank you for joining us tonight!
Thank you!
So, how has it been so far?
How did you guys like my rendition
of Mori Calliope's "Future Island"?
It was amazing!
Oh my god! Ina, so cute!
So cute, so cute, so cute!
Thank you!
And Gura performed Kiara's "Chimera"!
Whoo!
Gura, you're so cute!
And you performed it so well!
It's like... seeing Kiara, but... true!
And Ame! My piece was Ina's "Violet".
How does it feel having your own
song performed in front of you?
I mean, I always love it when you sing...
...and you bring a new energy to the song!
I liked it!
And just now, the three of us
performed "end of a life".
And we want to make things fresh and exciting,
so as you can probably tell...
...we've been singing each other's
original songs tonight!
And now we have two more songs that,
you know, you guys can enjoy.
Two more songs! Oh man!
But ladies, don't forget about the title
of our live concert tonight.
"The Show Goes On!" And it will!
Yes! Yeah!
So everyone, everyone, don't click away!
Don't! Don't! I see you!
Our next song will kind of deviate from our,
the shuffle that we've been doing,
but you're going to love it just as much, right?
That's right! Yeah!
Well, in that case,
let's not keep our guests waiting!
Up next is our penultimate piece!
Enjoy!
One, two, three!
The Show Goes On!
Lyrics: Steph Music, Arrangement: 山下智輝
Lyrics: Steph Music, Arrangement: Yamashita Tomoki
Light the floodlights, let's begin
We'll start stage right and shuffle on in
(It's time for Myth, ready to steal the show!)
We're jumping with joy, let's go!
Curtain's up, so cue the band
We'll keep on entertaining hand in hand
It's our greatest moment yet
A spectacle they'll never forget!
(We're all aglow, party from dusk to dawn)
(The show will go on and on!)
Tell them that we're here to stay and
Spread the news from Tokyo to Broadway!
Gleaming
(Ooh!) Spotlight
Get the gang together,
we're boogieing all night
Beaming
(Ooh!) So bright
Now we're feeling all right!
Since the day we met,
we've all been going strong
(It's been so long, ooh!)
And we'll keep moving right along!
So keep on dancing, yeah, you bet
Ain't nothing gonna stop us,
we're a perfect quintet!
(In harmony no matter where we go)
(It's meant to be, don't you know?)
We're gonna feel so alive when it's us five
Ready to put on another show!
There's a ton to celebrate
The mood is fun and we're feeling great!
From the rafters to the aisles
Contagious laughter and our biggest smiles!
We'll slay 'em like we always do
Make no bones about it!
We'll slay 'em like we always do, make no bones about it!
When I'm with you, it's divine, it's exquisite.
On land or in water, we've never been hotter; it feels sublime.
We're friends for all time!
(Come on, listen to the Tentacult and jive with me.)
(gonna shake your feathers here with KFP.)
(Deadbeats keeping rhythm while the Teammates spin.)
(The Chumbuds join right in!)
We're like a work of art, and I'm gonna keep you in my heart.
We'll stick together.
Myth forever!
Symphony of sight and sound, turning like a merry-go-round,
(We can get 'em cheering even more!)
(On and on and encore!)
Dream another dream with me,
Now it's time to change the key!
Light the floodlights, keep 'em lit,
Tonight's our night, and we've got a hit!
Get in line beside me now,
it's almost time to take another bow!
We'll stay on track, you know that I've got your back!
(I say) Get on the dance floor
(Okay!) Hear the applause roar
(Each day) The music will
Go on and on, and encore!
(Old friends) Wherever you go
(New gens) I'm gonna follow
(No ends) The music will
Go on and on, an endless show!
(Sighs)
Oh my legs!
Oh my god!
I'm getting so old!
That was intense!
Oh, so intense!
That was a good time.
Yeah!
Well, you guys just listened to Myth's new song,
"The Show Goes On!"
What'd you think?
Alright! Very show-tuney!
Yeah, Broadway!
We figured we'd stick with the Broadway theme
and make it something like, you know, a musical?
Something that would make everyone jump on their feet and dance!
And we would be dancing, and we would be dancing!
Yes, yes!
It was so goofy!
So genki!
Yeah, fun times!
And the title truly encapsulates what we think.
We really want the fun to last forever and ever...
with Myth.
And to make that happen, all of us in Myth
are going to do the best we can.
And those are the feelings that we packed
nicely into this new song.
Yeah!
Hope you guys will listen to it a lot,
because it will be on the streaming platforms very soon!
So get ready to wear out your speakers!
And also the MV is going to be right after this.
We're going to raid into it! Be ready!
Oh yeah!
Be ready for that?
Go check it out! Yeah!
But that's not all!
Maybe another little surprise...
what else we have...
merchandise coming out!
Merch! More goods! Stands! Let's go!
Exactly!
Now, we will not show it right now,
but it will be shown at the very end of the stream,
at the ending screen, so stay tuned for that!
Don't immediately leave the stream, okay?
Yeah, yeah!
So, we don't have much time left.
I thought I'd like to hear what you ladies are currently feeling.
Who wants to go first?
Oh, me me me!
Alright! Go Shark!
E-yah!
Whoa! Oh my god!
Shark split out of nowhere, I guess.
I guess she can do that, alright, fine, whatever!
That's why she was so excited to go first!
Of course! What about Ame?
It's showtime, baby!
Ame, it was really good, right? Right?
Hope you guys enjoyed it! Thank you so much!
Go Ame!
So good!
Good time.
Okay, who else, who else?
Maybe you?
Well, well, you know, it kind of reminded me
of like, you know, when Myth started together in the past,
and with our journey of a thousand years, and now with
all these performances into the future... Oh!
Future! Future! Future!
I like future! Future!
危険な海に浮かぶ島へ...
To an island floating on a dangerous sea...
...嵐が運ぶ皆祭 自分の名を知らぬまま
...a festival carried by the storm, still not knowing your own name
Sorry, sorry, not the eggheads!
Not the eggheads!
We're playing around too much.
Good segue into Calli!
True!
Oh me? Oh gosh!
Well, I don't know guys, um...
I feel like, I feel like, I just feel like
we've been through so much together and... and...
and I'm so happy to be by your side and you guys are the best!
E-yah!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
That's Broadway! That's not Broadway!
You guys don't like my theater moves?
No, no!
Gimme, gimme, gimme something wholesome, come on!
Fine, fine, fine. I love singing
songs that I love with people that I love.
That's it. That's all there is to it.
I had a lot of fun with you guys. You guys are the best.
And, uh, yeah, before I get too sappy,
somebody else take the mic. I think we all have
words for everybody, but next up is Kiara!
Kiara, what did you think?
Yes! Well, today I did a little bit of MCing here.
I hope I did it well.
But for me, you know, I realized,
when we joined, our oldest senpais, I think,
were around like four years, right?
Four years into the game.
And now, we're four years in!
Wow, so we're old!
We're like really proper senpais now.
And everybody, you gotta respect us, pay the senpai tax.
Pay up!
Pay up please!
So all of these four years, hopefully more, and
you know, I want to make more memories.
This was definitely a big, nice memory.
So the show must go on, the show goes on indeed,
just like the title.
We're gonna do our best, so please support us,
listen to the new song!
And with that, I think we can gather together!
All right!
Together! Huddle, huddle, huddle, huddle!
Myth huddle, Myth huddle, Myth huddle!
You guys ready? Here we go. All right.
Mori Calliope!
Takanashi Kiara!
Ninomae Ina'nis!
Gawr Gura!
Watson Amelia!
Together, we're...
Myth!
Let's go!
Okay, positions!
We’re ready to greet the world
We’re voyaging forward
With courage to run toward a brand-new start
Let’s go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully,
Meeting heart to heart
Connect the World
Lyrics: Steph Music, Arrangement: 中野領太
Lyrics: Steph Music, Arrangement: Ryota Nakano
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue
How will we connect in this new frontier?
We’re journeying through
Budding in a scene where no one’s ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars
Radiant and warm, charged with energy
That’s carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life
Surely,
We’ve gotta take that chance
We’re running non-stop, straight to the top, that’s right!
We’re ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase, creating a new place
Where we can shine
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We’re voyaging forward with courage to run toward
A brand-new stage
Let’s go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me,
And we’ll turn the page
Breaking through the doubt, we know we’ll figure out
A way to clear each towering trial
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge
With a smile
We’ll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing,
No matter where we are, no matter how far,
We can be stars
Let’s go!
I want to chase a wish and never-ending dream
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality
Take my hand and reach for this dream
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we built
We’re ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways, discovering highways
To everywhere
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation,
A dream unfurled
Let’s make friends,
Making a moment of history joyfully
Follow me,
We’ll connect the world
They’ll hear our song, ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues
Carry on
Starting now
Setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world
Yay! Kikkeriki, everyone!
Did you enjoy the hololive English -Myth- 4th Anniversary Live:
"The Show Goes On"?
I know it's hard to say goodbye,
but before we go,
we have some awesome merch to show you!
First up, we have this: the Acrylic Block.
The illustration theme is Broadway musical-esque retro outfits,
perfectly fitting for our live show.
And it was drawn by the amazing Aki Akane-sensei.
It's a two-layer design, giving it a nice depth.
The thick acrylic makes it look great just as it is.
Alright, on to the next one!
Next we have: Collection Cards.
These cards have a special touch with a translucent material
and foil stamping, making them feel extra festive.
Each of us in Myth has our own card,
so be sure to collect them all.
Alright, next up!
Let's see... ooh, we got Mini Mascot Plushies!
Each Myth member's mascot has turned into a cute plushie!
But this time, they're all dressed up with hats and ribbons
to match the live show. How cute!
And, you can attach them to your bag
and take them anywhere you want.
Let them see the world!
Okay, what do we have next?
Next up is the Crossbody Bag.
It's a simple everyday-use bum bag.
The inside design features Myth's motif icons,
making it super stylish.
Perfect for carrying the keychains around
when you go out.
Thanks, or should I say, Dankeschön, everyone!
I sure feel like I want to collect them, and I hope you do the same.
And last but not least,
thank you so much for supporting hololive English -Myth-.
Come catch us at the next show or stream!
Otsu-Myth!