(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Special Announcement! 3D SHOWCASE #KoboKanaeru3D
October 27 (Fri) 20:00 WIB / 22:00 JST
シルエット
Silhouette
Lyrics・Composition：谷口鮪
Lyrics / Composition: Maguro Taniguchi
いっせーのーせで踏み込むゴーライン 僕らは...
Ready, set, go! Stepping across the finish line...
...何も 何も まだ知らぬ
...We don't know anything, anything yet.
一線を越えて振り返るともうない 僕らは...
Crossing the line, looking back, it's no longer there...
...何も 何も まだ知らぬ
...We don't know anything, anything yet.
うまって うまって うまってく 煌めく汗がこぼれるのさ
Sweat is pouring, pouring, pouring down, sparkling as it falls.
覚えてないこともたくさんあっただろう
There must have been many things we didn't remember.
誰も 彼も シルエット
Everyone, every one of them is a silhouette.
大事にしてたもの 忘れたふりをしたんだよ
We pretended to forget the things we held dear.
何も ないよ 笑えるさ
There's nothing left, we can just laugh.
いっせーので思い出す少年 僕らは...
Ready, set, go! Remembering the boy we were...
...何もかもを欲しがった
...We wanted everything.
わかってるって あきづいてるって 時計の...
I know, I've realized, the clock's...
...針は 日々は 止まらない
...hands, the days won't stop.
うまって うまって うまってく 流れる時を時々 遠くにあって
Drowning, drowning, drowning, the flowing time is sometimes far away.
覚えてないこともたくさんあっただろう
There must have been many things we didn't remember.
誰も 彼も シルエット
Everyone, every one of them is a silhouette.
恐れて回ること 知らぬふりをしてるのさ
We're pretending not to know about turning in fear.
...いたよ
...wanted to be.
何もないよと笑い合えたさ
We were able to laugh together, saying "It's nothing."
ひらりとひらりと舞ってる
Fluttering, fluttering, they're dancing.
木の葉の様に揺れること無く過ごしていたいよ
I want to spend my days without swaying like leaves.
覚えてないこともたくさんあったけど
There were many things I don't remember, but...
きっとずっと変わらないものがあることを
That there are things that will surely never change...
教えてくれたあなたは
You, who taught me that, are...
消える消えるシルエット
A fading, fading silhouette.
大事にしたいもの持って大人になるんだ
I'll become an adult while holding onto the things I cherish.
どんな時も離さずに
Never letting go, no matter when.
守り続けよう
Let's keep on protecting them.
そしたらいつの日にか
Then, someday...
なにもかもを笑えるさ
We'll be able to laugh at everything.
ひらりとひらりと舞ってる
Fluttering, fluttering, they're dancing.
木の葉が飛んでゆく
The leaves are flying away.
Wah!
Akhirnya 3D!
Finally 3D!
Gimana?
What do you think?
Wuoah! Anime banget nggak?
Wuoah! Isn't it very anime?
Berisik kalian ya.
You guys are noisy, huh.
Entar, Kobo taruh dulu ya.
Wait, Kobo will put this down first.
Berat.
It's heavy.
Oke kalau gitu, Baka-baka-baka Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Okay then, Baka-baka-baka Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
Oke kita nge-vlog kali ya.
Okay, let's vlog.
Sini sini.
Come here, come here.
Pinjam dulu kameranya, kameramen. Oke.
Let me borrow the camera for a bit, cameraman. Okay.
Guys welcome back to my channel!
Don't forget to like, subrek and comment...
Don't forget to like, subscribe and comment...
and give... Kobo... I mean...
join Kobolonimbus let's go!
Oke di sini aku mau memperlihatkan nih pulau kecil aku ya.
Okay, here I want to show you my little island.
Hanya sebuah gubuk kecil doang.
It's just a small shack.
Di situ ada perahu ya, di situ ada perahu...
There's a boat there, there's a boat...
soalnya Kobo biasa pindah-pindah pulau ya.
because Kobo usually moves from island to island.
Karena mercusuar Kobo tuh banyak, nggak cuma di pulau ini doang.
Because Kobo has many lighthouses, not just on this island.
Nih lihat ya tuh.
Look at that.
Tuh! Wiii tinggi banget tapi ya.
See! Wii, it's really tall though.
Ya tadi kalian di awal udah lihat ya, cuma emang apa ya...
You saw it at the beginning, but... it's just...
tinggi banget jadi rada capek ke sana.
really tall so it's a bit tiring to go there.
Jadi nanti aja ya Kobo tunjukin ke kalian ya.
So Kobo will show it to you later, okay?
Oke oke, terus... outfit check! OOTD check!
Okay okay, next... outfit check! OOTD check!
Oke. Syu syu syu... look at my shoes.
Okay. Shoo shoo shoo... look at my shoes.
Look at my shoes. Uh the details. Uh.
Uh the details. Uh. Kalian bisa lihat nggak?
Uh the details. Uh. Can you guys see it?
Ha!
Terus ya... biasa lah ya.
Then... you know, the usual.
Terus ini ada jaket ya, gocap dapat tiga di pasar malam.
Then here's a jacket, fifty thousand for three at the night market.
Tinggal modif dikit nih ada kasih nama brand Rain Shaman.
Just a little modification, here I put the brand name "Rain Shaman".
Keren banget ya. Jadi kayak mahal juga gitu lho.
It's really cool, right? So it looks expensive too.
Hmm kelihatan mahal.
Hmm looks expensive.
Terus ya sisanya thrifting aja lah ya.
Then the rest is just thrifting.
Ya ada yang minjam M-chan, ada nih...
Some are borrowed from M-chan, and this...
sport bra juga punya Mak, minjam ya.
sport bra is Mom's, I borrowed it.
Ya gitulah. Aku masih mau nunjukin...
Yeah, that's how it is. I still want to show...
Eh?
Eh! Udah jam berapa kah ini?
Eh! What time is it now?
Eh? Aduh bentar-bentar guys aku harus ke sekolah dulu!
Huh? Oh wait, wait guys, I have to go to school first!
Aa is is is... sorry sorry sorry...
Aa... sorry, sorry, sorry...
bentar-bentar aku harus ke sekolah dulu.
wait, wait, I have to go to school first.
Ai! Cilus tolong bantu! Cilus!
Ai! Cilus, help me! Cilus!
Iya Cilus dalangin! Ah!
Yes, Cilus, lead the way! Ah!
Motoyaka aku takut, aku nggak mau telat!
Motoyaka, I'm scared, I don't want to be late!
Ah cepat-cepat motoyaka gambare gambare!
Ah, hurry, hurry, Motoyaka, keep going, keep going!
Aku takut telat, cepetan sembul sempur!
I'm afraid of being late, hurry up!
Wah!
Akhirnya nyampe kelas!
Finally arrived in class!
Ada Ayange... ehe.
There's my darling... ehe.
Oh! Asmara
Oh! Romance
Kalian ada nggak sih yang relate, yang rasanya jatuh cinta?
Do any of you relate, that feeling of falling in love?
Rasanya tuh berbunga-bunga deh.
It feels like flowers are blooming.
Gimana ya? Rasanya tuh kayak...
How do I put it? It feels like...
Dag dig dug...
Thump-thump-thump...
...hatiku.
...my heart.
Saat aromamu lewati hidungku.
When your scent passes through my nose.
Melotot mataku...
My eyes widen...
...melihatmu lewat di depanku.
...seeing you pass in front of me.
Seorang biasa saja...
Just an ordinary person...
...apa pantas tuk bersanding denganmu.
...is it fitting to be by your side.
Overthinking, tapi gamau ambil pusing.
Overthinking, but I don't want to worry.
Karna aku bukan kaum mendang-mending.
Because I'm not the type to compare.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
...berdebar rasanya...
...it feels like my heart is racing...
...ku di dekatmu.
...when I'm near you.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Dengar bisikan cinta lirik matamu...
Listen to the whispers of love from your eyes...
...hantam jantungku.
...hitting my heart.
Asmara...
Romance...
Oh oh, asmara...
Oh oh, romance...
Hari ke-sekian.
On the umpteenth day.
Masih tak berhasil...
I still haven't succeeded...
...mendekatimu.
...in getting close to you.
Ugh bagaimana...
Ugh how...
...melelehkan beku hatimu!!!
...to melt your frozen heart!!!
Mending nyerah dah? Oh tentu tidak.
Should I just give up? Oh certainly not.
Demi gapai impian...
For the sake of reaching the dream...
...kita harus terus belajar.
...we must continue to learn.
Belajar memahami bahasa cintamu!
Learn to understand your language of love!
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
...berdebar rasanya...
...it feels like my heart is racing...
...ku di dekatmu.
...when I'm near you.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Dengar bisikan cinta lirik matamu.
Listen to the whispers of love from your eyes.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Balas sinyal cintaku...
Reciprocate my signals of love...
...sekali saja!
...just once!
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Tidak adakah ruang dalam hatimu...
Is there no room in your heart...
...tersisa untukku?
...left for me?
Sore itu...
That afternoon...
Tumben-tumbenan kau duluan...
Strangely enough, you were the first...
...yang datang menghampiriku.
...to come and approach me.
Datanglah padaku.
Come to me.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Berdebar rasanya...
It feels like my heart is racing...
Ku di dekatmu.
When I'm near you.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Dengar bisikan cinta lirik matamu.
Listen to the whispers of love from your eyes.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Berdebar rasanya...
It feels like my heart is racing...
Ku di dekatmu.
When I'm near you.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Dengar bisikan cinta lirik matamu.
Listen to the whispers of love from your eyes.
Oh asmara...
Oh romance...
Terjawab semua sudah...
All has been answered...
...teka-tekimu.
...your riddle.
Karena kini ku t'lah menjadi...
Because now I have become...
Menjadi apa?
Become what?
Milikmu!
Yours!
Milikmu...
Yours...
Selamat 3D-nya!
Congratulations on your 3D!
Selamat 3D!
Eh bentar itu, itu kenapa ada...
Wait a second, why is there...
Kenapa ada papan kardus?
Why is there a cardboard board?
Ini lagi ngapain nih?
What's going on here?
Ini kenalin...
Let me introduce you to...
Pacar baru!
My new boyfriend!
Ya ampun...!
Oh my goodness...!
Namanya siapa ini?
What's his name?
Siapa ya? Gak sih, gak tau, tapi ganteng kan?
Who is it? I don't know, but he's handsome, right?
Iya, lumayan banget.
Yeah, he's quite something.
Diam.
Be quiet.
Mohon maaf nih, mohon maaf nih Aboy ya, bukannya gimana-gimana nih...
Sorry about this, sorry Aboy, it's not like that...
Tapi biasa nih cowok yang kayak gini nih...
But usually guys like this...
Halo, cowok yang kayak gini biasanya ada maunya.
Hello, guys like this usually want something.
Apa tuh maunya?
What do they want?
Gak gak, jangan dengerin dia.
No, no, don't listen to her.
Ayang, jangan dengerin dia.
Honey, don't listen to her.
Ya gitu sih.
Yeah, that's how it is.
Gak, gak mungkin gak mungkin.
No, no way, it's impossible.
Ayang!
Honey!
Ayang kamu dengerin aku gak sih?
Honey, are you listening to me?
Na- Ayang!
Na- Honey!
Itu...
That...
Mending dengerin aku, mending dengerin aku dulu nih.
Better listen to me, better listen to me first.
Gak bisa kayak gini, Ela.
It can't be like this, Ela.
Makanya...
That's why...
Mendingan kamu tuh...
It's better if you...
...jadi gepeng.
...become 2D.
Biar sama nih.
So you're the same.
Susah-susah nunggu debut 3D...
After waiting so hard for the 3D debut...
...masa jadi gepeng?
...you want me to be 2D?
MAGIIII!
Udah, udah, udah. Nggak usah ribut.
Enough, enough. No need to make a fuss.
Masa kardus ginian doang diributin.
Are you really making a fuss over just a cardboard cutout?
Ini bukan kardus ya!
This is not cardboard!
[Suara menangis]
[Crying sounds]
Eh, eh, mohon maaf nih.
Hey, hey, sorry about this.
Demi kebaikan kamu, mendingan kamu fokus 3D dulu.
For your own good, you'd better focus on your 3D showcase first.
Emang boleh?
Is that allowed?
Ini kubawa dulu ya.
I'll take this for now.
Balikin!
Give it back!
Semangat 3D!
Good luck with your 3D!
Tidak, jangan pacar aku... Magni manis...
No, don't, my boyfriend... Sweet Magni...
Endless Tears feat. 中村舞子
Endless Tears feat. Maiko Nakamura
君の心に包まれたまま 愛を誓い
Wrapped in your heart, I swear my love
眠れない夜何度過ぎてもね 受け止めて
No matter how many sleepless nights pass, accept me
今すぐ会いたい 涙止まらない 触れたくて
I want to see you right now, tears won't stop, I want to touch you
好きだから 苦しくて
Because I love you, it's painful
君のことを想うほど
The more I think of you
この涙こぼれるの
These tears overflow
このまま会えないとしても
Even if we can't meet like this
誰より 好きだから
Because I love you more than anyone
バイバイさっきしたばかりなのに
Even though we just said goodbye
会いたいが また溢れるの
The desire to see you overflows again
消えてしまいそうなあの日のワンキス
That one kiss that day that seems like it might vanish
君からのメールを待つの
I wait for a message from you
君と会えば狭まるタイムリミット
The time limit narrows when I meet you
二人の時間 大事に
Cherishing our time together
バイバイしてもまた会いたい
Even if we say goodbye, I want to see you again
君とのメールでまた再会
Reuniting again through your messages
変わる景色 街はトワイライト
The scenery changes, the city is in twilight
いそのこと君を奪い去りたい
I'd rather just snatch you away
君の温もりが消える頃
By the time your warmth fades away
夢から覚めれば現実のドア
If I wake from the dream, it's the door of reality
君のことを想うほど
The more I think of you
この涙こぼれるの
These tears overflow
このまま会えないとしても
Even if we can't meet like this
誰より 好きだから
Because I love you more than anyone
I love you... Love you... I love you... Love you...
I love you... Love you...
夜が明ければ 探す君だけを
If the night dawns, I'll search only for you
I love you... Love you... I love you... Love you...
I love you... Love you...
目を閉じれば My love for you
If I close my eyes, my love for you
あなたと...
With you...
今すぐ会いたい 限りあるタイム
I want to see you right now, limited time
永遠の愛 信じてはみたい
I want to believe in eternal love
離れること考えると胸が真っ二つに
The thought of being apart splits my heart in two
避けるようにタイト
Tight as if to avoid it
可愛げなフェイス よければ抱いて
A cute face, hold me if you'd like
引き裂かれるカウントダウンのようにブレイク
Break like a countdown being torn apart
Love baby, love baby 言葉をフリーズ
Love baby, love baby, freeze the words
ショーが始まった また次のシーン
The show has started, on to the next scene
想えば想うほど 降り積もる思い
The more I think of you, the more my feelings pile up
会えば会うほど...
The more we meet...
そばにいたいと 強く願うほど 明日さえ見えなくて
The more I strongly wish to be by your side, I can't even see tomorrow
いつか見つけるまで 離したくはない
Until I find you someday, I don't want to let go
離れたくはない
I don't want to be apart
Love you baby, love you
君は離さない
I won't let you go
君のことを想うほど
The more I think of you
この涙こぼれるの
These tears overflow
明けない夜の中 一人 君しか見えなくて
In the never-ending night, alone, I can see only you
君の心に包まれたまま 愛を誓い
Wrapped in your heart, I swear my love
眠れない夜何度過ぎてもね 受け止めて
No matter how many sleepless nights pass, accept me
今すぐ会いたい 涙止まらない 触れたくて
I want to see you right now, tears won't stop, I want to touch you
好きだから 苦しくて
Because I love you, it's painful
I love you... Love you... I love you... Love you...
I love you... Love you...
夜が明ければ 探す君だけを
If the night dawns, I'll search only for you
I love you... Love you... I love you... Love you...
I love you... Love you...
目を閉じれば My love for you
If I close my eyes, my love for you
あなたと...
With you...
Ah, so fun. Son...
Son? What's going on? Why are you crying?
Why are you so sad? We just sang a great song together. Come on.
心は痛い...
My heart hurts...
Your heart hurts? But why?
My boyfriend cheated on me.
He goes for Zeta.
Wait, hold on a moment. You have a boyfriend?
Tell me who he is, tell me where he is, and I will take care of everything.
Dad will take care of everything for you, Kobo.
I don't know, I don't know his name, but I love him!
Um... what?
I don't really think I understand, but it's okay.
It's okay, son. Look, sometimes things in life just don't go your way.
But it's alright. You'll be okay. I promise.
No! No, no!
I can't take this anymore!
Kids, man...
Here, just shoot me!
A gun? Kobo, I can't do that.
Just shoot me!
I can't do that. You're my son!
Tembak! Tembak! Aku gak tahan!
Shoot! Shoot! I can't take it!
Alright, alright. Well, it is my job after all, so I guess I'll do it.
If you insist, Kobo. Pick a place where you want to perish.
I think I will... maybe here.
Alright. Stand really still. Say your prayers.
I'm ready! Just shoot me! Shoot me, Dad!
Rest in peace.
Just doing my job.
What happened here? Calli, what did you do? Calli!
I... I didn't do anything. Alright, look. I know what it looks like.
Look, I shot her with a water gun. Alright?
With a water gun. Look, it's not lethal or anything.
But she's dead!
I'm calling... You should be teaching her... she's playing dangerous stuff like this!
You know kids, Kiara. Look, she's faking it.
She's faking?
Did we fail as parents, I wonder?
Come on, live!
Oh my god! Yes! Come back to me! Come on!
Mommy...
Yes, yes, yes?
Sorry, mommy. - Eh? It's okay, it's okay.
Oh Kobo, it took you long enough. Come on.
Get up before daddy gets in trouble. - Oh my god.
I'm back with the water!
Thank god. What happened, Kobo? What happened?
My boyfriend cheated on me.
Who's your boyfriend? Where is he?
That's what I said!
I don't know his name, but I love him!
Listen here you little shit. Forget about him.
Mommy is here. Let's just have fun together, okay?
Let's go! - Let's go!
Yeah, let's go! Sounds like fun! I'm coming too, right?
No! You go buy milk. - Really? Milk?
For breakfast. - Milk? Again? We need it?
Yeah! Bye-bye!
Okay, Kobo. Come on, let's do something fun, okay?
Yes! Mommy and daughter time! Bye!
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
No escape from romance scandals
消してあげる
I'll erase them for you
Mommy! Aku mau jadi president!
Mommy! I want to be president!
Ngapain?
For what?
Biar aku gak di-PHP cowok lagi.
So I won't be ghosted by guys anymore.
No! You're still a baby. Let me be the president instead.
宣誓！私が大統領になったら、人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします！
Oath! If I become president, women who flirt with other men will be exiled!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら、嫌だ友達だよって誤魔化す奴はヘソから電気流します！
Oath! If I become president, those who say 'we're just friends' will be electrocuted!
だ・だ・だ 大統領になったらね
When I become president...
ぶっ飛んじゃうほどセンセーショナル
It'll be sensationally mind-blowing
ズッキュン ドッキュン 射止めて
Shooting through the heart with a bang
徹底的にリサーチだ
Thorough research is needed
大嫌い しょうがない
I hate it, it can't be helped
クズは病気ね バイバイバイ
Scum is a disease, bye bye bye
権利 所在 地位 名誉
Rights, location, status, honor
何もないけど裁きたい でしょう？ ワン ツー スリー！
I have nothing but I want to judge. Right? One two three!
だ・だ・だ 大統領になったらね
When I become president...
まずは君を捕まえるね
First, I'll capture you
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spill everything
誰ですか あの女
Who is that woman?
ダメですか そうですか
Is it no good? Is that so?
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
No escape from romance scandals
消してあげる
I'll erase them for you
シル・ヴ・プレプレプレジデント
Sil-ve-Pre-Pre-Pre-President
「そんなことなったら、ただの仕事の付き合いだよ」
"If that happens, it's just a business relationship."
って言わすわ。二度とは立てなくしてやります。
I'll make you say that. I'll make sure you can never stand again.
先生！行くぜ！
Teacher! Let's go!
いや、もう効果が強引でさって 世を説くこちらには
No, the effect is already forceful. As I explain to the world,
冷徹なガスコンロが固まり。
a cold gas stove stands firm.
耳を突く まるでドファンキー ドリスキャン 鳴らす
Piercing my ears, like a super funky Doris Scan ringing.
まま待った 価格解消なしのスクープね
Wait, it's a scoop with no price resolution.
I wanna be you じゃない 悪くないのにね ハイハイハイ
I wanna be you... not really. It's not bad, though. High, high, high.
軽薄なほどイケてるじゃん 何にもないことあるんな。
The more frivolous, the cooler. There's nothing to it.
よっしゃー！ ワン、ツー、スリー！
Alright! One, two, three!
大統領になって貰ってね
If I become the President,
多分君は変わらないね
you probably won't change.
ヒラっと退けて
Casually brushing it off,
のらりくらり交わすのね
dodging with a smirk.
デートですか? こんばんは
Is it a date? Good evening.
本気ですか? そうですか
Are you serious? I see.
情熱とは不注意
Passion is carelessness.
微熱も消してしまいました
Even the slight fever has vanished.
Kiara! Kobo!
大統領になったらね
When I become the President,
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'll definitely catch you.
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel,
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spill everything.
どこですか? 今あんた
Where are you? Right now,
見つけちゃった バレちゃった
I found you. You're busted.
夜道にはご用心
Watch out at night.
さようなら代わりに銃声
Goodbye, and a gunshot instead.
シル・ヴ・プレプレプレジデント
S'il vous plaît, plaît, plaît, President
Hey!
Thank you Mommy!
My baby!
I'm good now, thank you!
Oh, I'm happy to hear that.
But you know, Mommy has to go home now and rest.
But I will sleep and dream about you!
Let's go! Yes!
So ganbatte Kobo-chan!
So good luck, Kobo-chan!
Ganbatte!
Good luck!
Aku datangmu... aku cintamu juga!
I'm coming... I love you too!
Bye-bye!
Okay, she's done now.
So Mommy doesn't know that I'm not going home yet, okay?
I still wanna show you guys something.
Aku mau nunjukin sesuatu yang keren banget.
I want to show you something really cool.
Parah kece parah.
It's super, super cool.
A trick using my rain shaman power!
Look at this!
Ush ush ush...
WOOOH!
雨！雨！雨！
RAIN! RAIN! RAIN!
WEH! Hujan tokger! Keren banget ya?
Whoa! Heavy rain! Really cool, right?
Rain shaman no chikara da!
It's the rain shaman's power!
Keren banget kan? Kobo Kanaeru gitu lho!
Cool, right? That's Kobo Kanaeru for you!
Dan udah mulai hujan...
And it's starting to rain...
Ah, this is also the first time you guys see my jellyfish umbrella, right?
Hmm? とても可愛いでしょう? 可愛いでしょう? 可愛いね?
Hmm? It's very cute, right? Cute, right? Cute, isn't it?
Arigatou!
Thank you!
By the way, every time you send a Super Chat, it will give more power to the rain!
Jadi setiap kalian kirim Super Chat, atau eh maksudnya bahasa sopannya apa ya?
So every time you send a Super Chat, or... what's the polite way to say it?
Every time you send your "love", it will increase the power...
...kayak amplifier gitu ya.
...like an amplifier.
Ya gitulah, kalian ngertilah.
Well, you guys understand.
Cuman kekuatan seorang Kobo Kanaeru doang yang bisa ngebuat hujan kayak gini cuy!
Only the power of Kobo Kanaeru can make rain like this, guys!
WEH! Thank you for the Super Chat! Udah sampe... udah sampe sebetis nih!
WHOA! Thank you for the Super Chat! It's already reached my calves!
Lumayan, bentar guys aku belum... belum mandi juga bentar.
Not bad, wait guys I haven't... haven't showered yet, wait.
Sekalian cuci muka. Nice, thank you!
Washing my face at the same time. Nice, thank you!
これ、君たちの愛だ！ありがとう！
This is your love! Thank you!
Mwah mwah!
え、ちょっと... 増えてる?
Eh, wait... is it increasing?
YA THANK YOU! THANK YOU TAPI AKU GAK BISA BERENANG!
YES THANK YOU! THANK YOU BUT I CAN'T SWIM!
EH CHOTTO MATTE! AKU GAK BISA BERENANG!
EH WAIT A MINUTE! I CAN'T SWIM!
BUT I... ADUH! TASUKETE!
BUT I... Ouch! Help!
Bentar, pelan-pelan kirim Super Chat-nya...
Wait, send the Super Chats slowly...
WOOOH! Oke santai...
WOOOH! Okay, relax...
Gaya kodok! Gaya kodok! Gaya kodok!
Frog style! Frog style! Frog style!
Yagoo-san tasukete!
Yagoo-san, help me!
Ah! Thank you! Thank you for the...
Thank you for this love! Thank you!
Nice!
Okay, thank you!
My back hurts...
Akhirnya pulang juga ke rumah.
Finally back home.
Ah, untung pakai jas hujan.
Ah, luckily I'm wearing a raincoat.
Luckily, my outfit is waterproof.
Oh, by the way, welcome!
Welcome to my lighthouse! ようこそ!
Welcome to my lighthouse! Welcome!
Ini dalamnya mercusuar aku. Ih, ih!
This is the inside of my lighthouse. Hehe!
Aku room tour dikit kali ya? Oke, let's go do a quick room tour, okay?
Should I do a quick room tour? Okay, let's do a quick room tour, okay?
Jadi di sini ada tangga karena mercusuar aku tuh tinggi banget sebenarnya.
So here's a staircase because my lighthouse is actually really tall.
Cuman ya, ya udahlah ya di lantai ini aja.
But well, let's just stay on this floor for now.
Nanti kita ke atas nanti-nanti aja, oke? Oke.
We'll go upstairs later, okay? Okay.
Lalu biasanya habis pulang sekolah aku langsung tidur. Langsung turu.
And then usually after coming home from school I immediately sleep. Straight to sleep.
Tapi ya karena aku buat tamu di sini jadi ya udah.
But since I have guests here, I'll just...
Aku room tour aja deh. Ya kan ya? Ya kan?
...do a room tour instead. Right? Right?
Oh, ini namanya Oyamatadase.
Oh, this is Oyamatadase.
Iya kan? Lucu lucu lucu lucu lucu. Hup!
Right? So cute, cute, cute, cute, cute. Hup!
Oke, lanjut. Ee di sini biasa tempat lutingan-lutingan...
Okay, moving on. This is usually where I loot...
...makanan-makanan diambil.
...where the food is taken.
Terus ini kalau mau nyantai ya sama teman-teman yang biasa saya luting.
And this is where I relax with the friends I usually loot.
Nah, ada apa lagi ya? Ada boneka-boneka. Ini banyak boneka, sorry.
Well, what else is there? Plushies. There are many plushies here, sorry.
Terus ada... Nih ada Fajri, Kipli, Kupli, ya absen dulu yuk.
And then there's... Here's Fajri, Kipli, Kupli, let's take attendance.
Ya ada Rio, ada Rai, ada Ryu. Ya banyak banget ya guys.
There's Rio, Rai, Ryu. There are so many of them, guys.
Terus ada beberapa koleksi instrumen aku kayak salah satunya piano keyboard sih, keyboard.
Then I have some instrument collections like one of them is a piano keyboard, well, a keyboard.
Sama terus ada tempat aku biasa streaming di sini. Apa sih?
And then there's the place where I usually stream. What is it?
Ada... Ada monitor tadinya cuman...
There was... a monitor earlier, but...
Aku lagi pakai TV ya. Lagi nyantai dulu.
I'm using a TV now. Just relaxing.
Terus itu ah lihat ada ukulele. Ih!
And then, oh look, there's a ukulele. Hehe!
Sama terus ada kulkas sama ini ada dua instrumen yang sering aku mainin.
And then there's a fridge and these two instruments that I often play.
Yaitu gitar listrik sama gitar akustik.
Namely an electric guitar and an acoustic guitar.
Enggak sih, aku lebih sering main gitar akustik.
No, I actually play the acoustic guitar more often.
Nah yang tadi aku mainin tuh yang ini guys, yang gitar listrik.
The one I played earlier was this one guys, the electric guitar.
Jreng jreng jreng jreng jreng. Yeah.
*strums* Yeah.
Terus sama ada violin, ini jarang. Lagi jarang sih, ya.
And then there's a violin, I rarely use it. Rarely for now, yeah.
Sama nih ada tanaman ini. Hmm! Kantong semar.
And then there's this plant. Hmm! A pitcher plant.
Udah... Udah berkembang biak banyak banget deh.
It's... it's grown so much.
Hmm, ini oi.
Hmm, so good.
Oke. Ya kalian lihatlah apa lagi?
Okay. Well, look what else is there?
Itu tuh, langit-langit! Ah ah ah langit-langit.
That, the ceiling! Ah ah ah the ceiling.
Aku punya lampu-lampu lucu di atas. Wah!
I have cute lights up there. Wow!
Lucu ya lampu-lampunya.
The lights are so cute.
Terus emang kayak apa sih? Ceiling-nya lucu banget kan?
And isn't it just...? The ceiling is so cute, right?
Gimana gimana gimana cantik enggak kamar aku?
How is it? Is my room pretty?
Kayak pemiliknya. Iya enggak sih?
Like the owner. Don't you think?
Ya ya, aku tadi lihat, "Kak Kobo coba dong mainin instrumennya".
Yeah, I saw earlier, "Kobo-kak, please play your instrument".
Hah, shikata ga nai wa. Berhubung aku baik hati dan tidak sombong.
*sigh* It can't be helped. Since I'm kind-hearted and humble.
Untung aku enggak berisik.
Luckily I'm not noisy.
Enggak ya, aku baik. Aku lagi baik nih.
No, I'm kind. I'm being nice now.
Ya udah deh. Kalian dengerin ya, oke?
Alright then. Listen up, okay?
Chotto matte kudasai ne.
Please wait a moment.
Aku mau ambil itu, gitar. Ya deh aku main gitarnya aja deh.
I want to take that, the guitar. Alright, I'll just play the guitar.
Sama buka jaket bentar ya, oke? Tunggu di sini sebentar.
And I'll take off my jacket for a bit, okay? Wait here for a second.
Oke, nih aku turutin.
Okay, I'm doing it.
Request bocil-bocil Kobo main gitar nih.
Fulfilling the request of Kobo's young fans to play the guitar.
Hmm... Lagu yang mellow-mellow kali ya? Oke.
Hmm... Maybe a mellow song? Okay.
Lagu apa tuh kira-kira Kobo? Ya kalian pasti tahu.
What song will it be, Kobo? Well, you guys definitely know.
Nyanyi bareng ya yang tahu lagunya.
Sing along if you know the song.
Kita nge-galau bersama, oke? Oke.
Let's be sad together, okay? Okay.
薄紅の時を
In the season of light pink
歌に形はないけれど
Uta ni Katachi wa Nai Keredo
Lyrics・Composition：doriko
彩る花びら
Petals coloring everything
ひらひら舞う光の中
In the fluttering light
僕は笑えたはず
I should have been able to smile
鮮やかな日々に
In those vivid days
歌に形はないけれど
Though Songs Have No Form
砂の白波　波に溶けて
White crests of sand dissolve into the waves
きっと夢が終わる
Surely the dream will end
真っ白な世界で　目を覚ませば
If I wake up in a pure white world
伸ばす手は何にも　掴めない
My reaching hand can't grasp anything
見上げた空が　近くなるほどに
The closer the sky I look up at gets
僕は何を失った？
What did I lose?
透き通る波に　映る僕らの影は
Our shadows reflected in the clear waves
青く遠く
Are blue and distant
あの日僕は世界を知り
That day I came to know the world
それは光となった
And it became light
僕は歌うよ　笑顔をくれた君が
I'll sing. You who gave me a smile
泣いてるとき　ほんの少しだけでもいい
When you're crying, even if just for a little bit
君の支えになりたい
I want to be your support
僕が泣いてしまった日に
Just as you were for me
君がそうだったように
On the day I cried
僕がここに　忘れたものを
The things I forgot here
全て君がくれた宝物
Are all treasures you gave me
形のないものだけが
Only things without form
時の中で色褪せないまま
Remain unfaded throughout time
透き通る波　何度消えてしまっても
No matter how many times the clear waves disappear
砂の白波　僕は君と残すだろう
I'll surely leave behind white crests of sand with you
そこに光を集め
Gathering light there
僕は歌うよ　笑顔をくれた君が
I'll sing. You who gave me a smile
泣いてるとき
When you're crying
頼りのない僕だけれど
Even though I'm unreliable
君のこと守りたい
I want to protect you
遠く離れた君のもとへ
To you who are far away
この光が　空を越えて羽ばたいていく
This light will fly across the sky
そんな歌を届けたい
I want to deliver such a song
僕が贈るものは全て
Everything I give you
形のないものだけど
Are things without form, but
君の心の片隅で
In a corner of your heart
輝く星になりたい
I want to be a shining star
Ah, sedikit nggak apa-apa lah ya.
Ah, it's okay if it was a little off, right?
Hahaha! Sedikit salah, sorry, sorry!
Hahaha! A little mistake, sorry, sorry!
I made some mistakes...
...because I'm so nervous.
This is my first time in 3D live singing with acoustic guitar.
The pressure is different from the usual karaoke.
You know, you know?
Sorry, sorry. Grogi!
Sorry, sorry. I'm nervous!
Ya gitu lah.
Well, that's how it is.
Ya udah lah, nggak usah galau-galau lagi lah. Yuk.
Alright, no need to be gloomy anymore. Let's go.
Entar ya, aku taruh ini dulu.
Wait a sec, I'll put this away first.
Entar ya, aku taruh kursi dulu bentar.
Wait a sec, I'll put the chair away first.
Entar, sambil pakai jaket dulu, ちょっと待ってね。
Wait, putting on my jacket too, wait a moment.
Oke, oke, oke, oke.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Sudah gerah, mari senang-senang bersamaku.
It's getting hot, let's have some fun with me.
Ya, jadi tadi aku sudah menunjukkan
Yeah, so earlier I've shown you
bagaimana ruanganku dan seisi-isinya.
how my room and its contents are.
Tapi masih ada satu...
But there's still one more...
This one more thing you guys don't know...
...and I want to show you guys now.
Now, right here. Yes,
masih ada satu yang belum kalian tahu.
there's still one more thing you don't know yet.
Lihat ya.
Check it out.
Eh, kok nggak... wait, rusak kah?
Eh, why isn't it... wait, is it broken?
Oi, oi! Oi! Oi!
Hmm, tadah!
Lift! My private lift...
...di istana Kobo.
...in Kobo's castle.
Oke, sebentar-sebentar, aku punya sesuatu harus dipakai.
Okay, wait a second, I have something I need to wear.
Tadah!
Now I'm ready.
Let's go to the sky!
Waa! Gimana? Keren kan
Whoa! How is it? It's cool, right?
fitur baru mercusuar aku?
My lighthouse's new feature?
Duh, basah banget.
Man, it's so wet.
Eh, kameramen, sini deh kameramen.
Eh, cameraman, come here, cameraman.
Nih, lihat nih.
Here, look at this.
Tinggi banget! So high!
It's so high! So high!
Ah, agak takut mainnya.
Ah, I'm a bit scared being here.
Kameramennya terbang, guys, keren banget,
The cameraman is flying, guys, it's so cool,
padahal platformnya kecil banget.
even though the platform is so small.
Ya udah, kita harus nyebrang dulu ke sana ya.
Alright, we have to cross over there first.
Ya nanti kalian tahu lah mau ngapain lah.
Well, you'll find out what we're going to do later.
Cuman ini...
But this...
Aku nggak tahu pelanginya bisa diinjek apa nggak ya, kayak aku takut tembus.
I don't know if the rainbow can be stepped on or not, like I'm afraid of falling through.
Jatuh kan nggak lucu ya guys, jadi kita lompat aja, oke?
Falling wouldn't be funny, guys, so let's just jump, okay?
I will jump, long jump. Oke? Oke.
I will jump, long jump. Okay? Okay.
Bismillah. Huh!
In the name of God. Huh!
Satu... dua...
One... two...
Tiga... eh!
Three... eh!
Scam! Kalian aku scam! Wiii!
Scam! I scammed you! Wheee!
Oke, oke.
Okay, okay.
For real, this one for real, oke? Kali ini beneran.
For real, this one for real, okay? This time for real.
Satu... dua...
One... two...
Tiga! Wah!
Three! Whoa!
Huh! Huh! Gila, keren banget gua.
Phew! Phew! Crazy, I'm so cool.
Let's go!
Tadah!
Doo! Kebunnya stage! Kawaii desho?
Tadah! The garden stage! It's cute, right?
Mite mite!
Look, look!
Ada pelangi lucu banget, ada tiga, satu, dua, tiga.
There are rainbows, so cute, there are three, one, two, three.
Terus ada awannya lagi mendung ya, lagi hujan tapi ya...
And the clouds are cloudy, it's raining but well...
Nanti bisa berubah lagi ya, kan aku pawang hujan ya.
It'll change later, I'm a rain shaman after all.
Gampang lah ya masalah ini cuaca.
Weather issues are easy.
Terus ada balon-balon, ada bintang kilau-kilau. Ih lucu banget!
Then there are balloons, there are twinkling stars. Oh, it's so cute!
Ada lantai, ada burung! Lihat nggak kalian?
There's the floor, there are birds! Do you see them?
Nggak tahu tuh burung siapa lepas.
Don't know whose birds those are, escaped.
Mehh, ya sudahlah.
Mehh, oh well.
你们想看Kobo中位偶像吗?
Do you want to see Kobo as an idol?
Hey!
It's me!
准备好没?
Are you ready?
もっと熱く高く 光よりもはやく
Hotter and higher, faster than light
Your heart 連れてくよ Higher
Taking your heart higher
圧倒的に Stunning 感じるはず Cuz why not?
Overwhelmingly stunning, you must feel it because why not?
ドキドキをあげる Come on! It's show time!
Giving you heart-throbbing excitement, Come on! It's show time!
それっぽいだけじゃね 物足りないでしょ So
Just looking like it isn't enough, right? So
欢迎来到我的天地
Welcome to my world
Anyone can keep up with me? Anyone?
孤城から見渡す景色
The scenery viewed from the lonely castle
知ってるのは私だけね
Only I know it, right?
我就是那么完美
I am just that perfect
Ah! もっと Addicted に Intoxicated に
Ah! More addicted, intoxicated
全部射抜いてあげる Ooh I'm too good!
I'll shoot through everything, Ooh I'm too good!
怖いものなんてない お遊びはおしまい
Nothing to be afraid of, playtime is over
ここから全てが始まっていくよ
Everything starts from here
Top of the top! Top of the world!
这地球就是绕着我转
This earth revolves around me
尽享不羁吧 Huh!
Enjoy the freedom! Huh!
高ぶる思い It's burning 感じるはず Eye to Eye
High-flying feelings, it's burning, you must feel it eye to eye
ドキドキが止まんない Don't miss the best time!
The heart-throbbing won't stop, don't miss the best time!
私じゃなくちゃね ならね
It's got to be me, no one else
物足りないってほど
To the point of not being enough
我来吸引这世界
I'm here to attract the world
I'm the one who you've been
waiting for
最棒的しか欲しくない
I only want the best
思いのまま 私ならね！
As I wish, if it's me!
谁让我那么完美
Who makes me so perfect
もっとMajesticに
More Majestic
Enthusiasticに
Enthusiastic
視線奪ってあげる
I'll steal your gaze
Ooh I'm too bad!
躊躇うことなんてない
No need to hesitate
綻びは見せない
I won't show any flaws
ここから世界は 広がってくよ明日へ
From here, the world will expand toward tomorrow
胸に手を当ててみたなら探して
If you put your hand on your chest, look for it
本当の心を
Your true heart
絶えず突き上げる振動が
The vibrations that constantly surge up
告げる真実を
Telling the truth
ほらバイアスや 思い込みが
Look, biases and preconceptions
邪魔をしても
Even if they get in the way
目を閉じないで
Don't close your eyes
私は逃げない！
I won't run away!
最高を見せたい
I want to show you the best
貫くよ
I'll see it through
もっと熱く遠く 光よりも早く
Hotter, further, faster than light
Your heart連れて そうどこまでもHigher
Taking your heart, yes, higher than anywhere
躊躇うことなんてない
No need to hesitate
綻びは見せない
I won't show any flaws
ここから歴史は 刻まれてくから
Because history will be carved from here
Just follow me!
もっとAddictedに
More addicted
Intoxicatedに
Intoxicated
全部射抜いてあげる Ooh I'm too good!
I'll pierce through everything, Ooh I'm too good!
怖いものなんてない
Nothing to be afraid of
お遊びはシマイ
The playtime is over
ここから全てが 始まっていくよ
Everything starts from here
Top of the top! Top of the world!
这地球就是绕着我转
The Earth just revolves around me
Top of the top! Top of the world!
Top of the top!
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Even though it's a night that doesn't matter
響めき煌めきと君も
With the noise, the sparkle, and you
NIGHT DANCER
まだ止まった 刻む針も
The ticking hands have stopped too
入り浸った 散らかる部屋も変わらないね
The messy room I've been staying in doesn't change either
思い出しては 二人 年を重ねてた
Remembering, the two of us grew older
また止まった 戻す針を
Stopped again, the hands I turn back
良く流した 聞き飽きるほど変わらないね
I've played it so much I'm tired of hearing it, it doesn't change
変わらないで いられたのは君だけか
Was it only you who could stay unchanged?
無駄話で はぐらかして
Evading with idle talk
触れた先を 躊躇うように
As if hesitating over what I touched
足踏みして ズレた針を余所に
Pacing, ignoring the off-kilter hands
揃い始めてた 息が
Our breaths started to align
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Even though it's a night that doesn't matter
響めき煌めきと君も
With the noise, the sparkle, and you
どうでもいいような夜だけど
Even though it's a night that doesn't matter
二人刻もう
Let's the two of us mark time
ふたり刻もう
Let's keep time together
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's a night that doesn't really matter, but
響めき 煌めき ときめきも 踊ろう
The echoes, the sparkles, even the heartbeats, let's dance
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's a night that doesn't really matter, but
あー
Ah...
どうでもいいから僕だけを
It doesn't matter, so just look at me
ふらつき 揺らめき ながらも
Even while staggering and swaying
どうでもいいような夜だけど
It's a night that doesn't really matter, but
ふたり刻もう
Let's keep time together
Ah...
Gimana?
How was it?
Keren gak?
Was it cool?
Buset, kurang keren apa gue?
Geez, how am I not cool enough?
Ya, tapi kalian tau gak sih apa yang lebih keren?
Yeah, but do you know what's even cooler?
Kayak...
Like...
Stage-nya keren kan?
The stage is cool, right?
Gila kapan lagi kalian ngeliat Kobo idol gitu?
Crazy, when else will you see Kobo as an idol like this?
Eh? Eh?
Bentar, bentar, bentar, eh kamera kamera!
Wait, wait, wait, hey the camera!
ちょっと待って！おい！
Wait a minute! Hey!
ども！
Hello!
3D配信のよ！
It's a 3D stream!
え？あれ？
Eh? Huh?
いや、灯台が見えたから遊びに来たんだよ今日！
Yeah, we saw the lighthouse so we came to visit today!
N-nande koko?
W-why are you here?
Sei, fly!
One, two, fly!
Kore haishin da yo! Dame da yo!
This is a stream! You can't!
Kobo no haishin! Dame da yo!
Kobo's stream! You can't!
Dame da yo!
You can't!
Kobo no 3D! Dame!
Kobo's 3D! No!
Dame! Dame!
No! No!
Oi oi oi oi!
You guys fly?
Guys fly?
Ah, sei fly!
Ah, one, two, fly!
Sei sei sei fly!
One, two, three, fly!
Da- oke.
Da- okay.
Ya mereka udah di sini jadi...
Well, they're already here so...
Kita ajak sesuatu kali ya?
Maybe we should ask them to do something?
Wanna take the stage for spin?
Wanna take the stage for a spin?
Spin?
OK! OK! OK! Spin spin spin!
違うよ！違うよ！
That's not it! That's not it!
え？え？え？
Eh? Eh? Eh?
スピンじゃない！
Not a spin!
E-etto... aa... asup... aa...
Perform together, okay? Perform.
Perform? OK OK!
OK OK OK!
First, sit down please. Okay.
First, please sit down. Okay.
Da- okay.
Sit down! Sit down!
Sit down! Sit down! Hayaku hayaku!
Sit down! Sit down! Hurry up, hurry up!
Eh? Dame? Dame?
Eh? No? No?
Sit down! Sit down!
Kore wa Kobo haishin. Sit down! Sit down!
This is Kobo's stream. Sit down! Sit down!
これ私の配信のよ！
This is my stream!
Oke, sit down!
Okay, sit down!
I have something...
...to put on your head, okay?
ちょっと待ってね。ちょっと待ってね。
Wait a second. Wait a second.
なんだ？なんだ？え？え？
What is it? What is it? Eh? Eh?
Wah! Ahahaha!
Rio, Rio, Rio senpai, come on, come on!
Rio, Rio, Rio!
Jangan gerak, jangan gerak!
Don't move, don't move!
No no no no no!
Ayo, ayo, ayo, come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Aaaa! Itai, itai, itai!
Aaaa! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Oi! Oi!
Hey! Hey!
Oide, oide, oide!
Come here, come here, come here!
Ayo, ayo, ayo! Come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
ムリ！ムリ！
No way! No way!
Aaa itai kuso!
Aaa it hurts, damn!
な、すごい！わ、すごい！
Whoa, amazing! Wow, amazing!
これ…これなに？
This... what is this?
新しいガールグループだよ！
It's a new girl group!
ガールグループだよ！
It's a girl group!
Posisi posisi position! Okay!
Position, position, position! Okay!
Hah!
あなたのアイドル
Your idol
サインはB！
The sign is B!
中！
Chu!
サインはB / Lyrics・Composition: 大石昌良
Sign wa B / Lyrics・Composition: Masayoshi Oishi
やっと会えたね 嬉しいね
We finally met, I'm so happy
待ち遠しくて足をバタバタしながら
I was so looking forward to it, kicking my feet
今日楽しみで寝られなかったよ
I couldn't sleep because I was so excited for today
おれもー！
Me too!
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
This is no time to be nervous
一分一秒 無駄になんてできない
I can't waste a single minute or second
さあ 始めましょう 君も
Now let's begin, you too
君も 君も 君も
You too, you too, you too
君の瞳の奥
Deep within your eyes,
僕を隠さなきゃ
I must hide myself.
でもならせ
But make it ring out!
いらっしゃいませ！
Welcome!
好きが集まり場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where 'likes' gather!
日常は
Daily life
雲のの中
is inside the clouds.
ここに来たなら踊らにゃ
If you came here, you gotta dance,
損損損！
or you'll lose out!
人がよかろう 今更関係ない
Whether people like it or not, it doesn't matter now.
過去をきちんさい とか気にしない
I don't care about the past or anything!
ちゃんと見えてる
I can see them clearly,
君のサイリウム
your light sticks.
今振れば飛ぶような小さな小さな才能だけど
It's a tiny, tiny talent that might fly away if shaken,
私を推してくれるのなら
but if you support me,
ワクワクをあげる
I'll give you excitement!
(Hai! Hai!)
あなたのアイドル
I'm your idol,
サインはB！
The sign is B!
(Chu!)
オレアイ！オレアイ！
Ore-ai! Ore-ai!
コボちゃん、おめでとう！
Congrats, Kobo-chan!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congrats! Congrats!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
じゃあ、バイバイ！
Well then, bye-bye!
Go, go, go away! Go, go, go away!
Go away, go away! Fly, fly, fly, fly, fly!
Bye-bye! Next, next, next, next!
おめでとう！バイバイ！バイバイ！
Congrats! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Terima kasih sama-sama.
Thank you, you're welcome.
Lama banget diusir-usir juga dari tadi ya.
It took so long to kick them out earlier.
Capek banget.
So tiring.
Ya, tidak terasa sudah di penghujung acara ya kita.
Yes, it doesn't feel like we're at the end of the show already.
Barangkali ada yang tertarik ya agensi-agensi modeling, pemancingan, persawahan...
Maybe some modeling, fishing, or rice field agencies are interested...
Aku mau nunjukin sesuatu, okay.
I want to show you something, okay.
Jajan! Kartu nama aku ya.
Tada! My business card.
Jadi bisa banget ya Bapak Ibu jika tertarik bisa hubungi saya lewat sini ya.
So, if you're interested, ladies and gentlemen, you can contact me through here.
Oke nih silakan.
Okay, here you go.
Apa? Ah ini apa Kobo ini apa?
What? Ah, what's this, Kobo? What's this?
Oh iya, ini itu adalah card case. Ini card case.
Oh right, this is a card case. This is a card case.
Jadi tuh Kobo nyimpen kartu nama tuh di card case itu.
So, Kobo stores the business card in that card case.
Oh kalian mau juga? Soalnya keren banget, asumpil, ya keren banget tuh tuh tuh.
Oh, you want it too? Because it's really cool, I swear, yeah, it's really cool. Look, look, look.
Ya udah ya udah, しかたがない (shikata ga nai), ya udah nih.
Alright, alright, can't be helped, here.
Tapi Kobo cuma punya satu doang.
But Kobo only has one.
Tapi it's okay it's okay because you guys can purchase it online, okay?
But it's okay, it's okay because you guys can purchase it online, okay?
Jadi semua bisa kedapatan.
So everyone can get one.
Ya udah dibeli ya nih keren banget, bisa buat melindungi kartu KTP, kartu pelajar, kartu SIM, kartu STNK...
So go buy it, it's really cool. It can protect your ID, student card, driver's license, vehicle registration...
Kartu semua kartu pokoknya bisa lah.
Basically any card will fit.
Oke? Oke mantap.
Okay? Okay, great.
Lalu next aku mau menginformasikan...
Next, I want to inform you...
Besok, tomorrow, holoh3ro 3D collab!
Tomorrow, holoh3ro 3D collab!
Lucu kan? Gila keren banget.
Cute, right? Crazy cool.
Oke note down the date, alright? Note down the date. Oke kalian catat, oke?
Okay, note down the date, alright? You guys take note, okay?
Oke nice nice. いこう、いこう！ (Ikou, ikou!)
Okay, nice nice. Let's go, let's go!
Last but not least, aku masih ada pengumuman penting lainnya nih.
Last but not least, I still have another important announcement.
Apa ya? Apa ya? Hmm... Ya udah yuk lihat bareng-bareng aja videonya.
What is it? What is it? Hmm... Alright, let's just watch the video together.
2023.12
NEW SONG RELEASE!!
お楽しみに！Stay Tuned! Nantikan Eaak!!
Stay tuned! Stay Tuned! Look forward to it!
Apa?! Apa?! Universal! Itu apa maksudnya Kobo?
What?! What?! Universal! What does that mean, Kobo?
Aduh aku juga nggak tahu.
Oh, I don't know either.
Ya, I don't know what is that. Just be patient, okay? Coming soon, really really soon, okay?
Yeah, I don't know what that is. Just be patient, okay? Coming soon, really, really soon, okay?
Ya, 終わったかな (Owatta ka na)? Ya udah terima kasih ya guys kalau gitu.
Well, is it over? Alright then, thank you guys.
Terakhir deh aku mau nunjukin gigi aku. Aaaa... susah-susah-susah.
One last thing, I want to show you my teeth. Aaaa... it's hard, hard, hard.
Ya udah kalau gitu, dada guys. Bye bye Kobo harus meninggalkan kalian sekarang.
Alright then, bye guys. Bye bye, Kobo has to leave you now.
Bye bye. Dadah semuanya. Bye bye.
Bye bye. Bye everyone. Bye bye.
Miss me, okay?
Tapi bohong!
Just kidding!
Thank you everybody for being here tonight!
Yo, Mantra Hujan!
Bapak-bapak, ibu-ibu, adik-adik, siapapun di segala usia!
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, of all ages!
Let's sing it together!
みんな 行くぞ！
Everyone, let's go!
Rapalkan mantra kilau cahaya sinari dunia
Chant the spell, a gleaming light to illuminate the world
Sunyi meresapi di ruang hampa
Loneliness seeped into the vacuum
Masalah datang dan pergi sudah biasa
Problems come and go, it's just normal
Ha... sendiri lagi
Ha... alone again
Enggan untuk melangkah
Reluctant to take a step
Kubuka mata menatap langit
I open my eyes, looking at the sky
Rintik hujan bergeming genangi bentala
Raindrops remain still, flooding the earth
Ha... seakan membisik "Ayo jelajahi dunia"
Ha... as if whispering "Come on, explore the world"
Melamun ke berbagai angan
Daydreaming about various fantasies
Tak akan selesaikan masalah
Won't solve the problems
Beranikan diri untuk melangkah
Brace yourself to take a step
Terobos...
Break through...
Segala rintangannya
All the obstacles
Walau hujan tak kunjung berhenti
Even though the rain never stops
Masih ada aku temanimu di sini
I'm still here to accompany you
Rapalkan mantra datangkan cahaya
Chant the spell, bring forth the light
Tuk sinari hari-harimu
To illuminate your days
Hilangkan semua rasa ragu
Get rid of all the doubts
Yang selimuti hati, pikiran dan emosi
That envelope your heart, thoughts, and emotions
Rapalkan mantra datangkan cahaya
Chant the spell, bring forth the light
Bukalah lembaran yang baru
Open a new page
Semuanya, masih semangat gak?!
Everyone, are you still hyped?!
Apa?!
What?!
Ketik 1 jika semangat! Woo!
Type 1 if you're hyped! Woo!
1 1 1 1 1 1 1!
Ready for another one, ya? Let's go!
Rapalkan mantra kilau cahaya sinari dunia
Chant the spell, a gleaming light to illuminate the world
Susah tidurku semalaman
Couldn't sleep all night
Degup hati sampai meriang
My heart's thumping until I'm feverish
Tak sabar tuk bersenang-senang
Can't wait to have fun
Di panggung megah bersama kalian
On this grand stage with all of you
Kau yang sedih di sini di sana
You who are sad here and there
Your Happy Sunrise memberi kehangatan
Your Happy Sunrise provides warmth
Merebut hati para pemirsa
Capturing the hearts of the viewers
Kulukis indahnya senyuman
I paint a beautiful smile
Melamun ke berbagai angan
Daydreaming about various fantasies
Tak akan selesaikan masalah
Won't solve the problems
Beranikan diri untuk melangkah
Brace yourself to take a step
Terobos apa?
Break through what?
Rintangannya! Let's go!
The obstacles! Let's go!
Walau hujan tak kunjung berhenti
Even though the rain never stops
Masih ada aku temanimu di sini
I'm still here to accompany you
Rapalkan mantra datangkan cahaya
Chant the spell, bring forth the light
Tuk sinari hari-harimu
To illuminate your days
Hilangkan semua rasa ragu
Get rid of all the doubts
Yang selimuti hati, pikiran dan emosi
That envelope your heart, thoughts, and emotions
Rapalkan mantra datangkan cahaya
Chant the spell, bring forth the light
Bukalah lembaran yang baru
Open a new page
Party people! Get ready!
Put your hands up in the air! Yo!
Hilangkan semua rasa ragu
Get rid of all the doubts
Yang selimuti hati, pikiran dan emosi
That envelope your heart, thoughts, and emotions
Rapalkan mantra datangkan cahaya
Chant the spell, bring forth the light
Bukalah lembaran yang baru
Open a new page
Yatta! Congrats Kobo!
Yay! Congrats Kobo!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Haji-mamahaho! Aku cinta kamu!
Haji-mamahaho! I love you!
Aku juga cinta kamu!
I love you too!
Aaa, jangan dong!
Aaa, don't do that!
Come here, son!
Kawaii, kawaii!
Cute, cute!
Eh, eh, ketinggian!
Eh, eh, you're too high!
Gak bisa, gak bisa ini, ketinggian ini.
I can't, I can't do this, it's too high.
Woe, enggak usah sombong!
Hey, don't be so cocky!
Yelah, gampang!
Geez, that's easy!
Pegangin, pegangin.
Hold me, hold me.
Iya iya, enggak usah ngomong-ngomong ya.
Yes yes, don't keep talking.
Nanti di-mute kok.
It'll be muted anyway.
Ayok bisa yuk!
Come on, let's go!
What?
Oh my god!
Nice.
Berantakan banget, coy.
It's a mess, guys.
Nice.
Oke, oke, I'm okay.
Okay, okay, I'm okay.
Idol pose! Idol pose! Let's go!
Yagooさん、Yagooさん！こっち、こっち！
Yagoo-san, Yagoo-san! Over here, over here!
Ayo Boss, jangan malu-malu sini napa.
Come on Boss, don't be shy, come here.
No, he's covering us! No!
Yay! He's all grown up, Yagoo-san!
Yagoo-san!
No, just kidding.
Ya udah, oke oke, udah-udah.
Alright, okay okay, that's enough.
Selesai!
Finished!
配信...終わった！
Stream... is over!
Bye bye!
Sungkum, sungkum, sungkum!
Bow, bow, bow!
Terima kasih!
Thank you!
Terima kasih semuanya!
Thank you everyone!
Bye bye! Hati-hati!
Bye bye! Take care!
Thank you guys!
Yagooさん、Yagooさん。ちょっと待って。
Yagoo-san, Yagoo-san. Wait a moment.
Ayangku.
My beloved.
Sungkum dulu.
Let me prostrate first.
Ah, oke, oke, oke.
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Almost forgot.
Biar sopan.
To be polite.
God bless Boss.
Yagoo, we love you.
ありがとう、Yagooさん。
Thank you, Yagoo-san.
In Yagoo we trust.
Thank you, Yagoo!
気をつけてね、Yagooさん。
Take care, Yagoo-san.
Bye bye!
Peace for real.
Come with me, come with me. Come on.
Oke, take care of Yagoo-san.
Okay, take care of Yagoo-san.
はぁ...終わったな。
Sigh... it's over, huh.
じゃあみんな、見てくれてありがとう...
Well everyone, thank you for watching...
...来てくれてありがとう。
...thank you for coming.
Bye bye! Muah!
Special Announcement!
3D SHOWCASE #KoboKanaeru3D